[upbeat waltz music]
Hey,
what's wrong with you?
What?
Your face--
it's like you're happy
or something.
I am happy, Frank.
'Cause of that dude
you're donking.
Floyd?
Yes.
He just gets me.
I think you've got
a little something--
Right here?
Other side.
Here?
Up a little.
In that area?
You got it.
Ugh, that movie was
a complete waste of time.
I thought it was moving...
my bowel
Heh heh.
Mmm...
Oh...
Reverse, reverse,
skip, skip, draw four!
Oh, hell no!
Ha ha!
That's awesome, Liz.
I'm really happy
that you found someone
to care about.
Because relationships
are hard.
So if you ever
need someone
to come over and videotape
you guys doing it,
or whatever,
I can make room
in my schedule.
Thanks, Frank.
You're welcome.
No judgments.
Don.
Jack, you old dog,
how are you?
I'm good, sir.
Of course you are.
Look at those eyes,
sharp, like a panther's.
Thank you, sir--
would you like to sit down?
I can't.
I took my grandkids snorkeling
at St. Bart's,
and got stung
by a jellyfish.
I got a welt
on my ass
the size
of a Red Delicious apple.
I'm very sorry
to hear that, sir.
Yeah.
Boy, Jack...
you really terrified
the people
with that fireworks
special of yours.
[march music & explosions]
Well, we were trying
for something dramatic,
and I don't regret trying.
Well, you gotta try.
As my old man always said,
If you try, you win.
And he was a hell
of a garbage man.
I just want you to know
we all still have
a lot of faith
in you, Jack.
Well, thank you, sir.
That means the world
coming from you.
But I'm taking
the microwave division
away from you.
I mean,
you're in the rough, Jack.
You gotta get back
on the fairway.
Yes, sir.
You ever think about
getting remarried?
Well,
I just got divorced, sir.
Everyone in this division
is married except you.
Look at Bob.
His wife looks
just like Walter Matthau,
but she's always there
for him.
That's the kind of companion
you need.
Think about that.
I will, sir.
I'm going to see
Tracy Jordan.
He is funny.
What's that film where
he turned into a dog?
Uh,Fat Bitch,sir.
That's it--
I love it.
Boy, that's
a great film.
I'm sorry
I let you down.
[exciting jazz music]
Thank you for agreeing
to meet with me, Don Geiss.
Would you like some Grenadine
or some fried rice?
I'm good, thanks.
Sir, I have
a movie project
that is going to blow
your mind.
I call itJefferson.
A movie version
ofThe Jeffersons?
I love it.
No, Thomas Jefferson.
I just recently found out
that he went to town
on one of my ancestors,
so we're related.
You want to play
Thomas Jefferson?
And Sally Hemings,
and King George.
I'm going to play
all the parts.
Did you know
he had a lisp?
[lisping heavily]
Whath's up, sthupid jerks?
I'm Thomas Jefferthon.
[chuckles]
So we're gonna need
about 35 million
to do this thing right.
I'm gonna get us
one of those big clocks.
We could hang it in there.
Sorry I'm late.
Aw, Lutz, that's okay.
I'm just glad
you're here.
Oh, you've got a face
like a baby's bottom!
Boop.
[chuckles]
I hate when you're
in a good mood.
It makes me feel unsafe.
Like when my mom
used to make daiquiris
and sing Tanya Tucker songs.
That sounds awesome.
Miss Lemon, Mr. Donaghy
would like to see you.
He's across the street
at Christie's auction house.
Oh, brother.
What's this?
Jack goes to Sbarro
when he's angry,
the New York Stock Exchange
when he's horny,
and Christie's auction house
when he's depressed.
He said he needs you
immediately.
Yeah...
that's the Liz face
I'm comfortable with.
You've been avoiding me,
Lemon.
How do you do that
without turning around?
To be perfectly honest,
the first couple of people
I did that to
were not you.
But...here we are.
Mr. Donaghy.
, you probably
don't remember me.
I'm Phoebe.
I handled the sale
of your ex-wife's jewelry
to an anonymous Arab.
Oh, yes, of course.
Those were such
lovely pieces.
(Phoebe)
The ruby and diamond
cluster ring
was particularly
exquisite.
That was
her engagement ring.
You know, I took the money
from the sale of those pces,
and I bought a sailboat,
and I named it after
my ex-wife,
and I sank it.
It's true.
TheBianca Blows
is somewhere
at the bottom
of the Peconic Bay.
If there's anything
I can show you,
please do let me know.
Okay?
Yeah.
I really do like these
equestrian paintings.
Isn't that magnificent?
Sometimes I wish
I were a horse.
Strong, free.
My chestnut haunches glistening
in the sun.
Are you okay?
Hmm?
Oh, yeah, sure.
You know,
I'm really sorry
that I let you down.
You should be.
My special was
a disaster.
I wouldn't say that.
[explosions and sirens]
You left me dangling,
Lemon.
I'm not a creative type
like you,
with your work sneakers
and your left-handedness.
I can't do what you do.
I know,
I dropped the ball.
I was just trying to do
what you said,
and have a personal life.
And I guess I got caught up
with this new guy.
Oh, right, flower guy.
His name is Floyd.
That's unfortunate.
I'd really like you
to meet him, Jack.
Fine.
I'd like to meet the man
that made Liz Lemon
shirk her responsibilities.
Let's say Persil, 9:00.
Be sure to wear a tie.
Are you sure you're okay?
I pitched my Jefferson movie
to Don Geiss.
He said no.
He said people only see movies
because of the previews,
and he couldn't visualize
my Jefferson preview.
He wants me to do
Fat Bitch 2instead.
Well, that doesn't even
make sense.
Everyone knows Fat Bitch died
at the end.
It's not the kind of stuff
I want to do anymore, Ken.
I want to be
taken seriously.
What should I do?
Well, remember
when Fat Bitch called
all her dog friends
together,
and they used their
high-pitched howling
to mess up the--
You're right, K.
I should make my own
Jefferson preview,
and show it to Don Geiss.
I'm never gonna finish
this bikini
before Nana's birthday.
Hey, Liz Lemon,
where you going?
Uh, home.
I gotta go get ready
for a dinner with Jack.
Listen, I'm gonna need
to make a fake trailer
for my Jefferson film.
I'm gonna need the
entire resources of the show
for no more than
three weeks.
You in?
No-wha
No.
Tracy,
you're not doing that.
We have a show on Friday.
Liz Lemon, you are
my Alexander Hamilton.
I don't know
what that means.
Writers, listen.
I need your help.
Well, I hope this isn't
too boring for you.
Are you kidding?
Jack Donaghy's a legend.
I've read his book,
like, 20 times.
Jack wrote a book?
Yeah.
Jack Attack:
The Art of Aggression
in Business.
Oh, no.
(Floyd)
He got here before us.
You're not supposed
to let that happen.
That's chapter two
in the book.
Hi, Jack.
This is Floyd.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, sir.
Well, you're Floyd.
The only other Floyd
I ever knew
was this Korean barber
who used to cut my hair
down in the 50th Street
subway station.
That's my dad.
I'm Floyd, Jr.
I-I'm just kidding.
Well, please.
Sorry.
I'm just nervous
to meet the head
of east coast television
and microwave oven
programming.
I just got the word
from Geiss
they're taking me
off microwave.
Oh, no.
Really?
Mr. Donaghy,
with all due respect
to Mr. Geiss,
I gotta say he's making
a terrible mistake.
This company's stability
in the small-appliance market
is in large part
your doing.
The dedicated popcorn setting
on your microwave
was the imagination
breakthrough of 1995.
In 2002, you increased
corporate earnings by 3%,
while the country suffered
through a recession.
AndAttack of the Clones,
which was seriously
the worst
of theStar Wars--
One sec, Liz, one sec.
And on a personal note, sir,
in my mind,
the Foo Fighters' song
Best of You
is about your
managerial skills.
Lemon, I want
to kiss your boyfriend
on the mouth.
Chapter 12.
I thought you were
gonna do it.
What are you drinking?
Club soda.
Oh, that's a shame.
Pete!
[snaps fingers]
[gasps]
Hey, Liz Lemon.
Could you go away
for a while?
I gotta get rid
of Freddie's erection.
Explain what is
happening here.
Freddie is playing
the part
of Thomas Jefferson's horse
Caractacus.
We needed a place
to keep him
till we shoot his stunts.
No, acy, I told you
not to do this.
Jack said I could.
This movie is my destiny.
It's the reason why God
put me on this earth.
[sighs]
I'll take you
off this earth.
(Phoebe)
The overwhelming violence
of the subject matter
is in deliberate
juxtaposition
with the pastoral beauty
of the terrain.
Jack, Tracy put a horse
in my office.
Lemon, you've met--
Hello.
You probably don't
remember me--I'm Phoebe.
We met the other day.
Yeah, yeah,
I remember you.
I'm Liz.
Oh, sorry.
I don't shake hands.
I have Avian Bone Syndrome.
Oh, boy, okay.
Hollow bones.
Lemon, I want your opinion.
Which ofthese two
do you like?
They're both beautiful.
They look just like the one
crapping in my office.
Did you tell Tracy
he could use the crew
to make a trailer
for his crazy movie?
Yes.
How's Floyd?
What? he's fine.
You know,
I called him earlier.
We had a very nice chat--
did he mention that?
No, he didn't.
Oh, he will.
He's a good man,
the Floydster.
Oh, "the Floydster."
Don't give him a nickname
before I do.
Um...the white horse.
I was wondering if--
[whispering]
Did I hurt you?
Just a little bit,
but that's okay.
(Phoebe)
Yes, the white horse,
it's--
Yo, Trey,
we got a problem.
Pray, who be this
Tracy Jordan
thou speakest of?
Uh, President Jefferson,
we got a problem.
Speakest.
That horse ate
your wig.
Well, stand guard
by his rump,
and await it
in his droppings.
Or we could probably
just go get a new wig.
I like you, young man.
You shall run
my university.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's very nice.
Hey, what are you
doing here, Jack?
Jack bought me
this painting.
Wow. Um...
Is that lion eating
the horse?
Or perhaps it's eating
universal health care.
[laughter]
I bought this
for the Floydster
to congratulate him
on his promotion.
Well, it's not
a sure thing.
I didn't know you were up
for a promotion.
Well--
We should go
celebrate.
I'm free for lunch.
Do you want to grab
a burger, or--
Shoot, I just said
I'd go to lunch with Jack.
Oh.
Why don't you join us?
Would that be okay?
Yeah, I guess so.
Sure.
[nervous chuckle]
It's kind of like
you two are dating.
Um, I think that Coulter
was right about Edwards.
So where's Pete?
He took his kids
to that Russian cat circus.
Wow.
You are bringin' it.
[chuckles]
Yeah, you like that?
Mmm.
[Floyd laughing]
It's got pockets--
are you into that?
Ooh, what's this?
A used Kleenex.
I feel like
I'm in a rap video.
Wait, let me turn on
my humidifier.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
It's so dry in here.
I really don't know how much
more of this I can take.
[chuckles]
Unh, unh...
Unh, unh.
Yeah.
Old school,
Kid 'n Play.
Here we go.
That's not that impressive.
That's Davy Jones.
[cell phone beeps]
Hey, it's Jack.
Jack--
what does he want?
He's just saying hi.
Oh, he wants to meet
at that diner on 71st.
Get a veggie burger
and a milkshake.
You wanna go?
It's midnight.
Yeah, we don't have
to go.
There, done.
Good,
'cause this VapoRub
isn't gonna get
under my nose
by itself.
[cell phone beeps]
He says goodnight.
And "sleep tight."
[cell phone beeps]
"And don't let the bed--"
All right, enough.
Gimme that.
"Jack, I have taken
a sleeping pill
"because I have a big
lawyer meeting..."
That's what we call 'em.
"in the morning.
Floyd."
[cell phone beeps]
"Lemon, is that you?"
I always sign it Floydster.
[musical ring tone]
It's Jack!
Don't answer it.
[telephone rings]
[ringing stops]
[door intercom buzzes]
[gasps]
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! [buzzing]
[gasps]
Can he see us?
The call is coming
from inside the house!
Turn of the lights
and get down.
[buzzing]
Jonathan, I want
to talk to Jack right now.
He's at Christie's.
But he left these
for you.
What's this?
Tickets
for you and Floyd
for tonight's
Knicks game.
For me and Floyd?
He tried to drop them off
at your house last night,
but someone pretended
not to be home.
Oh.
This is really nice.
Yes, he seems very taken
with Floyd.
And you, of course.
Are these good seats?
Yeah.
It's actually
a private box.
[p.a. announcer indistinct
in background]
[crowd cheering]
Hey, guys.
Mr. Geiss, I know we disagreed
on my next movie project,
but I hope this will
change your mind.
I give you this.
[beep]
[humming
(Tracy)
Ah...
hoe that dirt.
Put your back
into it.
Mr. Jefferson,
the British have invaded.
Ah, bring me my horse!
Bring me Caractacus!
You come along.
(announcer)
In a world without hope...
[weak British accent]
Who are these Americans
with their ridiculous ideas
of freedom and equalities?
(announcer)
One man would declare
his independence
for us all.
[slowed gunshot sound effect]
Aah!
[gunshot]
Eat that, King George!
[squeaking]
I shall call it Susan!
[gunshot]
I'm with child.
What?
Free me and make me
your wife.
Um, I'll have to
get back to you on that.
(announcer)
Source Award nominee
Tracy Jordan...
Kill them!
Kill them all!
(announcer)
NAACP Image Award presenter
Tracy Jordan...
and Academy Award watcher
Tracy Jordan is...
This is for you,
Don Geiss!
Ha ha!
[gunshot]
(announcer)
Jefferson!
Christmas, 2008.
Get me off
this horse.
[video off]
Well, Mr. Geiss,
what do you think?
Well, Tracy...
that was terrible.
The answer is no.
Let's talk about
Fat Bitch 2.
So I'm bored,
and I sit next to Don Geiss,
and I want to make
a good impression,
so I bought four bottles
of absolutely
fantastic champagne.
Lemon, you're gonna love
this story.
You told me
this story, Jack.
We're on our way
to Tokyo,
(Liz and Jack)
we're out over the ocean,
and the cabin pressure drops.
The masks are coming out
of the ceiling,
and the corks are popping out
of the champagne.
And I don't give a damn
about the masks,
I'm on all fours
trying to shove the corks
back in the bottle.
And Don Geiss says,
"Now, there's an executive
who knows how
to keep his costs down!"
[laughter]
That's great.
I'm gonna get
some more crab cakes.
Liz, you want anything?
No, thanks.
What are you doing?!
I'm watching the ballgame
with you and the Floydster.
But don't you kind of feel
like a third wheel, Jack?
No, Lemon--
you'rethe third wheel.
Excuse me?
Well, it's really
quite simple.
Men seek out the company
of other men they admire
and want to be like.
Floyd is me 20 years ago.
I'm Don Geiss 30 years ago.
20 years from now,
Floyd will be me,
I'm gonna be Don Geiss,
and Don Geiss will
be dead.
Who thinks like that?
Men do.
That's why you're
the third wheel.
Just back off, okay?
Lemon, are you telling me
to stay away
from your boyfriend?
Not that I blame you,
because I could
take him away from you
if I wanted to.
This is my life, Jack.
I know you're
in a bad spot right now.
But you can't use Floyd
to feel better about yourself.
It's not fair.
All right, how about
some kind of a time-share
arrangement?
You can have him Monday,
Wednesday, and Friday--
I don't want Friday--
we have a show.
Why am I even having
this conversation with you?!
Look at your life, Jack.
It's like this skybox.
It's fancy
and it's empty,
and it smells
like crab cakes.
Get your own Floyd,
because this one
is taken.
Oh, outstanding.
Thank you.
Sure.
Sir?
He said no.
Then he offered me
$7 million
to reprise my role
as Cocoa the dog.
? I'm gonna get
an iPhone ?
? Everybody's gonna
be jealous ?
No, I turned him down.
It's like a roller-coaster ride
of emotion in here.
Look, Thomas Jefferson made
his own country.
I'm gonna make
my own movie.
Finance it myself,
all on my terms.
Now, who's with me?
We all are, sir.
Good, good, good.
Now, first order
of business,
get that dead horse
out of my car.
Well, I'm sorry your friend
wasn't pleased with the Stubbs.
Yes, so am I.
You seem very preoccupied.
Well, it's just...
people don't like
fireworks anymore.
Were you aware of that?
They took away
the microwave division.
I'm having terrible
Lemon problems.
I'm eating all the time.
I mean, who needs
16 flautas after midnight?
Mr. Donaghy...
Jack.
Listen, if you're
still interested,
there is another piece
I'd like to show you
that you might enjoy.
I'll need to take you back
to the private office.
This piece
is very delicate.
Very few people
have handled it.
Oh, God,
I hope we're talking
about the same thing.
May I speak with you?
If this is about
the other night,
I am not gonna apologize.
This whole Floyd thing--
No, no, no.
You're absolutely right.
I have to make some changes
in my life,
just like you have.
Phoebe and I are
seeing each other.
Really?
Wow, that's great.
Now you have a Floydster,
and I have a Floydster.
Well, I don't think
Phoebe would appreciate
being referred to
as a Floydster.
But you like her?
You approve?
Of what?
Of her for me.
Yeah, sure.
Good.
Hello, I'm Phoebe.
I don't know
if you remember me, but--
Yes, Phoebe,
I remember you.
Hi.
May I ask you something?
Uh, Phoebe,
I want you
to be my wife.
Wait, what?
[gasps]
Will you marry me?
[whispering]
No!
The ruby diamond cluster!
I bought it back
from the anonymous Arab.
How romantic.
Ow.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Ow.
Oh, boy.
(Phoebe)
Careful, my bones.
www.tvsubtitles.net