And this is the two-bedroom.
Wow.
By the hammer of Thor!
Can you afford this place?
Yeah.
I can
with this new promotion.
It's...a lot more money.
Like "get away with murdering
my first wife" kind of dough.
Mm-hmm.
See, now, I could hang
a huge TV right there.
You could get
that third humidifier
you always dreamed about.
Slow down.
I'm not ready
to move my humidifiers yet.
Oh, I know.
I don't mean right away.
I just meant...someday.
Hopefully.
Yeah, good.
Someday.
But for now,
I got a great job.
A kick-ass girlfriend.
I deserve an apartment
to match.
And I think this
is definitely it.
I'll take this one too.
My son Ahmed will keep
his motorcycles here.
Oh! Thanks for coming.
Oh...ooh.
Lemon!
Oh, welcome back.
How was Paris?
Paris was fantastic.
We stayed in this little place
in the Seventh
that Phoebe knew about.
I'm Phoebe.
We've met before.
Jack proposed to me
outside your office.
I have hollow bones.
Like a bird.
Yes, no.
I remember you, hi.
Hi.
Well, I should go.
We've just won
the auction rights
to a fantastic collection
of Chinese erotica.
Pick out a good one for me.
Careful.
Bye.
So...have you guys
set a date?
Yes, we have.
May 18th.
That's Bianca's wedding date.
It was my idea.
That's fast.
Well, there are no rules
in love, Lemon.
My...Princeton roommate
did it the right way.
Dated his college girlfriend
for 13 years,
and the marriage
didn't last eight months.
And now he's
a post-op transgender.
Will you look at that?
Phoebe reset my watch
to New York time
while I was sleeping
on the plane.
She really
is a wonderful girl.
And I do hope the two of you
get to know each other better.
Okay, sure.
Why don't you have
a girls' day out?
Take Jenna with you.
You could have lunch,
go shopping.
Here...take my gold card.
Ooh, it's heavy.
It's...made of gold.
Ah. Wow.
Turned me down, Liz Lemon.
Who?
The damn bank.
I need a loan to finance
my Thomas Jefferson movie.
It's gonna be
at least $30 million
with all the Claymation
sex scenes in it.
And they didn't want
to pay for that?
It's all right.
The movie's just
a small part of my plan.
What plan?
The Tracy Jordan comeback.
I'm doing a comedy tour,
a Michael McDonald cover album.
Ah, boy,
I don't know, Tray.
I don't think of you
as a great multitasker.
What can I do?
I'm on my grind.
I'm gonna have
so much money,
my grandkids
are gonna play lacrosse.
Lacrosse, Liz Lemon.
"I'm on my krind."
Is that a...
There he is.
The Floydster!
I heard you were going in
for your final interview.
I wanted to put in
a good word.
All right, well,
that should put me over the top.
Oh, you're already there.
The other candidate
is an outsider.
And we like to promote
from within.
Plus, his name
is Alan Garkel.
You're never gonna lose a job
to a guy named Garkel.
Did someone say my name?
Nah, you're not
gonna beat that.
Well-played, Garkel.
Because Carl's trying
to kill the gophers,
but then the explosion
knocks Danny's ball
into the hole,
and he wins the tournament.
And that is the plot
ofCaddyshack.
I can't believe
you've never seen it.
Classic.
Oh! Jeez, I'm sorry.
Oh, you like Wagner?
No, I like Elmer Fudd.
? Kill da wabbit ?
? Kill da wabbit ? ?
My parents
were both poets, so I...
don't really get it.
So this has just been
a whirlwind romance for you.
Just a...whirl of wind.
Look, I know
what you must be thinking.
What kind of a woman
marries a man she hardly knows?
Whatisshe after?
No, no, no.
I don't think that.
I completely get it,
why you would wanna marry Jack.
I'd marry Jack
in a heartbeat.
I would have a three-way
with two Jacks.
You need to cool it.
Let's face it--
at our age,
we can't afford
to waste any time.
Mm-hmm.
Floyd and I have been
dating for a month.
Do you think I should be mad
that I don't have a ring?
Wow, howSex in the City
are we right now?
I'm Samantha,
you're Charlotte,
and you're the lady at home
who watches it.
Dude, check it out.
Bill Cosby hates you.
What?
Look here.
"Tracy Jordan
has made a career
"out of exploiting
black stereotypes.
He is an embarrassment
to African-Americans."
Why would he say that?
What have I ever done
to embarrass black people?
Uh...
Why are we doing this?
Because the Jets lost!
Mr. Jordan,
your manager called.
Temple University has canceled
your stand-up appearance.
And Michael McDonald
is denying permission
to record any of his songs.
In other words:
? Oh, Tracy, you can't ?
? Use any of my songs ? ?
This is no coincidence.
What are you talking about?
The bank loan.
The Michael McDonald
situation.
Temple University.
Dr. Cosby
is sending a message!
They're out to destroy me!
Who is?
The Black Crusaders.
Oh, Floyd
would love this one.
Yikes!
If I was gonna spend $600
to have my boobs pinched,
I would have gone
to that fundraiser
at the Clintons' house.
Come on, that was solid!
Liz, I'm concerned
I'm boring Jack sexually.
No, no.
No...ugh.
We've only
just got engaged,
and already our intercourse
is infrequent
and unimaginative.
Phoebe, I'm really not
that kind of girlfriend.
I would gladly pick you up
at the airport.
In Paris, he fell asleep
on top of me.
I mean, I just want
to make him happy.
If he's happy,
I'm happy, you know?
Mm.
Do you have
that credit card?
Thanks.
Hi, I'll take everything.
Liz, can you help me?
Yes, ma'am.
I don't know you,
but I will help you.
Damn it.
I can't believe it.
Garkel?
I'm sorry.
I'm just sick of it.
I'm so tired of this city.
I am so tired
of the rat race.
Fellas!
You gotta keep it down,
okay?
I got work in the morning.
Molnya is looking
very strong tonight.
Mr. Debarber, come on.
Fine.
20 across the board.
Yeah, you gotta
talk to your landlord
about that rat race.
That is my landlord.
Oh.
Yeah.
Maybe I just need
to go out of town
for a little while.
That's a good idea.
Vermont is always nice.
Or the Bahamas.
I was thinking of Cleveland.
That is also a place.
I just haven't been home
in a long time.
We need
to search your bag.
Ugh.
Of course they do.
You know, I dream
about moving back to Lakewood.
Or maybe even
Shaker Heights.
Big Creek Parkway.
Sending the kids
to St. John Bosco's, you know.
Maybe even cheering on
the tribe at the Jake.
This dream, this
is way down the road, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Three, maybe four years.
What's
this fungus cream for?
All right, that's it.
Show's over.
Gimme that.
Let's just walk.
So how long do you see yourself
living in New York?
Well, like, forever.
At least, I did.
Really?
You wanna end up
like that?
No.
I'm gonna be like her.
Oh, there is nothing
like New York in the spring!
It's--oh!
Ooh.
All right, come on.
This is the capital
of the world.
The culture, the div--
Ugh!
Uck!
You all right?
He spit in my mouth!
Ugh!
Let's go to Cleveland.
Oh, blurgh!
Hey, Frank told me
about that Cosby thing.
That is harsh.
Harsh?
I'm done.
The Black Crusaders want
to make an example out of me.
I'm not gonna ask you
who that is.
The Black Crusaders
are a secret group
of powerful black Americans.
Bill Cosby and Oprah Winfrey
are the chief majors.
But Jesse Jackson,
Colin Powell,
and Gordon fromSesame Street,
they're members too.
And they meet
four times a year
in the skull
of the Statue of Liberty.
You can read about that
on the interweb.
Ah, well, it must be true
if it's on the "interweb."
Right, uh-huh.
Make fun of me
all you want, Liz Lemon.
Do you know they'll
ruin anybody who they think
are making black people
look bad?
They tanked
50 Cent's movie.
The blew out
Terrell Owens' ankle.
And they canceled
Eddie Murphy's Oscar,
'cause he, uh, ran out
on Scary Spice.
And now they after
Tracy Jordan!
Tracy, I know the movie
is important to you,
and you're stressed out
and everything,
but keep it together, okay?
The cleanup continues.
Fortunately,
there were no injuries.
Tracy Jordan,
the Black Crusaders
are coming for you.
We'll have more on the weather
coming up...
Man, I wish somebody else
had seen that.
Hi.
Look what Phoebe got me.
Golf clubs?
Not just golf clubs.
These clubs
once belonged
to President Gerald Ford.
Oh, wow.
So what do you think
of Phoebe?
Oh, well...
we had fun.
And, uh, Phoebe bought
some bonkers underwear.
So have fun
with that tonight.
Well, not tonight.
Uh, may I?
Oh.
Thank you.
Not tonight
unfortunately.
She's, uh, speaking
in a seminar
up at Columbia.
And as much as I would
like to attend,
I haven't been above
72nd Street in over a decade.
Well, I'm glad
you're happy.
Ha!
It's all Phoebe.
We have an attraction that can
only be described as...
wolf-like.
Lupine.
Okay.
I am so exhausted.
Paris was,
to borrow a phrase,
just...bonkers.
Yes, Phoebe said.
Do you cover him?
Psst! Psst!
Phoebe isn't going
to Columbia tonight.
She had me call a car
to take her
to this address downtown.
So what do you want me to do,
go spy on her?
For Mr. Donaghy's sake.
I know you have
your doubts about this.
I can see it in your eyes.
It's weird, right?
Then again,
all relationships are weird.
I mean, my boyfriend Floyd
wants to go to Cleveland.
Ah, thank God.
Mr. Donaghy's office.
Just a quick look.
By the hammer of Thor!
Ew.
Jack, I have
to talk to you.
Is this about the Tracy situation? No.
Then it'll have to wait.
What Tracy situation?
I tried to call you.
He set fire to a cardboard
cutout of Al Roker,
and now he's locked himself
in his dressing room.
Oh, brother.
Tracy!
Come out.
Nobody is trying to get you.
Have you seen the cover
of this month'sOprahmagazine?
It's an anagram for
"Outlaw Sour Tray."
Who taught Tracy
about anagrams?
I'm gonna call
Dr. Spaceman.
Hey, car's downstairs.
You ready to go?
Um...
The Black Crusaders
are trying to get rid of me.
They want me to disappear
like Coolio.
Coolio is around!
What--
Would you also prescribe
something for Tracy
which would keep him awake
during sex?
Oh, great.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Thanks.
Let's get outta here.
? What hot spot's got
the hippest groove? ?
Welcome to Cleveland.
Good morning.
? Where all the real
gone daddies move ?
Good morning.
Hi.
Hello.
What smells so good?
Cleveland.
? Where the jet set swing
with hepcats ?
? Shop at Higby's,
then we'll hit the Flats ?
Excuse me.
Are you a model?
No.
Oh, you are so skinny.
You really should
eat something.
? I say, Cleveland, hello ?
? Yeah ?
? New York and Paris
just don't have ?
? The sights you see
and you can have ?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ugh.
Would you like to pet
a real police horse?
? Chef Boyardee
was born here ?
Yes!
? Come on, cool cats,
and play your skins ?
? In Lyndhurst
and the Burg of Twins ?
Oh, ladies first.
? I say Cleveland, hello ?
Hi, I'll have two hotdogs,
a pretzel with
extra melted cheese...
Hiya.
Ms. Lemon,
this is Kenneth,
the NBC page
in New York City.
I hate to bother you
out west,
but Tracy Jordan
hasn't come to work.
Kenneth, don't be
so New York uptight.
I'm sure he'll show up.
? Look over there,
I think I see a movie star ?
? Even movie stars,
they come to Cleveland ?
? To get away ?
? Tracy Jordan,
you've gotta get away ?
? Gotta get away,
gotta get away ?
? To Cleveland ? ?
Liz...
I have something important
I wanna talk to you about.
The top law firm
in Cleveland wants me.
And...I think
I should accept.
What? Really?
What's this?
It's a house
in the Heights
that I can afford.
When did you have time
to look for jobs and houses?
When you were at
the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
Did I tell you
I sat in ZZ Top's car?
And then I had lunch
with Little Richard.
And, I know
it's not TGS, but...
I'm sure you can find a job
at one of the local TV stations.
You sureould.
We need a host
for a new cooking show
on WKYC.
Uh...
Where have you been?
Cleveland.
For God sakes, Lemon,
we'd all like
to flee to the Cleve.
And club up
down at the Flats
and have lunch
with Little Richard.
But we fight those urges
because we have
responsibilities.
What's going on?
Tracy.
He's missing.
What?
No. Kenneth, have you
tried to call Tracy?
Yes, ma'am, I tried
all six of his cell phones.
It's almost as if
he never existed.
Or maybe he's not answering.
Lemon, TGS
without Tracy Jordan
is basically a puppet show.
You know,
I'm right here.
Oh, why am I doing this
when I could be happy
living in Cleveland?
What?
Floyd and I
are thinking of moving.
No, you're not.
Look, every great getaway
has that moment when you want
to pack it all in and stay.
That's how I ended up
with a timeshare...
in Port Arthur, Texas.
I don't think
that's what this is.
I mean, Floyd
is pretty great.
And, look, in Cleveland,
I'm a model.
Yeah, we're all models
west of the Allegheny.
I'm serious about this.
Maybe you should go.
I mean, your head is obviously
not in the game lately.
And now
you've lost Tracy.
Maybe you're burned out.
What is this?
This is Frank's
"Hot Baby" sketch,
which is regrettable,
but we have no Tracy Jordan
and a show in two days.
But, hey,
that's not gonna be
your problem
once you move to Ohio.
No, you're not.
Frank, that's
gonna get cut.
Blurgh!
Did you say
anything to Jack?
No, but I'm going to
if you don't.
Oh, grow up, Liz.
I didn't tell Jack
where I was going
'cause I didn't want him
to get upset about nothing.
That man was a former
lover of mine.
I was ending it with him,
forever.
Uh-huh, and are all
your ex-boyfriends
rich, older gentlemen?
I care about Jack.
I make him a better man.
You know how John Lennon
was better than
the rest of the Beatles,
but didn't realize it
until he met Yoko Ono?
Well, I'm Jack's Yoko.
Youwantto be Yoko?
This is none of your business,
anyway.
I'm marrying Jack.
He's everything I ever
wanted. Oh, I bet he is.
You don't know anything
about me, so back off!
What happened
to your accent?
Um...
I don't know what
you're on about.
You...daft wanker.
Hello?
Hello, Liz Lemon.
It's me.
Stacy Gordon.
Tracy, where are you
calling from?
I can't tell you that.
I'm sorry, Liz Lemon.
I wanna thank you
for everything you've done.
But I quit.
For God's sakes, Tracy,
where are you?
Starting a new life.
Because
of the Black Crusaders?
That's crazy.
Tray?
Damn it, Lemon,
why didn't you tell me
the Black Crusaders
were after Tracy?
Surprisingly fast.
Oh.
I'm on it.
I can't go to Cleveland.
Hi.
Hi. I'm sorry.
I just, I've been thinking
about this.
And I think you're great.
And obviously Cleveland
is great.
But I can't move.
I know.
My life is here.
My friends are here.
The sh is here.
And I've known you a month.
Oh, you hate me right
now, don't you? No.
No, it was a crazy idea
to begin with.
We were on a vacation high--
Exactly.
It's like a drug.
Right--
if the whole world
moved to their favorite
vacation spots,
then the whole world
would live in Hawaii
and Italy and Cleveland.
Totally, I mean...
But just knowing
that C-Town is out there
as an option for the future--
Liz...
it's gonna make it so
much easier-- Liz...
I took that job.
Blurgh.
Did you locate Tracy?
Ugh, not yet.
I'm working on it.
You know, you never answered
my question the other day.
What do you think of Phoebe?
Honestly, I wish
I had the guts
to do what you're doing.
Just...going for it.
God bless.
You still haven't answered
my question.
I...think she
likes you a lot.
And I think
she takes care of you.
And she's smart
and pretty.
And completely wrong.
And she doesn't
deserve you.
I think she's weird,
and I don't like her,
and her ex-boyfriend
is old.
And I don't even think
she's British!
And you
shouldn't marry her, Jack.
Please don't marry her!
Oh, my God.
Lemon, Phoebe was right.
You are infatuated with me.
What?
No! No, no, no.
Lemon, you
are a wonderful woman.
And you deserve to be
as happy as I am.
Maybe with Floyd, right?
No, don't mention Floyd.
Floyd is not happening.
Floyd is moving.
Floyd is moving?
What did you do?
What didIdo?
I acted like
a rational adult!
I didn't get engaged
to some gold digger,
and then delude myself
into thinking
that I could
keep up with her.
Yeah, Jack, I know
that you fell asleep
on top of her in Paris.
In Paris, France.
I think you should go.
Uh, Phoebe, darling,
Lemon was just leaving.
Blurgh.
www.tvsubtitles.net