michael:
my name is michael westen.
i used to be a spy until...
[ cellphone rings ]
Man: we got a burn notice
on you. you're blacklisted.
when you're burned,
you've got nothing --
no cash, no credit,
no job history.
you're stuck in whatever city
they decide to dump you in.
Where am i?
miami.
you do whatever work
comes your way.
you rely on anyone
who's still talking to you.
a trigger-happy
ex-girlfriend...
Should we shoot them?
...an old friend who used
to inform on you to the fbi...
You know spies --
a bunch of bitchy little girls.
...family, too...
hey, is that your mom again?
...if you're desperate.
someone needs your help,
michael.
bottom line --
as long as you're burned,
you're not going anywhere.
whether you're
hunting down extremists
in the mountains of kashmir
or tracking arms dealers
through the streets of moscow,
the life of a spy takes a toll.
so during downtimes,
you work out, eat right,
and try to recharge
your batteries,
because you never know
what's waiting for you
around the next corner.
Fiona:
hello, michael.
This is bud --
bail jumper.
We just got back from a lovely
time in the everglades.
You have a real chair
in this dump?
Poor bud's in a bad
mood. he didn't like
the music in my trunk.
Why is he here?
Oh, we're killing time,
Waiting for the bail bondsman
to open his office.
You know, he's been
throwing me more jobs
Than i can manage lately,
And i was thinking, as long
as you're still burned...
Trudging through swamps,
looking for guys like bud?
i'm not hurting for money
that bad, fi.
[ scoffs ]
could have fooled me.
Think about it, michael.
Your strategic know-how...
My expertise in the field.
My brains, your brawn.
[ scoffs ]
[ whoosh ]
Time for you to go, bud.
Mr. westen,
detective paxson, miami p.d.
This is detective lopez.
You mind if we ask you
a couple questions?
I'm in the middle
of something, actually.
Hmm.
I understand you're a bounty
hunter, miss glenanne.
Do you have
a bail-enforcer's license?
Uh, actually,
i'm freelancing.
Actually, you're
harboring a fugitive.
Consider this a warning.
Michael: uh, detective,
I spoke with some officers
at the station recently,
And i think we cleared up
all the questions they had.
Well, i have
different questions.
They're about
a traffic incident --
Three cars blown up,
three more totaled.
Apparently, we have a one-man
wrecking crew on our hands.
Well, how can you be
so sure it's a man?
I'm as progressive as
the next gal, miss glenanne,
But someone matching
mr. westen's description
Was spotted driving away
from the scene.
White male, dark hair...
[ clears throat ]
...athletically built?
I hope your department
pays overtime,
Because you're
gonna be searching
For a few hundred thousand
suspects.
I've got just one.
Stuff's been blowing up
pretty steadily
Since you arrived in miami.
So, are you gonna
answer my questions,
Or am i gonna pick my way
through everything you own?
That would be a workbench,
six power tools,
Four yogurts --
three yogurts.
I actually had one.
blueberry.
Well, you can tell me
all about it at the
station, mr. westen.
Get in the car.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
Welcome to your worst
nightmare, mr. westen.
You look wretched, michael.
Well, it's not a day spa
in there, fi.
Spent the last 24 hours
in the drunk tank.
So, detective paxson wasn't
questioning you the whole time?
Oh, no, there was
plenty of that, too.
[ sighs ] she's gonna be
some real trouble.
She already is.
she cost me my bounty.
I'll make it up
to you sometime.
Well, how does now sound?
i lined up a new gig.
I'll fill you in on all
the details over lunch.
Come on, fi.
not another bail jumper.
No, but one of my old
bail jumpers got me the job.
It's a referral.
So, how's stevie?
Doing time up at raiford
medium-security.
Says "hi," by the way.
Her brother jumped bail
on forgery charges.
I chased him to boca.
Had to hit him with a brick
to get him in the car.
Sweet guy.
He your partner?
Well, you'd have to
ask him that.
What can we
help you with?
[ sighs ]
this is my son, brandon.
He's been staying
with his dad, howard.
We're separated.
Howard hasn't let me see or talk
to brandon for three days.
Well, it sounds like
you should be talking
to a lawyer about this.
I have -- three of them.
They all say it'll take months
to get him into court.
Howard just needs someone
to knock some sense into him.
--
it's not a problem.
Anything else you need?
I just want to see my son.
Everything will be fine.
Right, michael?
[ horn honking ]
Excuse me.
Do you know my new girl?
She rebuilt this
engine by herself.
I'm telling you,
Just put a nice, sturdy tool
in that woman's hand --
I got it, sam.
find out anything?
Yeah, i asked around
about your lady detective.
Turns out you got
a stalker with a badge.
I mean, she checked
every self-storage place
From here up to
fort lauderdale.
She found some
surveillance video
Of you ducking into
a place down by homestead.
Not good.
what you got there?
Some c-4 and detonators.
Well, she's gonna own
them soon, 'cause she's
working on a warrant.
There's a hearing
in a couple of days,
But you got to get your stash
out of there before then.
Fiona:
are you coming, michael?
Oh, mike,
uh, you know,
Since i'm helping you
avoid felony charges,
I thought maybe there'd
be a lunch in it for me.
Michael?
Next time.
Geez.
i got you, baby.
Patricia: typical.
Howard spends 80 hours
a week at the office,
And he can't find an hour
to take care of his yard.
[ cellphone ringing ]
Fiona:
go ahead and take it.
Just keep your eyes
on the street.
This should be pretty
straightforward.
Yeah, ma?
It's somebody's
birthday today.
I thought you could come over
for a nice dinner
With sam and fiona.
We're celebrating
birthdays now?
We always did.
don't you remember sixth grade?
Your friend billy kane
was there.
it was his party, mom.
Well, it's never too late.
All right, where are we
getting takeout from?
Who said anything
about takeout?
[ paper hits floor ]
Howard!
So, you coming or not?
i'll try.
Michael, i don't want
to hear how you'll try.
i want you to promise.
fine.
i promise i'll try.
Howard!
[ engine turns over ]
[ tires squeal ]
You can stop now.
You can stop now!
Ugh! oh!
Howard...
We just want
to see your son.
Oh, you don't understand.
I'm sure whatever the
issue is, you can work
it out with your ex.
No! that's not
what i mean.
He was kidnapped.
Of course he was.
Brandon didn't come home
from school on thursday.
I got a call. uh, i don't
know the guy's name.
Is he asking for money?
No, i-i-i work
at a diamond wholesaler.
He wanted information
about an upcoming shipment.
Said not to contact
the police,
Or i'd never...
See brandon again.
He's calling today
with instructions.
How could you
not tell me?
I didn't want you calling
the police, patricia.
I was trying
to protect brandon.
That was not your decision
to make! he's my son, too!
Look, he just wants diamonds.
i'm going to give them to him.
Howard,
it's not that simple.
If this guy really
wants to disappear,
He has no incentive
to return your son.
Brandon's old enough
to identify him.
Whoa, whoa, w-what --
what are you saying?
You know what
he's saying, howard.
They're not gonna bring us
brandon back alive!
We should call the police.
no!
No cops!
he said he would kill him.
Enough.
Michael and i will
take care of him...
...without involving
the cops.
But you can't be at
each other's throats, okay?
When the kidnapper
calls again,
You're going to say
you're not doing anything
Until you get proof that
your son is alive and unhurt,
And then you're gonna ask
for a face-to-face meeting.
You think he'll come?
If he wants his diamonds,
he will.
And if we're lucky,
we'll follow him back
to where brandon is.
Well, won't that
be dangerous?
It doesn't matter.
i'll do it.
Whatever it takes
to get brandon back.
I told howard not to take
that stupid job.
Sales manager.
We were doing
just fine as reps.
You work together?
we did.
It was great till
he took that promotion.
Long hours, travel,
and now this.
well, i'm sure this
was not part of the plan
When he took the job.
Well, he should have
known the risk.
Patricia, i want you
to try something.
It's a relaxation exercise
i do in situations like this.
I want you
to close your eyes...
And breathe deep.
Picture a peaceful
mountain stream.
Can you do that?
Now picture yourself...
Drowning the kidnapper
in the stream.
You're taking a rock
from the stream
And raising it
above your head...
michael: fi.
...and with tremendous force,
you're bringing --
Fi!
We got something.
he's passed by twice.
smart criminals
have a variety of ways
to find out if a meeting
is under police surveillance.
some are more subtle
than others.
Howard, right?
yeah.
I'm santora.
Nice to meet you.
Ugh! oh! oh!
throw a few punches...
and any cops in the area
have to come running.
God! do something!
We can't.
he's testing us.
But he's gonna kill him!
he's --
Whoa.
patricia. patricia!
If you want your son back,
you'll stay in the car.
You got any friends around here
i should know about?
Ugh!
You tell anyone about
our little arrangement?
[ groans ]
look at me, howard.
behavior in a combat situation
is unpredictable.
sometimes trained soldiers
go screaming for the hills.
sometimes guys
who have never fired
anything bigger than a cap gun
turn out to have
ice in their veins.
[ breathing heavily ]
Nobody knows.
Let me see my son.
Today's headline.
the kid's fine.
Now, let's be clear.
You're not calling
the shots here.
You're not gonna make
any more demands,
And you're not gonna
try anything cute.
If anyone touches me,
If i'm a minute late
checking in with my guys,
You never see
the kid again.
Got it?
Yeah.
Good.
Ugh!
That's just
so you don't forget.
Now...
Let's talk
about my diamonds.
in the field, it's often
your human instincts
that jeopardize an operation.
helping people is great,
but there are times that
impulse can get people killed.
sometimes the right thing to do
is let a guy bleed for a while.
Stay here.
[ moans ]
He kept hitting me.
i didn't know what to do.
You did everything right,
howard.
He said he wants the stones
in 24 hours...
Or brandon dies.
That's not gonna happen.
How'd we do?
Uh, not so great.
Santora didn't
go near the kid.
He's hanging out at a bar,
sipping mojitos.
Mike, this guy's
not afraid to be seen.
But i thought you could follow
him to where brandon is.
I thought --
he's smart.
He's keeping the job
compartmentalized.
Howard's at the hospital
getting stitches.
That was all for nothing?!
Not nothing.
we'll know when he moves.
I got a buddy
keeping an eye on him.
Why can't you just grab him and
waterboard him or something,
Make him tell us
where brandon is?
You torture somebody,
They'll tell you anything
to make it stop.
No, there are better ways
to get reliable information.
Sam, how do you feel
about a little...
Reverse interrogation?
Never been a big fan, mike.
What's reverse
interrogation?
We used to do it
during the cold war.
You send one of your guys
in there to be interrogated
To learn what the bad guys
are worried about.
You play your cards right,
Their questions will tell you
all about them.
You play
your cards wrong --
Have a little faith, sam.
How long do you think
it'll take to set up?
Car, building...
Some cop lights --
a couple hours.
All right, call me
when it's done.
We're gonna find your son.
This is a valuable
lesson for you.
C-4 is meant to be used,
not stored.
I'll keep that in mind.
I'm serious.
All those times you told me
to make the explosions smaller,
I shouldn't have
listened to you,
Then paxson wouldn't have
anything to hang you with.
when you're concerned
you might be walking
into a police stakeout,
there are a number of things
to look out for --
parked cars or vans...
Hold on, fi.
...workers that seem
unusually preoccupied...
and curious kids.
no matter where you go
in the world,
little boys
like candy, puppies, and cops.
I think our detective friend
had a surprise planned.
Mr. westen.
Detective paxson and
detective forget-your-name.
You know, i was thinking
about renting one of
these storage units.
You mind if i look at yours?
Storage unit?
Yes, or you could give us
The fake name you used
when you rented it.
Or go ahead and clear it out.
don't let us stop you.
I think there's been
a big misunderstanding.
I actually heard
you were in the neighborhood,
And i came by to see you.
Yeah, i wanted to give you
some receipts --
You know,
give you a better idea
Of what i've been doing,
where i've been going.
That one's for breakfast.
fi had a spanish omelet.
Egg whites only.
thank you.
Well, if you get the urge
to destroy any evidence,
Stop by.
We'll be waiting for you.
Was that flirting,
or does she hate you?
I am not her type.
[ cellphone ringing ]
Yeah, sam?
Hey, mike, you ready
to do this? i'm all set.
Seriously, though, i think
this is a little risky.
I'm on my way.
[ siren wailing ]
when it comes to cover i.d.s,
impersonating a bad cop
is much better than
impersonating a good one.
an honest cop follows
policies and procedures,
from the way he cuts his hair
to the approach he takes
when carrying out
a traffic stop.
pose as a good cop,
and you have to go by the book.
pose as a bad cop,
and you can throw out that book
and write your own.
Hi, there.
detective finley.
Wow, nice seats.
What is that,
pearl leather?
Let me call my lawyer.
he can tell you all about them.
[ chuckling ]
all right, just relax.
I'm here unofficially.
Just think of this as...
a business meeting.
You want to do
a business meeting?
How about you make
an appointment?
[ chuckling ] okay.
When's a good time
to talk about someone
Who's trying to move in
on one of your scores?
Just worked a drug bust.
Heard something that
might interest you.
in the criminal world,
selling yourself as a colleague
often means
doing something illegal.
so while snorting lactose
isn't pleasant...
[ snorts ]
...it may put
people's minds at ease.
Oh ho! got this
on the bust, too.
[ sniffles ]
90% pure. mmm!
Puts hair on your chest,
i'll tell you that.
What's this you heard
about a score?
Yeah, it was a coke buy
down in overtown.
Busted a guy i know,
a junkie named shep.
So, he's trying
to get me to lay off him
'cause he says he knows
something about a plan
To, uh, rip you off.
Some junkie told you this?
Yeah, he's a snitch.
Hey, the guy's a mess,
but his intel's usually good.
So, why'd you bust him?
Well, i take him in every so
often just to keep him in line.
So, listen, i'm taking
him to the station.
For a couple of grand...
You can question him first.
Interested?
He said something about a kid,
if that means anything.
A kid?
Yeah, he didn't say
much more than that.
Man, i cannot
get over this leather.
It's hand-tooled, right?
Where is this guy?
Madeline:
so, what you're saying is,
Michael's missing
his own birthday party?!
H-he's busy.
Busy?
Busy being shot at
or busy get blown up?
Does he ever
take a day off?
Ow! damn it!
I mean, you know...
A little consideration
is all i'm asking.
I'm making an effort.
so should he.
Well, he seems to be
making progress.
Don't fool yourself, honey.
Loving michael
is always trench warfare.
Hmm.
You tell him
to come to the party.
Sam:
busted a few raves here.
Don't worry.
no one comes around now.
Place is condemned.
It's where i do
my, uh, freelance work.
So, the snitch is in there.
you got my money?
Here you go.
i'll take it from here.
Oh, oh, no, my friend.
That's not how it works.
We question
this guy together.
No offense, but i don't like
people knowing my business.
Yeah, no offense,
but i don't care.
Your business doesn't
concern me.
What concerns me is nobody
touches my prisoner but me.
I got my own way
of asking questions.
Yeah, and i got to explain
every scratch on the guy
When i take him
down to the station.
So if you want to come down
there with me, that's fine.
Otherwise,
we do this my way.
And what about later?
This guy shep
gets to mouth off?
[ laughs ]
don't worry about that.
I got enough on this guy to send
him to prison on the moon.
He'll keep his mouth shut.
Santora: so, nobody knows you
got this guy here, huh?
Sam: [ chuckles ]
don't get any ideas.
As far as my
supervisor's concerned,
I'm working on a case.
Officially, i'm in the middle
of interviewing you,
So if anything
happens to me,
He knows who to
come looking for.
Let's do this.
So, i don't know you...
But i hear you know me...
And my business.
interrogation professionals
don't ask questions directly.
they hide what they know
and don't know.
Aw, you're a real prince,
finley,
A real stand-up guy.
After all i've done for you,
this is what i get?
Nothing personal.
just business.
amateurs tend to ask
for exactly what they want.
Who told you about the kid?
it's like playing poker
with your cards showing.
I think your buddy here
wants to kiss me, finley.
Hey, i'm not that type.
Ugh!
Answer the question.
Sam:
who told you?
A friend of a friend.
I didn't get his name.
They didn't give me details.
i didn't ask for them.
All right, tell me
about this job.
[ sighs ]
They needed help
moving a -- a kid.
They wanted a place
that they could stash him
For a few days
off the street.
I found it.
can i go now?
You can go when i find out
what the hell is going on.
The guy who hired you --
He say when they
were planning this?
Oh, come on, you think
they're gonna tell me when?
Yeah, right after
they told me
Their vacation plans and their
social security numbers.
I don't know.
You got a smart mouth.
Maybe you should start
using it to save your ass.
They told me...
to find a place...
Where they could
stash the kid...
For a few days.
Do you want me
to say that slower?
Where'd you meet them?
Right.
do you think i'm stupid?
I tell you that,
And you're gonna go tell them
and i'm gonna get killed.
You worry about that later.
you got more immediate problems.
Ugh!
[ coughing ]
all right, all right.
All right.
It was a restaurant --
a diner, i think.
when people are desperate
for information,
they start
filling in the blanks,
often without realizing it.
it's something
fortune-tellers rely on.
it works pretty much
the same way for spies.
Think harder.
although fortune-tellers
usually don't get
smacked around as much.
[ groans ]
It was a diner.
It had burgers and fries.
The seaside diner?
Was that it?
off the causeway?
Yes. thank you.
I met the guy
at the seaside diner.
What'd this guy
look like?
Well, i don't know.
H-he was a guy.
Was a white guy, maybe.
"white"?
I'm just gonna go out in miami
and look for a white guy?
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
No! all right, all right,
all right!
It was -- it was --
the waitress knew him.
She called him "flowers."
They knew him there.
And that's it. that's --
that's -- that's all i know.
Man:
yeah, this is jimmy.
Get over to the
seaside diner now.
Ask around for a guy
named flowers.
[ chuckles ]
Surprising how much
a guy remembers
When you help him
out a little.
Listen, this is taking
longer than i thought.
I got to make a call.
you two play nice.
Fi, get over
to the seaside diner.
It's off macarthur causeway.
santora is sending a guy there.
You might be able
to tail him back to brandon.
Just stay out of sight,
all right?
Fiona:
stay out of sight?
You're seriously
telling me that?
Well, it's nothing personal.
Things are just getting
a little tense around here.
So, you and your friends thought
that you could rip me off?
That right? what was
the plan with the kid?
I told you everything i know.
i was supposed to get --
What was the plan?!
I was paid a lousy
150 bucks for this job.
You think i don't
want to tell you?
Put the knife away!!
You've got a sharp knife!!
Michael: get that knife
out of my face!
Fi, just go now.
Aah!
Fine.
You want to --
you want to know the plan?
Yeah, i do.
All right, well,
You're never gonna
know the plan with a knife,
Because cutting me up
ain't gonna turn me
into a mind reader!
Whoa, there, friend.
My prisoner...
My rules, remember?
Now, you want me
to lean on him,
All you have to do is ask.
We clear?
Now, put it away.
[ breathing heavily ]
We may have a lead
on brandon's location.
You're going
to get him now?
If things go
according to plan.
I'll come with you.
i can help.
Well, that's sweet
and very brave,
But you are gonna
get yourself shot.
Well, if that's what it
takes to get our son
back, i don't care.
Brandon is gonna
need you alive.
Getting shot
sounds noble
Until it actually
happens to you.
Don't volunteer for it unless
it's absolutely necessary.
Brandon's gonna be fine.
I know it.
You want to do something
for your son?
Don't forget this moment.
Yeah.
And don't ever
work together.
Not all couples
can handle it.
[ door closes ]
Okay, so,
this flowers --
He show you
where the kid is?
No, t-t-they drove me
through the neighborhood --
T-the route
they were gonna take.
I don't remember --
I've had enough of
you-don't-remember.
No more warnings.
I've answered
all your questions.
I want you to tell me
who is trying to rip me off!
And i want a house
on star island,
Filled with
strippers and bikinis,
But wishing just
doesn't make it so, man!
It's time to focus.
Now, listen, i assume there
isn't a sign on the place
That says "the kid is here,"
So how would he know
if he saw it?
Come on, you got guys
with the kid?
maybe shep saw them.
Yeah, i got two guys.
michael:
yeah, could be.
I saw a couple of guys,
but i didn't talk to them.
i don't know their names.
Did you see the kid?
no.
Okay, santora, so calm down.
he didn't see the kid.
Maybe it's not
the same place.
He didn't see him
because the kid
Is in a shed
behind the house!
Now shut up
and let me think!
searching for a concealed enemy
who could be anywhere
is a waste of time.
Yeah, it's jimmy.
Nobody's heard of "flowers"
at the diner.
usually, your best bet
is to stay put
and give your enemy
a reason to come to you.
What's going on?
Is there something
i should know about?
Don't worry about it.
Just get back to the house
and watch the kid.
[ camera shutter clicks ]
to tail someone, you need
both skill and instinct.
you need skill
because the driving is tough.
you can't get too close,
and you can't drift
too far away.
you can't go too fast
or too slow.
you need instinct
because every turn,
every lane change, every bridge
raises the risk of being seen.
anyone can be trained
to follow a car.
but it takes good instincts
to know when it's time
to stop following.
So, i had one of my guys
ask around.
No one at that restaurant
Ever heard of anyone
named flowers.
Why is that m-my fault?
Maybe he went
to the wrong place.
He went to the diner,
you lying son of a bitch.
Why would i lie to you?
That's it.
I'm shutting this thing down
before it gets any worse.
when you work
with someone long enough,
you learn to trust them.
when things go bad,
that trust is the difference
between life and death.
of course, knowing that doesn't
make it less terrifying
to back a play
you know nothing about.
Listen, uh...
I know this guy, shep.
I mean, he's a pain in the ass,
but his information is good.
Yeah? because he told
me some story about a
guy who doesn't exist?
Maybe the guy does exist.
He could be one
of your own guys.
So, one more time...
This flowers guy...
What did he look like?
He has, uh,
slicked-back hair.
He was a muscle guy.
Uh...
He wears
those muscle shirts,
You know,
to show off his arms.
That's the best i can do.
that's all i got.
That's flowers?
you're sure?
Yeah, that's the guy
who told me about the kid.
Ugh!
Hey, hey!
What is wrong
with you?
Santora:
that's my guy.
Like you said, my own guy
is trying to steal from me.
What guy?
His name's jimmy.
The guy i sent to the diner
to look for flowers --
it turns out the son
of a bitch is flowers.
He's supposed to be
watching the kid.
Instead, he's planning
to rip me off.
You know,
you can call it off.
Let the kid go.
Hell, just give him to me.
I'll tell his parents i found
him wandering around.
It's too late for that.
He saw my face.
it's over.
I got to clean
this whole mess up.
Whoa, whoa, what are you
gonna with that?
Listen, you've been
a stand-up guy.
I appreciate that.
And i don't want
to cause you problems.
But that guy
in there, shep...
He's got to die.
Now.
every profession
has occupational hazards.
butchers cut themselves,
house painters
fall off ladders,
and operatives get asked
to help kill their own people.
[ laughing ] hey.
you watch it, friend.
I got unis checking
on my interview.
Back off.
This is my snitch.
I got to be able
to explain what goes on.
My own guys
are turning on me.
If he's part of it,
he's got to go.
They all do.
Oh, i see, so i'm just
supposed to sit back
And hope none of this
blows back on me?
No way, pal.
that's not how this goes down.
You got any ideas?
i'm listening.
Yeah.
Yeah, i say that, uh...
Dropped him off by the road.
I let him out 'cause
he was sick from the dope.
I'll just tell them that --
that he attacked me,
And he tried to escape.
Wait, you?
Yeah. don't you remember?
he's my prisoner.
How am i gonna
explain a suspect
That's full of these
random bullet holes?
We'll have the damn fbi here.
it's better this way.
Put a few rounds
in his chest with my gun,
But you do it out by the road,
you understand?
Your gun? what the hell
are you talking about?
Look, i got to be able to sell
this story to my department.
If i don't,
they're coming after me.
Trust me,
it's better this way.
Come on, come on.
All right.
I'll go get shep.
You get your guy on the phone.
you tell him to sit tight.
I don't want this situation
any worse than it already is.
[ groans ]
[ both grunt ]
Michael: oh!
You all right, mike?
Yeah. you still pack
a pretty good punch, sam.
Yeah, well,
the good news is
Santora's planning on
going back to the kid.
Fi followed their guy.
They're holed up on an island
off the causeway.
And the bad news?
Santora wants
to kill you first.
I convinced him
to do it with my gun
Up on the side
of the road,
Make it look like you
were trying to get away.
How far is the road?
A couple hundred yards.
I guess it'll have to do.
Mike, if there was
any other way...
There isn't.
All right,
when you get free,
Take his car
and head to the causeway.
I'll get you the address.
Good luck, mikey.
Santora: hey.
Let's take a walk.
Listen, listen,
you don't want to do this.
This -- i could
tell you more.
I could tell you about
flowers and the plan.
Man, you don't
want to do this.
I know plenty already.
I mean,
why shut this down?
There's money
to be made here, man.
I-i could help you.
we could split it 50/50.
[ laughing ] oh, yeah?
[ sobbing ] i don't
want to die, man!
Please...
Please, i'm begging you!
[ grunting ]
[ grunting stops ]
[ coughs ]
[ tires squeal ]
He got away.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Where's my gun?
He took it!
He's got my gun?
we got to find him! now!
Could he be going
to meet up with jimmy?
I don't know. maybe.
And you told jimmy
to stay put with the kid?
Yeah.
where's the house?
We don't have time for this!
where's the house?!
Hibiscus island.
What address?
I got to know!
they got my gun!
Look, if i go down
for this, so do you!
1313 prospect street.
what are you doing?
They have a security office
on the island.
I'll ask
if they've seen him.
[ ringing ]
[ cellphone ringing ]
Yeah, sam?
Yeah, this is officer finley,
uh, miami p.d.
I'd like to know
if you've seen anyone
Go to 1313 prospect street.
Uh, there's someone
going there right now.
[ dialing ]
Fi, i got the address.
[ tires screech ]
[ gun cocks ]
people underestimate
the tactical importance of tv
in urban warfare.
guard duty's boring, and a
ballgame passes the time better
than, say,
looking for intruders.
more battles have been
decided by pennant races
than people imagine.
[ muffled shouting ]
Fiona: brandon?
We're gonna take you back
to your mom and dad, okay?
Santora:
the junkie's here.
We do him and jimmy first,
then the kid.
Okay, you cut
through the backyard,
I'll cover you
from the front?
Okay.
Have fun in there,
you son of a bitch.
Look who's here.
[ indistinct tv chatter ]
You thought you could
steal from me?
What the hell
are you saying?
where's the kid?
I said
where's the kid?!
I don't know!
he was just there!
I know what
you did, jimmy.
I know you're flowers.
i know everything.
I don't know what you're
talking about. get that
thing out of my face!
Put it down now! you picked
the wrong guy to double-cross!
I did everything
you ever said!
you sold me out
to a junkie!
it's always best to have
business arguments unarmed.
when tempers are high
and everyone's got a gun,
you never know what's
going to set someone off.
[ gunshot ]
[ gunshots ]
Jimmy, jimmy, don't --
I don't know
what to say.
You don't have to
say anything.
Think about leaving miami.
You don't want to be
around if santora's
friends come looking.
Oh, we weren't
planning to be.
We've, uh, talked about
making a fresh start
Somewhere else,
together.
Patricia: thank you...
For everything.
You ready?
[ chuckles ]
A fresh start...together.
Kind of inspiring,
don't you think?
I'd settle for
staying out of jail.
Come on, fi,
we got a date...
With the storage unit.
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
when a front door
is being watched,
your best option oftentimes
is just to make a back door.
if you don't mind getting damp,
a water saw is a great tool
for the job.
it will cut through the wall
much more quietly
than a metal saw
and won't ignite
anything flammable
that happens
to be lying around.
Hey, detective, uh,
would you like to come in?
I have
some more receipts.
Cute.
You know, i finally did get
a look at that storage unit
That didn't belong to you.
Find anything interesting?
Yeah, i found a hole
in the back of the wall
And a puddle
of water inside.
Yeah, the heavy rains
the other night
Must have done
some funny things.
This isn't over.
[ exhales sharply ]
Did you make this?
You like it?
I wanted this to be special,
so i cooked.
It's good.
[ laughs ]
Happy birthday, mike.
Beer. a five-pack.
thanks.
Yeah, it's imported.
It's supposed to be brewed
by some monks in belgium.
It's, uh...
It's really good,
or, you know, so i heard.
Would you like some?
Yeah, thanks.
Sam:
it's kind of pricy,
But i figured only
the best for you, mike.
Would you like
a bottle opener, sam?
Oh, no, no, i got one.
thanks. yeah.
I never leave home
without it.
Sam, you need
a bottle opener.
Why don't i show you
where it is?
[ sighs ]
Okay. sure.
[ clears throat ]
It's a bayonet.
Used during the first
world war for close fighting.
Fi...
Thanks?
Well, someone once told me
That caring for you
is like trench warfare.
So I thought you should arm yourself.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- Bierdopje.com
www.tvsubtitles.net