Subs by Raceman and Traff
www.forom.com
Excuse me.
There's a line, buddy.
There's two lines.
No, no, there's one line.
We're in it.
I'm just getting a hot dog.
We're all getting hot dogs.
What, you think
there's two lines
and we're all in this line--
you're the only genius
that got in the other line?
Can you believe this guy?
Don't line up behind him.
He cheated you.
Hey, shut up.
What do you want
on yours, baby?
I want all the hot dogs,
please.
Yeah, I'm--I'm buying
all the hot dogs.
Oh, come on, lady.
And I'm giving them
to the good people.
Who's that?
Kicking it down the street
Causin' a stir.
Who's that?
I know that you're wondrin'
That's her
That's her, that's her,
that's her, that's her.
Who's got
the kind of charisma that
The boys prefer.
Who's hot
and you know that she knows it.
That's her.
She's like a summer sky.
It's like some cherry pie.
And there is butterfly.
Me oh my.
Who flaunts her feminine magic.
That's her
That's me!
That's Pam!
The overly-confident
morbidly obese woman.
This fat suit
smells like corn chips.
Going again, please.
Thank you.
And this is the set
of The Girlie Show.
It's a real fun
ladies' comedy show for ladies.
Hey, everybody.
Look, here's someone
you never get a chance to meet.
It's the head writer
of The Girlie Show, Liz Lemon!
The Girlie Show.
Hold on, I'll connect you.
- Hey.
- What's up?
Hey, have you looked
at that Cat Lady sketch?
It's still
seven minutes long.
Yikes, okay.
Oh, and Standards has a problem
with that Michael Jackson bit.
But why?
Apparently you can't say
he's got a vagina.
Oh, it's--fine, I'll just
take the whole thing out.
Hey, you gotta tell that NBC page
to take it down a notch.
Oh, you mean Ken?
Yeah, he just embarrassed me
in front of a whole tour group.
I'll talk to him.
What is this?
Ah, well, you know how I hate it
when people cheat or break rules?
Yes, I do.
Well, I just spent
150 bucks on wieners.
Atta boy.
Chumley.
The beverage situation
around here is reprehensible.
Oh, good morning, sunshine.
Surely our massive conglomerate parent company
could spring for a samovar of coffee.
Yeah, or like
a big coffee dispenser.
That's what a samovar is.
Are there other black nerds,
or is it just you and Urkel?
Uh, Cerie, do you wanna
get some coffee?
No, thank you.
No?
Hey, Josh.
I need to change
your Michael Jackson thing.
Didn't you tell me you had
a Jay Leno impression?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Check it out.
So, uh, President Bush
is in the news again.
Have you heard about this?
No, Jay Leno.
The host of the Tonight Show.
I thought that's what
I was doing.
So, uh, my wife Mavis and I like
to go shopping for old cars.
You know?
No, no. Like Jay Leno.
Like, "Hey, here are
the headlines."
You ever--you ever notice
when you eat a lot of cheese, and you--
How is that different
from what I was doing, though?
And I don't think you need to
introduce the writers to the tour group.
I agree.
I thought they would find it interesting,
but they really did not.
Well, Kenneth,
just respect their privacy.
I promise I'll do better,
Mr. Hornberger.
Sure you will.
I just--
I just love television so much.
We all do.
Liz, they want you and Pete
on the 50th floor.
Who, Gary?
Tell him I'll be up
in half an hour.
No, they said now.
If they got cookies up there,
grab some.
Ooh, and get them to pay
for my Samovar.
Of course, I mean,
I assume that's what we're meeting about.
What about, uh, Ray Romano?
Can you do Ray?
Hey. God, oh. Debra.
There you go.
My brother's tall.
Right?
Are we in trouble
or something?
No way.
Gary loves the show.
Pleased with the ratings.
Right.  Of course.
They love us.
Where's Gary?
Gary's dead.
I'm Jack Donaghy.
New VP of development
for NBC/GE/Universal/Kmart.
Oh, we own Kmart now.
No. So why are you dressed
like we do?
I'm surprised
you're renovating.
This is
such a nice office.
It's a great office, but sometimes,
you have to change things
that are perfectly good just to, uh,
make them your own.
Please.
Ah, I'll call her back.
Is she at the White House line?
Great.
Tell them I need
a 4:00 a.m. tee off time.
Uh, five inches,
but it's thick.
Are you familiar with
the GE Tri-vection Oven?
I don't cook very much.
Sure, I got you.
New York, third wave feminist,
college educated.
Single and pretending
to be happy about it.
Overscheduled, undersexed,
you buy any magazine
that says "Healthy body image"
on the cover.
And every two years,
you take up knitting for...
A week.
That is dead on!
What, are you gonna
guess my weight now?
You don't want me
to do that.
That knitting thing is uncanny.
How do you do that?
Market research, my friend.
Years and years of market research,
which lead to my greatest triumph.
The Tri-vection oven.
Oh, my wife
wants one of those.
Could we get Pete
an oven, please?
Hey.
The GE Tri-vection oven cooks
perfect food five times faster
than a conventional oven,
because it uses three kinds of heat.
Thermal  technology
for consistent temperature.
GE Precise Air convection technology
for optimal air circulation,
and microwave technology
for incredible speed.
With three kinds of heat,
you can cook a turkey in 22 minutes.
Wow.
That is impressive.
The people upstairs think so.
That's why they promoted me.
That's why they sent me here
to retool your show.
Retool what now?
I'm the new vice president of
east coast television
and microwave oven programming.
That sounds like you program
microwave ovens.
I like you.
You have the boldness
of a much younger woman.
Lee, does my face
look bloated to you?
When I played that lady rapist
on Law & Order,
guess what the makeup guy
put on under my eyes
to take the puffiness out?
Hemorrhoid cream.
Ms. Maroney?
I have the cat wrangler
here for you.
Oh, is it that
horrible little--Hi.
Hey. Greta Johannsen.
It's short for "LaGreta."
Hi, great to see you again.
You too. I'm here
to introduce you
to feline actors
you're gonna be working with tonight.
Okay.
This is Po-Po.
And this here is Captain Boots.
Hello.
Uh, would you describe yourself
as "cat competent?"
Oh, yes. I love cats.
I used to have two cats.
But then I moved to this place
with hardwood floors,
so we had to
put them down.
I'm joking.
I've done several focus groups,
on this show,
and what I've gleaned--
The blonde, big-eyed girl
is popular with women and older gays.
Jenna, that's
my friend Jenna.
And the kid with the funny hair
is liked by women,
but you're missing men
between 18 and 49.
I'm not missing them,
they're just not there.
I think I can fix that.
So your job is, you take things
that are already working, and you fix them.
That's a great job.
Okay, let's--
Why don't we, um--
You're missing
that third kind of heat.
I want you to think about
Tracy Jordan.
Okay--the black guy?
The black movie star.
I flew with him on a private jet
to the Super Bowl recently,
and I found him very entertaining.
Isn't he, um...
crazy?
Tracy's had his problems
in the last few years.
I am a Jedi!
The important thing to remember is,
he was never charged with a crime.
It's not illegal to fall asleep
on your neighbor's roof.
Nor should it be.
Tracy Jordan is the third heat.
I don't know where we're gonna
find room in the budget for a guy like Tracy Jordan.
I think I do.
What are you doing?
Sometimes when I have
these stress dreams,
if I go to sleep in the dream,
I come out of it.
"This is not a dream."
Tracy Jordan is
in New York today, Liz.
I'd like you
to have lunch with him.
We have a show tonight,
Mr. Donaghy.
I don't know if your research
covered this,
but we do a dress rehearsal,
and then a live show.
That's  tonight.
This is lunch.
If it's not a good fit,
I'll drop the whole thing.
If I meet with Tracy Jordan,
and we mutually agree
that this is the worst idea ever,
you'll back off?
I'm known
for being reasonable.
Okay.
Alfredo, 2:00 p.m.
I'm not dressed for that.
You're dressed
for Burger King.
Should we make it
Burger King?
Pete, hang back for me.
Yeah, you bet.
Hey.
What happened to your head?
Uh, the sky is falling.
Do you have a pair
of dress pants
or a skirt or something
I could borrow?
Thank you, Lee.
Whatever.
Hey, you know
in that Cat Lady sketch?
Do I have to hold
a real cat?
Cat Lady sketch?
That thing's gonna get cut.
Oh, good.
Who's that?
That is
the new network dude.
Mmm, yummers.
He reminds me of Scotty
on General Hospital.
What? No, ew, Jenna.
Do not like that man.
That is a bad man.
God, you have a gift.
Laura Bush
is your size.
Hi, uh, what are you
doing down here?
I'm known for being
hands-on.
Clearly.
That's how you should dress
for work, by the way.
Yeah, if I was president
of the Philippines.
Afghanistan is a different
situation...
I'll have an apple juice.
Oh, we don't have
apple juice, sir.
Then I'll take
a vodka and tonic.
Hi, I'm Liz Lemon.
I know who you are.
I thought there was a...
strict dress code at this place.
I do recommend
the pumpkin ravioli.
They're very subtle.
So, Tracy, this Jack Donaghy guy
wanted me
to talk to you about
joining the cast of our show.
And I don't know
how you feel about that--
Lemme ask you a question.
Everybody at this table.
Did  he just say the word
"pumpkin" to me?
Yes, um, pumpkin ravioli.
Yo! I'm buggin'.
I can't do this.
I cannot eat here.
I can't eat here.
I got to go someplace where they
make food that I like.
Lemon, let's go.
I will not work
with Tracy Jordan.
It's just a rumor.
Have you seen
any of his movies?
The guy's sensibility
is just cretinous.
I saw the one where he plays, like,
five different characters.
Yeah, Black Cop/White Cop.
No.
Who Dat Ninja?
No, he-- He had to pretend
to be this old lady...
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
Goodness gracious!
You hooligans
better watch out.
'Cause this honky grandma
be trippin'!
Oh, yeah.
That movie was hilarious.
I saw it like five times.
Where's the love?
Right on, let me get two apple chickens
and some pecan waffles.
Nothing for me, I--
I had, like,
four hot dogs this morning.
Eat, Lemon.
Eat!
I hate skinny women.
Hey, Lorna.
Ten beers.
So, Tracy, we should talk
about the show.
Yeah, I ain't doing it
unless I can get to do it my way.
You know,
I want it to be raw.
HBO-style content.
Well, it's not HBO.
It's TV.
And I don't think
that it's a good fit--
You know, cause
I wanna drop truth bombs.
You know how pissed off I was
when Us Weekly said that I was on crack?
That's racism.
I'm not on crack.
I'm straight up
mentally ill!
Sure.
I got mental health issues.
Sure, well, you know...
Who doesn't, really?
Hey, has anyone seen Liz?
Or Pete?
She went out.
Well, who's in charge
when they're not here?
I'm in charge.
Oh. Okay.
Um, well, I'm not sure
about this costume.
I think it's hot.
Thank you.
I'm Jenna, by the way.
Ms. Moroney, I got
the hemorrhoid cream you wanted.
It's for my face.
Well, wherever you're putting it,
I think it's working.
You know, I don't--
I don't think you'd like it.
'Cause we work
a lot of hours,
and it's live TV,
which is risky.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like risky.
See, me and you,
we play the game.
We know how to be
acceptable.
Hello, great meeting.
I drink coffee, please.
This show is our chance
to break the shackles.
'Cause the white dudes
want to see us fail.
What white dudes?
All of 'em.
Jack Donaghy, General Electric,
George Bush, Karl Robe.
Karl Robe, you say?
Affirmative action
was designed to keep women
and minorities in competition
with each other.
To distract us while white dudes inject AIDS
into our chicken nuggets.
That's a metaphor.
Sure.
You should tell that
to Us Weekly.
Hey, Lemon.
You like karaoke?
I know a joint.
No, no, I--
I gotta wrap up this lunch meeting, Tracy.
I'll take you.
I just gotta make
a quick stop first.
You know what, when people say
they need to make a quick stop,
they usually mean at the bank
or the store.
No, thank you.
You know what, this is for
computer classes.
Know why I should do
this TV show, Lemon?
I really don't.
To get you rich.
'Cause you know
if I'm on that TV show,
it's gon' blow up.
How do you know
I'm not rich?
Your teeth.
You got to think
like these strippers, Lemon.
They know the window of opportunity's
only open for a moment.
You gotta get in
when you're young.
Get the money
and get out.
Yeah, well,
I'm not a sex worker, Tracy.
I don't have sex
for a living.
Neither do we.
Neither do they.
Yes, they do.
Where is my phone?
We are strong
No one can tell us
we're wrong
Searching our hearts
for so lo-ong
He's got charisma.
No, that's Charisma
over there.
Girlie Show.
Ken, send me a car, okay?
What is your location?
Dark Sensations,
in the Bronx.
I wish you were here.
Mr. Donaghy does not get
us showbiz people.
Let me talk to Pete, okay?
Oh, Pete got fired this morning.
That's so weird
that you don't know that.
Jack Donaghy thinks
he's gonna come into my house
and mess with my show?
Hell no.
Jenna and I worked
for years to get this show.
You know, I moved
from Chicago for this.
From Chicago?
I was in
Scottie Pippen's wedding.
Now Donaghy is trying
to steal it from us.
He already fired Pete,
who is a great producer.
He fired Pete?
He can't fire Pete.
You know what, I quit.
He can suck it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, suck it, Pete.
No, you're not listening.
You're not a good listener.
20 minutes to air.
But Liz said we were cutting
the cat lady sketch.
She said it stinks.
Ouch.
This is why Liz is wrong.
Animal humour is universal.
I  just don't think
that I'm good in it.
Do you think
I'm good in it?
I think this is your opportunity to go out there
and prove everybody wrong.
What--what do you mean?
Who's everybody?
The network that wanted
to fire you,
the focus groups that said
you had a weird eye--
You mean this eye?
Okay, this eye--
It doesn't open all the way
because when I was little, my sister peed in it.
Tonight is your opportunity to go out there
and change all of our minds.
What?
Where is Liz?
Liz?!
Four minutes to air.
That's four minutes to air.
Is Liz back yet?
No, which cat
do you want Jenna to carry?
I'm sorry?
Which cat?
Oh.
I want...that one.
Jack Donaghy to the control room,
please. Jack Donaghy.
Peanut's not an actor.
I just--I just
rescued him from a lab.
Hey, Lemon,
I'll drop you off.
Where do you live?
The studio.
I want you to drop me
at the studio.
I want to tell Donaghey
to his face that I quit.
And I want to do it
in front of the whole crew,
so that they know
he didn't fire me.
I wanna see that.
Gonna turn the lights
down low.
It's almost time
for the Girlie Show
Ooh, ooh, pull over.
Pull over here.
Tracy, I don't have time
for this.
This is where I grew up.
This is the Jordan
family estate?
Wasn't no Jordan
family nothin'.
This is where I was
in foster care.
Oh. Sorry.
Me and two other dudes
and a girl with messed-up fingers.
I'm so lucky
I got out of here.
It's not luck,
I mean...
You got out of here because you're
very talented, and... people love you, and...
Are you peeing?
Where's Donaghy?
I wanna talk to him right now.
Last time I saw him,
he was riding a crane camera.
Oh, I have Pete for you.
Pete, oh, my God.
I didn't know.
No, hey, listen.
It'll--it'll give me
a chance to spend more time
with my kids.
I'm quitting.
I'm quitting right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
You have the best job
in New York.
Don't quit over this.
Don't buy all the hot dogs. Okay?
I don't want to do this
without you.
Hey, I thought we cut
the Cat Lady sketch.
We're two minutes short!
So, let me introduce myself.
My name is Lurleen Katz.
And these are my cats.
She's using a real cat?
I cast that cat myself.
And sir, while they are my--
Ow! Aaugh!
No, no, no, no, no.
He's okay.
I need you to talk
for two minutes.
About what?
Anything.
All right.
These cats are more
than just pets, sir.
Why, just this morning--
Excuse me!
Where is the manager?
I'm from the government,
and I'm here to inspect your chicken nuggets.
Uh-oh.
Look at Shorty.
This honky grandma
be trippin'.
What's up, America?
I'm coming
into your house live.
Lemme hear you say
"We love you, Tracy."
We love you, Tracy!
I am the third heat!
He's brilliant.
Are you drunk?
Yes.
Why did you fire Pete?
Why did you disappear
all night?
Is this some kind
of a power play?
Yeah, yeah.
It's not so fun being "hands on"
with these bloodsuckers, is it?
Could we talk about this
on Monday?
No. I want Pete back.
I want it in writing
that Jenna's job is safe,
and I want a cappuccino machine
for the writers' room.
Fine.
I thought you were
going to quit.
Yeah, well, you don't know
everything about me.
You weigh 127 pounds.
Yeah.
Thank you,
good night.
You will be hearing
from Peanut's lawyer.
Good night,
sleep tight.
I can't wait to do this
with you every week.
www.tvsubtitles.net