Subs by Traff and Raceman
www.forom.com
Well, I don't know why
they need you in the studio.
Surprise!
Oh, my God!
Is this for me?
I can't believe you made all
this fuss over my birthday.
It's so incredibly thoughtful.
Let me give something
back to you guys.
* I believe the children are our future *
* Teach them well and
let them lead the way *
Hey, guess what, everyone?
I'm engaged.
Engaged?
Hey, this isn't gonna change the way
you dress or eat lollipops, is it?
No.
Oh, then congratulations.
This is for you, Cerie.
* I believe the children are our future *
* Teach them well and
let them lead the way *
* Show them...
* All the beauty they possess... *
Everyone, guess what?
There's an antique car
show out in the plaza!
How long is Jack gonna be?
He's still on the phone.
Area code 407?
Oh, no.
When did this happen?
407? Is that bad?
It's fine.
It's gonna be just fine.
Jonathan, these cheap phones
keep on shattering!
You can go in now.
No.
Who let 407 through?
Jonathan, we have drills for this!
Liz distracted me.
No, I didn't.
What's going on?
Business got you down?
Business doesn't get me down.
Business gets me off.
Now, what is your urgent
problem this time?
Well, the writers and I wanted to get TGS jackets,
but the guy in accounting says
that we can't have the jackets.
But Dateline has jackets.
Jackets?
Is this what you're talking about now?
Lemon, do you realize that your little show accounts for
3% of our revenue but takes up 90% of my time?
Hello?!
Now, would you do me a kindness, please?
And handle your problems yourself
and stop bothering me.
Is that too much to ask?
Absolutely!
Forget it.
I won't bother you
about anything anymore.
Wow, he's a little bit of
a stress eater, huh?
He puts up with so much.
All right.
Liz, you shoulda seen this guy
at the club last night.
Everybody at this party is a Jedi.
We must get our freak on
while our fruit is a-plentiful.
Oh, naw!
Oh, sounds like another great party
I wasn't invited to.
Tracy, thank you for
the funnest night of my life!
Love you, man.
I love you too, J Bird!
Yo, I don't like that dude.
It's disrespectful
when he imitates me.
I want him fired.
Oh, come on, it's a goof.
How would you like it if
I did an impression of you, Liz Lemon?
Hi, I'm Liz Lemon!
I like to wear man shirts.
Watch me skateboard.
I don't skateboard.
Hurts, doesn't it?
I'm not firing Josh.
You always take his side.
Tracy, stop tasering him.
See?
I need to be respected, Liz Lemon.
What do you know about respect?
Please, Tracy, just let it go.
Well, if you won't do anything about it,
then I'll just go over your head to Donaghy.
No, no no, do not do that.
Don't bother him.
I'll talk to Josh.
Hey, Cerie, what are you doing?
Oh, I let them do my make-up sometimes.
They say it's fun for them.
She's like a Barbie.
Oh, sorry, my babysitter got jury duty.
I think I'm going to kill myself.
So, Cerie, how long have you known this guy
that you're marrying?
It'll be two months in...
three weeks.
You'd love him, Liz.
He's so funny.
He does this thing
where he screams at limo drivers.
Yeah, it just kind of seems like
you're rushing into it a little bit.
I guess.
But we both wanna have babies
while it's still cool.
I already have
all the names picked out.
If it's a girl, Bookcase.
Or Sandstorm. Or maybe Hat.
But that's more of a boy's name.
Yeah, I was gonna say.
It's just, you're so young, Cerie.
There's no big hurry to have babies.
I mean, there are other things in life.
Like having a career. And working.
And...having a job.
And working.
You can have a career anytime.
But you only have a really short period
where you can be a young, hot mom.
If you wait too long,
you could be like...
50 at your kid's graduation.
50's not that old, Cerie.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you 50 now?
Paul Newman or Robert Redford?
I've told you 1,000 times, Newman.
Because  I enjoy his
salad dressings and lemonade.
Me too.
Okay, uh, Brad Pitt...
or George Clooney?
Do you think
I'd be a good mother?
What?
Something is kicking in.
And the last few months
I've just started wondering
if I'm ever gonna have a baby.
I mean, I'm so many steps away
from being able to do it.
And I panic that maybe
I waited too long.
What if my junk goes bad?
What if Cerie is right?
Wow, red wine is not your drink.
I'm sorry.
I'm in my right mind.
I just--it comes in waves, you know?
And I love my job
and I love my friends.
And if I am meant to crank out a kid,
then I have plenty of time.
Uh, not really.
Jenna!
No, Liz, I'm just saying.
If this is something you really want,
let's go for it.
I'll help you.
Please, let me help you for once.
We'll get you a guy.
Like that hot dancer
Madonna used to have Lourdes.
No no no.
That is not how I roll.
Forget I said anything.
Because you agreed to this.
I did not make you sign anything.
I will not be intimidated by you!
Good morning, Mr. Donaghy!
Go to hell.
No, thank you.
Kenneth, I'm sorry.
How do you do it, Kenneth?
How do you sit here every day
taking crap from people and you keep smiling?
My mother always told me
that even when things seemed bad...
there's someone else
who's having a worse day.
Like being stung by a bee
or getting a splinter.
Or being chained to a wall
in someone's sex dungeon.
Isn't that a kick in
the soft stuff, Kenneth?
I  mean, you gain strength from your mother
while mine is sucking the life out of me.
She calls me constantly. That was her.
That was her.
Complaining about where she's living.
Threatening to move in with me.
Oh, how wonderful.
No no no, that's not wonderful.
I run companies. Plural.
But to that woman...
I'm always gonna be the punk kid who cried
when Pop was run over by a mail truck.
Oh my, a mailman killed your dad?
No, Pop was my dog.
My dad left when I was two...
so I grew up calling my Collie Pop.
My mother is my best friend.
My mother tried to send me to Vietnam
to make a man out of me.
I was 12.
Well, my mother has her dark times too.
But that's when I tell her,
"Mama, you carried me for nine months.
Let me carry you now."
You are a remarkable human being, Kenneth.
I bought my mother a lovely
retirement home. In Florida.
With a tea garden and fake rocks made of foam
because she falls down a lot.
Got everything
she needs except a phone.
I told those people, I made it clear,
do not give her a phone.
It's her.
It's always her.
Hello?
This is Dr. Leo Spaceman.
Oh, hi, I'm sorry.
I got this number under fertility
in the Writer's Guild Health Manual.
I'm also listed under meth addiction
and child psychiatry.
So what can I help you with?
I should start by saying that
I can't personally help you conceive.
Something happened to me
while scuba diving.
Hey, so Jenna tells us
you're looking for a babydaddy.
She what?
Yeah. So?
So...
Are you kidding me?
Now, okay, before you say no...
I just wanna say...
our child would have a leg up
getting into Harvard.
Oh, really?
Did you go to Harvard?
'Cause you haven't mentioned it
in like three hours.
Our kid would have strong, flat feet.
And if you choose me,
I agree not to take my shirt off.
But I do like to get yelled
at during sex.
You're disgusting.
Yeah, that's a good start.
Ugh.
Get out of here.
Jenna had no business
telling you guys that.
Oh, hey, blue pages.
What? What's wrong?
Jenna told the writers that I'm looking for
a guy to get me pregnant.
Can you believe her?
I know.
It's so uncool.
I mean, why would she go to them?
Who do you know better than me?
Oh, come on.
Didn't you have a vasectomy?
No, I just told my wife I did.
And she doesn't get pregnant how?
I fake it.
Is Jenna out here?
Is she rehearsing?
She's onstage.
Excuse me, Ms. Lemon?
Uh...
I'm not usually this formal, nor this bold,
but I figure time is on neither one of our sides.
Uh, could you excuse us for a second?
I'd kind of like him to stay.
Very well.
Ms. Lemon... Liz...
I'd like to carry your child
if I might.
I have a small ferret farm
about 60 miles north of the city.
It's not much,
but it is self-sufficient.
I can get cable if you want,
'cause I know how much you like the TV.
Sometimes  I watch you watching it.
Think about it.
Jenna.
Stop telling everyone
I need someone to get me pregnant.
I'm not telling everyone.
All right, guys, check this out.
Oprah and Steadman are the same person.
You know what?
I don't have time for this conversation.
I don't have time for anything.
That's why he/she won't run for president.
Hey, you gotta stop doing that impression.
Tracy hates it.
What? But it's funny.
These guys like it.
The Mars probe didn't brake.
It was attacked by a Martian cougar.
This is how you take care
of things, Liz Lemon?
I'm going to Jack Donaghy.
No, no Tracy, please don't do that.
Too late. This is untoward.
This is not toward!
You better fix this, nerd.
Otherwise, Jack Donaghy is gonna kill me
and then he's gonna kill you.
And then he's gonna fold us up
in a pizza and eat us.
What?
Hey Liz!
I heard you're looking for a hook-up.
Oh, you know what?
Everybody, stop working right now!
I don't wanna have sex with any of you.
I have plenty of time to have a baby.
And I am not looking for sperm donors.
Okay.
But do you still want a sound hook-up
so you can listen to rehearsal?
Yeah, thanks.
How are you, Bobby? Good?
Great.
Yo!
Tracy. It's Jack Donaghy.
I hear we have a problem
with Josh Gerard.
Damn right!
Keeps impersonating me.
Making me into a caricature.
Well, I would take care of this if I could.
But it's tricky.
You see, Josh's father's an assassin
with the Russian mafia.
They call him El Matador.
Whoa. Those dudes are crazy.
Forget it, I don't need any of that noise.
It  happys me to hear you say that.
For being so understanding.
I'm sending you our new super
top secret invisible motorcycle.
For reals?
[laughing] For realses.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need to see a doctor.
I keep pooping during sex.
Lemon, we have a problem.
I have this whole Tracy/Josh
thing under control.
What are you talking about?
Nothing. What are you talking about?
You. You yelling at the crew.
You trolling for seed.
Oh, it's a big misunderstanding.
Jenna thinks
that I want to have a baby.
I should have known this was going to be a problem
when I decided to mentor a woman.
No, in fact, what I said was
that my body is trying to make me think
I wanna have a baby.
But my body is not the boss of me.
My brain is.
All right, if you insist upon
going all Murphy Brown on me,
let me give you a tip.
Don't smother your child with affection
to compensate for not having a man in your life.
Don't say you're the only man I'll ever love.
Even babies know that's creepy.
Of course.
Don't put little notes in their lunch bag
that say, "Mommy's watching you."
People find those things.
I bet you behaved yourself, though.
If your child is a terrific hockey player
and a gifted flautist, don't make them
play the National Anthem on the flute in front of their teammates.
Your mother did that?
Now she wants to move in with me.
I can't have that, Lemon.
Then be an adult and call her
and say you love her very much.
But that living together is
not going to work for you.
Oh, no. You don't know my mother.
This is a woman that actually had a heart attack
to prevent me from going on my honeymoon.
Maybe her heart broke because she spent 20 years
raising you and you're a total ingrate.
That's exactly what she said.
Is this what you want, Lemon,
to breathe life into another human being
just to spend the rest of your days
slowly sucking it out of them?
No, that's why my brain is the boss.
Speak of the devil.
Take a breath.
Be nice.
Hello, Mother.
So nice to hear your voice.
No, I am not on anything.
I know that things have been difficult for you lately
and I was thinking you carried me for nine months.
Let me carry you now.
Well, right back at you, Colleen!
Yeah, that's right!
You cut Pop's balls off!
And left him in the street to die!
Liz, check out my wedding dress.
Absolutely not, young lady.
Kenneth, get Donaghy on the phone.
Jonathan, I have
Tracy Jordan for Mr. Donaghy.
No. No no no no.
Tracy, please.
Do not bother Jack.
He is in a weird place right now.
Bebe Jackson's condo?
No.
A children's clothing store in Dubai?
Stop guessing!
What I'm saying is,
leave Jack alone.
Too late, Liz Lemon.
He called me five minutes ago.
Five minutes ago
I was with him.
How did he sound?
What did he say?
Nothing unusual.
Russian mobs, invisible motorcycles...
Sex pooping.
Are you insane?
What are you gonna do when Tracy asks Jack
for his invisible motorcycle?
Uh... Yeah, dummy.
Here's what you're gonna do.
It's not your mother.
Hello?
Donaghy!
What's up, Tray?
If in the future...
In the future...
- If I mention anything crazy...
- Like an invisible motorcycle...
- It means I'm off my meds...
- and should be ignored.
- should be ignored.
Also, I think Josh Gerard
is a young Alex Guinness.
Go back on your meds, Tracy.
- Hang up.
- What?
- Idiot.
Tracy, I've gotta go.
Idiot.
I think that went well.
Now you gotta call Tracy as Jack.
Or...
I could call him...
as Christopher Walken.
Do you not understand
what we're doing?
Jenna, did you tell Life and Style
that your favorite book is the Koran?
I just wanted to sound smart.
Oh, hi, baby!
Would you take her for a second?
I'm trying to finish her eyes.
Oh, I'm actually really busy.
I heard you were baby crazy.
No.
Yes, she is.
Please.
Oh, for the love of--nuts.
Okay.
Hi!
How about that, huh?
Yeah, she likes you.
Go ahead, walk her around.
Oh, okay.
Look how pretty I look.
Who's the cutest baby in the world?
How did I get home?
Why didn't you say something?
Jack Donaghy.
Now, I know you asked me
not to say anything.
But I think I know somebody that can help you
with your sex poop problem.
Hi.
Please don't hurt me.
I can't help it.
It just pours out of me.
I'm Jack Donaghy.
I'm important.
I just bought the moon.
Oh, my God.
I'm doing it again.
What?
Mother, I love you too.
But living together
is not gonna work out for me.
Yes, I went this morning.
I  don't know, regular consistency?
I can't do this.
Every day for the rest of
your or her life.
And she will outlive you.
She's like Castro.
And when you're done with that,
call my wife and tell her I'm sorry about
what happened with me and Keith and them.
Wait, who?
Oh, God!
It's true that you had the baby.
I don't know what happened.
One minute I was holding the baby
in make-up and then suddenly...
It was like highway hypnosis.
You know, when you pull into your driveway
but you don't remember driving home?
Oh, right right.
And you have someone
else's baby in your car.
I feel so terrible.
Give me the baby.
I'll try to smooth things over.
What's her name?
Well, Anna calls her Isobel,
but I call her Nancy.
I think it might be a good idea
if I give Anna the rest of the week off.
Seriously? We're really busy.
No, of course. Of course.
Stealing a baby? Really?
Hey, I found Isobel!
I'm a hero.
Hi, baby.
Hi, muffin.
Oh, I'm so glad you're back.
You're loving this, aren't you?
Oh, yes.
I'm a big fan of kidnapping.
Especially by my middle management.
So the thing you were saying about listening to your mind
and not your body, how's that going for you?
My body's telling me several things.
First of all, I need to start working out.
That kid was killing my arms.
Number two, I could be very happy
with a baby that looks nothing like me
and didn't bake in my oven.
Three, I gotta let myself
have a personal life.
What I've been telling you for five months.
Well, you're right again.
Right it down in your
little "I'm Awesome" book.
Where are you going?
You have a rehearsal about to start.
I stole a baby, Jack.
I'm taking a half day.
Fair enough.
I have to do some thinking.
Maybe it's impossible to have it all.
Career, the family...
But if anybody can figure out
how to do it, it's me.
That's going up.
Oh, nerds!
I was talking about you at work today, Mother.
I think my boss, Mr. Jack Donaghy,
wishes you were his mother.
Isn't that something, mother?
Yes, Kenneth, that's sweet.
Do you have me on speaker phone again?
Yes, Ma'am!
It's just like Charlie's Angels!
Oh, by the way, did you get your old
Halloween decorations I sent you?
Oh, yes, thank you!
I'm looking at the kooky skeleton right now.
I love it!
You're the best mother in the whole world!
Okay, calm down, dear.
Yes, Mother.
www.tvsubtitles.net