Now, Robot, kick 'em
in the knees.
Bears have weak knees.
And you should vibrate, 'cause
the robot's full of radiation.
Yeah, that's it.
Frank.
How many bears did I say
you could have?
One.
And how many do you see here?
Um, four?
Save a little money
for the rest of us, Frank.
You can't spend a bunch
of money on bear suits
that are only gonna be seen
for, like, 25 seconds.
Liz, nobody's gonna believe
that a killer robot
can get his ass kicked
by one bear.
It doesn't make any sense.
You're trying to bring logic
to the robot-bear sketch?
You can't have four bears.
Well, how many can I keep?
One!
Sorry, guys.
Uh, who did my Sudoku puzzle?
I have been looking forward
to this puzzle all morning.
Hey, Liz, could you
come up to my office
when you have a free moment?
I never have a free moment,
Jack.
Never, ever.
Really punch him.
Like karate.
Are you familiar with
the Japanese art of Reiki?
No.
It is the laying-on of hands
in order to improve one's life.
Hm, how does your life improve?
Do the hands
have money in them?
Human contact
is important, Lemon.
I can tell
from your stress level
that you have not been touched
in any way in quite some time.
Not caress??
Not massaged.
Not even groped
on the subway.
Where are you headed
with this?
Your mood affects
the quality of your work,
which, in turn,
affects me.
I would like to become
a resource to you
for improving
your personal life.
Do you agree that you need
someone in your life, Lemon?
No, I have bigger things
to worry about than my personal life.
I would think that a single
woman's biggest worry
would be choking to death
alone in her apartment.
I have a friend in town
I'd like to set you up with.
No, thank you.
Thomas is very bright,
has a wonderful sense of humor.
I think it's a good match.
Are you free on Thursday?
No, Thursday is poker night.
And by the way,
it is completely inappropriate
for you to be questioning me
about my private life,
and then trying to set me up
with someone
when you don't even know
anything about me.
Poker night?
Who plays?
Really?
That's all you got out of that?
I enjoy poker,
and I'd be interested
in seeing my new employees
under that kind of pressure.
You're not gonna come to our
crappy poker game, are you?
No, I'm not.
Good.
I bluffed.
Yes, I am coming.
Three can't go here.
It can go here.
Fine, I'll meet your friend.
So who is this
Thomas guy?
Oh, I don't know.
He's one of Jack's friends.
Oh, my God, isn't Jack
friends with Tom DeLay?
Am I going on a date
with Tom DeLay?
Ugh, why did I say
I would do this?
I haven't been on a date
since Dennis and I broke up,
and that was almost
a year ago.
It's gonna be a complete disaster.
It's just one date.
But if it is Tom DeLay
and you do go home with him,
be prepared for it
to get weird.
Josh, you and me.
Thursday night.
I know this guy that runs
an underground bird fight.
Oh, yeah.
I can't do that.
Thursday's poker night here.
Guys, we just need to try
the green screen stuff one more time.
Poker night?
I love poker.
I used to play all kinds
of poker with my aunt.
Crazy Seven.
Albuquerque Freakout.
One Card Stud.
Yeah, I don't think
those are real games.
Whatever.
Get ready to get took.
No, Mom, I can't make it Friday.
I gotta work.
Hey, Frank?
Hold on.
Yeah.
What do guys like?
Uh, porn.
No, I mean, if you were gonna
go on a date with a woman,
how would you want her
to act?
Like she was in a porn.
Hey, Lemon.
You're on for 8:00
for dinner at Café des Artistes.
Really?
Wow. What?
What are you
gonna wear?
This, probably.
I don't have time to go home.
No,  that won't do.
I want you to go out
on your lunch hour,
and find something.
At a women's clothing store.
Remind me what's better.
A pair of black Aces
or a pair of red Aces?
You guys,
I'm leaving.
All right.
Check out the valley.
Look at that.
Hey, look at you!
You look like
a fancy prostitute.
Okay, I got my chair.
I got my beer.
I got my lucky donut.
Oh, is there room
for one more?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
That's fantastic.
Could we just, uh--
Yes, yes, yes.
Donaghy, what up?
What up, Tray?
This round, Texas Doozy.
Face cards are wild.
Threes are jinx.
Fives are twos.
Tray, do you mind if I deal
this hand?
Be my guest.
Show me love.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
minimum bet in this game is $25.
Oh, Jack, we usually just play
for quarters.
Well, then you best go home and
put on your daddy's shoes, boy.
'Cause this is a man's game.
I call.
And I'll see that with...
This thing.
I call.
Pair of Jacks.
Ace high.
Three cowboys.
Oh, my God.
My wedding ring.
Now, you should all learn
from Pete's mistake.
My  wife's gonna kill me!
You see, in poker
as in business,
the key to success
is to determine
your opponent's strength and,
more importantly, his weaknesses.
Everyone has a tell--
a weakness of character
that manifests itself
physically.
Oh.
Like when Lutz here has
a good hand, he stops eating.
When Frank is bluffing, he asks
a series of insane questions to hide his nervousness.
Oh, really?
Is that what you think?
Is that what I do?
Am I doing that right now?
Yeah, I'm out.
Okay, Rainman,
tell me what I got.
Well, you have two of your
cards backwards actually.
I'm out.
Hi.
Pinot grigio, please.
This is beyond the pale.
Donaghy took me for $200.
Yeah, well I bet
my rent money.
And if I don't pay by the tenth,
my mom's gonna throw me out.
I'm all in.
Anybody else?
Oh, I'll play with you,
Mr. Donaghy.
Kenneth, how long you been
sitting there?
I'm taking Pete's place, 'cause
he's busy in the bathroom,
laying in his own sick.
Oh, my God.
He can't read Kenneth.
He's a blank slate.
Okay, what do you got?
I think I have what they refer
to as a royal flush.
Looks like
I'm the big winner.
Thank you.
Liz, hi.
I'm Gretchen Thomas.
Jack's friend.
Hey.
Great to meet you.
Hi.
Why would Jack just assume
that we're lesbians?
I am a lesbian.
Mm, that's awesome.
Is this the first time somebody's made that
assumption about you?
Lemon, don't let these girls
give you a hard time about who you are.
You know, you need to brush
your teeth more, young man.
Oh, my.
What an adorable little lesbian.
What?
I don't know.
Who remembers
that kind of thing?
Well, look, obviously
this is a miscommunication.
I mean, I'm certainly not
interested in chasing a straight girl.
Of course, yeah.
I completely understand
if you just want to go home.
No, it's fine.
I'll stay.
Jack is ridiculous.
Oh, I worked with Jack in Plastics.
He tends to approach
everything the same way.
Locate the problem.
Isolate the problem.
Set the problem up
with a lesbian.
That's a pretty good joke
for somebody from Plastics.
Well, I wasn't always in Plastics.
I used to work in Water
and Process Technologies.
Working mainly in primary metals.
Oh, so you have
a comedy background.
How was your evening with Thomas?
You mean, Gretchen Thomas?
The brilliant plastics engineer/lesbian?
What made you think I was gay?
Your shoes.
Well, I'm straight.
Those shoes are definitely bi-curious.
Regardless, I am straight.
100% completely straight.
Well, I'm sorry
if I offended you.
No, I'm not offended--
Good.
What do you know
about Kenneth the page?
I don't know.
He's a sweet kid.
Yes.
And  a surprisingly good
poker player.
Did you know that
his middle name is Ellen?
No, that's weird.
And that his Myers-Briggs-psychological testing shows
shows a rare combination
of extroverted, intuitive
and aggressive?
Really?
The same as mine.
He could be trouble
down the line.
Kenneth.
Kenneth Ellen.
All right then.
You're not a lesbian.
Duly noted.
I'll correct that on your file.
It's too bad, though.
Thomas thought
you were great.
- She did?
- Yes.
She said she thought you looked
like Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Really?
She said that?
Yes, I made her repeat it.
I was sure she meant Jason Lee.
Miss Lemon.
Yeah.
This is Pete's wedding ring.
I won it last night, but I don't
think I should keep it.
Could you give it back
to him for me?
Yeah, okay.
Did you win this, too?
I did.
I love how the light
catches it like diamonds.
Kenneth, it is diamonds.
Ah.
Hi, Mr. Donaghy.
Can I help you
with something?
You are a puzzle...
Kenneth Ellen.
And I'm going to solve you.
Yes, I am.
I can't believe you bet
your wedding ring.
I know.
The weird thing is
I had money left.
Hey, um, what famous person
would you say I look like?
Uh, present day
Linda Ronstadt.
No, Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Tootsie.
Never mind.
So how was your date?
It wasn't a good match.
What happened?
- Did he notice your facial tic?
- No.
Did you wear sandals?
- Did he see your toes?
- No.
You  blew it, didn't you?
Good job, Liz.
Way to go.
Another one bites the dust.
Ah, look at
your little face.
It was a lady.
Are you serious?
Where is my Emmy?
Hello?
Hi, Gretchen.
It's Liz Lemon.
Oh, hi.
Look, thiss gonna sound
really weird, but, um,
do you every worry about
choking to death
alone in your apartment?
Oh, it's so weird
you would say that.
I think about it
all the time.
I mean, you'd die,
and they wouldn't find you
until your neighbor's dog
smelled you from the hallway.
Ugh, yes, and they'd show
a picture of you on New York One.
And it's not just choking.
Ever since I turned 30,
every time I get in or out
of the bathtub,
I think in my head, "Careful, careful."
Yes!
Agh.
Everything's the worst.
Do you want to get some dinner?
Sure.
See you in 20 at Neptune.
Yeah, okay.
Perfect, yeah.
Oh!
Ow, ow, ow!
I did not die.
Man, this is amazing.
Oh, hey, Jack.
Welcome.
Welcome, everybody.
Damn, Jack, you went all out.
That's a giant shrimp.
Made out of shrimp and diving
into a bowl of shrimp.
Please, enjoy it, Tracy.
Hey, Pete, good to see you.
Jack.
Is Kenneth here?
I--I will check.
I've been playing
for two hours.
I'm tired of losing.
I'm gonna let my boy, Dotcom,
play a hand for me.
So, hey, Dotcom, are we going
to those three clubs tonight?
You know the doctor said
I have four hearts in my body?
All right.
Great.
Of course he did.
Come on. Damn it.
Hey, everybody,
this is Gretchen.
Oh, hey.
Oh, Thomas.
Jack.
How's everybody up there
in Pittsfield?
Oh, we miss you.
I love this woman.
Let's play some poker.
I call.
What have you got, Kenneth?
All clovers.
I win.
Very clever boy,
Kenneth.
But the curtain has been drawn back now,
and I know the real you.
I think he's confusing me
with someone else.
Liz, are you sure
you're not gay?
'Cause that chick is hot.
We're just friends,
like Oprah and Gayle.
Why is that so hard
for everybody to believe?
She's great.
You should marry that girl.
One problem.
I'm not gay.
Oh, Lemon, in the ten years
that I've known you,
you've had some really
terrible boyfriends.
I have.
There was the guy who was obsessed
with Charlie Chaplin.
Neil.
There was the guy
who played Halo under the name Slutbanger.
Dennis.
There was a tall,
gangly, red-haired guy
who played guitar
all the time.
Conan.
You're more relaxed with Gretchen
than you were with any of those guys.
So what are you
saying, Pete?
I should just
be a lesbian?
Well, I'm not saying it'll be easy.
You know, get drunk first.
Why do guys think women can
just flip a switch like that?
What if I said to you,
"Go be with Frank now"?
Ah, I would be honored.
Frank is a very tender,
beautiful man.
He's awesome.
You can't read his thoughts,
'cause he doesn't have any.
I raise you 200.
And I see your 200
and raise you 300.
Will you, little Kenneth Ellen Parcell
from Stone Mountain, Georgia?
Growing up in your momma's tract house,
dreaming of working on a TV show?
Dreaming of making it
all the way to the NBC.
You're scaring me,
Mr. Donaghy.
You've come a long way,
haven't you, Kenneth Ellen?
With your cheap loafers
and your page jacket,
but you'll always be
a pig farmer's son, boy.
'Cause I smell fried bologna
all over you.
I'm all in.
I'm out of chips,
Mr. Donaghy.
Hey, I got a fun idea.
You put your page jacket
on the table,
and if you win,
you can get it back.
If you lose,
you go on home.
You go on home,
little Kenneth Ellen.
All the way
to Stone Mountain.
He's bluffing.
Go for it.
Come on, trust yourself.
Trust yourself.
Don't do it.
No!
You can do it.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
Use your instincts.
You've got good instincts.
Do it, Kenneth.
I've got a pair
of twos.
Well, let's just
see-weeby here.
I've got a two, a four,
a nine, a six, and a King.
That means I win.
Kenneth.
Why did you bet
that terrible hand?
Why?
Because...I believe
that life is for the living.
I believe in taking risks
and biting off more than you can chew.
And also,
people were yelling,
and I got confused
about the rules.
Kenneth.
I wasn't really
going to fire you.
I  just wanted to remind you
that I could.
I want you back here
at 6:00 in the morning sharp
so you can sweep up
these shrimp tails.
Yes, sir, Mr. Donaghy.
Uh, I'm gonna have my eye
on you, Kenneth.
You will not be
disappointed, sir.
Well, it was nice of you
to let him keep his job.
The Italians
have a saying, Lemon.
"Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer."
And although they've
never won a war,
or mass-produced a decent car,
in this area, they are correct.
In five years, we'll all
either be working for him...
or be dead by his hand.
Hey, after Ikea tomorrow,
you wanna go see Margaret Cho at the Beacon?
Oh, boy.
Um, Oprah?
Yes, Gayle.
I think we need
to take a break.
Is this because I waused to
submit us for The Amazing Race?
Because I was 80% joking
about that.
No, it's--
You know, I said I'm not
into chasing straight girls.
And I kinda think that's
what's starting to happen here.
So... unless you're ready to make
a big life change,
I need to move on,
find my Steadman.
I thought I was Oprah
in this metaphor.
Also, you're gay,
so that's a little confusing.
You should say, like,
"My lady Steadman."
Okay.
I'm going out
on a limb here.
Okay, sorry.
Um, it's just--
If I try to imagine
us being together,
I think, "Yeah, okay,
this could be fun, you know?
"Picking out furniture and making flower beds
out of old railroad ties."
But the thing is,
if I'm gonna be with someone,
it has to be a guy.
You sound pretty sure about that.
What can I say?
I love a bald spot
and a hairy back.
You're alone there.
I should go.
I'll see you around.
Okay, wait.
Um, what if we made a pact?
What if we say
that in, like, 25 years,
if neither of us has someone,
we'll move in together
and be roommates.
And even though
I am not into the sex stuff,
if it helps you... I would let you...
do stuff to me.
I can't be around
you anymore.
Bye, Liz.
That's funny.
That's what the guys always say.
Who's gonna go with me
to cooking class next weekend?
Well, if by "cooking class"
you mean your bed,
and by "next weekend"
you mean tonight--
Oh, shut up.
I can see your wedding ring.
Idiot.
Subs by Raceman and Traff
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net