Subs by Raceman and Traff
www.forom.com
The flowers are lovely.
Thank you.
No, you hang up first.
Okay, on the count of three.
One, two, three...
No, I didn't hang up either.
Donaghy, I need your help.
I miss you too.
I said I miss you too.
You're breaking up.
Maureen?
She cut out.
I need $60,000,
or I'm gonna lose my house.
Which house?
I need $100,000,
or I'm gonna lose both my houses!
Tracy, I don't understand.
You've starred in 14 films.
You don't have any money saved?
Nah, I lost all of it.
Really?
Who's your money manager?
Grizz.
Worldcom, man.
Worldcom.
Look, Tracy,
I can't just give you money.
But what I can do is show you
how you can earn all the money you need.
You must know Arsenio.
Hall or Billingham?
You know someone
named Arsenio Billingham?
Put his name
and face on a product.
Because of Arsenio's "woof-woof" catchphrase,
we settled on dog food.
The product was a runaway success.
The company and Arsenio made millions.
I like that.
Put my name on something.
But what would I sell?
The product is irrelevant.
The people aren't buying that.
They're buying you.
Now, you come back with an idea
of a product you'd be willing to sell,
anything at all, and you'll have
all the money you can dream of.
I'm on it.
I forgot about that Worldcom mess.
Why you gotta be so obsessed
with telecommunications?
Get me Maureen Dowd
back on the phone, please.
Hey, I've got to miss
an hour of rehearsal today
because I just found out from my publicist
I've been booked on The View.
Oh, Jenna, that's great.
For the first time in your life,
you'll be in a room full of women
and you'll be the least crazy one.
I know.
(Liz) Oh, you know
what clip you should show?
"MTV: Darfur."
You and Tracy
were really funny in that.
Oh, this isn't for TGS.
It's for my movie.
The Rurr-Jurr has
a limited release next week.
Oh, congratulations!
I didn't know they had
a release date for The Rurr--
For that movie.
Oh, sorry.
Gotta take this.
Hello?
You still don't know
what the title is?
No! No one does.
It's gone on way too long
to ask her about it.
This title isn't hard
to understand, right?
No, it's awesome!
I love that we can work
while we're on cocaine!
Could it be Roar Her,
Gem Her?
No, that doesn't make any sense.
It's got to be Oral Germ Whore.
Okay, bye.
Sorry, that was my publicist.
You know, I have to admit,
I kind of like that Tracy Jordan is no longer
the only movie star on TGS.
Maybe I'll finally start getting
some respect around here.
What's up, flabby butt?
You look weird today.
Hey, Pete, you wanna see a comic book
with pregnant zombie nuns?
Yes, I do.
Cool.
And I have a screener
of the movie for you.
I want you to watch it.
Ah, The Rural Juror!
That is something.
I can't wait to watch it.
Oh, you won't be disappointed.
The source material was amazing.
It's hard to go wrong
with a Kevin Grisham novel.
- You mean John Grisham.
- Oh, no.
Kevin, John's brother.
Did you know that before Kevin was a novelist,
he worked at a recycling center?
Wow.
Yeah, and he just finished
writing a sequel.
It's called Urban Fervor.
Boy, these titles--
They really make you think.
Oh, wow!
Doesn't it seem like just yesterday
we were doing the show back in Chicago,
dreaming about being in the movies?
We've come a long way
from that apartment we shared
in Little Armenia.
Oh, it was so weird there.
You remember that neighborhood festival
where they killed a goat in the street?
Yes!
But we did have really
good luck that year.
Yeah.
I need to come up with a big idea
for a product to put my name on.
Something no one has thought of.
Something crazy.
I know a gentleman
who had a lot of crazy ideas.
He was a carpenter.
He wanted everyone to love one another.
Oh, you mean Jesus?
No-- Miguel from set design.
He's over there.
Eurek-o!
Hey.
What are you doing back here?
They're rehearsing your Paris Hilton sketch.
I'm trying to avoid Jenna.
She gave me a screener of her movie.
And?
Oh, Pete, it's awful!
I couldn't believe how bad it was.
Although, I guess it's no surprise that
Tony Hawk can't play blind.
So you must know the title!
Yes, yes-- The Rural Juror.
- The Rrr--
- Rural.
- The Ruh--
Eh.
(Pete) So, what are you gonna
do about Jenna?
(Liz) Same thing I've always done
when she's done something terrible.
Think of one thing nice to say
and then hug her.
So, what did you think?
Oh, my God!
You looked so beautiful.
The lighting was really neat.
Ethan and I both thought
the programs were really easy to read.
So, what nice thing are you going to say
about The Roaring Junior?
Uh, I don't know.
It's a mess.
No, you've got to tell them
that when Paris Hilton
tries to make out with the bear,
the bear has to act like he's into it.
All right.
Mr. Donaghy, stop what you're doing
because I'm about to blow your mind!
Hit it!
Tired of your sandwich making you angry?
Then behold the Tracy Jordan Meat Machine!
Stick any three meats--
Whatever you want!
Bologna, salami, boar--
Whatever!
Into this sexy lady
and she will melt them all together
into one delicious food ball.
Never again will you have to suffer
through the bread part of your sandwich.
I give you the Tracy Jordan Meat Machine!
(all) Meat is the new bread! Uh-huh!
What do you think?
Well, it's certainly not the worst
celebrity product idea I've ever heard.
Hi, I'm Whoopi Goldberg.
And you're Working Out
With Whoopi.
With Tracy Jordan behind this,
it just might work.
We'll roll it out in time for Christmas.
Manufacture it for four bucks,
slap your name on it, and sell it for 50.
So GE will produce
the Tracy Jordan Meat Machine?
Oh, no. No.
GE could never make something so, um...
Unique.
We'll have to pass this off
to one of our subsidiaries.
You see, GE owns KitchenAll of Colorado,
which, in turn, owns JMI of Stanford,
which is a majority shareholder
in Pokerfastlane.com,
which recently acquired
the Sheinhardt Wig Company,
which owns NBC outright.
NBC owns Winnipeg Iron Works
which owns the Ahp Chanagi Party Meats corporation
of Pyongyang, North Korea.
And they will make the Meat Machine.
Jack Donaghy,
you are the best.
(Tracy) You know what?
I'm gonna make you a mix tape.
You like Phil Collins?
I've got two ears and a heart, don't I?
All right, Jenna's on next.
Everyone shut up so we can hear the title
of this stupid movie.
And coming up,
I'll be talking to The Girlie Show star
Jenna Maroney about her upcoming project,
The Rrr-Jrr.
That is not helpful.
Hey, do you know the name
of Jenna's movie yet?
Oh, yeah, she gave me a screener.
- Okay!
- No, no, no--
I'm not telling you
anything about it.
I'm not giving you more ammunition
to make fun of her with.
So it's bad.
How bad?
Please!
Just give us one detail.
Okay, fine.
Jenna plays a southern lawyer
named Constance Justice.
You gotta let us see this.
- No!
- Come on, Liz!
No!
Oh, man.
Constance Justice.
Justice has been served.
Good stuff.
Tracy to the stage please for
Pull Your Own Wisdom Teeth.
(Jenna) Oh, excuse me.
Hey, there you are.
So, what did you think of the movie?
Oh, my God, Jenna!
The soundtrack was so moody.
What else did you like about it?
What? Oh, um...
You were good!
Your face was very expressive.
And another cool part was...the trees.
I gotta get back to work.
You didn't like the movie.
What?
Yes, I just said I like the movie.
No, you didn't.
You did that condescending
compliment thing you always do.
What? When have
I ever done that?
So, what did you think?
Oh, my God...
You looked beautiful.
The lighting was really neat.
Ethan and I both thought
the programs were really easy to read.
Well, that's not how
I remember any of that.
Look, Liz,
for once, be honest with me.
I want your real opinion.
Okay, I thought the story
was preposterous.
I thought the acting
was way over the top.
And I thought it was about
an hour too long.
It's only 90 minutes.
It's kind of a train wreck.
A train wreck? Okay.
I'm not trying to be a jerk here.
You asked me for my opinion.
No, no--
I understand.
Thank you.
I wasn't kidding about how cool
those trees were, though.
What were they? Oaks?
Damn it!
Where are my car keys?
Jack, Tracy--
What can I do for you?
Leo, we have a product
we want you to give a medical endorsement to.
I'll do it!
What is it?
It's called the Tracy Jordan Meat Machine.
It's a dual-press grill.
Say no more.
If it's giving people meat,
then I'm onboard.
I've always said
humans need more animal blood.
It keeps the spine straight.
We appreciate it, Leo.
You boys need anything
while you're here?
Some reds, yellows...
Just got some purples in from Peru.
No, I'm good.
Well, it would be rude not to take, uh...
One or two.
Now, The Rrr Jrr
is the true story of Rory Jerner,
whose pure furor
ensures a terrible murder--
Excuse me.
I feel like I'm getting
further away from it.
Hey, last night
I broke into Liz's office.
I got Jenna's movie.
Oh, how'd you get in there?
That weird security guard
Tony let me in.
I also looked on Liz's computer.
Her last two Google searches
were for singles yoga and scalp pain.
That is grim.
The Rural Juror?
Man, that's disappointing.
I had to let Tony watch me pee
to get that tape.
What?
Hey, you wanted to see me?
Yeah, I don't want to wear
this Paris Hilton nose.
(Liz) I'm sorry.
You have to wear the nose.
There's a whole bunch of jokes
in the sketch about the nose.
Well, to be perfectly honest,
I think the entire sketch is a train wreck.
Oh, I see.
We're not talking about the nose.
We're talking about the movie.
You're wrong about it, Liz.
It's getting some very positive early reviews.
Teenmoviescene.com gave it five out of five iPods.
Jenna, believe what you want.
I'm your friend. I'm telling you the truth.
Please--
Here's what's really going on.
It's killing you that
I'm in something good
that you had nothing to do with.
And now you're taking it out on me.
Oh, come on!
Well, enjoy kicking me around for now, Liz.
Because I won't be on your crappy
little show forever.
Really?
Really.
Well, Jenna,
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Ow! What the hell?
Oh, God, I'm sorry!
I didn't know
there was a person in there!
Pete, could you tell Liz Lemon
not to stand in my eyeline
while I'm rehearsing, please?
Pete, could you tell Jenna
she smells like a stripper?
So, uh...
Are you guys still fighting?
We've reached kind of an understanding.
She's not talking to me.
And to retaliate,
I'm writing impressions for her
that she can't do.
I did not have sexual relations
with that woman.
You guys can't go on like this.
You have to apologize to her.
I didn't do anything wrong!
She insisted on me telling her
what I thought of her crappy movie.
And then she attacked me.
Liz, I can't have the head writer
and one of the stars of the show fighting.
I can barely keep a lid on the feud
going on between Kenneth and Dougie from props.
Audience, let me ask you a question.
How many times has this happened to you?
Or this:
Seem familiar?
Bread is one of the worst
things in the world.
But we've always needed it.
Until now!
By burning three different types of meat together,
The Tracy Jordan Meat Machine
takes bread out of the equation!
Now your sandwich is
all of the good stuff.
That's delicious!
And it's healthy.
Hi, I'm Doctor Leo Spaceman.
I'm a working physician with a degree
from the Ho Chi Minh City School of Medicine.
Doctor Space-man,
is it true that bread eats away at your brain?
We have no way of knowing
because the powerful bread lobby
keeps stopping my research!
Well, folks,
bread will never maybe
attack your brain again!
Because with the Tracy Jordan Meat Machine--
Say it with me now!
(all) Meat is the new bread!
Where did you guys get this tape?
Oh, Josh broke into your office.
You went in my office
without permission?
Because I'm worried
about your scalp pain.
Hello, everyone.
Frank, could you tell Liz--
Nope, not interested.
Girl writer, could you tell Liz
that I don't--
Jenna, stop this.
It's stupid.
Let's just go in my office and talk.
Oh, there is nothing to talk about.
Stop making this something it isn't.
I just didn't like the movie
because it's bad.
These guys watched it.
They'll tell you.
Actually, we all kind of liked it.
What? No, you didn't.
Yeah, we all did.
It's not the best thing in the world,
but it's solid and Jenna's really good in it.
Thank you, Frank.
Look! Look at her!
She can't stand
that I'm in something good.
It's probably because
of her own intellectual insecurities.
What? Frank, shut up.
Fine, dismiss me.
I guess because I look weird,
I can't be perceptive.
I can't believe
you like this movie!
Oh!
Jeez, I hope those two work it out.
Relax, man.
As long as they're yapping at each other,
we're not working.
Enjoy it.
I want these everywhere!
I want every person here
eating from a Tracy Jordan Meat Machine.
Ow, ah!
Cheese and crackers,
that smarts!
What happened?
The grease burned me, Mr. Jordan.
The machine must be broken.
That one must be defective.
Oh, ow! My face!
My page jacket!
They all must be like that!
Where's Donaghy?
Can somebody
take me to a hospital?
Jenna, stop.
I just want to get past this.
What do you need me to do?
Well, you can start
by saying you're sorry.
To--
Fine.
I am sorry that I assumed other people
would hate the movie just because I hate it.
That was wrong.
That's it?
That's your apology?
Yeah. Are we good?
- We're good.
- Great.
So, do I have to wear the nose tonight?
Yes, you do.
Okay, well then
I hope you get bird flu and die.
What did you just say to me?
You are a big fake,
you know that, Liz?
She doesn't even need those glasses.
Really, I'm a fake, blondie?
I'm a fake?
Burning jets of grease, huh?
Were any of our people hurt?
- Only Kenneth.
- Good.
What are we gonna do?
We can't sell this.
You're right,
we can't sell this...
in the United States.
What?
We simply have to find a market
with lax safety regulations.
With your international appeal,
we can go anywhere.
How about the Ukraine?
Not the Ukraine.
I own some property
on the Dnieper River.
In Volyn?
Closer to Cherkasy.
Well, we'll find another country then.
How do you feel about Venezuela?
Can't do it, Donaghy.
I can't put my name on a product
that's gonna hurt people.
That's disappointing.
Although I admire your integrity.
Mr. Donaghy,
they need you on stage immediately.
Some kind of emergency.
For crying out loud.
I'm sorry that we're not
all weeping with gratitude
at getting to read your words.
I am so glad
I studied voice at Northwestern
so I could do raps about Suri Cruise.
Oh, please!
If it wasn't for me,
you'd still be slutting it up
for car dealership owners
so they'd put you in their commercial.
Oh, so now I'm a slut? Yeah.
Let me tell you something.
This slut slept with your brother!
Mitch?
Yeah, and let me tell you
something about Mitch.
He is disgusting in bed.
You know he's not right.
He was in a really bad skiing accident!
Ladies.
Sit down.
Now, what is this about?
It's about my movie,
The Rrr Jrr.
They've adapted The Rural Juror?
I'm a huge Kevin Grisham fan.
Jenna has taken the fact
that I don't like her movie
and blown it completely out of proportion.
She twisted my boob.
Liz, you wanted the movie to be bad.
You wanted me to fail.
Okay, let me tell you something, Jenna.
Liz has always supported you.
Even when I wanted you out of here,
she wouldn't give in.
I've never seen her so worked up.
She came at me with that
angry little badger face of hers--
There it is right now.
The point is,
she went to the mat for you.
And she was right.
- I know, but--
- But nothing.
Now you're accusing Liz
of undermining you?
They did warn me those diet pills
were mood altering.
Yeah?
I think you owe her an apology.
Oh, Liz...
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
You're right.
I did want the movie to be bad.
Wow.
The one time I try to take your side, Lemon,
and you sandbag me.
I'm sorry, Jenna.
I smelled crazy in here
and I assumed it was you.
God, Liz, I mean--
I wish you had written my movie too.
No, it's not that.
It's just--
The dream that we had in Chicago of getting famous--
We had it.
It was my dream too, Jenna.
Yeah, but you couldn't have been serious
about acting for a living.
You have brown hair.
Look, I like what I do now.
But there's still this sad little part of me
that wants to be the center of attention.
That wants to get my hair done
and get free clothes.
That wants to be you,
I guess.
And your movie just brought
all that stuff up again.
This is boring.
I'm bored now.
Oh, God, Liz.
I had no idea.
I'm sorry.
I'm a jackass.
No, I'm sorry.
So you really think I'm beautiful?
I never said that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Tell me (in russian): Feed me, Whoopi!
(all) Whoopi!
What's this?
I gave the Meat Machine to Whoopi.
Goldberg or Billingham?
Looks like Whoopi's made herself
another billion grivka.
Food ball?
Let's get personal.
Your father Werner was a burger server
in suburban Santa Barbara...
Yes, that's right.
When he spurned your mother Verna
for a curly-haired server named Roberta,
did that hurt her?
It was hard on all of us, yes.
I'll always be his little girl.
www.tvsubtitles.net