Has Bauer arrived at CTU?
No, not yet.
I need you to clear an entrance.
Why are you tracking
Jack Bauer?
What the hell's going on here,
Spenser?
I was following orders.
I'm sure if they're tracking
Jack Bauer, they have a reason.
BAUER:
This man is
a professional assassin.
He just killed Dr. Paulson.
He tried to kill me.
Did you let him into CTU?!
They told me he was here
to place a tap
on one of the servers.
That's all I knew.
Who told you?
The White House.
Mr. Gomez.
David Palmer was murdered
because he was about to expose
Walt Cummings' connection
to the terrorists.
You want the nerve gas?
Cummings is your connection.
McGILL:
Cummings is the President's
chief adviser.
How exactly do you suggest
we get to him?
I could secretly meet
with Mike Novick.
JACK:
Who did you tell?
Who did you tell?!
I didn't tell anybody, Jack!
Tell your men to stand down!
I'm sorry, sir.
We can't do that.
Put your hands
in the air!
Sentox gas is being
smuggled out of the country
by separatists who think
they're going to use it
against the Russians.
However, that nerve gas
will never reach Russian soil.
And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators
on those gas canisters.
As soon as they've reached
the terrorist base,
we'll trigger the canisters
by satellite
and release the gas.
You're a traitor.
You'll let things
play out as they are.
Otherwise,
your administration
will be implicated,
and your presidency
will be destroyed.
Mr. President,
my name is Jack Bauer
and I'm sorry to have
to confront you like this.
But your Chief of Staff
is withholding information
that is vital
to this nation's security.
Stop this!
I'm done talking with you.
You understand me?
So for the last time,
where is the nerve gas?
Stop! Stop!
I'll tell you!
It's on a freighter
leaving the port of Long Beach
at 2:30.
CTU, we've located
the target container.
No hostiles present.
You have a green light.
Take possession
of the canister.
Open 'em up. Let's go.
Open 'em all up.
Empty. Next. Moving on.
What do we got, nothing?!
There are no gas canisters
here, CTU.
The nerve gas is not here.
Where are the canisters?
I've told you everything.
We know you've altered
the arming codes, Mr. Cummings.
Erwich, listen.
We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate
with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country is about to pay
a very steep price
for betraying us.
I was approached six months ago
by a man named James Nathanson.
He was my contact.
Who is he?
Former CIA.
Said he was recruiting
like-minded individuals
for this initiative.
"Initiative."
Is that what you call this?
You helped terrorists
acquire weaponized nerve gas!
I told you we were gonna
trigger the canisters
once the separatists reached
their base in Central Asia.
This was not
supposed to happen.
But it happened!
You got into bed with these
people, and now they're
threatening to use the gas
on American citizens!
Oh, you make it sound like
our goal was to kill Americans!
What the hell was
your goal, Walt?
Explain that to me.
We're patriots, Mr. President.
We were acting in the best
interests of this country.
How is any of this
in our best interest?
Shoring up a strategic partner
in the war on terror,
ensuring a stable flow of oil.
How is any of that not
in our national interest?
WOMAN:
Chloe O'Brian's on the line.
Chloe, are you set up
for the trace?
All set, Jack.
We're ready to call Nathanson.
How long do I have
to keep him on the line?
Until I give you a signal.
Chloe, dial the number.
The line's been
disconnected, Jack.
There's nothing to grab onto.
They must know
something went wrong.
He's gone dark.
Damn it, Walt!
I don't want
this weapon deployed on US soil
any more than you do,
but Nathanson cannot help you
now and neither can I.
These terrorists
are operating on their own.
Mr. President, I think
he's telling the truth.
He can't help us, not anymore.
Aaron, get him out of here.
Yes, sir.
Jack.
What do we do now?
I need to be debriefed.
After that, I'm leaving, sir.
Given the current situation,
things have become
more complicated.
CTU is gonna have
to be responsible
for the retrieval
of the canisters.
Why are you leaving?
Sir, I have a daughter
that doesn't know
that I'm still alive.
If I have to disappear again,
in all fairness to her,
I don't think she should know.
Jack, terrorists just threatened
to deploy chemical weapons
on US soil.
They have the ability
to kill millions of people.
I understand that,
Mr. President,
and I believe that
CTU can handle this.
Jack, your experience can make
a crucial difference
in stopping them.
Look... you and I have
a complicated history.
I realize that.
And I'm not naive enough
to expect
any special personal
allegiance from you.
But I know your respect
for this office
and your concern
for this country
is just as strong
as it was when you served
under David Palmer.
I'm asking for your help,
just until this crisis is over.
I will reinstate you.
I will give you
all the support you need.
Mr. President, you and I...
Jack, please!
For God's sake, we need
to recover this nerve gas
before it's too late.
Micro-circuitry on this remote
has been tampered with.
As far as I can tell,
unless we can repair it,
we can't arm the canisters.
Rossler will have a way.
He should have called by now.
Our real enemy is Russia.
We should be figuring out
another way to get back home,
not wasting time trying to use
the gas against the Americans.
Question my orders again,
and I will kill you.
Do you understand?
They've closed the ports.
They will hunt us
until they find us.
So if we cannot use
the gas against Russia,
we will use it against America.
Get up.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Lynn?
Jenny, now is a really bad time.
Yeah, I know you're busy,
but I need to see you, please.
What is it?
I need some help.
You mean money.
Lynn, I'm clean.
I'm working two jobs
and busting my ass
to put my life back together.
How much?
$500.
Can I, can I come over there?
Absolutely not.
Why?
Are you afraid
I'll embarrass you?
Yeah, I am.
Lynn, I got nobody else
to turn to.
You know, I can't go back
on the street again.
If you don't help me,
I swear I'm going
to hurt myself.
For God's sakes, Lynn,
I'm your sister.
All right, listen.
Jenny, listen.
There's a parking lot
across the street from CTU.
I'll meet you there
in 20 minutes.
Okay.
Thank you, Lynn.
( sighs )
Sorry I'm late.
BUCHANAN:
I was just explaining that
Cummings provided us
with a schematic
of one of the canisters.
Triggering mechanisms
on the canisters can only be
activated via satellite relay.
Cummings says the terrorists
have been given
invalid detonation codes.
Then these canisters
are useless to them.
Unless they can find a way
to control
the triggering mechanism.
McGILL:
Are we running
evacuation scenarios?
Evacuation isn't feasible,
not without a time frame
or a target.
Erwich's threat was
intentionally vague.
What are we doing to track
these canisters?
Chloe?
I pulled a voice print
from Erwich's call to Cummings
and I'm doing a scan
of all satcom chatter.
If Erwich is in contact
with anyone on that bandwidth,
we should be able to intercept
and trace the call.
We better get lucky
'cause we just got a new
assessment from Civil Defense.
They're estimating that the
nerve gas from each canister
will create kill zones between
one and three square miles.
The terrorists are
in possession of 20 canisters.
We're talking about
potential casualties
in the hundreds of thousands,
perhaps over a million.
( phone rings )
Yeah?
Ivan Erwich?
Go ahead.
Jacob Rossler.
I was asked to call you
by a friend in Moscow.
You've been briefed
on our situation?
You need to reconfigure
the remote trigger for an Aatox
chemical delivery system, right?
Yes.
You have the canisters
with you?
Yes.
You'll need to start
by cutting into them.
Listen carefully
to my instructions.
( phone rings )
O'Brian.
WOMAN:
We just got a pattern match.
Send me the hit.
All interagency search protocols
are being run through CTU.
Ken, no one is
going around you.
All right, I'll make sure
that you're apprised
in real time.
Audrey, I thought
you should know.
Logan has asked Jack
to be reinstated
on a provisional basis.
He's been given
full autonomy and access.
We got a possible intercept
on Erwich.
This just happened.
ROSSLER:
On the inner casing,
you will find a display window
with a seven-digit readout.
I'll need them.
ERWICH:
And then what?
ROSSLER:
I will program a new chip
for your remote trigger.
Put me through to Jack Bauer.
Voice print is a 95% match.
It's Erwich.
EDGAR:
He was on a sat-phone.
I can't trace it,
but the call originated
from a landline downtown.
This is Bauer.
Jack, we may have
a lead on Erwich.
I'm listening.
We intercepted a call
between Erwich
and an unknown associate.
We weren't able
to trace Erwich,
but we may have a location
for the associate.
22 North Figueroa,
a penthouse.
Chloe, bring up
the building manifest.
See who's in there.
On it.
From what we heard,
Erwich is trying to acquire
some kind of activation code.
Yeah, he's trying to reconfigure
the trigger mechanism
so he can disperse the Sentox.
Bill, we're running out of time.
Okay, the penthouse is leased
to a man named Jacob Rossler.
Cross-checking.
He's a software programmer
indicted for high
security code infiltration,
identity theft.
Never convicted.
Okay, I'm gonna need
schematics on the building
and vectors for every entrance.
We'll have it for you
by the time you get there.
Bill, we're going to need
to go in covertly.
Have Curtis meet me
at the location
with a small team of four.
But tell them
to stay out of sight
until I get there.
Right.
We'll be in touch.
This is our
new destination.
They'll clear
a landing zone for you.
Mr. Buchanan, this building's
security system
uses proprietary technology.
It's a high-end platform.
It's a bitch
to hack into,
especially with
the time constraints
we're under.
So, get Edgar to help you.
Spenser is better.
Chloe, absolutely
out of the question.
CHLOE:
Spenser can
do this faster
than Edgar
and I put together.
He wrote an infiltration code
that took us
four months to hack.
That's a bad idea.
CHLOE:
Stay out of
this, Edgar.
He didn't know
Cummings was dirty.
His polygraph
proved that.
He's was spying on us.
He was spying on you.
He lied to you.
Sir, if you don't let
Spenser help us do this,
we're not going
to get it done in time.
He has to wear
a security wristband
and be under
constant supervision.
Fine.
( phone ringing )
Audrey Raines.
Audrey, it's Jack.
Hey.
Listen, I wanted
to tell you myself,
the president asked me
to stay on
until the canisters
were retrieved.
I heard that you
were reinstated.
Jack, you know
what this means.
You'll be exposed.
CTU can handle the crisis.
Audrey, I have to do this.
Jack, you don't owe them this.
Listen, Audrey,
the reason why I called:
I need to ask you
to do me a favor.
What?
Kim doesn't know
I'm alive yet.
I don't want her to find out
the wrong way.
Do you want me to tell her?
No, I just want you
to call her
and bring her in
to CTU.
I'll see her
when I get back.
All right.
Are you sure you're comfortable
doing this for me?
Of course.
Thank you.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, your swing arm
needs to be replaced.
With parts you're
looking at $475.
Yeah. We're open
till 5:00.
Okeydoke.
Can I help you?
Do you have
some kind of
precision tool
for cutting metal?
Sure.
Where is
everyone else?
Lunch. Why?
I need you to do
some work for us.
And we need it done fast.
If you do it,
you'll live.
Do you understand?
Yeah, yeah.
Just take it easy.
Why haven't I gotten an update?
Bauer left here
on some sort of lead.
Find out if CTU is any closer
to recovering the nerve gas.
Yes, sir.
How are you feeling?
Remarkably well...
for someone whose husband
tried to have her committed
without so much
as a good-bye.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come here
to fight with you.
You have every right to.
The two of us used to be
a pretty good team.
Do you remember?
I was the one you would
always come to first for advice.
I remember.
We've got to get back
to that relationship, Charles.
You're right, things are
going to get rough for you.
And you are going to need me
and everything
that I can give you.
I don't know what to say,
Martha.
Don't you ever do that
to me again.
( knocking )
Mike, please, come in.
Mr. President.
Mrs. Logan.
Mike.
Mike, I owe you
a profound apology.
You were in an impossible
situation, sir.
I understand why you did
what you did.
No.
I panicked, Mike, that's it.
Plain and simple.
I'm not proud of
how I handled myself.
I intend to make it right
from this point on.
I'd like you
to resume your duties.
Of course, sir.
Thank you, Mike.
( sighs )
CTU is in the process
of tracking down
the canisters,
but we still have to deal
with the issue
of Walt Cummings.
It's all right,
Mike.
I would like
Martha's input on this.
So what do we do about Walt?
We can't detain him
indefinitely.
Maybe not, but we can keep him
out of sight long enough
for us to construct
a credible narrative.
Mike...
are you talking about
a cover-up?
I mean,
exercising discretion
to spare this country
unnecessary humiliation.
Walt Cummings was complicit
in David Palmer's assassination.
He has allowed
these terrorists
to get their hands
on weaponized nerve gas
that is at this point
With respect...
a very real
and present threat
With respect...
Mrs. Logan,
if we go public with Cummings,
the president's reputation
won't be the only casualty.
The credibility
of this office
will be destroyed.
Charles, you are going
to take a hit on this.
But you won't be destroyed.
You did nothing wrong
except to trust someone
who betrayed you.
You are human.
You might be overestimating
the public's capacity
for forgiveness.
No. I'm not.
The only thing
they won't forgive
is being lied to.
I think you should issue
a statement to the press,
and the sooner
the better.
I agree.
Why don't you and I
work on it together,
see what we come up with.
Great.
Chloe.
Go to Station 3.
We don't have much time.
Thanks for getting me
reinstated.
I only did it
because I need your help
getting Jack through
the high-security building,
not because I forgive you
because I don't.
Have a seat.
We need to gain access
to the security server
at 22 North Figueroa.
It's a proprietary network,
so get to work.
Chloe?
I swear, I thought
I was falling...
I don't care, Spencer.
( keyboard keys clacking )
CTU, they've got eyes and ears
on building security.
We have two units,
one east, one west
of the building.
Chloe, do you copy?
CHLOE ( on earpiece ):
We're here, Jack.
Spenser's countervailing
the building's
security protocols.
What are you talking about?
Spenser's under arrest.
Buchanan released him
from Holding.
Fine, just give me
Rossler's position.
I've hacked into
the building's motion sensors.
According to them,
Rossler is still
in the penthouse.
I have two guards
on the penthouse level.
What about
the ground level entrance?
SPENSER:
There's one guard,
three surveillance cameras.
Okay. Stand by to take out
all security cameras
that are covering the front desk
and the elevators.
I can only shut them down
for 60 seconds.
After that, they will
reboot automatically.
That's as long as you have
to subdue the lobby guard.
Copy that.
Teams A and B, you will
remain in a holding position
till you get a "go" code.
We are three minutes out.
We have to cross
the street
to get to
Rossler's building.
ROSSLER ( on phone ):
Yes?
We're ready to cut
into the canisters.
You have to cut precisely
ten centimeters
from the bottom
of the casing
to reveal the trigger.
How thick is
the outer casing?
Five millimeters.
Call me with the identification
numbers when you're done.
We're in position.
We're set. We're ready to go.
Give me a few seconds
to access control.
Okay.
Here we go, Jack.
On my mark.
Camera's dark.
Federal agent.
Let me see your hands!
Elevator code, let's have it.
Uh... four, zero,
seven, three, pound.
Unit one, status check.
Just lost cameras A and C.
Tell him you don't know
why the cameras went down,
but everything is okay.
Everything is okay.
Status check: blue.
Don't know why
the cameras are out.
Everything's fine down here.
Turn around.
Back up to me.
Where are the elevators?
The elevator's
almost there.
You have
two floors to go.
The camera reboots
in ten seconds,
then you'll be
visible.
( elevator bell dings )
Move. Move!
Unit one, status check.
Where are you?
You tell him you had
to use the men's room.
Base,
headed to the men's room.
Something's wrong.
( machine beeping )
( phone beeps )
Yes?
GUARD:
Mr. Rossler?
We may have a situation.
What kind of situation?
I'm not sure.
Please remain
in your office
until you get
the all clear.
The guards look suspicious.
One of them has
an automatic weapon.
Copy that.
Federal Agents.
( gunfire, shouting )
You okay?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Get my vest.
Rossler's
on the move.
Where is he?
9:00.
( gunfire )
Federal agent.
Drop the weapon!
Put your hands
behind your head.
Do it!
Interlock your fingers.
Rossler is in custody.
I repeat:
All backup teams move in.
I need a medic.
We're patching you
into the Situation Room.
Someone else is
in the penthouse, Jack.
Where?
In the bedroom,
to your right. North side.
Curtis, cover him.
I got him.
Let me see your hands.
Let me see your hands!
Don't shoot.
Who are you?
I'm Inessa.
Who did that to you?
You are the police?
Counterterrorist
unit, Los Angeles.
He is holding me here.
I want to go home.
You need to cut
into the outer casing exactly
ten centimeters from the bottom.
The casting
is five millimeters thick.
You cannot puncture
the inner lining.
What's in these things?
Don't worry. Just do what I say.
Just... Can't you tell me
what this is all about?
Do you have a family, Cal?
A wife.
My wife is
in prison.
She's been there
for seven years.
Her only crime was to support me
while I fought for my country.
My son lives in a
state-run facility
He does not even remember
what I look like.
You want to know
what this is about?
Justice. It's
about ending tyranny.
When you're
finished,
we will leave.
You won't hurt me?
You're not my enemy.
The government is my enemy.
Hey.
You have my word.
Begin.
It's all right.
You're all right.
Just take a seat.
You're safe now.
Have a medic
take a look at her.
I want CT to do a full
background check.
I don't mind that
they've dressed his wound,
but make sure they don't give
him anything for the pain.
Yes, sir.
Curtis. Put him in a chair.
All right, let's go.
Get him up.
Easy on my leg.
CURTIS:
Just get him
over there.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with CTU.
25 minutes ago you contacted
a man named Ivan Erwich.
What did he want you
to do for him?
I want my lawyer.
You'll get a lawyer
as soon as I get what I need.
Mr. Erwich is in possession
of 20 canisters
of Sentox-VX nerve gas,
which he has
threatened to deploy
here in the United States.
I guess you have a problem.
No, sir. You
have a problem.
You've been conspiring with
and aiding a known terrorist,
which means I get to hold you
for as long as I want.
Now, we know Mr. Erwich
can't deploy the canisters
unless he reconfigures
the trigger mechanism.
Is that what
he wanted you to do?
Trust me. You don't want
to go down this road with me.
Go to hell.
( yells )
That's exactly where
I'm going to send you
unless you start
to cooperate.
You like hurting girls?
Curtis.
( yelling )
JACK:
When I finish with
you, you're gonna wish
you felt this
good again.
Where is Erwich?!
( moaning )
I want full immunity.
Unfreezing of all my assets.
And transport
to a foreign country
of my choosing.
No.
I need Inessa.
She comes with me.
That's the deal.
Maybe I'm not
making myself clear.
We're not making a deal.
Curtis.
( yelling )
( groaning and panting )
Jack, it's Lynn.
Go ahead.
We don't have the luxury
to engage in brinkmanship.
He's gonna tell us
what we want to know.
You may be right, but we're not
gonna wait around to find out.
Accept the deal.
That's an order.
Fine. It's your call.
We're signing off.
Make sure he follows through.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I've been instructed
to accept your proposal.
A certified agreement,
signed by the
Attorney General.
When I see that, I'll
tell you what you want.
But remember,
I want Inessa.
Your immunity agreement
is being drawn up.
Now I want something.
Where's Erwich?
I have no idea.
I don't know the man.
Not even what he looks like.
I first spoke with him
30 minutes ago.
We were put in contact
through a mutual
associate in Russia.
Who?
Sergei Voronov.
He's a commander
in the resistance
movement.
What's Erwich want?
He wants to reprogram the chip
of the trigger.
He's calling me back
with the identification keys.
What's your time frame?
Within the hour.
How is he going
to receive the package?
I was going to deliver it.
We haven't agreed
on a meeting place.
I want that chip.
It's in a safe place.
Once I see some paperwork,
I'll show it to you.
I want you to be ready to fit
that chip with a transponder
so we can track him.
Okay.
( touch tone beeps )
( phone ringing )
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
Where are we with Rossler's
immunity agreement?
We have the Attorney
General's sanction.
You should have the documents
in a few minutes.
Okay, good.
Did we get any
information
on the girl?
There isn't much.
Inessa Kovalevsky.
Reported missing
19 months ago from Kiev.
The assumption is,
she was kidnapped
by traffickers
in the sex slave trade.
She's 15, Jack.
15?
Okay, thanks, Bill.
I'll get back to you.
You can't take the girl.
Then you don't have a deal.
You'll have your
immunity, your freedom.
Leave the girl out of this.
No.
Inessa is all
I care about.
She comes with me,
or you lose Erwich.
( sighs )
I've almost finished compiling
those surveillance protocols.
Whatever you have, port it over
to Edgar's station.
Why?
He'll be finishing that task.
Fine.
Chloe, don't you
understand?
I know.
I'm glad you do.
You don't work here
anymore, Spenser.
That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
What?
Your reinstatement
was temporary.
Just until we got Rossler
into custody.
But there's still
a lot of stuff that
has to be done here.
We pulled people from Division.
We don't need you anymore.
These men will escort you out.
I know that was hard,
but you did the right thing.
Shut up, Edgar.
You're right.
We don't need that part.
Okay, "I promise a full
and open inquiry
"into this matter.
"I will not rest
until I've restored
"the faith that you have
placed in this office,
"and I can demonstrate to you,
the American people,
"that I bear its mantle
of responsibility
with respect
and deep humility."
See, this way,
you're assuming responsibility
for Walt's actions,
but you're also personally
taking the initiative
to bring him to justice.
Well, I'd like to run it by
Mike, but I think it works.
I think it's
the right move, Charles.
Thank you for
letting me help you.
I'm glad to have your help.
Been a long time since you and I
have worked together like this.
( phone ringing )
Yes?
Mr. President. Mike.
What is it, Mike?
I think you should come here.
I'm in the west hallway.
What's going on?
Just come here, sir.
I'm on my way.
( machinery whirring )
( whirring stops )
Good.
Cut him down.
Thanks for meeting me.
You got the money?
Jenny, I'm not here
to bring you money.
Here's the name of a doctor.
He's a good man.
I want you to call him.
I'll pay all
the expenses.
It won't cost you a cent.
We'll call him together.
I can't.
( grunting )
Don't hurt him.
Oh, my God.
Hurry up.
( coughing, groaning )
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Come on!
( coughing )
( groaning )
Rossler's been given
a shot for the pain.
We have air and land
pursuit units on standby.
As soon as he moves out,
we'll be ready.
No one's going anywhere
unless Erwich makes that call.
Stand by the phones.
Excuse me.
Audrey Raines.
It's me.
Hey.
Did you manage to get
a hold of Kim?
No. I tried her,
but she wasn't in.
I left a message.
Would you mind trying
again for me, please?
Sure.
Okay, thanks.
I want to contact my family.
When can I go?
I-I need to explain
something to you first.
Please, sit down.
For now...
we need you to go
with Mr. Rossler.
Just-Just for now.
Men like me, agents,
are going to follow you.
And when we get what we need
from Mr. Rossler,
they're going to move in
and they're gonna take
you away from him.
You don't know what he
does to me when we're alone.
I promise you, I won't
let him be alone with you.
I don't believe you.
I won't do it.
Please, let...
Let me go.
I'm sorry. I can't.
Then you are no different
than Rossler.
I am not Rossler.
Look at me.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
I promise.
We need you to get dressed,
please.
Thank you.
( machinery whirring )
Good job.
( silenced gunshot )
That's it.
Load the canisters.
Get rid of the body.
( phone ringing )
JACK:
Pick it up.
Yes?
We have the identification keys.
I'm messaging them to you now.
I've got them.
How long will it take
you to reprogram the chip
and deliver it back to us?
I'll be ready in ten minutes.
You and I need a place
where we can meet.
You're coming
personally?
Unless you have someone
who can install
and program a coded
binary chip.
I'll call you back in five
minutes with the location.
I'll be here.
Get him set up for a wire.
I'll get the girl.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Rossler, in a minute,
we're going to be
implanting a transmitter.
We're ready to go.
It's going to be fine.
What's happening?
Couldn't complete
the trace.
We've narrowed it down
to a ten-block radius.
( phone ringing )
Okay. Thanks.
( gunshots, shouting )
No! Hold your fire!
Get a medic in here now!
Inessa, give me the gun.
I know you don't want
to hurt anybody else.
I couldn't go with him.
( gun hits floor )
Is he gonna make it?
No. He's dead.
Rossler was our only link
to those canisters.
Erwich's gonna
call here any minute.
He's gonna expect
to talk to him.
www.tvsubtitles.net