What's going on?
What do you mean?
I'm your brother.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
It's all right, really.
Okay.
One more chapter and
we'll take a break.
( glass shattering )
David.
Get help!
Whoever did this,
I want them dead or in custody
by the time
the Russians get here.
BUCHANAN:
I would ask that you
consider postponing
the signing of the treaty, sir.
No. Absolutely not.
I think... that David was killed
because of something
he was about to tell me.
He said that it concerned
national security
and that it involved you.
Was she all right?
No, Walt,
she's not all right.
She's having
another one of her delusions.
What is this,
an interrogation?
I just don't like being lied to.
No one's lying to you, Derek.
Yeah, I'm not hungry.
Sorry.
You don't owe me an explanation.
If you had wanted to tell
me about your past,
you would have
told me already.
( cell phone ringing )
Yeah?
Jack, I know this isn't
protocol, please don't
hang up on me, I need your help.
They got Tony and Michele,
Michele is dead,
Tony's in critical condition,
now they're gonna kill me.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm sorry I followed you,
I'm just... I'm just worried
about my mother.
You're going with me.
( gunfire )
( gunshot )
( gunshots )
Hold your fire, Chloe!
Palmer was
my primary target.
( coughing ):
Set you up.
Make it look like
you did it.
You're the one
that killed Palmer.
Yeah.
( gunshot )
AUDREY:
The President's retreat
is still vulnerable.
You need to post two more
people here at Delta.
It's a high probability
point of infiltration.
We'll have to pull assets
from somewhere else.
Yeah, Marcie, hi.
Can you give me the figures?
Excuse me, sir.
Sorry to interrupt.
What is it,
Edgar?
We have a visual
on a suspect,
I thought you might
want to know.
He may be
the Palmer shooter.
Were you able to make an ID?
I think you
should see for yourself.
About an hour before
President Palmer was shot...
( typing )
...someone broke into
the service ance
of the building
across the street,
the one the sniper used.
We have a frame grab
from a security video.
I ran it through
a high-res filter,
so it may take
a few seconds to render.
Audrey.
What is going on
here, Jack?
They're setting me up
to take the fall for
Palmer's assassination.
Palmer's not even
president anymore.
Why would
they want him dead?
I don't know.
You need to get as far away
from here as you can.
Just disappear.
No, what
I need to do
is I need to find out who really
killed President Palmer.
How are you gonna do that?
Start at the beginning.
Investigate
the original crime scene.
David Palmer was visiting
his brother when he was shot.
Maybe he left something
there that can help me.
That's crazy. Palmer was
assassinated an hour ago.
The place is gonna be crawling
with Secret Service,
FBI, local police.
I need access
to a building schematic
and an interagency
deployment grid.
Can you get that
for me or not?
Yeah.
I should be able to log on
remotely from the site.
Okay.
Come on, let's go.
How could you kill that guy?
I'm sorry you had
to see that, Derek.
Gein the van.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
You're gonna do
exactly what I tell you
until I pass you off
to your mother.
Let go of me.
Let's get
something straight, kid.
The only reason you're
still conscious is because
I don't want to carry you.
Now get in the van.
EDGAR:
Preliminary analysis indicates
the video hasn't been doctored.
Then Jack was in the building
the sniper fired from
at the same time President
Palmer was assassinated.
That's impossible.
This whole thing is impossible.
Bill, you were there
when Jack was shot.
He had not pulse,
no vitals.
And I have no idea how Jack
staged his own death.
But I understand
his reasons.
He was about to be handed over
to the Chinese government
to spend the rest
of his life in prison.
None of that explains why Jack
would want to kill David Palmer.
I had Curtis
pull the phone logs.
Palmer, Tony and Michelle
were all talking to Jack
right before he was
supposedly killed.
Our working theory
is that they conspired
to help Jack
fake his own death.
Now you're saying that Jack
was behind the attack
on Tony and Michelle, too?
Why would Jack want to kill
the people who helped him?
CURTIS:
Something may have happened
and he stopped trusting them
to keep his secret.
Jack would
never murder his friends.
Audrey...
I don't want to believe
Jack did this, either.
But right now, it's
the best explanation
for the evidence
that we have.
I'm sorry.
The White House needs
to know about this.
Yeah, I'll call the President.
CURTIS:
Bill.
What is it,
Curtis?
I had Adamson run
a data recovery operation
on Tony's phone
records.
They show Chloe
was on those calls
with President Palmer and Tony.
Chloe knew Jack
was alive?
Apparently.
We called her in an hour ago,
she should
have been here by now.
EDGAR:
I've been trying
to call her on her cell,
but she's not answering.
I wanted to run
a locate
but Spencer talked me
out of it.
If anything happens
to her it's your fault.
Stop.
Have Adamson track her cell--
we need to get to her
before Jack does.
Put out
an interagency alert.
Jack Bauer is now
the prime suspect
in President Palmer's
assassination.
Emphasize that he's
a former agent,
well-trained and
should be considered
extremely dangerous.
CUMMINGS:
Excuse me, sir.
What is it,
Walt?
Mrs. Logan called again.
I can't keep putting her off
about this phone call
with David Palmer.
Why would David Palmer
call my wife
about
a national security threat?
That's what she says he wanted
to talk to her about.
A matter of
national security.
Maybe if I investigated
the phone call?
No, you need to stay
focused on the Summit.
I am, sir, which is why
we can't risk having Mrs. Logan
obsess about this phone call.
Showing her the truth
might help her get on
with her
responsibilities today.
So what are you...
what are you suggesting?
Well, if David Palmer
called her yesterday,
our communications office
will have a recording
of their conversation.
Get that for me.
Yes, sir.
And Walt.
Thank you for doing this.
( over intcom ):
Mr. President,
Audrey Raines
is holding on line three.
Ms. Raines, this
is President Logan.
You're also on
with Walt Cummings.
Sir, CTU has a suspect
in the assassination
of President Palmer.
Good!
Who is it?
Ms. Raines?
It's Jack Bauer, sir.
Jack Bauer's dead.
We've all been living under
that assumption, sir.
I don't understand.
What makes you
think it's Bauer?
CTU has verified surveillance
video placing Jack Bauer
at the same time,
in the same building
as the sniper who killed
President Palmer.
Audrey, this
is Walt Cummings.
Let me get clear on this.
Are you saying that
Bauer shot David Palmer?
We're proceeding
under that assumption, yes.
Why? For what possible reason?
David Palmer might have known
that Jack Bauer s alive,
knowledge that he shared
with three other CTU agents,
all of whom have been targeted
in the last hour.
The man does have a histor
of insubordination,
irrational behavior,
drug addiction.
Jack Bauer has a history
of great service
to this country.
How does thiaffect your threat
assessment for the Summit?
We're still recommending
that you delay or reschedule
until Jack Bauer's apprehended.
Ms. Raines, you have a suspect.
Find him.
Yes, sir.
Sir, President Suvarov
arrives within the hour.
Should we think about informing
his security chief that
he's a potential target?
No. No.
I-I want
this information limited
to those involved
in the manhunt for Jack Bauer.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
I found Haas.
He and his men
are all dead.
How did this happen?
I'm not sure.
The last time I spoke to Haas
was about to move
on Bauer and the woman.
Is there any sign of Bauer now?
No. I'll dispatch
a team and track him.
We'll have him in 24 hours.
No, let CTU find Bauer.
Once they have him in custody,
we'll take him out.
You're not concerned Bauer
will impede the operation?
He won't have chance.
We launch in less than an hour.
All of their hardware's
military spec.
Fragmentation grenades,
percussion grenades.
Here's a comm unit we can use.
Who are these people?
( phone ringing )
Yeah?
DIANE:
Frank,
will you please tell me
what's going on?
Diane, I know it's hard,
but please try not to worry.
Derek is fine.
Where are you now?
Um, I'm-I'm about a half hour
outside of L.A.
Just tell me where
to meet you.
I don't know yet.
Just keep heading
towards the city.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I can.
Can I talk to him?
Of course, yeah.
It's your mother.
Talk to her.
Mom?
Derek,
are you okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Are you sure?
Jack, we're about
a block away.
Say good-bye
to your mother.
I have to hang up now, Mom.
Derek, I love you.
Me, too.
Give me the phone.
Get to the back of the vehicle.
Go!
RADIO DISPATCHER:
Unit 14, clear.
WOMAN:
While security agencies
are remaining hushed,
speculation begins to grow.
We're told, though,
that that speculation
will not be addressed
because the government says
security right now
is of utmost importance.
Now, look behind me,
you'll see
the Los Angeles
apartment building where
President David Palmer
was assassinated
a little more
than an hour ago.
You can also see Americans
of all ages
have started to gather
to mourn
and pay their last respects
to the beloved
former president,
who surprised many
almost three years ago
with his 11th-hour announcement
that he would not be seeking
a second term.
All right,
go on through.
...cordoned off the area
and security...
Let her through.
( inaudible police radio
transmission )
We're clear.
Go on up front.
Hold the light
on the bag.
Can you get a wireless
access point from down here?
Yeah, I'm reading
the agents' transponders.
I can track their locations
to within three feet.
Jack, there are 167 agents
in and around the location,
25 of them in Wayne Palmer's
apartment alone.
I know-- that's why
we better hope that this
is gonna be the last place
they're gonna be looking for me.
Testing one, two,
testing
one, two, three.
Okay.
This is field ops
communation unit.
All you need to do
is put it in your ear
and we're set to go.
Derek, put out the light.
Officer.
I live in
this building.
I was told that...
( inaudible )
What...
Relax.
He's really
good at this.
You sure he's okay?
Yeah.
I think.
All right, do you copy?
Yeah.
( keyboard clacking )
CHLOE:
Wayne Palmer's apartment
is the penthouse.
( bell dings )
I'm going up now.
Jack, there are four agents
waiting at the lobby.
Hold off on going up
if you can.
( bell dings, door opens )
Too late.
( bell dings )
This first room is a study.
He told my mother and I
if ahis name's Frank.
Who is he, really?
His name's Jack Bauer.
Up until a year and a half ago,
he worked for
the government.
Is that why we're
in the building where
the president was killed?
Please don't ask me
any more questions.
C-Can't you at least tell me
why he had to pretend
he was someone else?
Certain people thought
the best way
to cover up their mistakes
was to get rid of Jack.
You mean, kill him?
Yes.
Jack had to give up everything
and everyone in his life,
including his daughter.
He has a daughter?
I've already told you
more than I should.
JACK:
I have the computer in the study
booted up.
President Palmer had
a user account.
Is it password-secured?
No. There are about
a dozen files;
only one of them's encrypted.
That's where I'm gonna look.
Okay, give me the
computer's IP address.
I'll upload a decryption
program to it.
Hold on.
2-9-2-dot-1-6-
2-dot-1-2-dot-2.
( door opening )
Someone's at the door.
Not according
to the deployment grid.
There are no agents there.
Do not move.
Do not raise your voice.
You son of a bitch.
You killed my brother.
Mr. Palmer, you know
I didn't do that.
Whatever evidence
they showed you against me
has been fabricated.
I served your brother
for years.
I would've gladly given
my life for his.
He was my friend.
The only reason
that I ahere
is to try and figure out
why and how he was assassinated.
I was hoping to find clues
on that computer.
Why don't you step
into the next room, Jack,
and ask the Secret Service
to help you find it?
Because I'm being set up.
Whoever's behind this
has planted evidence against me
making me the shooter.
It would be useless
to try and convince
the authorities otherwise.
You think
you're gonna convince me?
If I killed your brother,
why didn't I kill you
when you walked
through the door?
Think about this, Wayne.
Why would I be here?
Please... I need your help.
Jack, how do you expect me
to believe you
under these circumstances?
Take the gun.
Jack, what are you doing?
MAN ( over TV ):
That after two terms
in the House
and one in the Senate,
he was elected president...
There you are,
Mrs. Logan.
...recapturing for his party
key states...
David and I first got
to know each other
when he was elected to Congress.
He and Charles never saw
eye to eye politically, but...
David never let that get
in the way of our friendship.
Oh...
that picture's
from his inauguration.
At the ball,
I was one of the first people
David asked to dance.
...and above all, honor!
Mrs. Logan, I need
a few more minutes
with your hair...
I know! I can do it myself.
Just trying to help.
Um, I'm sorry, Evelyn,
I know. I'm sorry.
Mrs. Logan...
may I have a word?
Of course.
The president asked
me to look into
the call from David
Palmer that you...
told him about.
I was beginning to think
you were ignoring me.
Oh. So when did this
call take place?
Last night.
It woke me up.
I had fallen asleep
watching the news,
so it was somewhere
between 10:00 and 11:00.
Well, I'll have someone
pull up the call from
the audio archives.
PRESIDENT PALMER:
...very thing that will
defeat our enemies...
Walt.
He doesn't believe me, does he?
Charles.
He thinks I'm making
the whole thing up.
( cheering over TV )
I wouldn't say that, Mrs. Logan.
( laughs ):
Well, of course
you wouldn't say it.
( sighs ):
Mrs. Logan...
Walt, you can go now.
NEWSMAN:
...partially scarred
and weakened.
He leaves behind
a son and daughter,
as well as a shocked
and grieving nation.
David Palmer,
dead today at age 55.
Your brother say
or do anything
out of the ordinary
before he was shot?
He was acting distracted ever
since he came to Los Angeles.
I finally called him on it
this morning.
What'd he say?
He never had the chance
to say anything, Jack.
Yeah.
The decryption program's
finished running.
You should be able
to open the file.
Okay, I'm going
into it now.
( keyboard clacking )
WAYNE:
That's the first chapter
of his memoir.
That doesn't make any sense--
why would he encrypt that?
I mean, there are printouts
of it all over the place.
Maybe he hid some information
in the document.
We're gonna have to compare this
to the printout,
see if he added
or changed anything.
Got one right here.
You haven't sent the file
allocations; whas the problem?
I need a higher vel
access code.
Look, if you're still
upset about me and Chloe...
I don't care about that.
I care that if you hadn't left
her on her own this morning,
maybe she'd be okay right now.
Don't you think I know that?
Look, you're just making it
harder for me to do my job.
Use Chloe's access code: JJ72.
You won't get fire-walled
with it.
Thank you.
Edgar.
What?
This is weird.
I tried logging in
under Chloe's access code--
the system says
I'm already signed in.
Let me see...
( typing )
That's because Chloe's
logged in, remotely.
Are you sure it's her?
Yes-- see the way
the traffic's redirected
through an external socket?
Even I don't know
how to do that.
( sighing ):
Then she's alive.
( phone ringing )
Buchanan.
Sir, it's Edgar.
I think we can find Chloe.
How?
She's accessing our system
through a laptop.
I'm running a locate now.
What's she using
our system to do?
EDGAR:
All I can see from here is
she's tracking Secret Service
and FBI deployments.
The locate came back.
She's at Wayne Palmer's
building.
The signal's faint.
It's possible she's
in t parking garage
under the building.
Let me know
if she changes location.
Why would Chloe
be at the scene
of Palmer's assassination,
tracking agents?
She wouldn't be...
unless someone was forcing her.
What do you mean?
Maybe Jack left evidence behind
he needs to erase.
Surrounded by
all of those agents?
Bill, that doesn't make sense.
Jack can explain it to
us when we apprehend him.
This is Bill Buchanan at CTU.
I need to speak to
Yes.
Have you left yet?
No, we were delayed.
We're still loading
the truck.
You should be
on your way by now.
Be there in 20 minutes,
as planned.
Call me when
you're approaching.
Wait, stop, stop,
stop, stop...
Right there-- he added something
in the middle of a sentence:
a name and an address.
There.
JACK:
"Chevensky - 16 Transport Way."
Chloe, did you get that?
It looks like an address.
Yes. Transport Way is a street
at the Ontario airport.
Okay, I want you to check all
inbound flights into Ontario.
Look for a
passenger Chevensky.
Try and make
the connection.
Jack, the Secret Service
is changing its deployment.
JACK:
How?
CHLOE:
Suddenly, there are a lot
of agents moving
into the building.
I'm on my way down.
They know that I'm here.
Let me help you
get out of here, Jack.
No.
You can't risk
being connected to me.
And until we know
who to trust,
you can't tell anybody
about what we found,
do you understand?
I'm going to do
everything I can to find out
who did this
to your brother.
I'll be in touch.
Chloe, I need
another way out of here.
Checking.
Jack, across the hall,
through the kitchen.
One agent at the door.
Copy that.
( bell dings )
I'm in the elevator.
Where are they
concentrating their agents?
Jack, they cut off
accesso my grid;
I don't know where
the agents are.
They were grouping
in the lobby.
( bell dings )
I'm getting out
on the second floor.
Come on, Jack.
What'd you get for me
on Chevensky?
He's not a passenger,
he's a baggage supervisor
at the airport.
AGENT JENNINGS:
Jack Bauer! Agent O'Brian!
The perimeter is sealed!
There is no way out!
Step into view with
your hands in the air!
We know you're down here!
Step into view
with your hands in the air!
Do not shoot!
We need them alive!
JENNINGS:
No one fire!
Do not fire!
Step out of the vehicle!
Check the back!
Get the side!
Step to your left!
Get down on your knees!
Cuff her!
Open the back!
Back.
Clear.
JENNINGS:
Bauer's not here.
Secure the area.
JACK:
Get in! Give me my bag!
Come on...
Got it.
( phone auto-dialing )
( phone ringing )
Frank.
Yeah, it's me.
Listen, Derek
is all right.
I just need to know
where you are.
I'm on the 210
at the 10.
Okay, I want you to take the
10 East to the Ontario Airport.
When you get there,
I want you to go
to the parking lot
in front of the terminal.
I'll meet you on the west side
of that parking lot.
Do you understand me?
Yeah, yeah.
Diane, listen to me.
I am so sorry that I got you
involved in this.
But everything's
gonna be all right.
I'll be there in
a few minutes, okay?
Okay.
Okay. Thanks.
Mr. Buchanan, this
is Agent Jennings.
There's no sign
of Jack Bauer yet,
but we've apprehended
your agent, Chloe O'Brian.
She was trying to
escape our agents
and get away
from the building.
You're telling me
she wasn't under duress?
Not as far as
I can tell.
Put her on the phone.
Uncuff her.
Bill Buchanan wants
to talk to you.
Hi.
Chloe, what the hell's
going on?
Jack didn't kill anybody.
He's being framed to cover up
the real reason Palmer
was assassinated.
This is according to Jack.
This is according to the
man who killed Palmer.
I heard his
dying confession.
You'll find his body
at the refinery,
just north of the city,
at Variel and Topanga.
Chloe, do you have evidence
that Palmer's assassination
has anything to do
with the summit?
No. Jack's trying to
figure all that out.
BUCHANAN:
How? Where is he?
I can't tell you.
Why not?
Because I don't think
you believe him.
I think you're just
trying to arrest him.
Chloe, I'm not going
to ask you again.
I'm ordering you
to tell me where Jack is.
I'm sorry; I'd like
to tell you, but I can't.
Chloe!
JENNINGS:
Sir?
Bring her back to CTU.
Curtis, take a team
to the refinery.
See what you can find there.
Edgar, make sure
Chloe goes into
a holding cell
when she gets back.
That woman, Chloe...
she told me some stuff
about what you used to do.
( ghs )
Yeah, well, she shouldn't have.
Why did you have to lie?
Couldn't you have just
told us the truth?
First of all, Derek,
you have to understand
that I never thought anything
like this could ever happen.
After your mother
rented me that room,
I started to remember what
it was like to have a family.
( gentle laugh )
How nice it was.
I started to believe
that a guy like me
could actually get
a second chance.
I know you don't
believe this now...
but I really do care
about you.
And I care about
your mother.
I hope, one day,
you can understand that.
MARTHA:
Charles?
Evelyn said you wanted
to talk to me?
I do.
Did Walt find the tape
of the phone call?
I told him approximately
when it took place.
Why don't we sit down?
No. I don't want to sit down.
All right.
You don't need
to be concerned
that there's
any connection
between David's death
and the phone call
that he made to you.
He said it was a matter
of national security.
Those were
his exact words.
There's got to be
a connection, of course.
There isn't.
David was killed
by an unstable
ex-CTU agent.
This was not a conspiracy.
This was one man acting out
some kind of grudge.
Did you hear the call?
Marty, can we just drop this?
Did you or didn't you hear it?!
Martha, it's David Palmer.
Did I wake you?
MARTHA:
No, no, David, not at all.
What's going on?
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter
of national security,
but I'm hosting
a charity nner next month
for the Art in Action
Scholarship Program.
That sounds wonderful.
No. That's not what he said.
I would very much like you
No. That's not
what he said.
and the President
to be there.
Okay, David.
No, that is not it.
That is not it, Charles.
That's not it.
Thanks so much
for calling.
Let me...
Martha, listen!
Thank you, Martha.
Of course.
Please send
the president my best.
No, that's not...
that's not what he said.
Yes, it is.
No, that is...
that is a trick.
Listen to me...
I am not crazy.
Marty... Martha!
I know
what I heard!
I know what I heard.
I spoke to Dr. Hill.
He said if you were
not consistent
with your medication,
you could become
disoriented.
Your memory can
be affected.
He said that?
Yes!
That's why you remember
something different.
I know you don't like
how these pills
make you feel,
but you need to take them.
( sighs )
If Jack was responsible
for President Palmer's
assassination,
why would Chloe
cover for him?
It just doesn't make sense.
There's something else
going on here,
and we're missing it.
NSA just intercepted
some chatter
identifying the summit
as a target.
We're sourcing it now,
but the reliability
is approaching 95%.
Is there a timeframe?
Within the next 15 minutes.
That's when the Russian
president is scheduled to land.
President Logan said he
will not postpone this summit.
In light of this,
he may not have a choice.
Put me through to Mike Novick.
NATHANSON:
I'm watching Suvarov's
helicopter leave the airbase.
His arrival at the retreat
is on schedule.
As are we.
We'll go dark now.
No communication
until after you strike.
I will monitor
yourrogress from here.
Understood.
( speaking foreign language )
Mr. President?
Yeah, Mike, what is it?
CTU has confirmed
intelligence suggesting
President Suvarov's helicopter
will be targeted.
How good is this
intelligence?
Very good. They're updating
their recommendation
that you delay
or reschedule.
No. I've told them,
I'm telling you.
I will not postpone this summit!
Then at least have Suvarov
alter his arrival plan.
His chopper can land
at a different site
and he can be brought here
by motorcade.
The risk would be
substantially reduced.
And the impact of his arrival
would also be reduced.
I've got the media
waiting for a landing
five minutes from now!
Mr. President...
I don't want to
hear it, Walt.
It's up to Secret Service
and the Air Force
to protect our airspace!
Make sure they do the job.
There's your mom.
Hey.
I'm sorry about the way
I treated you earlier.
You're a good kid.
Go get your mom.
Mom?!
Oh, my God!
Oh, are you okay?
I was so worried!
I'm sorry.
You got to tell me
right now what the hell
is going on here, Frank.
My name's not Frank.
It's Jack Bauer.
I lied to you.
I lied to you
about a lot of things.
I'll explain as soon as I can,
but right now,
you and Derek need
to go to this address.
"CTU"?
Counterterrorist Unit.
I used to work there.
You need to ask for a man
named Bill Buchanan.
Tell him I sent you.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
When we get there,
what do we tell him?
Tell him the truth.
Where can I find the
Baggage Claim Supervisor?
Down that hall
to the left.
Thank you.
DOD is still giving
us the all clear
on the air space
and the retreat.
Any word from our agents
on the ground?
Okay.
I'm all quiet so far.
But if they're going
to attack the helicopter,
it's going to be now.
Hi, Mr. President...
Our intel must have been wrong.
Mom, do you see
those men?
Yeah.
That's where Jack went.
Something's wrong.
I have to tell Jack.
Derek, where
are you going?
Come back here!
Derek! Come back here!
Derek!
Come back here!
Wait! Excuse me!
I've got to get my son!
No! You...
Get off!
You can't...
Please move your car.
I've got to get
my son.
Derek!
Get back in!
Chevensky!
Why was President Palmer
killed?!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
( grunting )
You are going to tell me
what I want to know.
It's just a question
of how much you want it to hurt.
( gasps )
No!
( screaming )
( automatic gunfire continues )
( screaming continues )
Quiet!
( screaming stops )
You will not be harmed
as long as your president
complies with our wishes.
Derek!
Ma'am, stop!
I have to get my son!
You need to go
the other way.
My son!
Go the other way.
This is a dangerous
situation.
I have to get my son!
CUMMINGS:
I have dealt with
the Martha Logan situation.
She's not going to be a problem?
No. I was able to alter
the tape of the phone call
before the president
heard it.
There's no longer any evidence
on my end
that Palmer was trying
to warn her about the attack.
Good.
The terminal and the hostages
are secure.
It'll only be a matter of time
until the president
is notified of the demands.
All right.
www.tvsubtitles.net