As soon as I get the recording,
we're going to have
to involve your father.
You know I don't like
to be kept in the dark.
Tell me what this is all about.
I will. I just
need a minute.
I decide what needs
to be done, Mr. Anderson.
I never authorized you
to kill David Palmer.
President Logan?
And a man named
Christopher Henderson.
I know what you did.
I know what you're doing.
And I'm going
to put an end to it.
You asked to see me,
Mr. President?
Hal, I'm asking Secretary Heller
to tender his resignation
and I wanted you
here as a witness.
What?!
He came here to accuse me
of being complicit
in today's
terrorist attacks.
Miles set me up.
Please come with us,
Ms. O'Brian.
We traced your call
to a public phone
at Van Nuys Airport.
If Audrey Raines is
at that location,
you're in a lot of trouble.
You're supposed
to be in custody.
You helped Audrey Raines
break surveillance.
You're sick and you need help
and if you try to stop me,
I will recommend you for
psychiatric evaluation.
I haven't been able
to contact Jack or Audrey.
I haven't talked
to them either.
Whatever you tell me will remain
between the two of us.
I promise you.
Not here.
Outside the south stable.
Is Bauer dead?
Not yet, Mr. President.
He has the recording.
Yes, sir.
That evidence directly
implicates me
in David Palmer's death.
Son of a bitch.
What the hell's going on?!
They've come
for the recording.
Audrey!
I have her, Jack!
JACK:
What have you done to her?
The left
brachial artery.
She has about three minutes
before she bleeds to death.
Now throw me
that recording.
Jack, don't do it.
She's running out of time.
AUDREY:
Don't give it up.
Here it is.
Stay with me.
( panting )
I need to loosen
the tourniquet.
Oh! Ooh!
Good. The bleeding's stopped,
which means he didn't sever
the brachial artery.
I need to get you
to a doctor.
Jack,
I can wait.
Do what you have to do.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Keep your arm
elevated.
( panting )
( touch tone beeping )
FEMALE VOICE:
Chloe O'Brian is not available.
Chloe's not picking
up her phone.
Is there someone else who can
help you track Henderson?
No one who has the same access
to the CTU satellite network.
Jack, I'm so sorry.
This is my fault.
Audrey, stop it.
( phone ringing )
I'll be right back.
( ringing continues )
This is Jack Bauer.
Jack?
Why are you answering
Wexler's phone?
Wexler's dead.
Henderson and a commando unit
attacked us 15 minutes ago.
They killed all your men and
took the recording back.
Is Audrey all right?
She's fine.
Did you cut your
deal with Logan?
Logan accepted my terms.
Then he took a call,
and suddenly changed his mind.
That call must have come
from Henderson.
Jack, we have to get
the recording back.
If there's anything I can do
to help, let me know.
With all due respect,
Mr. Secretary,
I asked you for your help,
and you betrayed me.
Jack, I did what I thought
was best for this country.
I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
I need to go, sir.
( panting )
( touch tones beeping )
( phone ringing )
Hello?
Bill, it's Jack.
Jack, we've been waiting
to hear from you.
Did you get the recording
to Secretary Heller?
I don't have
time to explain.
Henderson's got
the recording.
I need Chloe
to help me find him,
but I can't reach her.
Chloe's here
with me, Jack.
She was arrested
by Homeland Security
for helping you, but
she managed to get away.
Put her on speaker.
Jack, where are you?
I'm at Van Nuys Airfield.
Chloe, listen to me.
Henderson left here
ten minutes ago with a recording
that implicates President Logan.
I need you to access CTU's
satellite data streams
so that we can find him.
If I log onto their system,
they're gonna find me
eventually, no matter what I do.
I don't need you
to track him for long.
Do you think you can do it?
I guess I can try
to slip in through the subnets.
Get back to me when you're in.
I'll set up a VPN pathway, so
that they can't trace our call,
but it will only work
with the phone you're using.
Okay. I got a hold
of Chloe. We need to go.
Okay.
Can you get up?
Yeah.
Slowly.
( groans )
Come on.
If we're going to do
extensive satellite tracking,
I need more
than my laptop.
I'm gonna have to network
onto your computer, even though
it's kind of pathetic, and
I need you to get that screen
to work for me.
All right.
I hope you don't mind me
bossing you around,
but technically,
I don't work for you anymore.
That's all right, Chloe.
Good.
( phone ringing )
( soft groan )
Oh.
Bauer.
Jack, I'm pulling up
satellite footage
of the airfield
from 15 minutes ago.
Look for an explosion
in the northwest corner.
Okay, I see it.
About five minutes after that,
a vehicle leaves the airfield.
That'll be Henderson.
He went south
on the service drive, and east
on Menders, then I lose him
on the grid.
Use another satellite,
traffic cams,
whatever you have to,
just find him.
It's gonna take us
a few minutes.
We're just setting up,
but we're on it.
Copy that.
Get back to me as soon
as you got him on a live feed.
( engine starting )
( tires squealing )
( groans )
What makes you think that
Henderson hasn't already
destroyed the recording?
He would have done it
immediately, in front of me.
Given me less of a reason
to come after him.
Why would he keep it?
It's his insurance.
( phone ringing )
Yes.
Is Bauer dead?
No.
What happened?
All that matters is
that I have the recording.
Have you destroyed it?
No, sir, I have not.
Why, what's the problem?
Actually, I'm making sure
they're won't be any problems.
I don't understand.
I may need protection.
That recording
gives it to me.
Protection?
Yes, sir.
Do you mean from me?
That's absurd.
With all due respect,
Mr. President,
it isn't absurd, as evidenced
by Walt Cummings suicide.
That was different.
You told me yourself
that was necessary.
And I'm assuming
that one day,
others will tell you
the very same thing about me.
Chris,
you and I have been in
this from the beginning.
Destroying
that recording
protects both of us.
I'm sorry,
Mr. President.
I give you my word it will be
kept in a very place safe,
and will only be made public
should I meet
with some... accident.
Chris, this is completely
unnecessary.
I'm sure it is, sir.
Then again,
I am a very cautious man.
( phone ringing )
Chloe, have you
got Henderson yet?
Yes, his car is
three quarters
of a mile in
front of you.
He had a head start.
He should be farther
along than that.
I don't know
what to tell you.
It's definitely the car
he left the airport in.
How long until
I've got a visual?
The road curves up
ahead, Jack.
You should be able to see him
once it straightens out.
Hold on.
( tires squealing )
Got him.
( engine revving )
( tires squealing )
( thudding )
( door squeaking )
( tires squealing )
Get down.
( chamber clicks empty )
Damn!
It's over, Christopher.
Turn around!
Put the gun down and keep
your hands where I can them.
Do it or I will kill you!
You kill me, Jack,
Secretary Heller dies, too.
What are you talking about?
There's always a contingency
plan, Jack. You know that.
My men have been tracking Heller
from a chopper ever since
he left Logan's Retreat.
Now, if I can't
contact them
every 15 minutes on the dot,
they have orders
to kill Secretary Heller.
Which means,
you got about
three minutes to save his life.
Jack?
Audrey, please get back
in the car.
Is he lying about my father?
Slowly walk towards me.
Put your hands
behind your head.
Get on your knees.
Cuff yourself.
( touch tones beeping )
Yeah, Jack.
Chloe, patch me through to
Secretary Heller's cell phone.
See if you can get a satellite
to lock on his signal.
I need you to download a visual
of his vehicle on my PDA.
He was leaving Logan's retreat
just before 1:00.
On it. Open up the parallel
channel on the NSA's landsats,
can radial slices
in three mile increments,
emanating from the
Retreat... sir.
Okay, Jack, I'm pulling up
the DOD database.
Here it is,
I'm patching you through.
Copy that.
( phone ringing through )
( phone ringing )
Heller.
Mr. Secretary, it's Jack.
I need you to confirm for me
if a helicopter's been
tracking your vehicle?
What's going on, Jack?
Sir, time is critical.
Is there a helicopter
above you or not?
Yeah, there's a chopper
above me.
Who are they?
Henderson's men.
He claims he's given them orders
to kill you
if I don't let him go.
Is he bluffing?
He doesn't do that, sir.
CHLOE:
Jack, I've got Heller's car.
I'm patching it
through to your PDA.
Copy that.
( helicopter propeller
whirring )
Jack... they have a laser sight
trained on me.
Get up.
You give me the recording,
I let you go: that's the deal.
No.
Come on, Jack,
you're wasting time.
We both know you're not going
to let Heller die.
I can hear him, Jack;
don't let him do this.
I'm going to walk
out of here, Jack,
and you're not gonna stop me,
so uncuff me.
Jack, don't let him go.
I don't have
a choice, sir.
Yes, you do.
If I had listened to you
in the first place,
none of this would be happening.
This is my responsibility,
I will not allow Logan and
Henderson to use me as a pawn.
Sir?
Do not let them
get away with this.
Make sure that the recording
gets to the right people.
Tell Audrey I love her.
Mr. Secretary,
what are you doing?!
No.
( engine revving )
( helicopter propeller
whirring )
JACK:
Chloe, are you still
on the line?!
Can you confirm that Heller
just drove his car
into the lake?
Yes.
Damn you!
Oh, my God, no.
How could you do this?
This isn't about what you think
is best for the country.
This is about your greed
for power.
Today, you have been
responsible
for killing an ex-president,
David Palmer,
and the secretary of defense,
two real patriots.
Damn you!
What happened to you?
Give me the recording.
I don't have it.
Where is it?!
I'm not going to
tell you, Jack.
and you know that-- no
matter what you do to me.
AUDREY:
Do it.
Kill him, Jack. Do it!
MAN:
Yeah.
Graham?
Yes.
You need to cancel the action
against Henderson immediately.
Why?
He has the recording,
but he's made arrangements
to have it released
if anything happens to him.
You should have exercised
more control over him.
There's a limit
to how much I can do.
Apparently.
Don't.
Don't you use that tone with me.
We've both made mistakes today.
You're right, Mr. President,
my apologies,
but the fact is, I think we have
a bigger problem than Henderson.
What? What are you
talking about?
At least he can be trusted
to act rationally,
in his own interest.
Unfortunately, the same
is not true of your wife.
My wife.
Apparently,
there's a secret service agent
named Aaron Pierce
who knows a little more
than he should.
He intends to share that
with Martha.
I'm well aware of that,
and I've taken steps
to deal with Agent Pierce.
But the real problem
is Mrs. Logan.
She continues to talk,
to ask questions,
talk about her suspicions.
People don't take her seriously.
They think she's unstable.
There are too many loose ends
lying around.
We cannot afford to have her
pull on one
and unravel everything.
You think
I don't realize that?
I think you're in a very
difficult position
and that you have been hoping
the situation with Martha
would resolve itself,
but it hasn't.
You must silence her.
I know.
But I'll handle this myself.
( flips phone shut )
MAN:
Mrs. Logan,
Agent Pierce
was transferred.
That's what you keep saying,
but it doesn't make any sense,
not at 1:00 in the morning.
We work around the clock, ma'am.
It's quite common
for agents
to get pulled off
details at odd hours.
Right when they're supposed
to have a meeting
with the First Lady
of the United States?
I don't know anything
about a meeting.
Well, I do!
I found Aaron's phone
laying on the ground,
right where we were
supposed to meet.
Now, I want you
to find Agent Pierce,
and I want you to get him
back here, right now!
There's a glitch in
the scheduling software,
I can not pull that
record up right now.
And are these glitches
quite common, as well?
Actually, no, but...
Mrs. Logan.
I'm Agent Adams.
I think I can
explain everything.
Well?
This is a sensitive
issue, ma'am.
President Logan would like you
to come with me.
Ma'am.
What is this
"sensitive" information?
Is it about
Agent Pierce?
I'm sorry-- you need to talk
to the president about that.
I'm asking you.
Do you know
where Aaron Pierce is?
No, ma'am, I don't.
Is this where my husband is?
I want to talk to him.
Charles?
Hello?
( dialing )
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
Henderson wasn't lying.
He doesn't have the recording
on him.
Could it be in his car?
No, he wouldn't
have left it behind.
There must have been
some kind of a hand-off.
What do you mean?
Well, that would
explain why he wasn't
any farther ahead of me.
when I left Van Nuys Airfield.
He must have stopped
and given it to someone.
Okay, I'll back trace the route
with the satellite,
see if I can spot anything.
Yeah.
Jack, we're getting that
recording and exposing Logan.
I don't care
how far I have to go
or what I have to do,
Do you understand, Jack?
Yes.
( phone rings )
Go ahead.
Jack, you were right,
I found the hand-off.
Henderson stopped and
rendezvoused with another car.
I'm sorry
I didn't see it before.
Can you track the other car?
BUCHANAN:
We're tracking
it now, Jack.
It headed back to Van Nuys.
Looks like the civilian
side of the airfield.
Pulled onto the tarmac.
Whoever was in it got out
and got directly onto the plane.
Isn't air traffic
still grounded?
Yeah, this is not
a commercial flight.
I'll find out what I can
about it.
CHLOE:
Jack, the plane is servicing.
It's about to take off.
Has Curtis been relieved
of his duty,
or is he still attached to CTU?
He's at CTU, taking orders
from Homeland Security,
but I think we can
trust him, Jack.
Where is he?
According to the
deployment grid,
he's 25 miles northwest
of you, with a tac team.
Bill, I want you to call him.
Get him to this location as soon
as possible.
I want him to transfer Henderson
and Audrey back to CTU.
Are you sure
that's a good idea?
Logan's in control at CTU.
Curtis will be able
to protect them.
Right now, it's our best
chance to secure Henderson
and get Audrey the medical
attention she needs.
Calling Curtis now, Jack.
Thanks.
What's happening?
The person Henderson
gave the recording to
just boarded a plane
at Van Nuys Airfield.
Why aren't you going now?
I'll go as soon as Curtis
gets here-- he's not far.
Jack, I'll be fine until then.
I'm not leaving you here alone.
Jack, if you don't get
that recording,
my father will have died
for nothing.
Jack...
for me.
Henderson is secure.
When he regains
consciousness,
I don't want you going
anywhere near him.
You don't even talk to him.
You understand me?
I understand.
We have to assume his people
are still looking for him.
They're gonna be monitoring
all non-VPN cell traffic,
which means, you can't make
or receive any calls
unless they come from me.
Here's Wexler's cell.
I've got the number.
All right.
Audrey, I don't feel right
about this.
I'm going to be all right.
I'm so sorry.
Jack, you have to go now.
Jack?
Make sure you get
that recording.
I will.
Let me know as soon
as you're done.
Vladimir Bierko has
regained consciousness.
But we're still waiting
for the medical assessment
to be finished before we can
begin the interrogation.
Let me know when they
give us the go ahead.
Final protocol shifts.
You can tell Washington
the transfer of authority
from CTU to Homeland
is officially complete.
Okay.
Two hours
ahead of schedule, Karen.
That is remarkable.
I'm sorry,
my head is
somewhere else.
Where?
We gave the President
Bauer's location
over an hour ago.
We should have
heard something by now.
The military authority
is handling Bauer.
Yes, I know, but this
doesn't make any sense.
The President insisted
we redirect our focus
from Henderson to Bauer.
We find Bauer, and then
he hands the mission
over to the military.
Karen, we're out of that loop.
( phone ringing )
( beep )
Karen Hayes.
Ma'am, we have a problem.
Chloe O'Brian got
out of holding,
and as far as I can tell,
she's not in the building.
MILES:
Not in the building?
How's that possible?
I'm still gathering
the details.
But I reviewed the surveillance
tape, and it looks like
Shari had a conversation with
her, and Shari let her go.
Shari didn't try
to stop her? Why?
I don't know. She
won't tell me.
I had security take
her into custody.
Good. Bring her up
here right now.
We need to focus on
how we find Chloe now.
My guess is
she'll try to contact Bauer.
I agree, but how?
She was using CTU resources
before to help Bauer.
Maybe she'll try that again.
Which means
she could try to access
our system remotely.
All she needs is a laptop.
That's right.
She'll disguise
her traffic.
Can you get through that?
I can trace
her physical location
by looking at the binaries.
Do it.
HAYES:
Wait outside.
Why did you let Chloe escape?
She intimidated me.
She intimidated you?
Sit down.
You are in a great deal trouble,
Miss Rothenberg.
You had better
start talking
to me now.
She said she'd recommend me
for psychiatric evaluation.
I'd lose my job.
I'm sorry, Miss Hayes.
There's something wrong with me,
I know that.
Shari...
And I should probably
see someone...
Shari!
Did Chloe tell you why she was
helping Audrey Raines and Bauer?
She thinks Jack is innocent.
Based on what?
Based on some
absurd idea
that President Logan
framed Bauer.
She even said something about
President Logan being involved
in the assassination
of David Palmer.
I mean, can you believe her?
And people think
I'm crazy.
MARTHA:
Damn it, open
this door!
MARTHA:
I don't know
what you think you're doing,
but you'd better
think again!
Unlock it.
MARTHA:
Open it!
( pounding )
Charles.
I want that man arrested!
And I want know
where Aaron Pierce is.
Shh.
Martha, calm down.
All right?
Aaron's fine.
I just transferred him
back to Washington, that's all.
In the middle of the night?
Doesn't make any sense.
And why am I
locked in this room?
'Cause we need to talk.
About what?
Martha, I've been
wanting to tell you this,
but I told myself
that you were
too fragile to handle it.
But that's not the truth.
The truth is,
I've kept this from you
because it's horrible
and because it's ugly.
What are you talking about?
What happened to David Palmer
wasn't supposed to happen.
He put himself in harm's way,
and he got involved
with something
that he shouldn't have.
What are you saying?
That I never authorized
his death.
You... mean...
you know who killed David?
Yes.
How do you know that?
He works for me.
What?
Martha,
it's very complicated.
What?!
There's an explanation.
What?! An explanation?!
Oh, my God!
Stop!
Go to hell!
Stop! You don't understand!
Oh, my God!
You're involved
in David's murder.
Martha...
Oh, my God,
oh, my God.
( sobbing ):
Why are you
telling me this?
Because you're on your way
to finding out
the truth on your own.
( sobbing )
And because you need to stop.
Stop what?
You have to stop
asking questions,
you have to stop
talking about this to everyone.
Never again.
Martha, do you realize
how traumatic this would be
for the country
if people were to find out?
Oh, yes, we're worried
about the country.
Damn it, Martha!
That's the most important
part of this!
This scandal would destroy
the American people's faith
in their government.
It would destroy our credibility
all over the world.
You lied to me.
Everything.
This whole day has
been one giant lie.
What you've done
makes me sick!
Martha, enough!
I know
that what I did, what I allowed
to happen, was a mistake.
It was a terrible mistake.
But it's done.
Right now, I need
you to swear to me
that you will do as I ask...
for the country, Martha.
I've forgiven you
many things, Charles,
but not this.
You've broken my heart.
I'm looking at you...
I hate you.
But I will keep my mouth shut.
Because the people
of this country
don't deserve to suffer.
You do, Charles.
RON:
Are you sure we're going to get
through this the way we planned?
What does that mean?
There's too many loose ends.
What operation
doesn't have loose ends?
Of course we're not
going to get through this
the way we planned.
No one ever does.
I have never made a deal
in my life that didn't feel like
it was going to fall apart
in the 11th hour.
Now, if you don't
have the stomach
to deal with
a few bumps,
then this is not the room
where you belong.
And that goes for all of you.
GRAHAM:
You're starting
to have doubts.
I can smell it,
and I don't like it.
You need to remember
the strength we had
18 months ago
when we started this thing.
We okay, Ron?
Yeah.
Think about your kids.
That's what I do
when I need to get focused.
Yeah?
The situation with Martha
is taken care of.
I spoke to her.
And?
And I made it very clear
that if she continues
with this behavior,
I will send her back
to the hospital in Vermont.
Well, you were going to have
her committed earlier today.
But you changed
your mind?
It's because
she found out the truth.
And I decided
I should keep her close.
What if she finds out
the truth again?
She won't.
And if she does,
I will handle it,
just like I
have all day.
Okay.
Fair enough.
You have done a remarkable job
today, Mr. President.
I will admit that.
Thank you.
It's about time I heard
some words of appreciation.
Oh, listen to me,
we were just talking about
how you've had to be
on the front line through this,
how you've had to get
your hands dirty,
while we could just sit back
and watch from a safe distance.
You've earned our trust.
And I am sure...
that you will do whatever it
takes to keep your wife in line.
Audrey.
Where's Jack?
I'm sorry about your father.
I never intended
your father to get
in the middle of this.
I've known Secretary Heller
a very long time.
He's an honorable man.
What time is it?
It's ten to 12 minutes since...
If those windows didn't collapse
when that car
hit the water,
it could have created an
air pocket or something.
20, 30 minutes in a submerged
car, even at 100 feet,
if there was
an air pocket.
Stop it.
Your father could be alive.
( straining )
Secretary...
Secretary Heller could be
alive inside that car.
If he's alive, you got to do
something about it.
I mean, if there's
a possibility
that he's living,
you got to call
military authority
or the emergency
services or something.
I mean, for God's sake,
he's your father.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop talking!
What, do you think I'm stupid?
You want me
to make that phone call
so that your people can find me.
Audrey, my people
are going to find us anyway.
And Jack's not
going to stop all this.
I'm trying to help your father.
Your father's drowning
in a car, and you're not
doing anything
about it.
You're gonna live with that
the rest of
your life.
Shut up.
He is dying,
and you are doing
nothing, Audrey.
You are doing nothing.
I swear to God,
not another word.
( cell phone ringing )
Yeah?
Jack.
I've got a visual on the plane.
It must be some kind
of diplomatic flight.
There's a lot of security
on the ground.
We have a problem.
What?
I've been tracking
the helicopter
that Henderson's men used
to shadow
Secretary Heller.
And?
It changed course,
it's heading towards where
Audrey's holding Henderson.
How could they find them?
CHLOE:
I don't know--
maybe they're using
satellite imagery, too.
The point is, they're going
to be there any second.
Where's Curtis?
Based on the speed
of the chopper,
he might not make it there
before Henderson's men, Jack.
Upload your visual to my PDA.
Advise Curtis of the situation,
I'll get back to you.
( speed dialing )
( cell phone ringing )
Jack?
Audrey,
listen to me.
Henderson's men have
zeroed in on your location,
they're heading
back towards you.
You've got to get
out of there now.
And just leave him?
JACK:
We don't have a choice.
Yes, we do, Jack.
I have the gun
and I can kill him.
Audrey, we need him alive.
Curtis's team is almost there,
they'll track him down
and they will secure him.
You've got to get out of there.
AUDREY:
Jack, he's responsible
for the death of
my father's death.
I can't just leave him here!
JACK:
Audrey, please,
listen to what I'm telling you.
You've got to start moving now.
Audrey!
HENDERSON:
Stipes, get over
and get these handcuffs off me.
( metal clanking )
Heller's daughter's
somewhere in this
building-- kill her.
Then get back here,
we'll deal with Bauer.
( muffled shriek )
( whispering ):
Audrey, it's me.
Stay down.
( gunfire stops )
Secure him for transport
back to CTU.
You okay?
Yeah.
CURTIS:
Hostiles are down
and we have
Henderson in custody.
( sniffling )
( speed dialing )
( cell phone rings )
Yeah?
AUDREY:
It's me.
What's happening?
Curtis's team killed
Henderson's men
and they're taking Henderson
into custody.
Jack, I tried to shoot him,
but I couldn't.
The only thing
that matters is
that you're safe.
I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Let me speak to Curtis.
Curtis?
It's Jack.
Go ahead.
Yeah, Jack?
Curtis, I want you to transport
Audrey back to CTU
as quickly as possible.
And get her over to Medical.
And I want you
to tell Karen Hayes
that no one is have access
to Christopher Henderson.
CURTIS:
She'll be taken care of.
But as far as Henderson goes,
CTU is more interested
in apprehending you
than taking your advice.
Just do what you can.
I'll get back to you.
( speed dialing )
( phone ringing )
( speakerphone beeps )
Jack, is Audrey
all right?
JACK:
Yeah, she's gonna be fine.
Curtis is in control
of the situation.
Chloe, what have you got
on the plane?
The details
just came in.
You were right, it is
a chartered diplomatic flight,
security-level eight,
scheduled to leave
at 2:00 A.M. or sooner.
Okay, we need
to find out
who's onboard
so we can try
and figure out
who Henderson passed off
the recording to.
I'll try-- it's not
going to be easy
getting past the
State Department's
firewall.
I understand.
Bill, see if you could slow down
the departure of this flight
so I can figure out
a way to get on it.
All right, Jack.
There's a maintenance gate
on the northwest side
of the airfield.
You should be able to get
close to the plane there.
I know, I'm there.
Just get back to me
as soon as you've got
the passenger list.
GUARD:
All clear.
Go ahead.
( grunts softly )
Yeah?
Jack, we've tried
everything we can
there's no way
to delay the plane.
It's taking off in
less than ten minutes.
Okay.
Has Chloe got the
passenger list yet?
I still can't get past
the firewall.
Chloe, I need
that list.
Jack, I'm trying.
( phone snaps shut )
( computer chirps )
( snapping fingers ):
There you are.
( phone ringing )
Yeah?
I got O'Brian.
HAYES:
Did you find her on our system?
Yes, she's using one of
our nodes to try to log-in
to the State Department
network.
Do we know why?
No, but she was using a work
around I'd never seen before.
so I machine-coded a matrix
to get through...
Miles, we just
need to find her.
Where she is?
I'm running a physical trace.
It's a private house.
Cross-referencing
with property records.
( computer beeps )
Karen...
she's working out of
Bill Buchanan's house.
Are you sure?
Positive.
We have a Tac Team
not far away.
I'll dispatch them now.
What's their ETA?
I'm showing less then
seven minutes.
Good, keep me posted.
( speed dialing )
NOVICK:
Novick.
Mike, it's Karen Hayes.
Karen.
How are things going over there?
HAYES:
It's a rough transition
from CTU to Homeland,
but we're getting through it.
NOVICK:
That's good to hear.
What do you need?
I need some
clarification.
We were sent over here
on a directive
from the White House,
but we've been
dealing exclusively
with Vice President Gardner
until about two hours ago.
What happened
two hours ago?
The president called me himself
and ordered me
to arrest Jack Bauer
on evidence he was
unwilling to share with me.
Yes. I know about that.
Have you seen the evidence?
No, actually, I-I haven't.
HAYES:
Mike...
Who has seen it?
I don't have
a good answer for that.
Are you telling me
you're not in the loop?
Actually...
I don't even think
there is a loop.
The president is keeping his
own counsel at the moment.
That's a first.
Yes. It is.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
Uh, nothing that I can say
with any authority.
All I know is that...
it's been a strange night.
I see.
NOVICK:
I wish I could be more helpful.
No, Mike, actually,
you've been very helpful.
Thank you.
( dialing )
( phone ringing )
( speakerphone beeps )
Hello?
HAYES:
This is Karen Hayes.
You have less than seven minutes
to get Chloe out of there.
Karen, I don't
know what
you're talking about,
Chloe's not here.
Bill, stop.
Miles traced Chloe
through
a remote node
she's accessing.
And if you don't
believe me,
tell her he used a machine-coded
matrix to find her.
Karen, why are you warning us?
Because I may have made
a mistake earlier.
A lot of things have
not made sense today,
until Shari told me
what Chloe said.
About President Logan
being... involved.
I've got to go.
Just get out of there, now.
Chloe, we have to go.
I can't leave yet.
Jack needs the
passenger list.
Chloe, if they find you here,
you'll be arrested.
You have to go now!
Not yet.
It's the last one!
Let's get this thing
out of here.
( mechanical door whirring )
www.tvsubtitles.net