( crying )
Your wife survived the attack.
Thank God.
LOGAN:
I should never have given in.
I should have ordered back
the motorcade.
The terrorist attack failed.
We have to assume
they'll make good
on their threat to use
the Sentox nerve gas
on American soil.
Listen, I-I made
a mistake.
I didn't think that
I had any choice.
MARTHA:
You didn't stand up to them.
You saved my life.
You're welcome.
Country's lucky
to have men like you.
I'm lucky.
Mrs. Logan?
Christopher Henderson
was responsible for setting up
the deal that allowed
the terrorists
to gain control of the Sentox.
He left me for dead.
BUCHANAN:
Right now,
Henderson is our primary link.
JACK:
You are going
to tell me now
how to find
the rest of the nerve gas.
Do it, Jack.
Get it done.
Shoot me.
( gunshot )
( screaming )
Oh, you son of a bitch.
I shot her above the kneecap.
She can still walk.
Son of a bitch.
You make me shoot her again,
she'll be in a wheelchair
for the rest of her life.
Tell him what
he wants to know.
I can't.
I'm bringing
Christopher Henderson
into CTU.
I'm sorry...
I need an interrogation room
prepped.
I don't care
that you took my wallet.
I just need
to get my keycard back.
It's of no value to you.
It just lets me in and out
of this building.
JENNY:
Okay, you told me
we were just going to take
his cash and a credit card.
That's how I'm getting us
all this money.
$20,000 line
of credit
right here.
Who's going to pay you
that kind of money?
( gunshot )
( screams )
I have the keycard.
BIERKO:
How long will it take for you
to reprogram it?
Five minutes, and then
we will be able to use it
to access CTU.
Good.
* *
BIERKO:
Yes.
I'm reprogramming
the CTU keycard right now.
Will it work?
I need to change the ID,
but preserve McGill's
executive entry privileges.
It won't be a problem.
Good.
Our couriers are delivering
the canisters to the targets.
They'll be in place soon.
When are you
launching your attacks?
After you're done at CTU.
I'm a few minutes out.
Call me when you're there.
Understood.
( beeps )
( keyboard clicking )
BUCHANAN:
We were able
to neutralize the attack
on the hospital, sir.
Good.
Do we have any idea
what the terrorists'
next target might be?
We're working with federal
and state authorities
to harden security
around the highest-value targets
in Los Angeles.
In other words, no.
We're completely in the dark.
We're just sitting around,
waiting for Bierko
to hit us again.
We do have one
promising lead, sir.
Jack Bauer was able to recapture
the man who escaped,
Christopher Henderson.
Henderson was
a defense contractor
who brokered the sale
of the nerve gas to Bierko.
Is this the same
Christopher Henderson
who worked at CTU?
Yes, sir. He was head
of Field Ops,
until Jack brought him down
on corruption charges.
And this Henderson knows
how to find Bierko?
We believe so,
but he's not cooperating.
Jack's bringing him in
for further interrogation.
Keep me posted
on any progress.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Buchanan,
Tony Almeida's
been asking to see you
down in the Clinic.
I don't have time right now.
Tell him I'll get to him
as soon as I can.
And, Ms. Raines.
Kim Bauer is here.
She's just
clearing Security.
Put her in the Field Ops Office,
please.
Yes, ma'am.
BUCHANAN:
What's Kim Bauer doing here?
Jack asked me to call her.
Does she know?
Not yet.
Who's with her?
I don't know,
but I'll find out
from Security.
Excuse me.
( touch tone beeping )
( phone ringing )
This is Bauer.
Hey, it's me.
Is Burke prepped
for the medical
interrogation?
Yes.
Jack, Kim just
arrived at CTU.
What did you say to her?
Nothing yet.
Good. I want her
to hear it from me.
Jack, it might be easier for her
if she knows that you're alive
before she sees you.
When I first saw you...
It's-it's just...
Yeah, I know.
I-I... I understand.
Look, when you talk to her,
just explain that the reason why
I couldn't tell her
I was still alive was 'cause
I was trying to protect her.
Of course, I will.
Audrey, thank you.
Kim's at CTU right now.
You know, after you died,
Chase left her,
and she hit bottom.
Did you know that?
It's only right now she's
putting her life back together.
Or maybe you did know that,
but you just couldn't
do anything about it, huh?
This doesn't concern you.
Oh, I think
it concerns me, Jack.
Miriam and I were there
for Kim when you weren't.
Whatever you think of me,
we love that girl.
Are you okay?
( sighs )
Both my parents died here.
I swore I'd never come back
to this place.
Well, we can leave
right now if you want.
Here, she's coming.
Kim.
Hi.
This is Barry Landes.
Audrey Raines.
So, what is it?
What did you have to tell me
that was so important?
I-I think it would be better
if we talked in private.
Whatever you have to say, you
can say it in front of Barry.
Kim, I really think
that that this...
No, no, it's-it's okay.
It's about your father.
What about my father?
He's alive.
Kim, he wanted to tell
you, but he couldn't,
in order to
protect you.
Someone inside the
government wanted
your father dead,
so he staged
his own death and
went underground.
He knew that you
wouldn't be safe
if he told you
that he was alive.
I didn't know either
until this morning.
I thought maybe if I told you
now before you saw him,
it might be a
little bit easier.
He's on his way
in now to CTU.
Hello, Mike.
Mr. Vice President.
I thought you were
in Salt Lake City today.
Hal canceled his engagements
to be here, Mike.
I think you'll agree
we need all hands on deck
to deal with this
Sentox situation.
Of course, Mr. President.
Okay.
So, what's on
your mind, Hal?
Mr. President,
when these terrorists attack,
you're going to need
to maintain order.
And I submit to you,
the plan you're
implementing with CTU
is inadequate.
Sir, it was drawn up
after a careful study
for an attack
of just this magnitude.
CTU is already coordinating
with first responders.
Fine, and they should
still do so.
But what I'm proposing
is something far more sweeping.
And I believe
it's warranted by the facts.
Andrew?
begin with,
I'm revising all
of CTU's casualty estimates,
based on the assumption
that the terrorists will hit
all of these high-profile
targets: hospitals,
malls,
sporting arenas,
transit hubs.
My low estimate is
400,000 casualties.
NOVICK:
Now, that's a considerable
upward revision.
I'd like to know
how you reached it.
Well, you're free to talk
to my working group.
You know, frankly,
I believe that
there are a lot of people
who don't take this threat
seriously enough.
I assure you
we're taking it very seriously.
We have no agenda
but to do so.
Considering these
revised numbers,
what's your
recommendation?
Well, I believe
you should be thinking
of a preemptive declaration
of martial law
in the greater
Los Angeles area.
NOVICK:
Mr. President,
martial law is
appropriate only
as a last-ditch
measure,
not as a preemptive one.
Go on.
Every study we've done
has shown it would
incite more unrest,
not less.
And you couldn't do it without
approval from Congress.
Which is why
we won't call it martial law.
No one is going
to play semantics here
when we're putting troops
on the street
to try to keep people
from killing each other.
You're talking about a panic
that hasn't happened.
Right now, the public
isn't even aware of a threat.
You declare martial law,
you'll have to tell them.
How long would it take
to deploy the troops?
I've already been in touch
with the Pentagon.
National Guard and Army units
are on standby, pending
your decision.
Mr. President, I-I agree
there's a case
to be made, but for God's sake,
let's make it to Congress.
We can declare
an emergency session...
We don't have
time, Mike.
Hal is right.
This-This attack
could take place
any minute.
If CTU can't find this man
Bierko, we're going
to get hit.
It would be smart
to have control of the streets.
This is a mistake, Jack.
You don't want
to do this.
Get out.
I'll get immediate
immunity if I talk.
You know it,
and I know it.
And I'm not even going
to ask for it.
Damn it, Jack.
Will you listen to me?
I'm not trying
to protect myself.
I'm trying to protect
this country.
What do you mean?
You don't want to
know what I know.
You get me to talk,
I promise you
you'll just be opening
Pandora's box.
Tell me, and let me
judge that for myself.
That's what I thought.
BURKE:
I'll set him up in Holding.
Let me know when he's ready
for interrogation.
Yes, sir.
Jack.
Keycard, please.
Oh. All clear, sir.
Yeah.
Okay, well, thanks.
That was Curtis;
he's on his way back
from the hospital.
Okay, good.
Audrey.
Did you speak to Kim?
Yes.
What was her reaction?
She's a little confused.
You should also know
that she's here with someone.
I think it might be
her boyfriend.
His name is Barry Landes.
Where is she?
She's in the Field Ops Office.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah.
Hey.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what you expect me
to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Why didn't you just tell me
you were alive?
I couldn't.
If you knew
I was alive,
you would
have been at risk.
I had no choice.
You could have chosen
to trust her.
I'd like to speak with
my daughter alone, please.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
I don't care what you think.
I'm sure you don't.
All that matters is you,
and the judgments you make.
Even if it affects
those that love you.
Kim.
Barry, please,
let me speak
to my dad.
I'll be right outside.
Don't judge him.
He was there
when no one else was.
The most painful thing
that I've ever been through
was having to walk away
from you.
Even more painful
than losing your mother.
But it was the only
way to make sure
that you would be safe.
I buried you.
I... I know.
( sighs )
You know, there's something
wrong with people like you.
You can't hold on
to anything.
Chase couldn't either.
He tried for a while,
and then he was gone,
just like you.
And now, you're back...
and I'm just supposed to...
I'm happy that you're alive.
I am.
But I can't give you
what you want right now.
Okay.
I understand that.
I need you to know
that I'm sorry, and I...
Please, just go.
Excuse me.
Burke needs you
in Holding.
I'll be there in a minute.
I've got to go.
Barry's got a conference.
We have a plane
to catch.
Please, Kimberly...
I want you to stay
just a little longer.
There are some things
that I still need to tell you.
Please?
I'll talk to Barry.
Fine.
I'll be right back.
* *
( fan whirring )
BUCHANAN:
You call for me, Tony?
Yeah.
What's going on?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
What do you mean?
What do you think
I mean, Bill?
My wife was killed this morning,
right in front of my eyes.
And nobody here has told me
who did it, or why.
The investigation
is ongoing, Tony.
Come on, Bill.
I used to work here.
I know that's what you say
to people when you don't want
to tell them the truth.
The truth is you're
not an agent anymore.
And what you're asking
me is classified.
Tony, it doesn't
matter what I tell you,
there's nothing you can do.
I know there's nothing I can do!
Look at me, for God's sake!
I just want to know who did it.
I think for the sake
of all the years
I've given this place,
and all the sacrifices I've made
I think, I deserve to know.
Don't you?
All I can tell you is...
Michelle's murder
was part of a bigger plan...
to supply terrorists
with Sentox nerve gas.
Who's behind it?
Who's responsible, Bill?
The highest we've been able
to get up the chain of command
is someone you might know
from when you worked here.
Christopher Henderson.
What?
Why?
We're working
on it, Tony.
Don't let him
get away with this, Bill.
Don't you let him cut a deal.
I won't.
What do we know about the man
who's with Kim?
He's registered
with the state as a
clinical psychologist.
She was his patient?
I think so, yes.
He's ready.
Whatever he's not telling us
is important.
He knows what's coming.
And he's willing tolerate
an inhuman amount of pain.
Open the door.
( door opens )
Damn it, Christopher.
I don't think
you became a part of this
because of self-interest.
I honestly believe
that you think
what you're doing right now
is the best thing
for this country,
but it is not your
choice to make.
That's good, Jack.
Disarm your subject's
resolve by showing empathy,
and respect for his agenda.
This is not a joke.
Thousands of lives are at stake.
people that we promised to
protect, to make feel safe.
There is enough time for you
to tell me what I need to know
to stop this insanity.
Please.
I'm sorry, Jack. I really am.
But I can't tell you
what you want to know.
Start it.
Mrs. Logan.
Mrs. Logan,
if I could have a minute.
If this is about Aaron,
it doesn't concern you.
No, Mrs. Logan, it doesn't.
And I'm not here to discuss it.
What is it?
The country's facing a crisis.
The President needs you.
( chuckles )
He, he needs me.
If you think the decision
to let the attack
on the motorcade proceed was
easy for him, you're wrong.
I was with him when he got
down on his knees and prayed.
He did?
He loves you.
He didn't want to lose you.
But with the lives of so
many people in jeopardy,
he felt he had no choice.
We've known each other
a long time, you and I.
Why don't you stop
talking about
what a positive
influence I am,
and tell me precisely
what it is
you're trying
to get me to do.
Vice President Gardner
is advising your husband
to declare martial law
in Los Angeles in preparation
for the release
of the nerve gas.
He wants to do it
without congressional sanction
or a timetable
to lift it.
He can't just rewrite the law.
Hal's got an agenda.
Well, he's wrong.
This will make things far worse.
Mrs. Logan,
all I know is,
the President is listening
to Hal Gardner.
And it will only
help the country
to have him
listening to you as well.
EDGAR:
No, hold off on deploying
units seven through 12
until we finalize
our target scenario.
What is it?
I was running
a channel clearance,
and I noticed that one
of the environmental systems
put out a trouble flag.
It's probably a tech crew
changing out a circuit board.
That's what I thought, but
I logged on to the manifest.
There's nothing scheduled.
Carrie, I'm in the middle
of coordinating with
first reonders.
We're on high alert; I
don't have time for this.
You don't have to snap at me.
I just thought
someone should check it out.
Then check it out.
Carrie.
( drilling )
Can you forgive me?
You acted like the President
of the United States.
Yes, I did.
But you wanted me to
be your husband first.
Can't pretend that I didn't.
But...
I still love you
as much as I always did.
Martha.
Shh.
There'll be plenty of time
for us later.
You have to get back to work.
The country needs you
more than I do.
Hello?
Anybody working on the system?
Chloe.
Hi, Kim.
You're still here.
Yeah.
Look, my father said that
he had to do something.
You know how long
he's gonna be?
No, sorry.
Chloe...
I'm kind of busy right now.
You knew my father
was alive, didn't you?
For a year and a half
you've known.
Yeah.
He trusted you.
Only because he had to;
I helped stage his death.
You don't have to make excuses.
I'm not making excuses.
Four people knew he was alive,
two of them are dead:
President Palmer,
and Michelle Dessler;
and Tony Almeida's
in serious condition.
Michelle's dead?
The only reason
I'm alive is
because your dad found me
in time.
I know this is
really hard for you,
and it's none of my business,
but you should try
to cut him some slack.
( door opens )
What's going on, Bill?
Lynn...
What is it?
We just got a call from LAPD.
They found your sister's body
in her apartment.
She'd been shot.
What?
I just talked to her.
I saw her today.
That's impossible. She can't...
I'm sorry.
The police ID'd her body.
My God.
If you need a phone
to make some personal calls
or talk to the police...
Her boyfriend did this to her.
Tell me he's
in custody.
Is his name Dwayne Thompkins?
Yeah.
He didn't do it.
They found his body, too.
Lynn, the police are trying
to make sense of something.
Do you know if either
your sister or her boyfriend
were involved
in dealing drugs,
or had ties to....
organized crime?
Uh...
She was a...
pretty serious user.
But organized crime--
no way. Why?
The killings were clearly
the work of a professional.
Oh, my God.
I need to see
preliminary forensics.
Who's investigating?
I have to talk to them.
I can arrange a meeting...
No, I have to talk
to them now.
They have to search
the apartment.
See if my keycard is there.
What are you talking about?
What keycard?
My CTU keycard!
She has it, Bill!
What was she doing
with your keycard?
It was stolen from me,
all right?
Her boyfriend took it.
Why didn't you
report this?
I'm reporting it now!
We don't have time
to argue about this.
Call and see if anybody
used it to breach security.
It was taken about...
about four hours ago.
( phone rings )
O'Brian.
Chloe, I'm in Holding with Lynn.
I need you to check
the gate logs, now.
What am I looking for?
Check and see if anyone
used Lynn's keycard
to enter CTU in
the last four hours.
Isn't Lynn standing
right next to you?
Chloe, do it!
Oh, my God.
It's showing
that his card was used
less than an hour ago
at the executive entrance.
He was already here...
Lockdown CTU now!
This is Chloe O'Brian.
Initiate a lockdown now.
Mr. Bauer, I'm sorry.
I don't know
what's going on.
He should be
talking by now.
Damn it, Christopher.
It's enough.
I don't want to do this.
Just talk to me!
( faintly ):
I can't...
His vitals are crashing.
I need to stabilize him
in the Clinic
before administering
another dose.
( alarm blaring )
( cell phone rings )
This is Bauer.
We've been compromised.
Someone used a stolen keycard
to access CTU
less than an hour ago.
Did you get an ID?
Not yet.
They didn't use
the card to exit.
They're still here.
We're in lockdown,
starting a search.
I'm on my way.
Get him over to medical.
Stabilize him.
Don't let anyone near him.
Did you get him?
Still working on it.
Exits are sealed.
Security cleared Third East,
they're going room to room.
Give me a comm unit.
Audrey, is Kim
still up in Field Ops?
With Landes, yes.
Get her down here.
I want a guard on her.
I'm on it.
EDGAR:
I think I got him in Third West.
He's in processing.
Could exit
south or north.
Jack, take north.
We'll give you updates.
Mac's team
will head south.
Copy that.
Pull up north
and south angles.
There he is.
Edgar, run his face
through recognition software.
Where's Carrie?
We need to check
for grid intrusions.
She's checking on a warning
signal in a B-socket.
Got it.
Checking the grid.
( groans )
You're gonna help me
get out of here.
He's in the north corridor.
Chloe, cover for me.
I want to see
what's keeping Carrie.
Go ahead.
BUCHANAN:
All units,
he's moving west
in the north corridor.
He's got one of our men.
Enter your passcode.
But it's a lockdown!
Just do it.
( beeping )
( alarm blares )
He's in the north stairwell,
sub-level B.
Jack, do you read?
I'm on my way.
Bill,
he's in the stairwell.
I don't think so, Jack.
Davis said he checked
sub-level B.
Bill...
It was all clear.
No, he's doubled back.
He's using the stairs
to get the roof.
All right, Jack.
I'm sending you
into the landings.
Let me know
when you're ready to move.
Copy that.
( alarm continues )
Freeze!
Let me see your hands!
Slowly.
Drop the gun!
Now!
Bill, it's Jack.
Hostile's down.
He's dead.
It was the only shot I had.
Do you have an ID, Jack?
We've got a bigger problem
than that.
He's got a device on him.
Looks like a relay switch.
Hold on.
He's got a PDA.
Oh, my God.
What is it, Jack?
It's a schematic
of CTU's ventilation system.
I think he tried to deploy nerve
gas throughout the building.
Order an evacuation.
Code six!
Everybody out!
Go! Go!
Jack, I have Kim with me.
Stay with her.
I'm on my way.
Make sure Burke
gets Henderson
out of here
as fast as he can.
All right, I'm on it.
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
O'Brian.
Chloe, what's going on?
Edgar, get out
of the building now!
Carrie?
( alarm continues )
We have to get out
of the building now.
What's going on?
Just hurry!
What's wrong
with those people?
Oh, my God.
The nerve gas
is making its way in. Go.
The ducts run
from the outside in.
"Outside in"?!
What does that mean?!
They start at the perimeter
and reach
the building core last.
Auto-lock
the outer doors.
Which rooms can we seal?
I'm working on it.
Burke, I need you to stand by.
We can't leave the building yet.
I'll let you know
where you can move Henderson.
Chloe, what rooms
can we lock down?
Hold on!
We can lock down
the Situation Room,
the upper offices
and Clinic Isolation.
Go, people!
Kim, everybody, in the
Situation Room! Move now.
BUCHANAN:
I'll access Comm from my office!
Burke, you can move
Henderson
to the Clinic Isolation.
Seal it off for bio.
I repeat:
Get in the Situation Room now.
Move!
Chloe, seal it.
Seal all the rooms.
Open the door!
You have to let me in!
Oh, my God.
Let her in!
We can't break the seal.
You have to try
and find another exit
out of the building.
Hurry! Go!
Chloe, are the rest
of the rooms sealed?
Yes, it's done.
( gagging and choking )
Everybody, stay calm.
There's nothing
we can do for her now.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Chloe.
www.tvsubtitles.net