Previously on 24:
We have waited patiently
for you to renounce
this unholy pact
with our oppressors,
but we have heard nothing.
This it the cost
of that silence.
If you choose to sign
this corrupt document,
understand that you will also
be staining it
with the blood
of the remaining hostages.
If CTU can't
pull this off in time
that's upwards
of 60 people, Mike.
Mrs. Logan, if someone
altered the recording
of your conversation
with David Palmer,
the president needs to know.
Between the summit
and the hostage situation,
he's not in the frame of mind
to deal with this.
Until the treaty's signed,
I'm not letting this
out of my sight.
What did she tell you?
She said it was a transcript
of the call she had
with David Palmer.
I under President Logan
wants us to go
into the terminal
as soon as possible.
Yes, before the treaty
is signed.
Curtis, what's your situation?
My men are in place,
and we're setting
the entry charges.
We should be able to make
our entry on target.
I assume Mr. Bauer's
been taken into custody?
Well, I plan
to debrief him here.
Bring him in now.
Diane, what's going on?
What's wrong?
Derek is inside the terminal.
I see him.
He's with the other hostages
but he's not hurt.
Please don't let anything
happen to him.
This is not your fault.
I'm the reason you went
along with them.
This is not over.
We got a problem.
One of the hostages
is missing.
He was working
with the terrorists.
Give me a description;
I'll take care of it.
I'll help you now-
let's go.
Buchanan just gave orders
to take you into custody.
I watched Beresch
give this guy a key card.
Something else
is going down here.
We've got to find this guy now.
Sorry we have to bring you in
like this, Jack.
It's all right, Mara.
I understand.
A year and a half.
How did you manage to stay
invisible for so long?
Apparently I wasn't as invisible
as I should have been.
Tyler.
Mara, it's Curtis.
Put Bauer on.
It's Agent Manning.
Yeah?
Jack, you say the suspect
was hiding among the hostages?
Yeah, right up until
the assault began,
somewhere around 10:30.
Then he must have broken
for an exit.
What exit was closest?
Without an alarm?
Between gates six
and seven.
Thanks, Jack.
Yeah.
Pull up external video
starting at 10:30.
All cameras covering
gates six and seven.
We're away.
Mrs. Logan?
Oh, my God.
Help!
Something's happened
to the First Lady.
Get a doctor, now.
According to Jack, he should be
between gates six and seven,
just outside this view.
I got this feed
from ten minutes ago.
Try camera seven.
Camera four.
All right, there he is.
Tighten up.
Yellow Tie. Got him.
Now let's follow him.
Damn it. What camera covers
the adjacent sector?
14A, but it's a bad angle.
Pull it up, anyway.
Match the time codes.
Okay, here he is.
This is two minutes,
25 seconds later.
What hangar is that?
Hangar Double-B.
Has it been searched yet?
No. It was outside
the secured perimeter.
All right, I'm going to take
a field team, head over there.
Send this info to Comm.
Team A with me.
Let's go!
Hangar Double-B.
Let's go.
CTU. Stiles.
Edgar, Jack told us
about a suspect
hiding among the hostages.
We just picked up surveillance
on him.
He entered Hangar Double-B
at roughly 10:57.
Did you check it out yet?
No, we're going in now.
I'll need comm.
I'm on it. Chloe, what volume
is airport facilities on?
Hennessy Four.
Team Two, cover the rear.
* *
Check it out.
Everyone else,
search the building,
see what you can find.
* *
Craig, it's Curtis.
Send a forensics team
down here now.
Tell them they'll need
a full bio-pack
with spectrum analyzers.
Any problems getting
the canisters out?
No. They were hidden exactly
where you said they'd be.
Everything on schedule
with our transport?
Customs documents are being
finalized at the port. Good.
The Russians will finally
understand the consequences
of occupying our homeland
when we turn Moscow
into a graveyard.
When did this happen?
A few minutes ago.
I came back in,
and I found her on the bed.
What do you mean "came back in"?
You mean you left her alone.
What happened, Doctor?
Is she all right?
She seems to be now,
but I'd have to do some tests
to find out why she blacked out.
I didn't black out.
Someone did this to me.
Someone attacked me, Charles.
Shh, shh. Martha...
You have to do something.
They're trying
to get me.
No, no one's trying to get you. Yes!
We just want you to
be well. Honey, listen.
Listen, listen.
I had the proof,
and now it's gone.
What proof?
What are you talking about?
The proof
that David Palmer called me
to warn me about today.
Are we still on this?
We've never been off of it.
You just wouldn't
listen to me.
Sir.
Is everything okay?
I think so.
No. No, damn it,
it's not o... okay!
You people have got to listen
to me.
I had a document,
from the archive room.
Where was this document?
I am trying to tell you.
It was hidden in my blouse.
It's gone.
Someone stole it from me.
Martha, you've been under
a lot of stress.
We all have.
Let... let...
No, let Dr. Hill...
Let Dr. Hill examine you
and we can figure out
how to get you better.
You don't believe me.
You don't believe your own wife.
I have an important phone call
from the Secretary of State
that I have to get to.
If there's any sudden changes,
you get back to me
as soon as possible.
Yes, Mr. President.
Charles, don't leave.
Honey, I'll be
right down the hall.
No, no, no, honey,
honey, don't leave me.
You need to get some rest.
Ple...
Close that door.
What do I do about this, Walt?
This is what she was like
before you sent her to Vermont.
Are you suggesting
that I readmit her?
You have to consider
the option.
For her sake.
She said she'd rather die
than go back in there.
Sir,
if she's going to persist
with these conspiracy theories,
it's only a matter of time
before she talks to someone
who believes her.
Then we really will
have a problem.
I wish you were wrong,
but I don't think you are.
Do you want me
to handle this, sir?
Make the arrangements.
But don't let Martha find out.
Let me be the one to tell her.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Have you handled
the problem there?
Yes.
Martha Logan won't be giving us
any more trouble.
Good. Erwich has just
completed transferring the gas
to the semi
and is on his way to the port.
And the authorities
don't know
anything's been stolen?
Not yet.
Then the only thing we have left
to take care of is Bauer.
Where is he?
On his way to CTU.
Mm. He's getting too close.
He's already started
putting the pieces together.
I know.
He needs to be taken out.
I'm handling it myself.
How?
Once he gets to CTU, your hitter
won't be able to get near him.
I've have someone on the inside
who can help us.
Then use him.
Done.
You sure those
readings are right?
They're right.
2,000 parts per million.
That can only be military grade.
I'll tell him.
Where are you going?
I need you to finish
the shell script.
Not now.
Since when do you say "not now"?
According to this,
the hangar was leased
to some offshore company,
but it's been vacant
for at least 18 months.
Sir?
I just heard from Curtis.
He was right.
There was nerve gas
in hangar Double B.
That's what killed the rats.
There were trace amounts found
in the animals' blood.
But the concentrations
were definitely mil spec-
weaponized.
So this man in the yellow tie,
the suspect that Bauer's
telling us about
that's what he was
doing at the airport?
Stealing canisters of nerve gas
out of the hangar?
Stealing from whom?
Military destroyed
its stockpiles years ago.
Well, maybe this nerve gas
wasn't produced by the military.
Edgar, have forensics get a
signature off the trace samples.
See if they can figure out
who manufactured it.
Chloe, elevate our alert status.
Activate all available personnel
and get Curtis back here.
We're gonna need
everyone we have.
I wouldn't issue a statement
about the First Lady
for another couple days.
Let your successes today
run front and center
on all the networks.
That sounds right.
Dr. Hill, please, come in.
How's Martha doing?
Well, she's asleep now.
Have you figured out
what caused the blackout?
I spoke with her psychiatrist,
Dr. Carlstrom,
and none of the medication
she's been prescribing
would have caused
this kind of collapse.
So we still don't know
what it was.
Not yet, no.
Mr. President, I need
to speak to you and Walt alone.
Thank you, Doctor.
Keep a close eye on her.
We'll talk soon.
Yes, Mr. President.
What's up, Mike?
I'm afraid the situation
at the airport
has taken an unexpected turn.
What's the problem?
The hostages were saved,
we've captured or killed
all the terrorists.
Not all of them.
One of the terrorists was
posing as a hostage.
He used the hostage crisis
to cover a theft.
A theft?
What was stolen?
A cache of chemical weapons.
What kind of chemical weapons?
Nerve gas.
Is it ours?
No, sir.
CTU is still trying
to source it.
But it was buried
in a bunker at the airport.
It seems this man
had another crew
waiting for him there.
Do we have any idea what
the terrorists are planning?
Well, they haven't
made any demands
or issued any threats, yet.
Well, what are we doing
to stop them?
CTU is running
an interagency search effort.
They're coordinating
ground operations,
filtering intelligence.
Has the press found out
about this, yet?
No, sir.
It's being kept internal.
Whatever retaliation
we were bracing for an hour ago
is nothing compared to what
these people
are capable of doing now.
Sir, I'll assemble
the Homeland Security team
to discuss evacuation scenarios.
I sent everyone updates
on the airport forensics.
What did you want me on next?
Check the task list.
You don't need to
ask me every time you need
something new to do.
I don't care if
you are my boss
or if you regret sleeping
with me last night.
No one talks to me like that.
Really?
I just did.
Now, what's your problem?
I don't have a problem.
Then what do you want?
Nothing.
Edgar.
Look, I'm sorry
that my private life
hasn't remained private today.
I'm thinking the opposite.
What do you mean?
You're too private.
We've known each other
for years.
And today I find out
you're keeping secrets from me?
Haven't you ever taken
a psychology class?
People keep secrets.
I don't.
Not from my friends.
Why didn't you tell
me Jack was alive?
Oh, come on.
It's called national security.
Yeah, well, what about Spenser?
I didn't even know you
two were going out.
Give me a break.
Okay, when we find the nerve gas
and the alert level drops,
we can have some chamomile tea
and I'll tell you
all my secrets, okay?
You paged me.
Has Bauer arrived at CTU?
No, not yet.
When he does, I need you
to do something.
We have our hands full
searching for the nerve gas.
Bauer is a priority.
I need you to clear
an entrance into CTU.
I'm sending it now.
Okay.
Miss Raines.
I'll get back to you. Yes?
I take it you're up to
speed on the nerve gas
stolen from the airport.
I was just filling in DOD.
Diane Huxley and her son were
brought in to be debriefed.
I'd like you to interview her.
Interview her about what?
Any information she has
that could help us
find the nerve gas.
What could she possibly
know about that?
I've reviewed the evidence
against Jack Bauer,
and I'm inclined to agree
with your assessment
that he was framed for the
assassination of David Palmer.
Thank you.
I also think that whoever
framed Jack is also involved
with the theft of
this nerve gas.
Which means that Diane Huxley
could have had contact with that
person without realizing it.
I- I'm not
a trained interrogator.
But you know Jack Bauer
better than anyone else in here.
You have something in
common with this woman.
It might help her open up.
I realize it's awkward,
but I need you to do it.
Fine.
I'll see what
I can get from her.
Thank you.
Where is she?
She and her son just
cleared security.
Miss Huxley, I'm Audrey Raines.
Hi.
Hello.
This is my son, Derek.
Hi. I'm gonna be asking you
a few qutions.
And Derek, I want you
to be checked out by a doctor
while I speak with your mother.
There's nothing wrong with me.
It's just procedure.
When you're done,
you and I will speak.
Can you take him
to medical, please?
It's okay,
I'll see you in a bit.
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
Is Jack gonna be here soon?
He's on his way in.
Come with me.
I had no idea he worked
in a place like this.
It's just up these stairs.
Did you know him before?
Yes.
I knew him.
A lot of people here thought
you were dead until today.
Yeah, I know.
Excuse me.
Chloe.
Hi, Jack.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
We wouldn't have made it
out of that airport
without your help.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Bauer, Lynn McGill
from division.
Mara, I'll assume custody
at this point, thank you.
You're no longer a suspect
in President Palmer's murder,
but while you're here,
you will need this.
It'll give you level
two clearance. Thank you.
Was Agent Manning able
to apprehend the suspect?
No.
It seems the person
you identified
used the hostage
situation as a cover
to steal a cache of weaponized
nerve gas from the airport.
Nerve gas? How do
you know that?
McGILL: Following your lead, Curtis
found trace amounts in a hangar
adjacent to the terminal.
We don't know
how much there is and
where it came from,
but it is a military grade
chemical weapon.
Do you have any leads?
Not yet, but we're gonna run
the search operation from here.
You're not gonna be able
to track these terrorists
fast enough with a standard
search operation.
The only way you're gonna
get that nerve gas in time
is if you find out who ordered
the hit on David Palmer.
I agree.
I think Palmer was about
to expose this plot.
I think that's
why he was killed.
I also think that if you can
help us identify
who framed you,
we can intercept this nerve gas
while there's still time.
Hello, Jack.
Hey, Bill.
President's been informed
of the nerve gas.
He wants to ensure
the media doesn't find out.
Well, make sure Division
restricts information flow.
We'll continue this
conversation when I'm done.
Good to see you
again, Jack.
It's good to see you,
too, Bill.
I'm so sorry
about Michelle.
I never meant
to put her in jeopardy.
Of course, you didn't.
How's Tony doing?
He's still
unconscious,
but the doctor says he's
going to pull through.
Good.
We're gonna need to speak to him
as soon as possible.
They know to call us.
Jack...
Audrey has been
working for us.
She's here in the building now?
She's debriefing Diane Huxley.
Why is she talking to Diane?
Lynn asked her to.
I'm not used to
calling him Jack.
He said his name
was Frank Flynn.
I thought he worked
for the oil company.
You probably know more
about him than I do.
We all thought he was dead
for the last year and a half.
So what do you want to know?
You said that Jack was living
with you for the last...
six months,
is that correct?
He was renting a room.
So, you don't have a personal
relationship with him?
I'm not sure that's any
of your business.
I'm sorry, I just...
I need to know
how close you and Jack were,
whether he confided
in you or not.
Jack's a private person.
I always knew he was
keeping something from me.
I just never
pushed it.
I accepted him for who he was.
Ms. Raines...
whoever he was before...
it doesn't change
the way I feel about him.
He was good to me,
he was good to my son.
He meant a lot to us.
He still does.
I see.
Did anyone ever come by
and ask about Jack?
What do you mean?
Someone knew
that Jack was alive.
It's critical
to our investigation
that we find out who that was.
No. No one asked about him.
No one ever came
to see him.
Can you excuse me
for a minute, please?
Yeah.
Jack.
I don't even know
where to begin.
You have to believe me.
I couldn't tell you
I was still alive.
Jack, you don't need
to apologize.
I did it for your
own protection.
It's been hard for me,
thinking you died,
believing that I was angry
at you...
that I hated you.
I wasn't able
to forgive myself for that.
You had every
reason to hate me.
I was responsible
for Paul's death.
I lied to you.
Jack.
You made a hard decision.
I never imagined I'd get
another chance to tell you this.
But I want...
I want you to know
that I don't blame you
for what happened with Paul.
Thank you.
Jack...
There's so much that I want
to say to you, I know its...
Mr. Bauer.
Mr. Buchanan needs
to see you.
I'll be right down.
I should go.
Evelyn, is Mrs. Logan
still asleep?
Yes, she's finally
getting some rest.
Good.
You should probably start
gathering some of her things.
I thought the president
was staying through the weekend.
He is... but she'll be
leaving today.
Where's she going?
Just make sure
she has the essentials
to make her trip comfortable.
Yes, sir.
Edgar said he saw you
come in here.
What are you doing?
Setting up a new socket.
We're overloaded
from the NSA database.
Why are you here?
Looking for you.
What for?
I need to get into
your utilities volume.
Why didn't you message me?
Okay, I wanted
to say something, too.
Let's not make a big drama
out of it.
What?
I was unfairly harsh to you
a few minutes ago.
I didn't mean anything.
All right.
Apology accepted.
It wasn't really
an apology,
it was more of
an observation.
I mean, the fact...
Spenser.
Damn it, why do I do that?
It's Chloe.
What is it?
I need to know
Spenser's clearance level?
Why are you asking?
Spenser works for me, and I need
to know his clearance level,
so could you please
open the header file
and give it to me, Edgar?
Fine.
Level three.
Chloe?
Call Buchanan, tell him
I need to talk to him now.
It's important.
Division sent me.
One of your mainframe
servers is cycling slow.
You're not on the manifest.
I was told it'd
be taken care of.
I'm going to have to clear this
with the systems administrator.
Are you Hank,
from on-site support?
Yeah.
My fault.
I was supposed to advance him
an emergency clearance. All right.
Place the bag
on the conveyor belt,
and walk right through, sir.
All clear.
Thank you.
I'll show you the way.
Mr. Cummings told me
it would be best
to keep you off the manifest.
Classified material
generally runs
on servers nine
and twelve.
All the information you need
on Bauer should be there.
I don't know what
files Mr. Cummings
asked you to download,
but you need to keep vector
counts the same,
or it'll get flagged.
I got it.
Okay.
I need to get back
to my station.
Evelyn, what are you doing?
Mrs. Logan,
are you feeling better?
Why are you
packing my things?
Walt Cummings asked me to.
Why?
Where are we going?
I don't know if the president's
going with you.
Evelyn, stop. What's going on?
They just asked me
to get you ready to leave.
They're sending me to Vermont,
aren't they?
Charles is having me committed.
I'm sorry,
Mrs. Logan.
I honestly don't know
anything else.
It's fine.
I'll getting dressed.
Edgar, my FGA is locked.
Where's Chloe?
How should I know?
Can you unlock this?
No.
Mr. Wolff?
Please come with us.
What do you want?
Mr. Buchanan has ordered us
to take you to him immediately.
I'm in the middle
of a critical task here.
Mr. Stiles
has been authorized
to take over your work load.
Did you know about this, Edgar?
Yeah. I just got the bulletin.
Sorry.
Mr. Wolff.
Please.
I'm coming.
Chloe?
Sir.
What is going on here?
Sit down, Spenser.
You've been
burrowing
into classified CTU protocols
without authorization.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Stop- I know you were logged
onto the security subsystem,
where you had
no right to be.
We're going through
your system
so you might as well
tell us now
what you were doing.
I told you I was opening...
That's enough!
You've accessed files
outside your clearance level
at least 18 times in the
four months you've been here.
Sir, whatever you think
you've found,
it's a mistake.
I've done nothing wrong.
Come on, Spenser,
you obviously have
your own agenda
here.
I don't have an "agenda."
And while you're at it,
why don't you explain
why it was necessary
to crawl into my bed.
Which certainly
wasn't
what it appeared to be,
just like your work here
isn't what
it appears to be!
Chloe, Chloe.
Chloe, let me
handle this, please.
Sir, obviously you can't take
anything she says
into consideration.
I was careless.
And, inadvertently,
I caused her
some emotional pain.
Oh, please.
And now she's trying
to get back at me.
I don't think so, Spenser.
Sir, I'd like
to talk to a lawyer.
Forget about a lawyer!
We're in the middle
of a terrorist crisis
There are lives
on the line.
You're going to tell us
what you've been
doing here,
and you're going
to tell us now.
I hope this goes better
than when I sent her
up there the last time.
Dr. Hill and his staff
are on standby
if she overreacts.
I'm not looking forward
to this.
Evelyn?
Mr. President.
Where is she?
She's in the bathroom, sir.
Martha?
Marty?
Are you sure she's in there?
Yes, sir.
She's getting dressed.
Marty?
Aaron?
My wife is gone.
This is Pierce.
We have a priority alert.
The First Lady has left her
quarters and is unaccounted for.
All agents in the main wing,
move to points north and west.
Anyone spotting her,
check in immediately.
So the only people
who knew you were alive
were David Palmer,
Tony Almeida,
Michelle Dessler
and Chloe O'Brian.
Yeah, and at least one other
person who killed David Palmer
and tried
to frame me for it.
And you don't know who that
other person might be?
No.
Any theories?
About a year and a half ago,
David Palmer called me.
Told me there's someone
in Logan's administration
targeting me.
Which is why you faked
your own death
and assumed a new identity?
Yeah, except it didn't work.
I believe that whoever tried
to kill me 18 months ago
somehow found out
I was still alive,
and waited until today
to exploit that information.
Someone inside President
Logan's administration?
That's what David Palmer told me
a year and a half ago,
and I believe him.
Well, first of all,
that would mean
someone in this
administration is also tied
to the theft
of the nerve gas.
Yeah. You're going
to have to look into that.
Well, even if you're right,
there are hundreds of people
in Logan's administration.
It would take an investigation
of that magnitude months
to gain any
traction-
and we don't have
months to work with.
WOMAN
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but Dr. Paulson is calling
from medical.
Put him through.
DR. PAULSON
Mr. McGill?
Yes?
Tony Almeida's regained
consciousness
and is in recovery.
Can he talk?
Yes. He's very weak,
you'll have to be brief.
Let him know I'll be down
in a few minutes.
Tony asked if be could
speak to Jack Bauer first.
He says it's important.
He's a friend of mine.
Tell Mr. Almeida that Jack
will be down in few moments.
I'll let him know.
Thank you.
I'll be right back.
Jack.
What's going on?
I know
you're busy.
I...
I just wanted to apologize.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
Yes, I do.
I thought you were
just another loser,
trying to take advantage
of my mom.
I was wrong.
You were trying
to protect her.
Your mother is lucky
to have someone
who loves her
as much as you do.
As soon as this is over,
I promise you,
you and I are going
to get a chance
to sit down and talk.
But right now
I have to go.
Yeah.
Take care of your mother.
Who gave you the Level Five
authorization?
Don't look at me.
Answer him!
I can't.
I can't talk to anyone here
about this.
Whatever you were doing
is over, Spenser.
Sir, I was able
to pull Spenser's screen
activity from the archive.
This is what he was looking at
ten minutes ago.
Looks like he was using
in-house surveillance
to track someone
through CTU.
Why are you
tracking Jack Bauer?
What the hell's going
on here, Spenser? I
was following orders.
I'm sure if they're tracking
Jack Bauer, they have a reason.
Who is they?
I won't say anything else.
Chloe, find security,
have them locate Jack now.
Dr. Paulson?
Yes.
I'm Jack Bauer.
Tony Almeida wanted
to speak with me.
Oh, of course, Mr. Bauer.
Just remember
to please keep it brief.
Thank you, sir.
Tony.
Tony, it's Jack.
Jack,
you all right?
I think he cracked my rib.
I've been trying
to reach you,
but the lines
were locked out.
What happened?
Who is he?
I don't know,
but he's a professional.
He killed Dr. Paulson,
then he tried to kill me.
You have any idea
how he got into CTU?
We identified a mole working
in Chloe's department.
Who?
Spenser Wolff.
We've been interrogating him,
but he hasn't talked yet.
Where is he?
Holding.
Get a doctor down here
to monitor Tony Almeida now.
Lock this room down.
Contact Lynn McGill,
have him meet me in Holding.
Bring up visual surveillance
on Medical Room Two.
Open the door.
Get up!
Did you let that man into CTU?
This man
is a professional assassin.
He just killed Dr. Paulson,
and he tried to kill me.
Did you let him into CTU?
No. They told me he was here
to place a tap
on one of the servers.
That's all I knew.
Who told you?
I was here as part
of an Internal Affairs
investigation.
Are you starting to understand
how much trouble you are in?
Now, I'm gonna give you
one more chance.
Who told you
to let that man into CTU?
The White House.
Mr. Cummings
in the White
House.
Cummings recruited me
after I started working here.
He said that
they wanted to make
sure CTU was operating...
within the rules.
You have to believe me.
I thought
I was serving the President.
Yeah. Take him back
to Holding.
Walt Cummings
killed David
Palmer, and he tried
to have me killed.
Even if it is true,
we have to build a case
before we call
the President.
We don't call the President.
He's here in California.
We go see him now.
Cummings is the President's
Chief of Staff, Jack.
And his friend.
Without any hard evidence,
CTU can't touch him.
I'm not CTU.
I'll go get Walt Cummings
myself.
www.tvsubtitles.net