What happened to David Palmer
wasn't supposed to happen.
He put himself in harm's way,
and he got involved
with something
that he shouldn't have.
You know who killed David?
He works for me.
MARTHA:
You lied to me.
This entire day has
been one giant lie!
What you've done
makes me sick!
Martha, enough!
I need you to swear
to me that you will do
as I ask for the country.
I hate you.
The situation with Martha
is taken care of.
There are too many loose ends
lying around.
We cannot afford to have her
pull on one
and unravel everything.
She won't.
I have the recording.
Have you destroyed it?
No, sir, I have not.
You and I have been in this
from the beginning.
Destroying that recording
protects both of us.
I've got O'Brian.
Where is she?
She's working
out of Bill Buchanan's house.
Did Chloe tell you why she was
helping Audrey Raines and Bauer?
'Cause she thinks
Jack is innocent,
that President Logan
framed Bauer.
This is Karen Hayes-- Miles
traced Chloe to your house.
You have less than seven minutes
to get Chloe out of there.
Karen, why are you warning us?
Because I may have made
a mistake earlier.
Chloe, if they find you
here, you'll be arrested.
You have to go now.
Not yet.
BAUER:
It's over, Christopher!
Turn around!
Give me the recording.
I don't have it.
Where is it?!
BAUER:
Henderson wasn't lying.
He doesn't have
the recording on him.
There must've been
some kind of a hand-off.
Henderson stopped and
rendezvoused with another car.
Can you track the other car?
We're tracking it now, Jack.
It headed back to Van Nuys--
looks like
the civilian side
of the airfield-- pulled onto
the tarmac; whoever it was
got out and got directly
onto the plane.
CHLOE:It is a chartered
diplomatic flight.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, we've tried
everything we can.
There's no way
to delay the plane.
Okay, call me
when you've got 'em. Yeah.
Bill, are you out?
The field team's almost there.
Chloe's packing
the comm gear she needs
to stay in touch with Jack.
Where is Jack?
Van Nuys Airport.
He stowed away
on a diplomatic flight
that just took off.
What? Why?
He's trying to find a recording
that implicates President Logan.
And someone
on that flight has it?
Yes, and we don't know who.
That's what Chloe's been trying
to find out.
Hang on. Yeah?
Field team's a block
away from Buchanan's.
I'll set up here for the
remote debrief of O'Brian.
No. Put it in
the Situation Room.
Oh, I thought you wanted...
I want it in
the Situation Room. Go.
Bill, the field team's
gonna be there any second.
Get Chloe out of there now.
How close are they?
One block.
All right, I'm gonna have
to run interference.
It's more important
that she gets away.
Good. I'll bring you in.
You'll be treated
as a suspect.
We never talked.
BUCHANAN:
Understood. They're here.
Out the back.
Bill, wait.
Have Chloe call me
on a dry channel.
Either one-five
or two-seven.
Dry channel,
one-five or two-seven. Got it.
There's a gate in back.
Follow the path
between the houses
to the alley,
turn right and go
to Ventura Boulevard.
What about the curfew?
There's a hotel
on the boulevard,
the Miramont.
You should be able to make it
there without being spotted.
What about you?
I'm gonna make sure
you're not followed.
I'll be at CTU,
probably in Holding.
Why in Holding?
Karen's gonna place
me under arrest.
If you need anything,
contact her.
Why is she...
Chloe, please, just go.
( knockingat door )
Who is it?
MAN:
Homeland Security.
Mr. Buchanan,
we need you
to open the door.
We're under order
from Karen Hayes.
I'll be right there.
What, uh, what's going on?
Please step aside, sir.
We need to search the house.
No, I'm not stepping aside.
Do you have a warrant?
Where's Chloe O'Brian?
I have no idea.
Sir,
don't make us use force--
we know she's been here.
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Where is she?
I don't know
where Chloe O'Brian is.
She's gone.
Sir? This is a recent
file from Comm.
Only O'Brian
could access it.
Talk to us, sir.
I'm not talking to you.
I'll talk to Karen Hayes.
Mr. Papazian,
we are on site-- it appears
Chloe O'Brian was here,
but she is gone.
Is Bill Buchanan there?
Yes, sir.
We lost O'Brian.
Damn it!
Put him on the
phone, please.
Hello?
Don't play games with me, Bill.
Just give me
O'Brian's location,
or I will make it
very bad for you.
From what I understand,
Miles, she got out of CTU
right under your nose.
You're the one who ought
to be concerned, not me.
Bill, this is Karen Hayes.
Tell us what you know now.
Stop wasting our time.
I'm not saying any more.
This is Ed.
Ed, bring Buchanan in.
Set up a grid search for Chloe.
She's probably got a car,
which means
she's about 15 miles out.
Copy that.
But the agents on site
are trained for
interrogation.
Why are you
bringing him in?
Because I want
to run this, Miles.
But now it's us
who are wasting
time here.
Don't worry.
I will make him talk.
I'll be in my office.
( phone line ringing )
HAYES: Yeah?
I'm set up
at the Miramont Hotel.
Make sure no one looks
for me here.
I'll take care of that.
Tell me what else you need.
Jack's on diplomatic flight 520.
Pull up the manifest.
Got it. Flight 520 to Frankfurt.
Okay, put everything you've got
from that flight under
the shared volume so I can get
to it.
Crew, passengers, cargo,
everything.
Done.
Okay, I see it.
Thanks.
( phone rings )
( panting )
Yeah.
CHLOE: Jack, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did you get what I need?
I've got the passenger list--
it's gonna take
some time to cross it
against Henderson.
What about the air marshal?
That I'll have
in a couple of minutes.
Okay, good. What's
happening at CTU?
They're still under orders
from the president to stop you,
but Karen Hayes
is backing us.
Openly?
No, but she's
letting me help you.
If there's proof against Logan,
she wants it found.
The proof is
on this plane.
Check the flight manifest,
figure out which passenger
has a connection to Henderson
and get back to me
with the air marshal's
seat number.
I will.
I don't think so.
Oh, hey. I was
just asking.
You don't have to go
all feminist on me.
Did you see that?
21st-century woman.
We better get
used to it.
( computer beeps )
( phone rings )
Yeah.
Jack, I found the air marshal--
his name is George Avila.
He's sitting in 7A.
Anyone sitting
next to him?
No.
Okay, good.
Get back to me
when you've got the
connection to Henderson.
Got it.
( quietly ):
Excuse me.
Is that seat taken?
No.
Thanks.
The stewardess said I could
change seats-- I was next
to the galley,
it's kind of noisy.
I'm trying to get some rest.
Yeah?
Okay, the man you're looking
for is in seat 12D.
His name is Hans Meyer.
He's with
the German government.
He's been connected to Omicron
since the mid-1990s.
He's worked directly
with Henderson.
That's it.
Okay, I've got it.
Mr. Meyer?
Yes?
My name is George Avila.
I'm the air marshal
on this flight.
What's wrong?
It's nothing serious.
We found something
that we think is yours.
It should have been
in the baggage
compartment.
We'd just like you
to come back
to the galley and
identify it for us
so we can properly
stow it.
Please, sir. We'd
really appreciate it.
If you have any
carry-on bags,
you should bring
them with you.
I don't.
Very well.
What makes you think
it was mine?
Ticket stub.
They have taken away
all my medication.
I need to get to it.
I'm sorry, ma'am. They won't
let me give that to you.
What do they think I'm going
to do? Kill myself?
Over that son of a bitch?!
I just called the president
of the United States
a son of a bitch.
No reaction?
He must have some kind of law
on the books against that,
or am I immune, just like he is?
Do you have a first name,
Agent Adams?
It's Justin, ma'am.
You don't have much of
a personality, do you, Justin?
This is Novick.
It's Martha.
Are you still in the retreat?
Yes. I'm just down the hall
from your room.
I need you to come here
right away.
I'll be right there.
They've cut me off
from my medication.
You haven't been cut off.
Dr. Hill said you had enough
in your system right now.
You need to wait
a few hours.
I don't want to wait
a few hours, Mike.
I need something now.
What's going on, Mrs. Logan?
I don't need counseling, Mike.
I just want a damn pill.
Sit down. Sit down.
Thank you, Agent Adams.
We've been through some
tough times before, Martha.
Just follow the doctor's
orders for now.
This is more than
just a tough time, Mike.
None of this is going
to go away.
I just have to live with it.
What do you mean,
"It's not going to go away"?
What are you talking about?
I... I shouldn't have said that.
Martha, it's me.
Say what needs to be said.
What needs to be said
I can't say to you.
Why not?
Listen, Mike,
I just...
I just need
to get some sleep.
I'm just...
My nerves
are shot from today.
I just need something
to calm me down.
I just need
to get to my medication.
The president doesn't want
you to leave the room.
Then you can bring it here.
I just want to take
a couple of pills.
I need to sleep.
You can watch me take them.
I'll see what I can do.
( phone rings )
Yes?
GRAHAM:
They found Bauer yet?
No, they haven't.
That's not good.
I know that's not good.
I'm putting pressure
everywhere I can.
I don't think I have to tell you
how disastrous it would be
if Bauer gets his hands
on that recording.
That's exactly right.
You don't have
to tell me. I know.
When I find him,
I will call you.
Is there
anything else?
No.
Good.
Mr. President?
What is it, Mike?
There's something I think
I should call to your attention.
Yes?
Your wife is in
a very agitated state.
I don't know
how to proceed.
Proceed with what?
She wants me to bring
her her medication
against doctor's orders.
That's all I need right now
is to deal with her!
No! No!
No more pills.
And she shouldn't be wasting
your time with this anyway!
Mr. President.
Is there something
going on that I
should know about?
Why? What did she say?
She needs more medication
to calm herself down.
Something's clearly
bothering her,
but she didn't want
to talk about it.
I don't see where any of this
becomes your business, Mike.
I'll tell you where,
Mr. President.
I'm your Chief of Staff.
If there's something going on
that I don't know about
that involves national security,
it is my business.
This isn't national security,
Mike.
It's our marriage.
I think both of us
realized today,
at this point,
our relationship is nothing
more than a facade,
and one that we're going
to have to keep up
for as long
as I'm president.
I think that
she's reacting to that, Mike.
I see.
I'm sorry, sir.
Mike?
Give her what she wants.
Lord knows, she's
in a lot of pain.
( groaning )
Where are you hiding it?
Hiding what?
What-What do you want?
What the hell is this?
I know who you are.
I know your connection
with Omicron.
I know your history
with Christopher Henderson.
He asked you to take something
out of the country for him.
Where is it?
Christopher Henderson?
I have not seen him in months.
Don't you lie to me!
I'm not lying, I swear!
I know Henderson,
but I don't know
what you're
talking about.
Did you check your luggage?
Yes.
Find it.
Move!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Homework?
Homework, yeah.
I didn't know they
had WiFi in here.
Could you leave me alone?
I can't talk right now.
( laughs ):
You're a little, uh,
freaked out
because of the curfew thing.
Join the club.
Yeah, okay.
When you come up
for air, I'm buying.
MAN:
Airport Customs.
This is Chloe O' Brian
from CTU Los Angeles.
I need to talk to somebody
in passenger clearing.
I'll need verification.
Agency ID: CTU 99A-12.
( bell dings )
The captain has turned on
the fasten seat belt sign,
as we are expecting
some turbulence.
Please return to your seat
and make sure your seat belt
is securely fastened.
( rumbling )
The passenger in 12D must
be in the forward lavatory.
You should get him out.
The captain said it's
going to shake pretty hard.
There's nobody in those.
I just checked.
Then where is this guy?
MAN:
I don't know. Maybe
he changed seats.
( loud rumbling )
( screaming )
( quietly ):
Call the captain, and tell him
the air marshal's down,
and a passenger's
missing!
What's going on here?!
Please be seated, sir.
Now, sir!
Yeah?
Captain Cotter, this is Dan.
The air marshal's
been assaulted.
What?
Assaulted?
What's going on back there?
I don't know, sir,
but he's been
knocked out,
and a passenger's missing.
Okay, okay. Secure the cabin.
Keep the passengers
under control.
What's going on?
There's a problem
in the cabin.
Make sure our
door is secure.
It is. What kind of problem?
The air marshal's
been knocked out.
Call L.A. Center,
get vectors
for an emergency return.
Mr. Avila, what happened?
The man seated next to me--
where is he?
I didn't see him.
We got to find him.
Damn it.
What?
Mike, come in.
So, do you have
something for me?
This is just enough
for a couple of days.
Dr. Hill's going
to come in...
Thank you, Mike.
Thank you.
I'm going to get ready
for bed now.
Is there
something else?
Yes, there is.
Earlier you said
something to the effect
that I didn't know
everything that
was going on.
I was confused.
I wanted my pills.
I don't think so.
Are you calling me a liar?
I just spoke with the president.
And I got the same feeling
from him I get from you.
Which is?
That you're both
covering something up.
You know, Mike, I'm the one
around here
who's supposed to be paranoid,
not you.
I know you, Martha.
And I know
the president.
He said this was all about
marital difficulties.
I think there's
something else.
What is it?
Don't shut me out.
Maybe I can help you.
There is something
else, Mike,
but it's between me and Charles.
If that changes, I promise
I'll let you know.
I don't know what you think
Henderson gave me.
I saw no one.
I was picked up
at the Consulate
and brought directly here.
There are witnesses,
you can ask them.
Is this your only
piece of luggage?
Yes.
If you're lying to me,
I'll find out.
I am not lying.
Please, if there is someone
on this plane
that has something you want,
it is not me.
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
Jack, I don't think Hans Meyer
is our guy.
Why not?
The timeline
doesn't match.
He's been in customs
for the last three hours
clearing himself
onto the flight.
The plane's turning.
What does that mean?
It means they
know I'm on board.
Chloe, keep looking.
Okay.
( metal rattling )
Are you sure
he's down there?
There's nowhere else
he could be.
Tell the pilot
he can do it.
But there's a passenger
down there with him. He'll die.
There's over 50 passengers
up here. Call him now.
Do it.
Captain, the air marshal says
the baggage area
is secure,
and that you should begin.
( gasping )
( loud hissing )
Air's coming in.
It's not coming in,
it's going out.
What do you mean?
They're depressurizing
this area.
What's going to happen to us?
If we don't get
into the main cabin,
we're going to lose
consciousness.
( phone ringing )
Jack, what's going on in the
plane? Security net just issued
a bulletin.
Chloe, I need you to patch
me through to the pilot.
I don't know
if I can do that.
Chloe, they're depressurizing
this area.
We're going to lose
consciousness.
Okay, okay.
( phone ringing )
Yeah, Chloe.
Jack needs us to patch him in
to the pilot of the flight.
Can you get through
on a CTU sub-channel?
I'll try. Hold on.
I'll stay on the line.
MAN:
Air control operator 44.
Yes, I need you to patch me
through to the pilot
of diplomatic flight
five-two-zero out of Van Nuys.
Hey, what
do you got?
A little voice-over
IP going on there?
Please leave me alone.
No, seriously, I can help.
I know a way for you
to get some free bandwidth.
Really?
Absolutely.
Sit down.
Cool.
Wow, nice piece.
Never seen one
of these before.
What is that?
( electrical crackling )
It's a CTU Series four.
Chloe, they've opened the line
to the pilot.
I'll patch him through.
Thanks. Okay, Jack, I'm putting
you on with the pilot.
Go ahead.
This is Captain Stan Cotter.
Who am I speaking to?
Captain, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with the counterterrorist
unit in Los Angeles.
I'm the man
in your baggage hold.
What do you think you're doing?
I'll explain everything
in a moment,
but you're going to have
to restore
air pressure to this area.
Sir, I remind you,
I am a federal agent.
What kind of a
federal agent
knocks out
an air marshal?
I don't believe you.
Sir, I was patched through
to you by a CTU sub-channel.
I couldn't have done that
unless I had clearance.
All I know is,
you have a gun
and you have breached
airplane security.
Captain, this is a matter
of national security.
Now open the damn hatch!
( air hissing )
What do you think?
He couldn't have patched in
through CTU if he was hostile.
There's no point
in taking a chance.
In a couple of minutes
he'll pass out.
From there,
the air marshal can handle it.
Captain, we are running out
of air down here.
( air hissing )
Captain, I know you can hear me.
There is a man on board
your plane that is a danger to
you. That's why I am here.
Open the hatch!
I can't do that.
Okay, you son of a bitch.
( air hissing )
( shouting )
What the hell was that?
The aileron conduit's
been breached.
What?!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
You're going to kill
everybody on this plane.
That's up to you.
Open the hatch.
I'm not letting
you up here.
Then you'll be responsible
for everything that happens.
( people screaming )
All right, all right,
all right.
Sue, I'm going
to stabilize the pressure
and I'm letting him up.
I want you to unlock
the hatch.
The cockpit's secure.
He can't get in here.
Yes, Captain.
What do you think
you're doing?
The captain ordered me
to open the hatch.
Both of you,
turn around
and grab the wall.
Now!
You...
in the baggage hold.
Do it.
Now.
Close it.
Lock it.
Out of the galley now.
Get back to your seats.
What's going on?
Sit down!
He has a gun!
( people screaming )
Everybody just stay
in your seats.
Face forward.
Put your hands on your head.
Do what I tell you
and no one will get hurt.
If you don't,
people will start to die.
Get the captain
on the phone now.
Sir, he's in
the main cabin.
He has a gun.
Get the first-class passengers,
move them into the main cabin.
Everyone to the main cabin.
Captain, this is Jack Bauer.
I want to assure you
I have no intention
of hurting any of
your passengers.
I need to find something
that's on the plane.
It's a matter
of national security.
What do you want, Bauer?
I want you to remain
in a holding pattern
so I can search
your passengers.
If you're really
a federal agent,
then you know I have
to land this plane.
Sir, that won't give me
enough time.
That's not my problem.
I have a gun.
Your air marshal is down.
Captain, it is
your problem.
You need to remain
in a holding pattern,
do you understand me?
You do what you have
to do, Mr. Bauer.
My job is to land
this airplane.
And that is what
I am going to do.
Captain? Captain...
MAN:
That's all we have
on Flight 520, sir.
Okay, look, I want updates
on the situation
on a minute by minute basis
if necessary.
GRAHAM:
Yes.
I just got word
from the FAA
about a hijacking aboard
a diplomatic flight that left
Van Nuys a half hour ago.
So what?
Jack Bauer is
the hijacker.
What is he doing
on that flight?
Looking for the recording
that implicates me
in David Palmer's death.
Henderson handed it off
to somebody
before he was arrested
and Jack must know
that it's on board.
Then you shouldn't be
wasting your time
talking to me.
Order the plane down,
and grab Bauer before
he can hurt us.
Wait, what are you saying?
That he hijacked the plane?
Not exactly.
He has control of the cabin.
The pilot is landing the plane.
What about
that recording?
He's still looking
for it,
but there's no guarantee he'll
find it before the plane lands.
And after that,
it's all over.
The president will have
his people
arrest Jack at the airport
and isolate him.
What are we
supposed to do?
Just keep helping Jack.
Chloe, I need to see
that evidence.
Call me if you need
anything from here.
Fine.
Give me a second.
What's Bauer doing
on Flight 520?
You have no idea
what you're dealing with,
you little ass-kisser.
You don't talk to my people
like that, Bill.
Take him to Holding.
It's no wonder CTU fell apart
under that guy.
Miles, I know you're
trying to help,
but I'll take it
from here, okay?
WOMAN:
Western Operations.
This is Miles Papazian,
Homeland Security, Los Angeles.
Pass code 21 double six.
Put me through to Mike Novick.
One moment, please.
Yes, Miles. What is it?
I need your input, sir, because
I'm having a problem
with Karen Hayes.
I'd like to preface what I'm
about to tell you
by saying that I
don't wish to be
second-guessing...
I don't have time
for prefaces.
Karen Hayes was called in
to replace Bill Buchanan.
She was hand-chosen
by the vice president
to take that post.
I understand that, sir.
Are you saying you feel
she's unfit to do the job?
Four hours ago,
she relieved Bill Buchanan
for ineffectual leadership.
He's been working covertly
with Chloe O'Brian
to aid Jack Bauer,
a federal fugitive.
Which means Buchanan needs
to be dealt with appropriately.
What has Karen done?
She sent in a tac team
to pick them both up,
but by the time they got
there, O'Brian was gone.
But instead
of having the team
do the interrogation
of Buchanan onsite,
Karen wasted 20 minutes
by bringing him in to CTU.
Maybe she felt
the interrogation
would be more effective
with CTU resources.
But, sir, she isn't even using
rudimentary CTU resources.
She wants to do a soft
Q and A by herself.
Any leads we may have had
on O'Brian have dried up.
Wait a second, Miles.
I'm not going to pass judgment
on Karen Hayes at this point.
She's not
interrogating a terrorist.
She's dealing with a high-
ranking federal employee.
Sometimes finesse
and diplomacy
are better than coercion.
Your concern
is duly noted, Miles.
If you'll excuse me,
I need to see the president.
Karen.
Shut up, Bill.
We're offline. Now we can talk.
Look, you can continue
this charade of me being
under arrest if you want to,
but Jack
needs our help.
And he's getting it,
but make no mistake, I am
still in charge of this
facility, and until I see
that evidence,
I must remain skeptical.
Have you talked to Chloe?
Yes.
What's Jack's status?
He's searching the cabin
for the evidence,
but the pilot is going
to land that plane.
How much time does Jack have?
15 minutes.
To search over 50 passengers?
That's impossible.
STAFFER ( over intercom ):
Ms. Hayes.
Yes.
The president
and Mike Novick want an update
on the hijacking
of the diplomatic flight.
Put them through.
Go ahead, sir.
Ms. Hayes,
this is the president.
Talk to me about 520.
We know that Bauer's
involved, but we don't know why.
Isn't it obvious?
Bauer is a fugitive
and he's looking for safe
passage out of the country.
Well, that's certainly
a possibility, sir.
Listen to me. This
man is desperate.
He will say
or do anything.
He's not to be trusted.
We need to take him down now,
dead or alive.
Yes, sir.
Mr. President.
Look. You call the pilot
and you tell him
that I don't care
if Bauer is making
threats or not,
that plane has
to land immediately.
And when it lands, I want
my Secret Service detail
to take him into custody,
is that clear?
Ms. Hayes?
Yes, Mr. President.
The president has had knowledge
of everything
that's happened today.
He wants that plane down
before Jack finds the evidence.
We have to buy him more time.
I don't have the authority
to keep that plane from landing.
Sir.
It still doesn't
make sense to me.
What?
Jack Bauer
has been on the right side
of everything that's
happened today, up until now.
Well, right now,
he is hijacking a plane.
This man is not stupid.
He's appeared
to do the right thing,
but right now,
he's backed into a corner,
and he's desperate.
Do you really believe that, sir?
I absolutely do.
Bauer's lied to us all day.
MAN:
Flight Operations.
This is Chloe O'Brian again.
Yes, Ms. O'Brian.
The copilot, Don Faganson,
didn't check in
when he boarded Flight 520.
Mr. Faganson didn't board.
Why not?
He was replaced
at the last minute.
By whom?
Scott Evans, the new copilot.
Here are your things,
Go back to your seat.
( phone rings )
Yeah.
Jack, it's the copilot,
Scott Evans.
How do you know?
He used to fly for Hatton Air.
It's a private charter company
that worked exclusively
for Omicron.
Evans was assigned
to Henderson's group.
He flew him around
for over a year.
Okay, I need you to
patch me through
to the captain
on a discreet channel
so Evans can't hear me.
Okay.
Sit down!
Now!
Everybody stay in your seats
and no one  will get hurt!
CHLOE:
Go ahead.
Captain, this
is Jack Bauer.
I'm speaking to you
on a discreet channel.
The person that
I'm looking for,
the man with the
evidence that I need,
is sitting next to you.
He's your copilot,
Scott Evans.
That's ridiculous.
Sir, my sources
have informed me
that Evans was a
last-second replacement.
Can you explain to me
why you're not flying
with your regular copilot,
Don Faganson?
Captain, Scott Evans
has been connected
to a known terrorist.
You need to open the door.
This conversation is over.
Damn it.
What did he want?
He's desperate.
Wants us to land.
This is messed up.
Yeah.
Bad luck for you, huh?
Why?
Well, wasn't Don supposed
to have your seat tonight?
Yeah.
What happened to him?
I don't know.
I got the call, so I'm here.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
( groans )
Could you, uh...
Could you take the
stick for a second?
You okay?
Yeah. I just...
got a cramp in my leg.
Yeah. Those are a bitch.
Yeah.
( groans )
I'm the only one
who can fly this plane.
Now, you don't strike me
as a man who's willing to die
for Christopher
Henderson.
Give me the recording.
( cocking gun )
Do it.
Slowly.
Get up.
Get back in your seat.
You're going
to land this plane
or I'm going to put
a bullet in your head.
( phone ringing )
Yeah, Jack.
Advise CTU I have the recording.
I'll be on the ground
in less than 15 minutes.
Got it.
NEWSCASTER:
At this hour, there are still
many unanswered questions
surrounding
David Palmer's death.
During the emergency press
conference, the president
announced that the terrorist
threat was over...
( phone ringing )
Yes.
MARTHA ( weakly ):
Charles.
If I'm going to live with this,
then you're
going to have to help me.
Help you do what, Martha?
Understand.
I...
I know you're a good man,
and that deep down,
you do what's best
for this country.
Of course I do.
Then why...
why didn't you come to me?
I'd have been there for you.
I could have
talked you through it.
For God's sake, Martha,
for the last three years,
you've been one click away
from a nervous breakdown
every single day,
and I'm gonna come to you
for advice?
( phone rings )
I'm gonna have to take
another call.
No. Charles, no, no.
We'll talk later.
( sobbing )
( cell phone ringing )
Yes.
Bauer's got the evidence.
He is in control of the plane.
How do you know that?
We just picked up a call from
Chloe O'Brian to Karen Hayes.
What do we do?
You are going to have
to shoot down that
plane, Mr. President.
What?
It's the only option
we've got.
Otherwise, you go to prison
for treason and murder.
www.tvsubtitles.net