This is Bauer.
Jack, Air Traffic Control
just received
a VCI distress signal
from your aircraft
that effectively authorizes
President Logan
to shoot you down.
Start taking us down.
Do it now.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, the F-18
is within 15 miles.
PILOT:
My radar is locked
onto the target.
Lower the landing gear!
We're going too fast!
Touch it down!
( screaming )
( screeching )
We're ready to move Bierko.
Thank you.
I'll be right out.
Vladimir Bierko,
you're being transferred
to a primary holding facility
in our district
headquarters.
Jack, the attorney general
is on his way
to his office
right now.
He'll be ready for
a video conference
in ten minutes.
JACK:
Chloe, I want you to prepare
the recording
for playback.
I want you
to clean it up
and apply
a digital signature
so we can establish
a chain of evidence.
You work alone.
We got the evidence.
President Logan's going to pay
for David Palmer's
assassination.
The spectacle of a sitting
president on trial for murder
would be devastating.
Yes, it would.
If only there were a way that
we could prevent
such a trial from taking place.
( phone rings )
MILES:
Mr. President?
You don't know me.
My name is Miles Papazian,
I work under Karen Hayes.
What is this about?
It's about a recording, sir,
if leaked, could significantly
compromise national security.
Why are you telling me this?
I feel compelled to intervene,
and I just I wanted to make sure
that you would approve.
I do, Mr. Papazian,
I do approve.
Get out of here, Miles.
I'm just doing my job, Chloe.
Well, if your job is
is to slow things down,
then you're doing
really good work.
I'll tell Karen
you'll be ready.
The attorney general
will be on the line
in five minutes.
Did you tell him
that the recording
implicates President Logan
in Palmer's assassination?
No. I feel he needs to hear it
directly from the source.
Fine.
We're minutes away, Chloe,
what's your status?
Everything is set up.
I've got a T-1 line hooked in
to the attorney general,
the other two lines are secured
on dedicated channels.
What other two lines?
We're patching in
a representative
from the House
Judiciary Committee
and a Congressional liaison.
We need their support
to call for
an emergency session
of Congress
to begin impeachment
proceedings.
Impeachment proceedings?
What about an arrest warrant?
We'll never get Justice
to indict a sitting president.
Removing him from office
is a necessary step
to begin full
criminal prosecution.
All right, Chloe,
let's check the sound levels.
Play the recording.
( recording playing
white noise )
What's wrong?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
Where's the recording?
This is what's on
the digital medium.
That's impossible.
See if there's an overlay,
check your connections.
There are no mistakes.
Damn it, Chloe,
you were responsible
for this recording.
What the hell happened?
I just told you,
I don't know.
But if there was something
on this memory chip,
it's been erased.
( phone rings )
Yes?
STAFFER:
Excuse me, Ms. Hayes.
The attorney general's
holding on the line.
Ms. Hayes?
I heard you.
Bill Buchanan will
take the call in a moment.
I'll tell him we're having
technical difficulties,
we need to postpone
the conference.
Someone got to
that recording.
Perhaps it was damaged in
your attempts to retrieve it.
It wasn't.
Chloe, who had
access to this room?
No one.
Someone did!
Who had access to this room--
think about it!
Miles was in here.
What?
You sent him in here
to check up on me
while I was setting up.
HAYES:
I never sent him in here!
Jack...
HAYES:
Security, stop Mr. Bauer.
Mr. Bauer!
Jack, don't!
You son of a bitch.
Let go of me, Bauer.
Do you know how many
people lost their lives
so I could bring
that evidence in?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
We know it was you.
Let him go, Jack.
Jack, let him go!
Where are you going, Miles?
I've been transferred.
I was told to report
immediately.
The order should be
coming through any minute.
Transferred to where?
The White House.
How could you do this, Miles?
This is not over.
There will be
an investigation.
Do what you
have to do, Karen...
...but I work for
the president now.
Jack, I'm so sorry.
I don't know how he did it,
he didn't even
touch the recorder.
Karen, Audrey Raines
heard the recording
when I played it
for Secretary Heller.
I know that she will
sign an affidavit...
Jack, not now.
Chloe, take the recorder
down to Processing.
Break down the memory chip
and see if
you can
restore anything.
Fine.
Ms. Hayes?
The president's calling for you.
Line two.
Mr. President.
LOGAN ( over phone ):
Karen,
what's this I hear
about a conference call
you've scheduled
with the attorney general?
Is there some problem
I should know about?
HAYES ( over phone ):
It's nothing, sir,
a mistake.
The conference call
was canceled.
Good, I'm glad to hear that.
Listen, the real reason
for my call is Jack Bauer.
What about Jack Bauer?
I'm embarrassed to say
that after further review,
it appears that the evidence
against him is, at best,
inconclusive.
Now, we'll have our lawyers
continue to work on it,
of course,
but for the time being,
I'm suspending the arrest order.
You're dropping the charges
against Bauer?
That's correct.
Mr. President, you have had
this office, other agencies,
and the military dedicate
all manpower and resources
into apprehending Jack Bauer.
Yes. Based on evidence I
initially thought was credible.
And now I have new information
that's convinced me that
the original intel was faulty.
Am I to release
Bauer, sir?
I'll leave that
to your discretion.
Thank you, Karen.
Good work.
We'll be in touch.
Yes, Mr. President.
He's letting me go
because he knows he's won.
What does he gain
by releasing you?
I'll be on my own.
Alone, unprotected,
a perfect target.
Word just came in--
Bierko's escaped.
What?!
How long ago?!
The convoy that was moving him
to District was hit
about ten minutes ago.
They took out all
our agents except one:
Davis, on line three.
( phone beeps )
Davis, Karen Hayes.
What happened?
Our lead car got taken out
by an IED.
I counted six attackers.
Bierko got away
before I could call in backup.
Did you see the vehicle?
Negative.
I blacked out when I took one
in the shoulder.
There's a medevac team
on the way.
DAVIS ( over speakerphone ):
Before I lost consciousness,
I overheard Bierko
talking to his men.
He said they're
not finished.
"Not finished"?
Yes, ma'am,
I'm certain he said
something about a
nerve gas canister.
Did he say anything else?
I'm sorry, Ms. Hayes,
that's all I heard.
All right, Davis, stand by.
The medical team will
be there in a minute.
Copy that.
Why would Bierko even mention
the Sentox?
I don't know.
I assumed all the canisters
were destroyed in the explosions
at the distribution
center.
How many canisters has
forensics accounted for?
By the time the fires
were put out,
there was not enough left
to do a full accounting.
Damn it.
Bill, raise
an inter-agency
alert.
I need LAPD to do a sweep
of the ambush area
for witnesses.
I want search helicopters.
I want Chloe to have full domain
over surveillance
satellites.
This is priority one--
we have got to find
Vladimir Bierko.
( metal door rattling )
We held one in reserve,
just as you ordered...
but I still don't
understand why.
We can't do much damage
with one canister
of nerve gas.
You're so wrong.
E-Excuse me?
Agent...
It's Agent Cole,
ma'am.
Cole.
I'm sorry, Agent Cole.
My husband said
that Aaron Pierce
had been transferred
to Washington,
and this is
Agent Pierce's phone.
I was wondering
if you'll be so good
as to make sure that
it's returned to him?
Of course.
Was there anything else, ma'am?
No.
There's nothing else.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry about this, Aaron.
Listen to me, Aaron.
You think you know
what's going on.
( sighs )
I'm here to tell you, you don't.
Then why don't you explain it
to me, Mr. President?
I understand Jack Bauer
led you to believe
that there was a recording--
something that tied me
to David Palmer's murder.
That recording doesn't exist.
That's not what I've been told.
You're not hearing
what I'm saying.
The recording
doesn't exist.
It's over.
You have a choice here, Aaron.
You are a good man.
You're a fine agent.
I see no reason
to throw away your career.
But I need to know
that we can put this behind us.
If you'll give me your word
that you'll let this drop,
I will make sure that
you are reassigned
to whatever post you want.
Except for the White House,
of course.
So...
what's it gonna be, Aaron?
Are my terms acceptable?
There is nothing
that you have said or done
that is acceptable to me
in the least.
You're a traitor to this country
and a disgrace to your office.
And it's my duty to see
that you're brought to justice
for what you've done.
Is there anything else, Charles?
I know Pierce,
Mr. President.
Served with him
for five years.
And his loyalty is
to David Palmer.
Believe me when I tell you,
he's going to be a problem.
( dialing )
( cell phone ringing )
Mr. President.
I confess, I didn't expect
to hear from you again.
The situation's
changed.
Everything's
under control.
The recording's been destroyed;
it's no longer a problem.
That's very good news,
Mr. President.
But what about the people
who've already heard it?
Can't do anything without proof.
I don't think any further action
needs to be taken.
Then can we assume you've got
the rest of your house in order?
If by that you mean
my wife, yes.
Yes, she's cooperating fully.
As for Aaron Pierce, that's
another matter, but, um...
I'm taking care of that.
Of course.
What about Jack Bauer?
I've already given Karen Hayes
permission to release him,
and the arrangements that we
discussed about taking him out
have already been
set in motion.
It appears you have
everything well in hand,
Mr. President.
Yes, yes.
I said I would handle it,
and I have.
Situation's contained, there's
nothing more to worry about.
I'll call you back.
Mike?
Sir.
What is it, Mike?
I just got off the phone
with Karen Hayes.
Vladimir Bierko has escaped.
What? How?
The caravan transporting him
to District was ambushed.
Damn it!
I thought we rolled CTU
into Homeland Security
just to avoid
screwups like this.
There's more, sir.
They have reason to believe
Bierko might be
readying another
terrorist attack.
What kind of attack?
Well, CTU's working on that now.
I want constant updates.
You keep me apprised
of the progress.
Yes, sir.
Chloe, any luck?
Only the bad kind.
None of these satellites
were positioned
toward the ambush site.
By the time I
queued a redirect,
Bierko and his men
were long gone.
You try CalTrans?
I'm back-streaming now.
So far, I've
come up dry.
Keep trying.
We've got to get
an ID on the vehicle.
I know.
That was LAPD command.
They've combed the area,
but they can't find
any witnesses.
None?
4:00 a.m. in
the middle of
a curfew; there simply
wasn't anyone there.
Then we have nothing.
We've got Henderson.
What about him?
Henderson set up Bierko
with the nerve gas
to begin with.
No, we've already been
down that road.
He won't talk to us,
and you know that.
That was about
protecting Logan.
If Henderson's the
patriot he says he is,
he's not gonna want those
terrorists to succeed.
Trust me,
you're wasting your time.
He's not gonna help us.
He will if we offer him a deal.
That's not gonna happen.
Jack.
No.
Not this time.
Not this man.
We're running
out of options here.
This is about saving lives,
not indulging a grudge.
You think this is
about a grudge?
He killed an ex-President
of the United States.
He tried to kill the
Secretary of Defense.
You want this man to walk
with full immunity?
It's not about
what anyone wants,
it's about doing
what has to be done.
Nobody knows that
better than you.
Bierko is going to
kill innocent people.
Henderson might be
our only chance
to stop him.
Jack...
what would David Palmer want
you to do if he were here?
The best way to honor his
memory is to make the choice
to save others.
Obviously, I can't stop you
from doing this.
If you're gonna give him a deal,
at least let me present it.
All right.
Thank you.
Since you're clearly
no longer a fugitive,
I assume they retrieved
that recording.
Someone got to it
and erased it.
I'm not here to talk
about the recording.
Bierko escaped
about a half an hour ago.
He's gonna carry out
another attack.
I'm sure he will.
You bruised the man's ego when
you stopped his first attempt.
You know him.
You know how he thinks.
You studied him
before you set up this deal.
What's he gonna do?
Why should I help you?
You call yourself
a patriot.
Prove it.
These terrorists
are gonna attack
the country that you love,
because you betrayed them.
Why don't you help me put out
the fire that you started?
They sent you in here
to broker a deal, didn't they?
What's the offer, full immunity?
That just must be
really eating you up inside.
What do you think?
You were responsible
for the murder
of people that I cared about.
I am sorry
about David Palmer, I am.
But what I did
was in the interest
of the destiny of this country.
And I'm not talking about
the version you read on
the op-ed pages pages
ofthe New York Times.
I'm talking about
the politics of survival--
the way the world really works.
Do you want immunity or not?
Immunity is worthless.
Yeah.
( beeping )
Jack.
That recording
was my only immunity.
They give me a piece of paper,
I walk out of here,
I'm a dead man.
It's two days, two hours,
two months, who cares?
They're gonna take me down.
Who's they?
Same people that made Walt
Cummings look like a suicide.
Come on, Jack.
You can't really believe
that Charles Logan
masterminded all of this
by himself.
Give me the names.
You can't touch them.
But they can touch you.
I'll help you catch Bierko.
But not for an immunity deal.
I need something more,
and you're the only person
can make it happen.
What do you want?
To disappear,
just like you did
so they wouldn't turn
you over to the Chinese.
Except, I'm not gonna
make your mistake.
I'm gonna leave the country,
I'm gonna take Miriam with me.
You don't need my
help for that.
Actually, I do.
All of my contacts are still
loyal to the President.
I need somebody I can trust
to cover our tracks.
I need somebody who can do
a better job of it
than those incompetents
who failed to cover yours.
What makes you think
that I'm not gonna kill you
the second this is over?
Because you're
gonna give me
your word.
And I know what your word
is worth to you.
So it's all I need.
Anything less than
Bierko's head on a plate,
this deal is off.
Fine.
Now, Bierko is gonna hit hard,
so you gonna think fast
Chloe, do a phone
check on these 14 names.
I want you working out
of the Situation Room.
What do we have?
Henderson gave us 14 names
that he believes
Bierko's gonna contact first.
Chloe's doing a phone check
and pulling up relative data.
Is Tactical standing by?
They're on priority alert.
I put Curtis Manning in command,
if it's all right with you.
I trust your judgment, Bill.
Security's getting ready
to bring Henderson in here
for a debrief.
Excuse me for one second.
Audrey.
Jack, I just heard
about the recording.
Has it really
been destroyed?
President Logan managed
to get to it.
My God.
We have a more
immediate problem.
Bierko. I heard that he escaped.
That's why I came back out here.
I was hoping that I could help.
Why is Henderson
coming out of Holding?
We're using him
to help us find Bierko.
Audrey, Karen
made a deal.
She gave him immunity.
What?! Jack,
how can you let this happen?
You know what that man has done.
We didn't have a choice.
Bierko's our number
one priority.
We know
he's planning another attack.
Without Henderson's help,
we won't find him.
BUCHANAN:
Jack!
I think we've
got something.
Audrey, I'm sorry.
I've got to go.
CHLOE:
Out of the 14 names on the list,
only one has an active
cell phone-- Joseph Malina.
Joseph Malina's an arms dealer.
Used to be
a military contractor
until they accused him
of selling secrets.
But they couldn't
prove anything,
so he beat
all the charges.
You know him?
Well enough. I did business
with him before and after
he was arrested.
HAYES:
What do you have on him?
Malina got a 12 second call
on his home phone at 4:03 a.m.
from a pay phone in Van Nuys
not far from the ambush site.
A minute later, the same
pay phone got a call-back
from a GSM Sat phone.
In other words, he
took down the number,
called from an
untraceable line.
Sounds like our guy.
Tell Curtis
to mobilize his tactical team.
Hang on, hang on.
What good is that going
to accomplish?
You're going
to bring Malina in here.
You think he's just going
to roll over on Bierko?
He didn't cut a deal
when he was busted before,
he's not gonna cut a deal now.
And even if you can crack him--
I don't think
you can--
you're going to need hours,
and you don't have hours.
What do you suggest?
I suggest you send me in
to talk to Malina.
I'll find out
what Bierko got from him.
I don't think so.
Jack, don't be stupid.
You know you can't get anything
out of this guy,
and his computer makes
this place
look like
an Internet cafe.
He's got the absolute,
most sophisticated,
state-of-the-art
security system,
including a Phoenix Shield.
We can get through it.
Not a Phoenix.
It's a poison pill firewall.
Any attempt
at circumventing it,
and the hard drive does
a cold-start erase,
at which point, you can forget
about retrieving any data.
Take him back to Holding.
I don't think
we have a choice here.
Karen, please, don't do this.
Jack, I know
how you feel,
but Henderson's right.
We can't afford
to gamble on this play.
Damn it, Bill,
you cannot trust this guy.
HAYES:
I agree.
That's why I'm sending you
with him.
I want him under your guard
on a tight leash.
If he tries anything,
I swear to you,
I will kill him.
Then don't let it get
to that point.
* *
Get in.
Adams, listen to me.
You don't have to do this.
Logan isn't worth protecting.
You know that.
He's not going
to get away
with any of this,
and neither will you.
Shut up and get in the trunk.
Use your head.
Logan wants me
dead because he thinks
I know too much,
that I'm a liability.
How soon before
you're just another liability?
( both grunting )
( grunts )
MARTHA:
What are you doing?
Ma'am please stay
where you are.
Aaron?
You're going to shoot me?
I'm the First Lady.
You're going
to shoot the First Lady?
Who are you calling?
Mrs. Logan,
this is my last warning.
( grunts )
( silenced gunshot )
( shallow breathing )
( whimpering )
( crying )
Martha.
Aaron!
( crying )
Aaron, stay with me.
Aaron! Oh, God.
Oh, God, Aaron.
CURTIS:
Jack, we're coming up
on Malina's place.
( tires squealing )
( engine revving )
Curtis, I want you
to set up a perimeter.
I want a man at each
possible escape route.
You got it.
As for you, you
got ten minutes.
You don't get the
intelligence from
Malina by then,
we come through the door,
and we interrogate him.
I'm gonna tell you again, Jack,
interrogating won't work.
This guy won't break.
Then you better hope
your way does.
Get me an audio pack.
Undo your shirt.
Wait a minute.
You can't wire me.
Why not?
Well, think
about it, Jack.
You heard Malina's file.
This guy didn't get where he got
by being careless.
He's got a scanner, frequency
detector, God knows what else.
The second I walk
through that door with a wire,
the bells go off,
this thing's over.
Look, you don't
trust me, fine.
And just so we're straight,
I don't trust you, either,
but neither one of us can afford
to blow this operation.
We're all set. Men
are in position.
No games, Christopher.
I don't need another reason
to put a bullet in your brain.
You got ten minutes.
Have CTU in-monitor
channel 8.
Hold up.
Go.
( beep )
Who is it?
What do you want, Chris?
We have to talk.
What, at 4:30 in the morning?
About Vladimir Bierko.
You don't waste my time,
I don't waste your time.
You're going to want to hear
what I have to say.
( buzzer sounds )
( door creaks open )
( panting )
( buzzer beeping )
( whirring )
( beep )
Hey!
What's so important
it couldn't wait?
What are you
looking for?
Is there another way out
of here?
What the hell are
you talking about?
Jack, I don't like this.
What's Henderson doing?
I don't yet.
Maintain your position.
I repeat,
maintain your position.
Secure-cache the files.
Anything you can't do without.
Why?
Because there
is an entire phalanx
of CTU agents outside,
including an ex-agent
named Jack Bauer.
He's selling us out, Jack.
HENDERSON:
Now, Bauer is running me.
I cut a deal with him,
but I know
this guy's gonna kill me
first chance he gets.
JACK:
Curtis, move your team in now.
All teams, move in now!
You bastard,
you brought him here!
He was coming here anyway.
So secure the files,
crash the system.
Stop wasting time, and do it!
( panting )
( whirring )
( blow torch hissing )
( panting )
Give me a weapon.
( glass shattering in distance )
Freeze! ( yells )
( groans )
( grunts )
( Curtis groans )
Christopher!
Let me see your hands! Now!
Slowly stand up.
Put the weapon
on the counter.
Step back.
Curtis,
how are your men?
CURTIS:
My men are fine.
I've been hit,
but I'm okay.
Call in medical;
get him transferred back to CTU.
What's Malina's condition?
Gunshot to the hip.
He's losing blood.
Stabilize him,
keep him alive.
I had him, Jack.
30 more seconds
was all I needed.
You played me.
This is over;
you're going back.
No, you blew it, Jack.
What are you talking about?
I got him to life the firewall,
and he was about to dump
all of his files
onto a flash drive
before you jumped the
gun and busted in here.
Now you're going to waste a hell
of a lot of time
trying to decrypt those
files off a mainframe,
so you'd better pray there's
something on there you can read.
Cuff him.
Bill, this is Jack.
Get Chloe to open up a channel.
I'm going to send you some files
from Malina's computer.
I'm on it, Jack.
Chloe, I need you
to access these files,
find out which ones were opened
in the last ten minutes.
They'll tell us
what Malina sold Bierko.
They're coming through now--
hang on.
Bill, Curtis was hit--
he's stable,
but I'm having him transported
back to CTU.
All right, Jack,
I'll tell Medical.
Send a chopper
over to this location.
As soon as we know
what Bierko's target is,
we're going to need
to move fast.
Okay, I got through
the firewall.
It's still going to take me
some time to decrypt the files.
Chloe, just do it as quickly
as you can.
Bierko's going to release
the Sentox gas soon.
We need to know where.
There, you should
have everything.
Let's go.
Aaron?
Charles lied to me.
He said you'd been transferred
to Washington.
That agent, um...
Adams,
my husband ordered him
to kill you, didn't he?
Yes, ma'am.
But I'm sorry
to tell you...
the president was involved with
much worse things than that.
I know.
I was going to let him
get away with it... all of it.
I was going to keep quiet.
We have to do something.
I'll hide the body,
get him in the trunk,
but I can't drive it
out of here.
The president has to believe
that I'm dead.
I need to lay low,
keep out of sight.
I can do it.
No. No.
Yes, Aaron, I can drive it.
No, you need to get back
inside the residence.
Your husband can't suspect
that anything has gone wrong.
You need to find Mike Novick.
Mike?
Tell him everything.
And tell him
to meet me here.
Okay.
Aaron, promise me...
promise me that
if something goes wrong
and you're in danger
of getting caught,
you will find a way
off these grounds,
and you will leave.
Promise me.
You have my word.
Secure him
by the tailgate.
( dialing )
( phone ringing )
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
How is Chloe doing
with the files?
Almost there, Jack.
Okay, I got it.
Wait, there's something more.
Classified defense contracts
and plans.
It's a Russian submarine, Jack.
The Natalia-K524,
Delta-IV class.
It's here for inspection
by our navy.
Why is the U.S. Navy inspecting
a Russian submarine?
It's part of the treaty
that President Logan
and President Suvarov signed.
There's a provision that calls
for the sharing of technology.
Where is it docked?
Docking Station 8.
It's a non-military shipyard
at the Port of Los Angeles.
I'll deploy TAC teams
to the port.
Good.
Chloe, hold on.
What's the armament package
on a Russian Delta IV-class sub?
Best of my knowledge, 12
Scorpion land attack missiles.
Are they nuclear?
No, but they're fast
and accurate.
ey carry multiple warheads.
One could take out
several city blocks.
( helicopter propeller
whirring )
Uncuff him.
Karen, it's Jack.
Are you still there?
Yes, Jack, I'm here.
Okay, I need you
to put me in touch
with the ranking U.S. officer
on the Natalia.
We need to get them to lock out
their onboard weapons systems!
All right, I'll have Audrey
call DOD
and open a priority line
to the sub,
and she'll get back to you.
Okay, thank you.
You're coming with me.
I found Bierko's
target for you.
The deal was Bierko's head
on a plate.
What do you want me to do
now-- kill him for you?!
The only reason
you're going with me
is 'cause you know
the weapons systems.
Go!
( phone ringing )
This is Bauer.
Jack, I've got the U.S. Navy's
ranking officer
on board the Natalia--
I'm putting you through.
Okay, Audrey,
stay on the line.
All right, Jack, hold on.
AUDREY:
Lieutenant Southern,
you're on with Jack Bauer.
Agent Bauer, what is this about?
JACK:
Lieutenant,
we believe the Natalia
has been targeted for
a terrorist attack.
You need to
secure your vessel
and lock down your weapons
systems immediately.
Ski!
Call all hands,
set Condition Delta,
seal the bridge
and aft hatches.
Aye, sir.
You need to put
your men on alert.
There's a threat
to your submarine.
( speaking Russian )
Now, what is the nature
of this threat?
We think the terrorists are
after your missiles on the sub.
I'm going to check right now.
Sailor! I've got that.
Report aft.
Bauer.
I'm checking topside.
Lieutenant!
Damn it, Audrey, I've lost him.
Notify DOD.
All right, Jack, I'm on it.
Captain, how far out
are we?
Just over five minutes, sir.
( device beeps )
( typing )
Read me the code
we got from Malina.
PETROV:
"Alpha 255
Tango Romeo 99."
( beeps )
We have control
of the weapons system.
Are the missiles loaded?
Vertical tubes are loaded
and ready.
Loading horizontal tubes now.
www.tvsubtitles.net