Evelyn, I need you
to stay focused.
The recording of the phone call
that you made
between President Logan
and Henderson
is in a safety deposit box.
Which bank?
City Trust and Savings
in Agoura Hills.
Jack knows there's no point
in going public
till he has
that evidence in his hand.
None of this
should have happened.
This whole thing was planned
to make our country safer.
and it all spiraled
out of control
when you decided
to kill David Palmer.
We have to focus
on stopping Bauer
before he finds that recording.
Karen, I'm issuing
an executive order
for the immediate apprehension
and arrest of Jack Bauer.
I want you to run point on this
and I want you
to make this CTU's top priority.
Understood, sir.
You know, if we really
want to find Bauer,
we need to keep watch on anyone
he might contact for help,
starting with Audrey Raines.
Don't fill your father in
on the particulars.
Just set up the meeting.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I have the recording.
I need to see you in person.
Can you reroute
your plane to Los Angeles?
All right, yes.
I'll see you there.
Jack, are you aware
President Logan's issued
a warrant for your arrest?
The vice president's
not the one
who's behind this, is he?
No. It's Logan.
As soon as we have
the evidence in hand,
we're going to pass it off
to Secretary of Defense Heller.
HENDERSON:
It had to be done, sir.
LOGAN:
I decide what needs
to be done, Mr. Henderson.
I never authorized you
to kill David Palmer.
You know what we need.
The instant that Bauer steps
outside that bank building,
you take him down.
Kill the others
and secure the recording.
( gunfire )
( bullets hitting metal )
( machine gun fire )
We got the evidence.
Have you listened to it?
Yeah, there's no doubt
it's Logan.
We're talking about taking down
the president
of the United States.
This checkpoint is just one
of many that have been in place
for several hours now.
Despite his announcement
that Los Angeles
is no longer
under threat of attack,
President Logan has ordered
that martial law
remain in effect.
While the move
has drawn criticism
from lawmakers
and civil rights advocates,
the president
is defending his decision
as a necessary precaution.
( phone ringing )
He's citing the need...
( mutes TV )
Yes.
HENDERSON:
It's me.
Is Bauer dead?
Not yet,
Mr. President.
You said your men had him.
Bauer triggered
the bank alarm.
The authorities came before
our men could get to him.
Bauer used the cover of
the firefight to slip away.
He has the recording?
Yes, sir.
That evidence directly
implicates me
in David Palmer's death.
Only if he gets it to someone
who can do something about it.
We'll have Bauer
before that happens.
How?
Mr. President,
you've established
direct control over CTU,
and CTU is heading up
the search effort
for Bauer.
You're putting an awful lot
of faith in their ability.
This city is locked down.
CTU will find Bauer,
and when they do,
make sure you're the first to
know so my men can intercept.
( intercom beeps )
Yes, Mr. President?
Karen Hayes at CTU.
Put it through to my office.
We're sifting satellite
and CalTrans video
for Audrey Raines's
vehicle.
I've distributed her file photo
to military checkpoints
throughout the city.
If she used her DoD credentials
at any of them,
there should be a record.
Well, I hope we're not wasting
our resources on Raines
when we don't even know
she's helping Bauer.
Karen, she dumped
the tracker.
There's a reason she doesn't
want to be followed.
( intercom beeping )
MAN:
Miss Hayes,
the president's on line one.
Yes, Mr. President.
Where are we, Ms. Hayes?
Still running
active manhunts
on both Jack Bauer and
Christopher Henderson.
I told you
to prioritize Bauer.
I have, sir.
I've allocated my
resources accordingly.
If David Palmer's killer
is still at large
when the morning
news cycle begins,
then all the success we've had
handling these terrorists
will be undermined.
I will find Bauer, sir.
You let me know
the moment you do.
Yes, Mr. President.
Bauer, right?
Audrey Raines.
She knows where he is,
and those protocols aren't going
to be enough to track her.
You still
think Chloe
helped Audrey
break surveillance?
I'm sure of it.
Remember, Audrey insisted
Chloe be assigned to her.
Then we need to
confront Chloe.
No, no, no, no, no.
She'll just deny it.
There's a way we can
use her to find Bauer.
It's all right. It's him.
JACK:
Bill, over here.
Jack.
Bill Buchanan,
Wayne Palmer.
Sorry about
your brother.
What the hell's going on, Jack?
The military authority,
every law enforcement agency
across this country
has a warrant for my arrest.
What for?
Killing David Palmer.
That's impossible.
We cleared you
this morning.
I'm being set up again,
this time
by President Logan.
He was complicit
in David Palmer's assassination.
My God, you're serious.
Logan's using the military
to try and stop me
from exposing him.
Mr. Buchanan, we
have the evidence:
a digital recording
of a conversation
made between President Logan
and Christopher Henderson.
I need to get the recording
to Secretary Heller.
He's gonna take it
to the Attorney General,
and they'll file
for the warrant.
But until then,
Wayne's a target.
I need you
to take him
somewhere safe.
Of course I will.
Where are you
gonna meet Heller?
Van Nuys Airport.
( engine starts )
JACK:
Yeah.
Jack, my father landed.
Where are you?
I just dropped Wayne Palmer off
with Buchanan.
I'm on my way
to the airport now.
All right, I'm on the north
side of the emergency runway
at hangar 112.
I'll be there in
a few minutes.
All right, hurry.
Dad.
Hi, sweetheart.
Hi.
Thank you so much
for doing this.
Well, I don't know
what it is I'm doing,
so don't thank me yet.
These men in your
security detail,
do you trust them?
With my life.
Dad, I need to be sure
that they are loyal to you.
What's going on?
( car approaches )
Dad, I will tell
you, but only you.
Stay here.
You know I don't like
to be kept in the dark.
Tell me what this is all about.
I promise, I will.
I just need a minute.
Mr. Secretary.
What the hell are
you doing here?
He's a fugitive.
Every law enforcement
agency in this state
is looking for him.
He's innocent.
Then why don't you
turn yourself in?
Mr. Secretary, I swear to you,
I had nothing to do
with David Palmer's
assassination.
I'd like to believe you, Jack,
but you're acting
like a criminal.
I don't have a choice;
they're setting me up.
Mr. Secretary, I only need you
for a few minutes.
I need to show
you something,
but privately,
inside the building, please.
Thank you, sir.
HENDERSON:
It had to be done, sir.
LOGAN:
I decide what needs to be done,
Mr. Henderson.
I never authorized you
to kill David Palmer.
HENDERSON:
Palmer was nosing around.
President Logan?
And a man named
Christopher Henderson.
HENDERSON:
He'd have found out
about your involvement.
For God's sake, sir,
he called your wife.
LOGAN:
I can handle my wife.
Right now, my concern is keeping
this operation from collapsing
like a house of cards.
HENDERSON:
You're protected, sir.
Every thread ends with Cummings.
He thinks he's running this,
and you need to keep
playing it that way.
LOGAN:
I know my part, Mr. Henderson.
You just do as you're told.
( recording clicks off )
JACK:
President Logan
supplied the terrorists
with the Sentox
nerve gas.
What?
His plan was to deploy the
nerve gas en route to Moscow.
That way, he could expose
the terrorists and use them
as an excuse to invoke the
military terms of the agreement
that he made earlier
with Suvarov.
This was all in an effort
to gain control
of the oil supply
in Central Asia.
David Palmer found out about it,
and that's why they killed him.
How do you know that recording
hasn't been fabricated?
I trust the source.
Mr. Secretary, I promise you,
this will stand up
under scrutiny.
I wish I could say
I was surprised, but I'm not.
I watched Charles Logan
rise on the tide
of his own ambition.
I was terrified
when he took the oath.
Sir, I'm very sorry
that I had to involve you,
but I needed someone
who had access
to hand-deliver this to
the Attorney General.
So you contacted me.
You're the only one
I could trust.
All right, then.
Thank you, sir.
You need to go
with your father.
He's going to need someone
to corroborate the evidence
to the Attorney General.
What about you?
I'm going to go dark
until the Attorney General
comes forward.
I'll call Buchanan; I'll let
him know what's happening.
All right. Jack,
everything's going
to be okay now.
Yeah. Go.
Okay.
Jack, one more thing.
What, sir?
( grunts )
Dad, what are you doing?!
Secure my daughter.
You're playing
a dangerous game here, Jack,
and you're
playing it wrong.
Turning Logan's crime
into a public spectacle
will not bring back
David Palmer.
It'll tear this nation apart.
You're not only destroying
the president,
you'll be destroying
the presidency.
The collateral damage
of the truth
will cripple this nation.
So what are you going to do?
Bury the evidence?
No.
You're coming
with me, Audrey,
and we'll use the evidence
to get Logan
to step down quietly.
Once he's gone,
we'll have a chance
to set things right again.
Doug, I'm trusting you
to keep this
item safe.
Audrey, are you coming
with me or not?
Dad, I can't.
Then secure them both
until you hear from me.
Dad, please, no!
Mr. Secretary,
you can't make
a deal with him!
Do you know what's going on
in the Situation Room?
It's some sort
of briefing.
No one told me.
It's a Class 3.
That's all I know.
I'm a department head.
I should be in all Class 3s.
That's all I know.
Shari, what was
that briefing about?
Just a protocol review.
I don't believe you.
Why not?
'Cause you're a bad liar.
Miles just gave me
a bunch of busywork
to do in the
Archives Room
to keep me out
of the briefing.
Do you ever think
there might be a reason
he kept you out?
He thinks I helped Audrey
break her
surveillance.
Is that what it was about?
I've already said too much.
Please don't ask me
any more questions.
Come on, Shari,
you owe me.
I stuck my neck out for you
with Miles.
Tell me what happened in there.
Miles found Audrey.
He activated a transponder
on her car.
So they know where she is?
We're running an operational
support right now.
That's what
the briefing was about.
They sent a tac team
ten minutes ago.
Please don't tell anyone
I said anything.
Here she comes.
( phone ringing )
Damn, she's good.
She set up
a proprietary com channel.
How long will it take
to track her call?
Not long.
Pick up.
( line continues ringing )
Somewhere in
the Valley.
Looks like
a pay phone.
I've got the
receiving end
narrowed down to
a one-mile radius.
Why isn't Audrey
picking up?
MILES:
Narrowing...
Got it.
Where?
Van Nuys Airport--
the emergency runway
adjacent to
the main field.
Move the tac team out now.
Van Nuys Airport.
Miles is forwarding
the coordinates.
Get me the president.
You said they sent the tac team
ten minutes ago.
Miles set me up, and you helped.
You're working
against us, Chloe.
You have no idea
what you've done.
Miles said that...
Miles is an idiot.
If anyone should know that,
it should be you.
I can't believe you
went along with him.
Please come with us,
Ms. O'Brian.
Where are we going?
Let's go.
Mr. President, I need to remind
you that we still don't have
confirmation that Audrey Raines
and Bauer are at the location.
You'll find out soon enough.
I'll have the military authority
follow up on it.
The military?
Sir, I just dispatched
my tac team.
Call them back.
I don't understand...
Jack Bauer is a very
sensitive problem.
There are political
ramifications.
I've decided
to handle him directly.
And besides, you must have
your hands full,
transitioning CTU
to Homeland Security.
I'll recall my team, sir.
Good.
Now the president
wants oversight
on the Bauer operation.
MILES:
He's the president.
He can do what he wants.
( phone rings )
Yeah.
CTU thinks they
found Bauer.
Where?
Jack, what if
my father's right?
What if he can get Logan
to step down quietly?
Maybe that is the best thing
for this country.
These people brokered
chemical weapons to terrorists.
They've killed an ex-president
of the United States.
Logan's not going
to make a deal
with your father,
and even if he did,
he wouldn't keep it.
Henderson wouldn't
let him.
The only thing
your father's doing right now
is making himself a target.
You want to help him?
Help me get the recording back
before he speaks to Logan.
Look, Mike,
this isn't me being territorial,
but if the president
wants Jack Bauer,
why doesn't he let
us take care of it?
Now, look, I've been
on other things.
Let me find out
what's going on.
I'll get back
to you, Karen.
Thank you, Mike.
...Will be lifted
within the next two hours,
but the curfew
will remain in effect...
( knocking )
HAL:
Come in.
That's only
six hours from now.
Okay.
David Palmer's body's being
flown back to DC at 7:00 a.m.
The president and I both want
to be there when the coffin's
put onto the plane.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
What's up, Mike?
I just got a call
from Karen Hayes at CTU.
Do you know
about the president's decision
to pull them off the acquisition
of Jack Bauer?
No, but what's the problem?
The problem is it doesn't
really make sense.
Karen's teams
are closer.
They can do it
more efficiently.
Bauer's more likely
to cooperate with them
than with a group of military
police he doesn't know.
Well, Karen and her team
have barely gotten CTU
back on its feet.
I'm sure the president
just feels more confident
with the military units
already in place
because of martial law.
Well, the military has
its hands full, Hal.
What do you want me
to say, Mike?
It's the president's call.
I can see it both ways.
( phone rings )
Yeah?
WOMAN:
Operations.
Beth, it's Mike Novick.
Put me through
to General Warren, please.
Yes, sir.
( phone rings )
This is Warren.
BETH:
Sir, I have Mike Novick
on the line for you.
Go ahead, Beth.
BETH:
He's on.
What is it, Mike?
General, can you give me
an update
on your search
for Jack Bauer?
What are you
talking about?
The one
the president ordered.
We never received such
a call from the president.
I see.
I-I'm sorry to disturb you,
General.
You should try to get some rest,
Mr. President.
Yes, I know.
I should try to get some rest.
What is it
you want, Mike?
I just got off the phone
with General Warren,
who's running
military operations
here in Los Angeles.
Why would
you be talking with him?
Karen Hayes
over at Homeland raised
a few good points
I thought I'd
follow up on.
What good points, Mike?
She doesn't understand
why she was taken
out of the loop on this
Jack Bauer situation.
You know, I really don't care
what Karen Hayes understands.
She should be doing her job
and not bothering my advisors,
asking questions
that diminish my authority.
Be that as it may,
I did follow up,
and, uh, now, frankly,
I'm a little mystified
by some things.
What things
mystify you, Mike?
Well, you told Homeland
that you wanted
the military
to pick up Jack Bauer,
but I just spoke
with General Warren,
and he's unaware of
any such directive.
Because I didn't go
through General Warren.
May I ask who you
did go through?
Mike, let's get
one thing straight:
I don't answer to you.
Of course not, sir.
However, I will
tell you this:
I-I have decided to use
a covert task force
to bring in Jack Bauer.
The reason I'm doing that
is because Bauer presents...
special circumstances.
Special circumstances?
I want this
completely off the radar, Mike.
The Chinese government may still
believe that Jack Bauer is dead.
If they find out
that he's alive,
they're going to blame us.
They're going to, uh, accuse us
of fabricating the story
of his death.
Um, wouldn't we be keeping
the circle smaller
if we let Karen handle this?
Her people already
know about Bauer.
They're working
under a secretive mandate.
You know what, Mike?
I am tired of being
second-guessed.
I've been dealing
with-with-with...
wall-to-wall crises
for the last 18 hours,
and I think I've done
a pretty damn good job
of leading the country.
Of course, Mr. President.
You came in here suggesting
that I should get some rest.
That's the one
recommendation
of yours
that I intend
to take.
Thank you, Mike.
to a public phone
at Van Nuys Airport.
If Audrey Raines
is at that location,
you're in a lot of trouble.
Miles, this situation is more
complicated than you think.
You have no idea what
you're dealing with.
But you do.
Yes.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because I can't.
You think the rules
don't apply to you
because you're smarter
than the rest of us,
but I have news for you.
They do, and you're not.
I won't miss you
when you're gone.
Miles.
Don't touch me.
What?
Jack Bauer did not kill
President Palmer.
He's a Federal fugitive
wanted for the murder
of a former president,
which means you're going
to jail, O'Brian.
For a long time.
Miles.
I don't think
you're as big of a jerk
as you pretend to be.
I need to speak to you.
Yes, sir.
No, sir, I've been there
the whole time.
What are you doing, Chloe?
You're supposed
to be in custody.
Miles let me out.
You're a worse liar than I am.
Shari, don't do that.
You helped Audrey Raines
break surveillance.
Yes, I did it
for a good reason.
I can't get
into it right now.
Well, I don't really think
you have a choice.
Listen to me for a minute.
Jack Bauer did not
kill President Palmer.
He knows who did it.
He may need
my help to prove it
and I can't help him
if I'm in custody.
Then why don't you
just tell Karen?
Because she won't believe me.
Nobody will,
not without evidence.
It's President Logan.
What are you talking about?
The evidence Jack is trying
to get implicates Logan
in the assassination of Palmer.
That's ridiculous, Chloe.
You know your
sexual harassment
charges against Miles?
I know you were lying.
You're sick and you need help,
and if you try to stop me
and it turns out I'm right
about Jack, and I am,
I will recommend you for
a psychiatric evaluation.
And you won't like that,
trust me.
MARTHA:
Charles.
You coming to bed soon?
I doubt if I'll get
much sleep tonight.
You should try.
Yeah.
You okay?
I'm fine.
It's just, uh...
It's been
a challenging day.
Okay.
Come to bed.
I will. Soon.
( phone ringing )
Yes?
I'm sorry to disturb you,
Mr. President,
but Secretary Heller
is on the line.
He insists on talking to you.
Tell him I'll call
him back tomorrow.
He says it's urgent, sir.
Put him through.
Yes, James.
Thanks for taking my call,
Mr. President.
You said it was urgent.
I need to see you, sir.
See me about what?
I'd rather speak
to you in person.
Fine, but I won't be back to
Washington for a couple of days.
I'm in L.A., sir.
I need to see you
tonight.
Tonight? What is this about?
I'll be there shortly
and we can discuss it then.
I don't like your tone, James.
In case you've forgotten,
you're addressing
the President
of the United States.
I know who I'm addressing.
And I think you know exactly
what this is about.
When will you be here?
Five minutes.
Fine.
James Heller? What does he want?
He's getting flak
from the Joint Chiefs
about my decision
to maintain martial law.
You would think
that these people
would show some allegiance.
Can't James handle it himself?
Apparently not.
Come to bed when you're done.
I will.
( speed-dialing )
( phone ringing )
We're leaving now.
How long will it take you
to get there?
Ten minutes.
We may not have
that much time.
James Heller is
on his way here.
He insisted on
seeing me right away.
Jack got to him.
What if Bauer's given
him the recording?
Heller's not stupid enough
to carry it with him,
and without it,
whatever he knows
or whatever he thinks
he knows won't matter.
You think Bauer still has it?
I'm sure of it.
I'll hold Heller off
as long as I can,
but you phone me the second
you have the evidence in hand.
Right.
What is Secretary Heller
doing here?
I don't know, ma'am.
But you have an idea.
My husband says
it's about his order
to maintain martial law,
but I think
it's something else.
If you know what it is,
will you please tell me?
I can't.
You can't?
Or you won't?
Please don't ask me
anything more, Mrs. Logan.
Whatever you tell me will remain
between the two of us.
I promise you.
Aaron...
you can trust me.
You know that.
Not here.
Meet me in
a couple minutes.
Where?
Outside the south stable.
James.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I hope this was important.
I know what you did.
I know what you're doing.
And I'm here
to put an end to it.
You have to be
a little more specific.
You are responsible
for the murder of David Palmer.
That's outrageous.
I heard a recording--
a conversation
between you and man named
Christopher Henderson.
When Palmer found out
about your insane plan,
Henderson had him killed.
And you let it happen.
Where is this recording?
It's in a safe place.
I would like to hear it.
Why?
You know exactly
what you said,
and so do I.
It's burnt into my memory.
How dare you stand there
and judge me?
You have no idea.
Until you sit in my chair,
you don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
Your chair
is not a throne, Charles.
I'm protecting the interests
of our country.
You mean oil.
Yes.
Yes!
This country needs energy
more than you or anybody
in this gridlocked
government cares to admit.
We'll see how you judge me
when the cost of oil
goes up over $100 a barrel
and the people
who put me in office
can't afford to heat their homes
or run their cars.
And you think that justifies
the blood on your hands?
What do you want?
I want you to drop
the trumped-up charges
against Jack Bauer.
And leave my daughter alone.
Anything else?
Announce your resignation
by tomorrow morning.
Blame it on the crushing
stress of today's events,
or blame it on
whatever you want,
just as long as you go public
by the start of
the morning news cycle.
And then what?
The recording will be kept
under lock and key,
and this will remain
between us.
Call in Vice
President Gardner.
I want to be here when you hand
him your letter of resignation.
Get in here.
I haven't been able
to contact Jack or Audrey.
I haven't talked
to them either.
CTU might have them
in custody.
I need to tap into
their current protocols.
Where's your workstation?
This way.
Homeland changed my access code.
I can create
a workaround.
If CTU has Jack,
it's all my fault.
( beeping )
( phone rings )
( grunts )
I can get us out of here.
Watch the door.
( grunts )
He's got restraints
in his pocket.
Wexler, status report.
Mark, come in.
Don't move.
Don't... move.
Slowly put the gun on the ground
and kick it towards me.
Do it!
Put your hands
where I can see them.
Give me the recording.
Slowly.
Stand up.
What did you do
to my partner?
He's fine.
Son of a bitch!
Take cover behind
the wheel! Now! Move!
Move!
What the hell's going on?!
They've come
for the recording!
If you and I are gonna get
through this alive,
we need to work together.
Give me my gun!
( grunts )
( gunfire continues )
( explosion )
Audrey?
HENDERSON:
I have her, Jack.
Now don't make me kill her.
There's been too much killing
today already, so just throw out
that recording.
Let her go, Christopher.
After I have the recording.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you protecting Logan?
I'm protecting something
much more important
than Charles Logan.
What?
The integrity
of our government.
Our government has no integrity.
Not when someone
like Charles Logan occupies
the Presidency.
Christopher,
you can make this right.
You can help me stop him.
Sorry, Jack.
Now throw me the recording.
I'll give you the recording
if you let
Audrey go.
I wish I could believe that.
I give you my word.
I'll tell you what.
I'll meet you halfway.
What does that mean?
( muffled groaning )
Get up.
Audrey?
Just hold still,
Ms. Raines.
( muffled screams )
Damn it, Christopher!
Here she comes, Jack.
Walk out slow,
or I'll kill you.
Audrey.
( panting )
HENDERSON:
That's far enough,
Ms. Raines.
What have you done to her?
The left brachial artery.
She has about three minutes
before she bleeds to death.
Now throw me that recording.
Jack, don't.
HENDERSON:
She's 15
seconds closer to dying, Jack.
Give me
the recording.
Jack, don't do it.
HENDERSON:
She's running
out of time.
Don't do it, Jack.
Don't. Don't
give it to him.
Here it is!
( pained groan )
( Audrey whimpers )
Audrey.
( panting )
Easy, easy, easy.
Easy. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Jack, go get him.
Go get him. Go.
Stay with me.
( Audrey panting )
I'll be right back.
( groans )
Here you are.
( groaning )
( Jack panting )
( panting )
( groaning )
I need to move you.
Come on.
( groans )
All it needs is your
signature, Mr. President.
James, we can find another way
to handle this.
There must be something
I can give you,
something that you want.
You're giving me
exactly what I want.
You asked to see me,
Mr. President?
Hi, Jim.
I thought you'd be on a
plane back to Washington.
What are you
doing here?
I'll let
President Logan
tell you.
Mr. President.
Hal...
( phone rings )
Yes.
HENDERSON:
I have the recording.
Really?
I'll call you back
after I've secured a vehicle.
Thank you.
Hal,
I'm asking Secretary Heller
to tender his resignation.
I wanted you here
as a witness.
What?!
He came here to accuse me
of being complicit
in today's
terrorist attacks.
I don't know
how he can
make such an accusation
without any evidence.
He orchestrated a conspiracy
to let terrorists acquire
stolen nerve gas.
That's insane, James.
He sanctioned the assassination
of David Palmer!
And I have the evidence.
Where? Show it to us.
Who was on the phone?
Who made that call?
( two beeps )
I want your resignation
on my desk by the morning.
If any harm comes
to my daughter...
Gentlemen!
Please
escort Secretary Heller
out of my home.
( Audrey whimpers )
( Audrey screams )
www.tvsubtitles.net