I'm issuing an executive order,
imposing a curfew
on all civilians
in the Los Angeles
metropolitan area.
This curfew will be effective
immediately and will be enforced
by the military.
They're talking about this
like it's
an illegal action.
Don't worry, Mr. President.
I'm in control of the situation.
Hasn't it ever occurred to you
that he proposed this whole
thing to set you up for a fall?
Hal's only motivation
is what's best for the country.
There's going to be a fallout.
And you know it.
You're here to shut
this place down, aren't you?
I told you before,
the White House...
I know what you
told me before.
Now tell me the truth.
CTU is being absorbed
by Homeland,
which means
from now on,
every operational decision
needs to go through me.
There's something
from my brother
I need to give you personally.
I should be there
within the hour.
You coming here?
I know
it sounds impulsive, Aaron,
but I'd rather see you
sooner than later.
I'm hoping there's somewhere
we can meet discreetly.
( tires squealing )
Does she have the schematics
and the access codes?
Yes. Everything
we need.
Release the Sentox here...
and 200,000 people die.
The decryption key
is Charlie-Alpha
3-9-Alpha.
It worked.
This is what
you wanted.
JACK:
Drop the gun!
I'm with the German Federal
Intelligence Service.
I've been undercover
for the last six months,
gathering intel
on Collette's clientele.
If we don't find Bierko,
hundreds of thousands
of innocent people
will die here today.
JACK:
Let him go!
He's given us what we want!
Put your hands up!
As for the data
I sold to Bierko,
it's something that I received
from a contact
from the Department
of Defense.
What's his name?
Her name?
Audrey Raines.
You were lying to me.
She sold me the
information, Mr. Bauer.
Apparently, she
had a price.
Chloe, I need you to do
something for me right away.
Check out Audrey Raines's
activities in the
last 18 months.
Audrey? Why?
I'll explain later.
I'm particularly interested
in any unusual connection
between her and Christopher
Henderson or Walt Cummings.
You think she has something
to do with their conspiracy?
I don't know what to think.
Please do it quickly.
Audrey.
Yes, sir?
I'm afraid I have to
take you into custody.
What? I don't understand.
Am I being arrested?
Detained.
On what grounds?
Collette Stenger's been passing
information to Bierko,
information he apparently
intends to use
in his next attack.
She claims
she got the information
from someone at DoD,
and she named you
as the source.
She's lying.
That's impossible.
We already uncovered one mole
in the White House today,
Audrey.
I have no choice.
What kind of information
did Stenger say I gave her?
I've told you as much
as I can at this point.
Prep Ms. Raines
for interrogation.
Does Jack know that
I'm being detained?
Yes.
He sanctioned it.
COLLETTE:
It's the truth.
Audrey Raines was my contact
at the Department of Defense.
You met with her
face-to-face?
Yes.
Good, then you'll be able to
recognize her when you see her.
Of course.
CTU AGENT:
She identified Ms. Raines
from photographs
on the way here.
If you were lying to me,
I'm gonna make this
the worst day of your life.
You understand?
Put her in Holding.
Burke's interrogation methods
should only be used
as a last resort.
The situation warrants
a more aggressive approach.
Then do the same thing
to Collette Stenger.
Stenger is protected
by an immunity agreement.
We can't touch her
unless the information
she's provided turns
out to be false;
then we can nullify
the agreement.
So we can torture
our own people,
but we can't
touch a criminal?
I've known Audrey Raines
for years.
I trust her implicitly.
So does everyone else.
Maybe that's the problem.
Bill, we don't have
the luxury of time.
Intel indicates that
an attack is imminent--
within an hour.
Tens, maybe hundreds
of thousands of Americans
are at risk,
and we just got information
that Audrey Raines
knows about it.
Karen, the decision
is yours.
But any adverse consequences
that result from insufficiently
aggressive action taken now
will come down hard on you.
What is Agent Burke doing here?
KAREN:
We're talking about authorizing
the medical interrogation.
On Audrey?
Yes.
That's ridiculous.
I'll handle
the interrogation.
I can't allow that.
Karen, I brought this to you.
I called it in.
You can't pull me off
of this now.
Your emotional involvement
with Ms. Raines
is not exactly a secret, Jack.
That has nothing
to do with this.
That's right.
You always put the work first.
You never let your feelings
get involved.
Is that what happened
with Nina Myers?
Nina Myers was a mistake--
I've never denied that--
but she was deep cover
for years before
I even met her.
She fooled a lot of people
for a long time, not just me.
Well, maybe Audrey
is fooling people, too.
You might be right, Karen,
but if I were you,
I would think twice about
who you're willing to
invasively interrogate.
Audrey Raines is
the senior advisor
to the Secretary of
Defense, James Heller,
who happens to be her father!
And if you were wrong,
he's gonna eat you alive.
At least let Jack talk to her
for ten minutes first.
She deserves that much.
If she's guilty...
she doesn't deserve anything.
That's the point.
She hasn't
been proven guilty.
After she's been prepped, you
can see her for ten minutes.
But at the first sign
you're less than objective,
you're out.
Understood.
Thanks, Bill.
I don't believe
Audrey is guilty
of anything, Jack.
Neither do I.
The one thing we do know is,
Bierko is going
to release the Sentox
in the city sometime
in the next hour.
If Audrey knows anything
that can help us find him,
she needs to tell us now.
Keep an eye on the
traffic patrol.
Bierko's gonna need to
move those canisters.
He's gonna need
transportation.
With the curfew in place,
I might get lucky
and pick up a trail.
Yeah.
( man groans )
( siren whoops )
( grunts and groans )
( scuffling )
Hey, break it up!
( man groans )
OFFICER:
Break it up now!
Gentlemen, I said, break it up!
( gunshot )
Take their uniforms and weapons.
Now we have a police
escort to the target,
the curfew won't
be a problem.
( whispering ):
Chloe, walk with me.
You were doing background
on Audrey?
Yeah.
What have you got?
You're not going to like it.
I found the connection between
Walt Cummings and Audrey.
What kind of a connection?
They dealt with each other
a few times--
the usual stuff between DoD
and the White House.
But there is something else.
What?
Chloe, what?
They both stayed at a place
called the River Hotel
in Pikesville,
Maryland,
last April.
So?
So, Pikesville isn't
exactly a hot spot
with top-ranking
federal officials.
It wasn't a coincidence
that they were there
the same night.
Chloe, what are you
trying to say?
They didn't just stay
in the same hotel,
but they stayed
in the same room.
How could you
possibly know that?
Because I e-mailed photos
of them to the manager.
He recognized them both.
He showed me phone bills,
room service receipts.
I can show you a few
if you want.
No. I'm sorry.
I believe you.
It doesn't mean she was part
of their conspiracy,
but it doesn't exactly
look that good either.
Make copies of everything
you've got
and put them in a folder for me.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
My name is Shari Rothenberg.
I work in Section Five
downstairs.
I know where Section Five is.
Right. Uh, Mr. Buchanan told me
to report to Chloe O'Brian.
Is that you?
You're gonna have
to wait a second.
Um, I'm here to replace Edgar.
I understand he died
in the attack.
Yes, he did.
Well, if he was
a friend of yours,
I'm sorry.
( sighs )
Thanks.
He worked at Station Six.
It's right there.
Are you familiar
with the Gavilan
matrix analyzer?
Yes, I am.
Use it to make sure
our databases are current.
Some of them may have
fallen behind in the
past couple of hours.
No problem.
( sighs )
( phone ringing musical tones )
Jack.
Sit down.
That's the dossier you gave me
on Collette Stenger.
She says that you provided her
with information
from the DoD.
I know. Bill told me.
That's ridiculous.
You know it.
Jack, you're wasting time
that we don't have.
I had to ask CTU
so that I could
interrogate you.
I have a job to do.
If I don't do it,
Burke will, and I promise you,
you do not want to see him
walk through that door.
Fine.
What kind of information
did she say I gave her?
She said you provided her
with a structural schematic
of Bierko's next target.
What kind of structure?
She didn't know.
She just delivered the package.
She claims
that I gave her information,
yet she can't tell you
what that information is,
and that's enough
to make me a suspect?!
Damn it, Audrey! You know
what this nerve gas does?
They are planning
another attack.
We will not ignore any leads.
I have nothing to do
with these terrorists.
How did Collette Stenger
get your name?
I don't know.
My father is
the Secretary of Defense.
I'm an easy target.
Maybe she's trying
to use him or embarrass him.
Is he involved?
Oh, Jack, you know him
better than that.
You worked with him.
He would never do anything
outside the law,
and neither would I.
The two men that we know
are part of the conspiracy
are Walt Cummings and
Christopher Henderson.
Have you had any
contact with these men?
Christopher Henderson.
I have never heard...
I'd never heard of him
before today
and, um...
Walt Cummings I-I have met
a couple of times, yes.
Where?
Um, DoD briefings.
That's it?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Open it.
The River Hotel,
Pikesville, last April.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Um... We happened
to be there at the same time.
We may have had
a drink or two together.
You weren't having
drinks with him.
You shared a room with him.
You slept with him.
Yes.
I was still recovering
from losing you, Jack.
He, uh...
He had just separated
from his wife,
and I slept with him once
and then I broke it off.
Why'd you break it off?
Jack, please, it's complicated.
Why did you break it off?!
Because he wasn't you.
Why did you lie to me
when I asked you
the first time?
'Cause I, I was...
I was afraid
that you'd think less of me,
that you wouldn't
be able to forgive me.
Because you slept with someone
after you thought I was dead?
Because I slept with someone
who turned out
to be a traitor, Jack.
Is that the only time
you spent with Cummings?
Yes.
Did he ever
talk to you
about a terrorist attack,
nerve gas?
No.
He ever mention
Christopher Henderson?
No.
Damn it, Audrey!
Jack, I... Jack!
Tell me the truth!
I am telling
you the t...
You've already
lied to me once.
You tell me what you
know, or I promise you
this will become
very unpleasant.
I'm telling you
everything.
All right.
Do what you have to do.
Damn it, Audrey.
Tell me the truth!
Jack. I am telling you
the truth, I swear.
This is over!
You understand? This is over!
If you ask me,
she broke him
and not the
other way around.
Karen.
He didn't push her hard enough,
and you know it.
He's protecting her.
She's innocent.
We have to be certain.
I am certain.
Jack is certain.
Well, I'm not.
Karen.
Send Burke in.
I have to do this, Bill.
I can't waste
any more time, and
make sure that Jack
doesn't interfere.
Okay, I'll pass that on.
Shari. That was
the agent
at Bierko's safe house.
The place is empty.
Forensics is still looking, but
they don't expect to find much.
Upload that information
onto the subnets.
Oh. Right.
I checked your file.
You're not qualified
for Level Three work,
and that is not a Three.
I'm provisionally qualified.
It's all in my
supplemental file. Go ahead
and check it
if you want.
All right, Shari.
First mistake, I yank
the provisional
and you're out of here.
What's with him?
Two years ago
we both worked
in the San Francisco office.
There was a sexual
harassment thing.
Miles?
It was subtle at first,
and then it
got really bad.
Finally filed
a grievance.
What happened?
He got off
with a warning.
These things are
really hard to prove.
They said we
didn't have
enough evidence
to go to trial.
I can't get
into any details.
The file is sealed.
Don't worry.
I don't need details.
But I guess I'd better
not make any mistakes.
Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm sorry. This is
out of my control.
Karen wants
to push Audrey
a little harder.
No, her interrogation
is over.
Jack, I'll try to stall her
as long as I can.
Jack, I have orders
to take Miss Raines to Holding
for further interrogation.
I don't care about your orders.
That's not gonna happen.
Get out of my way.
Jack, stop it!
Jack, don't make this
any harder than it is.
( taser buzzing )
AUDREY:
Stop it, Jack! Stop it! Jack!
Bill, do something!
Bill!
Hello.
Mr. Henderson, it's Brennan.
Is Wayne Palmer dead yet?
No.
Explain.
We rolled his car, but
he survived and got away.
It was sloppy work.
We'll make it right.
Well, you damn well better.
You know what's at stake.
Yes, sir.
PALMER:
This is Wayne Palmer.
At the tone, leave a message.
Steve, has Wayne Palmer
come through a checkpoint
within the last half hour?
Yeah, he was cleared through
Checkpoint 6 30 minutes ago.
What, he's not here yet?
No, he's not, and I can't
reach him on his cell.
If you're worried, I
can send out an alert.
No.
Actually, he kind of wanted to
keep his visit under the radar.
I think I'm going to go out
there and take a look myself,
in case he had car trouble
or something.
Do me a favor.
Keep this between us,
would you?
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
KAREN:
You need to
calm down, Jack,
and remember
who's in charge.
Audrey Raines is innocent.
She slept with a known
conspirator and lied about it.
That doesn't concern you?
She slept with him once
and lied about it
because she was embarrassed.
That hardly makes her
part of this conspiracy.
Why did Collette Stenger
name her as the source?
She must have gotten
Audrey's name from Henderson.
Why would Henderson want
to implicate Audrey?
Henderson doesn't want
to implicate Audrey.
He's coming after me.
He's trying to make me
lose focus.
And he's trying
to pull you off target.
And he's done it.
These plans must
have been made
some time ago, when Henderson
had every reason to believe
you were gonna be killed.
Karen, listen to me.
This is what I do for a living.
And the first rule
of engagement
is that you have
a contingency plan.
And this is his,
and it's working.
You're getting ready
to interrogate Audrey Raines
when you should be
interrogating Collette Stenger,
because she still has
information that we don't have!
Stenger has immunity.
She's being protected
by a federal marshal.
That's your doing, Jack.
You made that deal!
I know.
But if I can prove
that Collette Stenger
is withholding information
from us,
that act alone
negates her deal.
I'll be able to start
questioning her again.
She will give me Henderson.
And once I have Henderson,
he will lead us
to the nerve gas,
and that's what
we're supposed to be
focused on!
What are you suggesting
we do, Jack?
Let me and Chloe find proof that
Collette Stenger is lying to us.
If we don't,
you lose nothing.
But if we do, we can
stop this thing from happening,
I promise you.
Karen, please.
Excuse me.
These matrix sweeps
are partials only.
Where's the rest of the data?
I thought matrix data
could be sent unfiltered.
That's not protocol.
I thought it was
all right in house.
Only if it's authorized.
Who authorized it?
I did.
She did it under
my authority.
I take full responsibility.
I don't believe you.
Believe what you want.
That would be sloppy, O'Brian.
You don't work
like that.
She told you about my alleged
sexual harassment, right?
Well, she's lying.
Listen...
No, you listen.
There are 17 canisters of
nerve gas about to be deployed
somewhere in Los Angeles, and
we're trying to find them.
If you interrupt our work
one more time, I'll file
a complaint with Division.
Then you'll see what
protocol's all about.
Thank you.
Chloe, we need to help Audrey.
We don't have much time.
How?
We need to find
the connection
between Collette Stenger
and Henderson.
We found Collette's name
on Henderson's computer.
It's not enough.
We need proof that they had
direct contact,
preferably more than once.
You think Henderson gave
Collette Audrey's name?
I'm sure of it. I want you
to use outside agencies,
including foreign.
Put it on a priority channel.
I'm on it.
We have an
important delivery.
There's no delivery scheduled.
I'm gonna need to call this in.
( gunshots )
Stay out here
and watch the perimeter.
( indistinct conversation )
Who's in charge?
I am.
We need access
to the control room.
Can you take us there?
What are you guys doing here?
Can you take us
to the control room?
Yeah. It's that way.
Good.
Keep cooperating and no more
of your friends will die.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Mikhail, take the canisters
to the main distribution tank.
Quickly!
( steam hissing )
This is it.
Don't move.
Hands away from the console.
Sam, what's going on?
Ah, Sam... I'm not an engineer,
but I know enough,
so you'd be wise not to try
to deceive me.
What we're doing here
is very simple.
We're going to release
a certain substance
so that it flows
into your pipelines.
What kind of substance?
That's not your concern.
But at the pressure
which currently prevails
in these pipes, the substance
will react chemically
with the gas
and become inert.
So I need the pressure reduced
by about 50%.
Sam, don't do it.
Do you understand what I want?
You want PSI cut by half.
Exactly.
And how long will it take?
Could take an hour.
You don't seem to care very much
for your friends, do you, Sam?
No, no, don't!
I might be able to do it
in 30 minutes.
You have 15.
Better get started.
PALMER:
Don't move!
Drop the gun.
Now!
Move away from it.
Now get on your knees.
Mr. Palmer.
It's Aaron.
Oh, God.
Aaron, what are you
doing out here?
I was looking for you, sir.
So are some other people.
Let's go.
( gasps )
BURKE:
Ms. Raines, we know you
conspired with Mr. Cummings.
I didn't.
Who else in the White House
was involved?
I don't know.
You know, Ms. Raines.
I don't have... have any names.
You're gonna
give me a name...
I swear I don't know, I...
We don't have the time,
Ms. Raines.
Give me a name!
I don't... I swear.
I don't know.
Chloe, what have you got?
I found some masked entries in
Collette Stenger's cell phone.
The decryption program...
Come on, Chloe.
Bottom line: Henderson placed
eight cell phone calls
to Collette Stenger
within the past three months.
Where's Collette Stenger now?
Holding Room 3.
Bill, we have a connection
between Henderson
and Collette Stinger.
She received eight calls
from him that she
didn't tell us about.
That voids her agreement.
It's off.
That's for
the president to decide.
Call the president!
You need a rescinding order
to question her, Jack.
Get him to back off of Audrey!
Get me the president.
What's your connection
with Christopher Henderson?
I have an immunity agreement
signed by your president.
She's right.
She can't be
questioned.
We have proof
that she withheld information.
Her deal's been rescinded.
The order's on its way.
When it gets here,
she's all yours.
An innocent woman is being
interrogated because of her.
Look, I'm sorry, sir,
but  you have to go.
We know you lied to us.
We know that you did not get the
schematics from Audrey Raines.
Henderson told you to
use her name in case you
got in trouble, right?
You do not want to try me.
Yes.
He tell you why?
No.
He's using you.
He wanted you to get
inside my head.
It worked.
Now I'm... upset.
You have three seconds to
tell me where the target is,
or I will kill you.
Where's the target?!
A natural gas
distribution center.
There are dozens of those
in the city. Which one?
I don't know.
I swear.
( hammer cocking )
I don't know.
I don't.
Jack, what's going on?
Bierko's targeting
a natural gas
distribution center,
but we don't know which one.
Natural gas?
He can use it as a delivery
system for the Sentox.
He can get it
into people's homes.
I need you to get Chloe on it.
We need to find out which one.
Right. The rescinding
order will be here
in 15 minutes.
Good. Give it to the marshal.
He'll be looking for this, too.
Please, no more.
I'm begging you.
Please. Don't do
that. Please...
( sobbing )
Please. I'm telling
you the truth.
You're bringing this
on yourself.
( screams )No!
Stop it! Make him...
This can end whenever
you want it to...
Let her go!
Shut it down now!
Jack!
You are finished in here.
She is innocent.
You can confirm it
with Buchanan.
I said you're finished.
Get out!
Audrey, are you all right?
I don't know.
It's over.
I promise you,
it's over for good.
My God, what's happening to me?
What's happening?
( moans )
Henderson set you up...
to get at me, to throw me
off his trail.
Come here.
I'm so sorry.
Jack, the only thing
that got me through this...
was knowing that you would come.
I knew you would come.
I'm so sorry.
( sniffles )
( cell phone rings )
Bauer.
Jack, it's Bill. We need you.
Go.
Jack?
I'll be right there.
Yep.
Bill, I want you to send someone
over from medical
to Interrogation 1 to
tend to Audrey Raines.
Okay.
Thanks.
Gonna be all right?
Go. It's okay.
Our satellite covers only 60%
of the distribution centers.
If our target's not in that
grouping, we're out of luck.
Can we redirect
any other satellite?
I'm trying.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, the medic's
on the way.
JACK:
Did you identify
the distribution center
that they're gonna hit?
We're pulling in
more satellites.
Our analysts tell us
once the Sentox hits
the main tank, it goes
right into the pipes,
where it becomes impossible
to stop.
From there, it goes straight
into people's homes.
How many casualties
are we talking about?
The largest centers serve
90,000 people.
We could have twice
that many casualties.
If our intel is correct,
we have 15 minutes.
Okay, I'll prep a team
with Curtis. We'll go airborne.
We'll be ready as soon
as you ID a target.
Mr. Buchanan?
There may be a faster way.
I was a chem major
at Cal Tech.
Most toxins become inert
under high pressure.
The PSI would have
to be lowered
before the nerve gas
was introduced.
Chloe, can you monitor
the pressure levels
at the distribution centers?
Yeah. I have citywide
readings of them all.
Hold on.
Wilshire Gas Company.
The PSI has dropped to 75%
in the past ten minutes.
We have to assume that's it.
I'll tell Jack.
Great work, Sherry.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Did you see the way his hand
brushed across my shoulder
as he walked by?
What?
That was wrong.
He shouldn't have done that.
( rustling )
What is it?
Get down!
Get in the car!
JACK:
Chloe, what's the PSI level?
PSI level is down to 57%.
Another seven is all they need
to deploy the Sentox.
How long will that take?
Four, maybe five minutes.
Jack, the PSI level
can only be adjusted
from the main control room.
It's the large building
in the center of the complex
two floors down from the roof.
Copy that.
Okay, we'll insert here.
We'll advance
to the control room,
locate and secure the canisters.
We're almost there.
The noise from the plant
should cover our descent.
We're ready.
Good.
Get back here.
How much longer?
A few more minutes.
I can't lower the pressure
any faster
without risking a shutdown.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Do you have any
heat signatures?
Yes, but I can only scan
from the exterior of the site.
There are two guards
patrolling the perimeter.
I've given the pilot
an approach vector
to keep you from
their line of sight.
Maintain this position!
Go!
CTU,
the team's away.
They're on the roof.
The PSI level is down
to 54%.
CTU, we're inside.
Jack, Bierko will be ready
to deploy any minute.
Copy that.
( silenced gunshots )
Silencers off.
Door.
Bierko!
( gunshots continue )
( beep )
Keep moving! Cover me!
Curtis, the Sentox is already
in the system.
Who's in charge here?!
Listen to me.
You have Sentox nerve gas
running through your pipeline.
Can you shut down
the pumps?
By the time we power down,
gas will be
in the main tanks,
then it's out into the city.
Where's the closest pipeline
that feeds those tanks?
Just out the door
to your left.
It'll have a red arrow
on it.
Give me the C4 and a timer,
then get these people
out of here.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, what are you doing?
In order to deliver the Sentox,
it had to mix with natural gas.
If we could ignite that gas
before it leaves the plant,
the Sentox will
be incinerated.
Bill, this is the last chance
we've got to stop this threat.
The Sentox has been in
the system for one minute.
You have 50 seconds
before it gets out.
Charge has been set.
Curtis, are you clear?
Just about.
Keep going.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, are you clear?
Jack?
Jack, respond.
Come on, Jack.
( loud explosions )
Jack, you okay?
Curtis, I got a visual
on Bierko.
Jack, you won't have time
before the main
tank explodes.
Right now he's our only
connection to Henderson.
Jack!
Bill, he's going in.
JACK:
Bierko!
( rumbling explosion )
( loud thud )
Jack, that's it.
The main tanks are going.
Get out!
www.tvsubtitles.net