Any problems getting
the canisters out?
No. They were hidden exactly
where you said they'd be.
Russians will finally
understand the consequences
of occupying our homeland when
we turn Moscow into a graveyard.
Erwich has just cleared
airport security.
Then the authorities don't know
anything's been stolen.
Not yet.
Then the only thing we have
left to take care of is Bauer.
You paged me?
I need you to do something.
We have our hands full
searching for the nerve gas.
Bauer is a priority.
I just signed a treaty.
Now all of a sudden
I find out
that the terrorists
are still out there...
with nerve gas.
MARTHA:
You people have to listen to me.
I had a document.
It was hidden in my blouse.
It's gone.
Someone stole it from me.
This is what she was like
before you sent her to Vermont.
Are you suggesting
that I readmit her?
For her sake, if nothing else.
Aaron, my wife is gone.
We have
a priority alert.
You've been burrowing
into classified
CTU protocols
without authorization.
SPENSER:
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Stop. I know you logged on
to the security subsystem
where you had no right to be.
AUDREY:
Someone knew
that Jack was alive.
It's critical
to our investigation
that we find out who that was.
( grunting )
Did you let that man into CTU?
This man
is a professional assassin.
He just killed Dr. Paulson,
he tried to kill me.
Who told you to let
that man into CTU?
The White House.
Mr. Cummings.
JACK:
I don't understand
the problem.
David Palmer was murdered
because he was about
to expose Walt Cummings'
connection to the terrorists.
When Cummings failed to frame
me for Palmer's murder,
he tried to kill me.
All that may be true, Jack,
but we don't have proof.
We can prove that Cummings
used Spenser to get
Jack's assassin into CTU.
All we have
is Spenser's word.
That's not enough
to build a case.
You don't
have time to build a case.
You want the nerve gas,
Cummings
is your connection.
Cummings is the President's
Chief Advisor.
How exactly do you
suggest we get to him?
I can secretly meet
with Mike Novick,
enlist his help.
How do we know
Novick's not in this
with Cummings?
Because I know him.
He'll listen to me.
And the President
will listen to him.
With Novick's help,
we can isolate Cummings.
Jack, as much
as I appreciate
you wanting
to be involved,
you don't work here
anymore.
That's exactly the reason
why I should do this.
If it backfires, there'll
be no fallout on you.
I think it's worth a try.
I agree.
It's your call.
( sighs )
All right, Jack.
But just so we're clear,
this is about
finding the nerve gas,
not getting revenge
for David Palmer.
Understood.
Work out your protocols
with Ms. Raines.
We'll keep
looking through
Cummings' background
for anything
that supports our case.
We're gonna need to set up
a secure channel for you
to contact us on.
We'll drop you
as close to Logan's
retreat as possible.
Can you bring up
the satellite photo
of the compound?
Jack, I'm sorry if
I'm being a little distant.
I just...
It's taking me a little while
to get used to you being alive.
I understand.
I'll call Novick.
Jack.
When Cummings finds out
that you're still alive,
he's gonna come after you again.
Yeah.
( cell phone ringing )
Yes?
NATHANSON:
Is Bauer dead?
I haven't received
confirmation yet.
Your man should have
taken care of this by now.
Perhaps he had to alter
his strike window.
Has the nerve gas
reached the port?
Not yet.
But they should
be arriving any minute.
Good. I have to go.
I'm late for a briefing.
You have all the shipping
documents in order?
The canisters
will arrive at port
in your country in eight days.
Ground transportation to your
base camp will take another day.
Will you need my help
getting them to your target?
No. I've arranged
transport to Moscow.
( indistinct talking )
Have they found my wife yet?
No, sir,
but Secret Service is confident
she's still
on the grounds.
If they're so damn confident,
why can't anyone find her?
What the hell
are they doing?
I'm sure it's just a matter
of time, Mr. President.
Sorry I'm late.
I was just
setting up the video.
This was made
by terrorists,
to document the effects
of exposure to nerve gas.
It was recovered
from a training camp
two years ago.
Disorientation occurs
moments
after exposure.
Now the video jumps forward,
no more than a couple
of minutes, we estimate.
Within that time,
there's permanent damage
to the central
nervous system.
Violent seizures
take over.
Bronchial membranes
blister and peel away.
Death occurs within...
Stop.
Now, according
to DOD,
the Sentox-Six nerve gas
stolen from the airport
is far more lethal than the gas
we just saw used.
( beeping )
If released in a town
or city, for example,
the cloud will remain lethal
for much longer.
Are we any closer
to finding the canisters?
There haven't been any reports
of progress, sir.
Excuse me,
Mr. President.
I need to return a call
to the State Department.
Do you have
those updates, Walt?
Yes, here's one from CTU.
Also one from Homeland Security.
( phone beeping )
This is Bauer.
Jack. Mike Novick.
It's good to hear your voice.
Yours, too, Mike.
I'm so sorry about David Palmer.
I know how much
he meant to you.
Yeah...
What's going on?
I have a lead on
the stolen nerve gas.
Isn't CTU
coordinating
the search?
This is something I need
to bring directly to you.
I don't understand.
I can't talk about it
on the phone, Mike.
We need to meet.
No one can know about this,
not even the President.
I'm not comfortable with
all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me some idea
what this is about.
It concerns Walt Cummings.
There's an area
a few hundred yards outside
the southwest gate.
It's at the far side
of the property
from the main house.
Thanks, Mike.
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
Jack...
Hey.
They said we can leave soon.
I know, I heard.
What about you?
Are you coming home
with us?
No, I need to stay here.
CTU still
needs my help.
Derek, I'd like to speak
with your mom for a moment,
is that all right?
Yeah, of course.
Take him downstairs.
She'll be there soon.
You're not coming back
to us at all, are you?
No.
I never thought I was going
to be back here at CTU.
I would never have
gotten you involved
in all of this,
I promise you.
It's the woman who interviewed
me, isn't it? Audrey Raines.
You were involved with her.
I could tell by the way
you looked at each other.
I was with her before
I had to disappear.
Are you still
in love with her?
Yes.
Does she still love you?
I don't know.
Mr. Bauer.
Your transportation's
standing by.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Thank you.
Yeah.
( sniffling )
NOVICK'S VOICE:
I'm not comfortable
with all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me
some idea what this is about.
JACK'S VOICE:
It concerns Walt Cummings.
NOVICK'S VOICE:
There's an area,
a few hundred yards outside
the southwest gate.
It's at the far side of the
property from the main house.
Your man didn't
do his job.
Don't put that
on me, Nathanson.
You were supposed to have
Bauer killed hours ago.
I'm not going
to warn you again.
Pull yourself together.
You heard the call, didn't you?
Bauer's coming here to expose
my role in all this.
You're assuming
he knows the extent of it.
Well, it's obvious
he knows enough.
Now, what the hell
am I supposed to do?
At this point, there's only
one thing you can do.
Mrs. Logan,
please come out
of there.
Mrs. Logan...
Aaron...
don't let them take me.
You've got to
listen to me.
They're just trying
to help you.
No. No.
They're trying to set me up.
They're trying to make it
look like
I had a breakdown,
so they can
cart me off to some
psychiatric hospital.
Ma'am...
Aaron...
It's someone in my
husband's administration.
They're trying
to shut me up
because I know the truth.
What truth?
David Palmer.
I know...
( radio static )
Don't let him take
me, Aaron. Please?
We have our orders,
Mrs. Logan.
I'm sorry.
Aaron... please...
Aaron...
Audrey, did you check
with the airports?
Yes. They've all been alerted
on the missing canisters.
And CHP?
Same thing.
Trucks are being checked
at all major interstates.
Make sure there's no mention
of the Sentox nerve gas.
The White House is clear
about that.
Yes, I know.
The bulletin only describes
the missing canisters.
There's no mention
of chemical weapons.
Good. The last thing we need
is for the public to find out
that nerve gas is out there.
( quiet beep )
( loud beep )
( clanking )
Schaeffer...
...what were you
doing in there?
Making sure the canisters
were secured properly.
Don't want them
knocking around
when this gets loaded
onto a ship.
My men secured the canisters
according to my instructions.
You don't need
to be concerned.
All right.
Here are the customs
documents you need
when the shipment arrives,
along with the remote
trigger and the arming codes.
I'll take the rest
of my payment now.
Our arrangement was you'll get
your final installment
when the ship
left port.
There's not gonna be a problem.
They're loading out
in less than an hour.
Then you won't have long
to wait.
Fine.
Ms. Raines?
Yes.
We've been released.
Oh, good.
Can I ask you
something?
Of course.
Do you still have
feelings for Jack?
I'm sorry,
but that's personal.
I know, but he's been
living with my son and me
for the last six months.
We started to become a family...
...and I care about him.
Do you know
he still loves you?
If you don't love him,
let him go.
( phone rings )
Bauer.
Jack, it's Audrey.
What's going on?
Jack...
What?
Audrey, what?
When this is over,
are you coming back?
I don't know.
Are you going back
to Diane?
No...
I don't know what
I'm doing yet.
I haven't had any time
to think about it.
Is it true what she said?
What'd she say?
That you still love me.
I never stopped
loving you...
not for one second.
Then don't go away
again, Jack, please.
It's more complicated
than that.
I know.
It's time.
I gotta go.
Jack...
I have to go.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Okay. Bye.
No, no!
Keep me out of this!
The last thing I want to do
is comment to the press
about the roadblocks
going up.
And we can't have any
leaks about the nerve gas.
It would just
cause a panic.
Come in.
Pardon me, sir.
We found Mrs. Logan.
Is she all right?
She's fine, sir.
She was hiding
in the stables.
( heavy sigh )
Stables? What the hell
did she think
she was doing?
Mr. President...
I feel awkward
mentioning this, but...
Mrs. Logan said
some things...
About David Palmer.
Yes, sir.
I've heard her conspiracy
theories, Aaron.
I've heard them all.
But thank you
for your concern, Aaron.
They found my wife.
Good.
Mr. President...
we need to talk.
What is it, Walt?
I was hoping
to spare you from this,
but I'm afraid Jack Bauer
is forcing my hand.
He's on his way here to
meet with Mike Novick.
Bauer? Why?
He's going to accuse me
of helping
the terrorists
acquire the nerve gas.
That's ridiculous.
No, sir.
It's the truth.
What did you say?
Through a proxy, I leaked
information to
the terrorists
about where the nerve
gas was hidden.
You have to understand, sir,
this gas was never going
to pose a threat
to American lives.
Never pose a threat?!
People died in the airport!
Hostages were killed!
We had hoped to limit
the collateral damage.
"Collateral damage"?!
What are you thinking?
This is an unspeakable crime.
Walt... you have to answer
for this.
Mr. President...
it's in your best
interest to hear me out
before you make
that phone call.
( slams receiver )
What do you mean
"my best interest"?
Sentox gas is being smuggled
out of the country
by separatists who think
they are going to use it
against the Russians.
However, that nerve gas will
never reach Russian soil.
And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators
on those gas canisters.
As soon as they reach
the terrorists' base,
we'll trigger the
canisters by satellite
and release the gas.
So everything
that happened today
was just to kill
a some terrorists?
No, the goal is to
produce a smoking gun,
proof of the existence
of weapons of mass destruction
in Central Asia.
This is unbelievable.
It's necessary.
It will finally
give us a pretext
to increase our military
presence in the region,
guaranteeing the flow of oil
for the next generation.
How dare you.
How dare you act
without my consent.
How dare you put
this administration--
this entire country in jeopardy.
You're a traitor.
No, no, Mr. President,
I am a patriot!
Doing what needs
to be done
for the continued safety
and well-being of this nation!
My God...
you gave the order to have
David Palmer killed.
That was an unfortunate
but necessary intervention.
He found out too much
and we had...
Walt!
You're rationalizing murder,
the murder of a president.
You're going to contact
these people
and recover the nerve gas
before it leaves the country.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Why not?
I don't know where
the nerve gas is.
And the man I have
working inside
has gone dark--
he's unreachable.
Now, you'll let things
play out as they are.
Otherwise, your administration
will be implicated
and your presidency
will be destroyed.
Jack.
Thanks for seeing me
like this, Mike.
What is it?
Did you tell anyone
we were meeting?
Of course not.
Son of a bitch!
Who did you tell?
Who did you tell?!
I didn't tell
anybody, Jack!
MAN ( over loudspeaker ):
Jack Bauer,
stay right where you are.
Put down your weapons
and put your hands up.
What's the meaning
of this?!
Tell your men
to stand down!
I'm sorry, sir,
we can't do that.
He's here at my request!
We have orders
to use force
if necessary.
Orders? From who?
The President of
the United States.
Get on your knees.
Thanks.
Novick and Bauer have
been taken into custody.
So we're just gonna
lock Mike Novick up?
For the time being.
Well, what good will it do?
Eventually, he's gonna get out,
and he's gonna talk
to the press.
What can he say?
He doesn't know anything.
I thought you told me
he talked to Jack Bauer.
We stopped Bauer before he
could give Mike any details.
What's he gonna think?
We're detaining him.
Bauer was about to divulge
national security secrets
that Mike's not
authorized to hear.
That's why Mike's
being detained.
And what about Bauer?
He must have talked
to other people at CTU
and told them
what he knows.
As soon as this
nerve gas leaves
U.S. soil,
it's gonna be very difficult
to prove
that either of us
is connected
to this in any way.
And you're sure that
these-these-these
detonators will work,
that the Sentox gas
will be released
before it can be used
against the Russians?
Yes.
Right now all you need to do
is authorize me
to terminate
CTU's involvement
in this matter.
We'll tell them we've got the
situation under control,
and that we'll
deal with Bauer.
Who, after all, is not
officially affiliated
with them any longer.
All right.
Good.
( phone rings )
Yes?
Mr. President, I have
Mrs. Logan for you.
Not now.
Yes, sir.
Dunley.
What is Jack Bauer doing here,
why is he under arrest,
and why wasn't I told?
Orders of
the president.
Directly?
No. It came through
Walt Cummings' office.
Okay. Thank you.
We're no longer running point
on the search for the canisters.
We've been ordered off
by Division.
Why?
The White House
wants to use
their own people
to coordinate from now on.
That doesn't make sense--
we'll waste hours
getting another agency
up to speed.
Yeah, I know.
I tried calling the president.
He's not taking my calls.
What about Mike Novick?
Jack should be with him by now.
Novick's people say
he's unreachable,
and Jack's cell goes
right to voice-mail.
Something's wrong.
Yeah, I know, but I don't know
what we can do about it.
I do.
What?
We can disregard
the order.
We're not disregarding
a presidential order.
If we don't, we will not
find this nerve gas.
Sending Jack Bauer
to have a conversation
with Mike Novick as a
private citizen is one thing,
but I'm not about to start
considering disobeying
a direct order from
the White House.
That's because you don't
have the experience
to know any better.
( soft chuckle )
Mr. Buchanan,
will you step outside
for a moment?
I can't have you talking
to me like that in front
of these people.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Are we clear about
who's in charge here?
Yeah, but my advice stands.
If this order jeopardizes
our chances of finding
that nerve gas,
it's your responsibility
to ignore it-- at
least until we can
make our case
to the White House.
You also need to learn
to make decisions
faster.
Bill...
One more thing that
comes with experience.
Lynn,
if we don't do
everything in our power
to stop these terrorists,
we're not doing our job.
( panting )
Okay, disregard the order.
Thank you.
EVELYN:
Is there anything else
you'd like me to pack for you?
Maybe a few of your...
nicer dresses?
I'm being confined to a
psychiatric ward, Evelyn.
I don't think there are gonna
be any black-tie events.
Sorry.
How'd this happen?
What's that, Mrs. Logan?
Charles and me.
I was his confidante.
All those years in
Congress, my... opinion
was the one that
mattered most to him.
And now I'm...
...less than an
afterthought.
I'm sure the president
would be here if he could.
He's the President
of the United States, Evelyn.
He can do whatever he wants.
If he wanted to be here,
he would be.
( zipping suitcase )
( door opens )
Mr. Bauer, you're being moved
per the president's
orders.
Where?
To a class three
detention facility.
On what charges?
I was invited here
by Mike Novick.
Those are my orders, sir.
You're Pierce, right?
Aaron Pierce. You served
under David Palmer.
Yes, I did.
I need to speak with you
just for a moment, please.
That's not possible.
It concerns David
Palmer's killer.
All right.
David Palmer was assassinated
because he was on the verge
of discovering that the
terrorists that attacked us
today were being helped
by someone within
Logan's administration.
Who?
Walt Cummings.
Why would Mr. Cummings
be involved
with terrorists?
I couldn't tell you.
But I can tell you
that the terrorists
are now in possession
of a weaponized nerve gas,
and Walt Cummings may be
the last chance we have
to stop them in time.
Walt Cummings ordered the
assassination of David Palmer.
I know that's hard to believe,
but I can prove it, it's true.
Actually, it's not
that hard to believe.
The First Lady also thinks
someone in the administration
was involved.
Your primary responsibility
as lead agent
is to protect the President
of the United States.
Someone in his administration
is undermining his authority.
That is equivalent
to a coup d'\tat.
Agent Pierce, please...
please, I need your help.
Bauer's escaped.
When? I didn't get
a code alert.
My comm's down.
Call it in, have agents
cover the west gate--
that's where he was headed.
What about you?
I'll take your post.
Go.
Yes, sir.
That was NSA--
CTU hasn't transferred
the search operation
to their jurisdiction yet.
What's the problem?
I don't know.
But you need to
call Lynn McGill,
make sure we're in charge
of this.
I've been avoiding his calls
because he's just gonna ask me
why I'm pulling CTU off
the search operation,
and I don't know
what to tell him!
You don't have
to tell him anything.
You're the president.
Agent Pierce,
we're in the middle
of a meeting, if you don't mind.
Mr. President,
my name is Jack Bauer,
and I'm sorry to have
to confront you like this,
but your chief of staff
is withholding information
that is vital
to this nation's security.
( blow lands )
Stop this!
I'm the President
of the United States--
get your hands
off this man!
Agent Pierce, do something!
I am, Mr. President.
I'm upholding my
oath to protect you.
That won't have
any effect, sir.
I've overridden
the distress line.
Mr. Cummings is guilty of
conspiring with terrorists.
He facilitated the theft
of a military-grade nerve gas,
and today is responsible for the
death of at least three people,
including David Palmer.
I know about that, but
there's an explanation.
What do you mean,
you know about that?
Mr. Bauer, please, I just
found out a couple minutes ago.
It's very complicated.
I don't know
what this man has told you,
but we need to find
that nerve gas now,
and I mean immediately,
before it is too late.
It's already too late.
What do you mean?
Apparently, it's on its way
out of the country.
Where is it?!
He told me he doesn't know!
He's lying to you, sir!
The man I have
inside has gone dark,
I don't know.
I'm done talking with you,
you understand me?
Now you read my file.
First thing I'm going to do,
I'm going to take out
your right eye,
then I'm going to move over,
and I'm going to take our
your left.
And then I'm going to cut you.
I'm going to keep cutting you
until I get
the information that I need,
you understand me?
So for the last time,
where is the nerve gas?
( Cummings grunts )
Stop.
Stop! Stop!
I'll tell you!
( breathlessly ):
I'll tell you.
It's-it's on a freighter leaving
the port of Long Beach at 2:30.
JACK:
How is it concealed?!
In a container
carrying medical supplies.
What's the container number?
I don't know.
What's the number?!
I don't know!
I-I'd tell you, I swear.
LOGAN:
Mr. Bauer!
( grunting )
I don't know.
( strained grunting )
( intercom beeps )
MAN:
Mr. Buchanan, I've got
Jack Bauer on line three.
Jack, what's going on?
We've been trying to reach you.
Bill, hold on. I'm going
to put you on speakerphone.
Bill, I'm standing here
with the president.
The nerve gas is
at Long Beach Harbor
in a container full
of medical supplies
on a freighter bound
for Central Asia.
It's set to depart
at 2:30 p.m.
How solid
is the intel, Jack?
It came directly
from Cummings.
Mr. President, we've
been trying to reach you
about an order we received
changing our jurisdiction.
Disregard the order.
Then you want CTU to maintain
operational control
of the retrieval?
Yes. Absolutely.
I'm alerting CBP.
Get hazmat teams in there
and set up a perimeter.
Have medical teams standing by
in case the gas is released.
Got it.
Good work, Jack.
Are you heading back
to CTU?
I don't know yet.
Jack, we'll let you know
when we have more information
on the container.
Copy that.
Mr. President, Agent Pierce
and I are prepared
to hand ourselves over
to the authorities now.
Aaron.
Yes, Mr. President?
Take back your shield and get
Walt Cummings out of my sight.
Yes, sir.
He told me it was too late,
and I believed him.
You need to understand,
I trusted Walt Cummings...
but he lied to me.
I was coerced.
There is, uh, one more thing
that we need to discuss.
What is that, sir?
You.
The fact that you're alive
presents problems
for both of us.
( softly ):
Yes, Mr. President.
I accomplished what
I set out to do,
which was to identify and
locate David Palmer's killer.
I would like to stay on until
the nerve gas is retrieved.
After that, I give you my word
I will simply disappear again.
All right.
I think that would be best
for the good of the country.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Bauer.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I'll see you soon.
( knocks on hood )
Wait. Hold up, Kevin.
What's happening?
Martha.
Charles...
Come on. Get out
of the car.
Be careful.
What?
You were right.
There was a conspiracy.
David was trying
to warn you and warn me.
I should have listened
to you.
( stammering ):
I-I...
Y-you... you believe me now?
It was Walt Cummings.
He lied to me.
He convinced me that
you were out of control.
Walt?!
Sending you back
to the... the clinic
in Vermont
was his idea.
And you went along with it.
I'm sorry, Martha.
Sending me away
without a word...
like I was... some nuisance
to be gotten rid of.
Excuse me,
Mr. President,
but you wanted to know
when a link with CTU
was established.
Yes, um...
thank you, Wendy.
See that
the First Lady's bags
get back to
her room.
Of course.
I've got to go.
Chloe, do we have confirmation
on the intel Jack gave us?
There's only one ship scheduled
to leave the port
of Long Beach at 2:30.
It's a freighter
heading for Central Asia,
leaving from Pier F.
We don't have CTU teams
in the vicinity,
but we've got a Customs
and Border Protection
task force on site
under our directive.
All right, make sure
that CBP understands
the nerve gas is
housed in 20 canisters
of gray metal
that are unmarked.
They're going
out in a shipment
of medical supplies.
Yeah, yeah,
they know all that already.
But there's going to be
about a thousand cargo
containers on that ship,
and we don't know
which one the
nerve gas is in.
It's container 539146,
box seven.
I was able to hack into
the ship's manifest.
It's the only container
stocking medical supplies.
That's great.
Make sure all the strike
force units have that.
Right.
Lynn, the White House
is requesting
a live feed from the assault.
We'll have Chloe
patch them in once
the TAC teams
reach the staging area.
All right, got it. Yeah.
That's him.
BUCHANAN ( over speakerphone ):
His name is Ivan Erwich.
He's a chemical engineer
trained at the University
of St. Petersburg.
Joined his country's separatist
movement six years ago.
Do we have
any clearer images,
any file photos?
No, which is why
we need you to I.D. him
when the strike force
has a visual.
Okay, just make sure
that CPB knows
that we need
to take Erwich alive.
They know. Stand by.
What's the situation?
The strike team
is in place, Mr. President.
We're just waiting
for the video feed to come up.
Feed's up.
FINN ( over monitor ):
CTU, we've located
the target container.
No hostiles present.
You have the green light,
Agent Finn.
Remember, do not discharge
your weapons
unless absolutely necessary.
If a bullet breaches
one of those canisters,
we'll have
a massive casualty situation.
FINN:
Copy that.
Masks on.
Go!
Don't move!
Put your hands
in the air now!
He's dead.
Open 'em up.
Let's go! Open 'em all up.
This one.
Empty. Next.
Moving on, moving on.
No.
FINN:
Come on, get it open.
Empty. Next.
Come on, move it.
Open it, open it.
Next.
Open it, come on,
come on.
What do we got?
What do we got?!
Nothing?!
There are
no gas canisters here, CTU.
Repeat, the nerve gas
is not here.
Get Walt Cummings in here now!
Yes, sir.
Damn it!
The nerve gas
isn't there.
It has to be.
Where are the canisters?!
I don't know.
I-I've told
you everything.
They have
to be there.
Oh, God...
What is it?
That's Schaeffer,
the man we had inside.
They must've found out
we reprogrammed
the detonators.
( phone ringing )
It's his cell
phone, sir.
Who's calling you?
That's Schaeffer's number.
JACK:
Bill?
Yeah, Jack?
I want you
to monitor
and record this call.
We're on it.
Answer it now.
Yes?
ERWICH:
We know you've altered
the arming codes,
Mr. Cummings.
CUMMINGS:
Who is this?
I think you know my name...
as I now know yours.
Your man Schaeffer confessed
everything.
Is President Logan with you?
The President
had nothing
to do with this...
nor did anyone else
in the government.
I was acting alone.
Do you really expect me
to believe that?
It's the truth.
Erwich, listen.
We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate
with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country is about to pay
a very steep price.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FORD.
Built for the road ahead.
www.tvsubtitles.net