CTU is being absorbed by the
Department of Homeland Security,
and Christopher Henderson
remains an open protocol.
MILES:
Ms. Raines signed
a detailed statement
documenting
the numerous missteps
made today by CTU,
and by you,
in particular.
CHLOE:
I don't understand,
why am I staying
and everybody else
is being let go?
Because Ms. Raines requested
that you keep your position.
I had to keep Karen
from replacing you,
that's why
I signed the document,
I didn't have a choice.
Why were those men
trying to kill you?
David had a source
inside the White House.
Who's the source?
Mrs. Logan's assistant.
I have proof about who's behind
everything that's
happened today.
( whispering ):
Someone killed David...
and they just
tried to kill me.
I have to go now...
Give me what I need!
They kidnapped
my little girl.
Evelyn.
I promise you we're going
to get your daughter back.
I already told them
I wouldn't give up
any information
until I have my daughter.
JACK ( over radio ):
We need Henderson alive;
do not shoot to kill.
Did you bring what we discussed?
I have the evidence with me.
I want my daughter.
She's moving.
Give me the evidence, Evelyn.
Now.
( gunfire )
( screaming )
Wayne, I didn't get him--
if you got a shot, take it!
( gunshots )
( tires squealing )
Chloe, it's Jack, Henderson
escaped in Evelyn's car!
Do you have him on satellite?
We can't lose him!
Evelyn's been hit.
JACK:
It's not serious,
but it's gonna
have to be dressed.
Evelyn, you've got
your daughter back,
now tell me what
I need to know.
Who is behind this?
Is it the vice president?
The vice president
has nothing to do with this!
LOGAN ( over phone ):
You promised me you would
control the situation.
I didn't count on Jack Bauer
showing up, sir.
Bauer and Wayne Palmer
won't be around long enough
to tell anybody else
what they know.
HENDERSON ( over phone ):
I will not let you down.
See that you don't.
WAYNE:
The lanes are cut off.
Okay, Evelyn, I need
you to stay focused.
The recording of the phone call
that you made
between President Logan
and Henderson
is in a safety
deposit box--
which bank?
Which bank?
City Trust and Savings
in Agoura Hills.
Where's the key?
My jacket pocket.
Mom?
JACK:
It's all right,
sweetheart,
your mom's going to be fine.
She's going
to be fine, okay?
Jack, you heard
what they said.
We have to get off this road,
there are military patrols
everywhere.
There's a motel up there
on the right.
Turn in there.
I want to go home.
We're gonna get
you home, honey.
We're gonna get you home.
Wayne, can you get us a room.
I'll keep watch.
Make sure you keep
pressure on the wound,
I'll be right back.
( phone speed dialing )
( ringing )
Hello?
JACK ( over phone ):
Audrey, it's Jack.
Have you got Henderson
on satellite yet?
No, Chloe wasn't able
to reposition in time.
JACK:
Damn it!
Are you still
on a secure line?
Yes. Why,
what's going on?
Evelyn didn't
implicate Gardner.
She implicated President Logan.
Oh, my God, Jack.
Logan? Are you sure?
She said he was responsible for
everything that happened today,
starting with providing the
terrorists with the nerve gas.
That's what David Palmer
found out.
That's why
they killed him.
Are you saying that
President Logan
ordered Palmer's
assassination?
Henderson gave
the order.
But Evelyn says
she has evidence
that shows that President Logan
was complicit.
What kind of evidence?
She recorded a conversation
earlier this morning
between Henderson
and President Logan.
She put it in a safety
deposit box in a bank.
We're on our way
to get it now.
Jack, the city is
under martial law.
I know. I need you to upload
every military
checkpoint to my PDA
so we can navigate
our way around them.
All right,
I'll take care of that.
Audrey, as soon as I have
the recording,
we're going to have
to involve your father.
We need someone in the
government, someone credible,
to present the evidence.
All right.
He's on his way back
from a summit in Japan.
I'll call him
on the plane.
Okay. Make sure
you leave CTU
before you
do anything.
You don't think that
they can be trusted?
Right now,
we can't trust anyone.
Logan will have every federal
law enforcement agency,
the military,
all at his disposal.
And he will use them
to try and stop us.
Don't fill your father in
on the particulars.
Just try and
set up the meeting.
I'll get back to you
as soon as
I have the recording.
All right, I'll upload
those checkpoints.
Yeah.
Wayne?
The bank manager
was listed.
That's his address,
he's not far.
Good. Let's get them
in the room.
( gently ):
Hey... we need
to get inside now.
Come on, it's okay.
JACK:
Give me your arm.
( straining )
You can sit
right here, okay?
Okay. Lie down
here on the bed.
( groaning and panting )
JACK:
I'm sorry, but
it's not safe enough
to take you to
a hospital yet.
Let me see,
let me see.
( moaning )
Wayne?
Take Amy outside
for a second.
( groans )
Okay, even though
the bullet went through,
I'm still going to have
to clean out this wound.
It's gonna hurt.
But I promise you
I'll get you to a hospital
as soon as I can.
In the meantime,
I'm going to have Wayne
look after you.
No. I'll be fine.
You need to get the evidence.
And you'll need help.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
Keep pressure on it.
Sweetheart, you can
see your mom now.
Give me the car keys.
Let's go.
I haven't been able to pick up
Bauer's trail yet.
LOGAN ( on phone ):
So he got away.
And there's nothing to stop
him and Wayne Palmer
from going to the media
with everything they know.
Jack knows there's no point
in going public
until he has proof.
He won't make any accusations
until he has
that evidence in his hand.
This evidence, this... this
recording that Evelyn made
of our conversation.
Are you any closer
to finding out
where she's hidden it?
No, sir, not yet.
But she was wounded,
and I will find her;
we're monitoring hospitals,
emergency services.
This is containable,
I promise you.
Please spare me your
promises, Mr. Henderson.
It's all gone wrong.
None of this
should have happened.
All these killings...
This whole thing was planned
to make our country safer.
Stronger.
To protect our interests.
And it all spiraled
out of control
when you decided
to kill David Palmer.
Mr. President,
what's done is done.
And right now,
we have to focus
on stopping Bauer
before he finds
that recording.
No.
You have to focus on it.
Why haven't the analysts
finished the hourlies?
They're still getting
up to speed on CTU's protocols.
We knew this wasn't going
to be a seamless transition.
Sometimes I wonder if it
was even a necessary one.
Karen...
CTU's performance
today has been
considerably less
than stellar.
Dozens of people
have been killed.
And they weren't
even able
to prevent an attack
on themselves.
Do you really believe,
under the circumstances,
that we could have
done any better?
CHLOE:
Ms. Hayes?
The president is on line one.
Put him through
to Bill Buchanan's office,
I'll be working out of there
from now on.
And have Medical notify me
as soon as Bierko
has regained consciousness.
Miles.
Yes, Mr. President?
Karen.
Do you know where Jack Bauer is?
Not at the moment, sir.
He was due back here
30 minutes ago
to lead the Bierko
interrogation.
He's gone off grid.
I'm not surprised.
Karen, I'm issuing
an executive order
for the immediate apprehension
and arrest of Jack Bauer.
I want you
to run point on this,
and I want you to make this
CTU's top priority.
Yes, sir.
For purposes
of the warrant,
I'll need to know what
Bauer's being charged with.
His role in the assassination
of President David Palmer.
But I understood that
he'd been exonerated
of that charge, sir.
You, yourself,
reinstated his credentials.
I know, but I didn't have
all the facts then.
Some new evidence
has come to light.
New evidence?
Yes.
I'm looking at it right now,
and I will forward it to you
at the appropriate time.
Yes, sir.
Karen.
Obviously, this is
a very sensitive matter,
and for now I would
like you to treat
the origin of this warrant
as confidential.
Understood, sir.
Put out an alert
on Jack Bauer
to all federal law enforcement
agencies and NSA.
I'll also get military
the warrant--
they have more men
on the street than anyone.
I don't like this.
Pulling our resources off
finding Christopher Henderson
to go after Jack Bauer
without knowing the evidence?
It's a direct order
from the president.
You know, if we really
want to find Bauer,
we need to keep watch on anyone
he might contact for help.
Starting with Audrey Raines.
What's this?
Chloe, open it up
and make it look like
this is what
we're talking about.
Okay...
Can you get me
a secure channel,
so the calls
on my cell phone
can't be monitored?
Using a VPN pathway, sure.
Take somebody
about an hour to crack.
Why, what's going on?
I just spoke
with Jack.
Gardner isn't the one
who's behind this.
It's President Logan.
What?
Jack is on his way
getting proof.
I'm leaving now to go help him.
Take a CTU walkie.
( computer chimes )
Audrey.
It's a warrant
for Jack's arrest.
It's starting.
What do we do?
Heading out?
Yes, I'm going
to try to grab
a couple hours
of sleep.
I came to talk
to both of you
about the warrant.
Well, let's start with
why the hell it was issued.
There's new evidence implicating
Jack in David Palmer's
assassination.
That's ridiculous.
I was there when
the assassin confessed.
All you have to do is
check the log.
I know about the logs, Chloe.
My orders are to bring Jack in.
New evidence?
Have you seen it?
It's forthcoming.
Who ordered this, Karen?
I'm not at liberty
to discuss that.
When was the last time
you spoke with Jack?
About an hour ago.
We haven't had contact since.
I hope I don't have
to remind either one of you
that you have
a legal obligation
to notify me
if Jack contacts you.
Look, I know this may seem odd
to the both of you--
frankly, it does to me--
but let's remember
it's in everyone's best interest
to bring Jack in peacefully.
Have a good night.
Thank you.
VALERIE ( over phone ):
Harris.
Valerie?
Audrey's on her way.
What's your status?
We're placing
the transponder
on Audrey's car
right now.
HAYES ( on phone ):
Good.
There won't be many cars
on the road,
so use the tracker
and stay out of sight.
Will do.
We don't want anything
to stop Audrey
from leading us to Bauer.
That's the house.
Okay.
What's the bank
manager's name?
Carl Mossman.
You got your gun?
Yeah, but we don't need them
for this, do we?
He's not going to let
into his bank
in the middle of the night
unless he thinks
he has to.
Jack, why don't we just try
telling him the truth?
Would you believe it? The
only way we're going to have
his full compliance
is if he's scared.
If you're uncomfortable with
that, you should stay here.
( grunts )
Damn it.
They've got a magnetic alarm.
( panting )
We're in.
MAN ( on TV ):
...that will take place
within the hour.
At that time,
President Logan is scheduled
to make a statement
to the American people
about the successful resolution
of today's terrorist threat.
Did you hear
something?
Like what?
I don't know.
Carl?
Hang on.
I'll be right back.
Don't you move.
Rose, call
the police...!
( groans )
Cover him.
Put the phone down.
Put the phone down now!
Bring him in here!
Just stay calm, and
everything will be fine.
Oh my God. Carl...
Take a seat on the bed.
Okay, look, our money
and jewelry's in floor safe
in the closet.
We're not interested in that.
You're gonna get us
into your bank.
( panting )
I can't do that.
It's not that I won't. I can't.
The alarm system and the vault
only allow entry
during business hours.
Don't lie to me.
Every bank has
procedures
to allow access
during an emergency.
Hey! No, no!
I'll take you
to the bank.
( quietly
whimpers )
JACK:
Slowly
get up, get dressed.
Go on. It's all right,
it's all right, it's all right.
I want four
of your neckties.
Tie her up
to the chair.
Ankles and wrists. Make
sure she doesn't move.
Come on.
Yes, hi. This is Audrey Raines.
I need to speak
with Secretary Heller, please.
Mr. Secretary, there's
a call coming in for you
on an over-air
encrypted channel.
It's your daughter.
Audrey, is everything okay?
Hi. Uh, yes, I'm okay.
Dad, I need your help.
Is this a secure line?
Very secure.
Is this about the arrest order
for Jack?
I was just informed.
Dad, I can't go into details
right now, but Jack is innocent.
He's being set up.
Set up by whom?
What the hell
is going on, Audrey?
You call me this morning,
to tell me that Jack's alive.
Now I get word
he's a suspect again
in the Palmer
assassination.
Dad, I can't talk to you
about it right now.
I need to see you
in person.
Can you reroute your plane
to Los Angeles?
Dad, I would never ask you
to do this
if it wasn't
extremely important.
All right, yes.
Thank you.
The closest airport is Van Nuys.
We're about an hour out.
I'll call you on final approach.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll see you there.
I'll see you.
Bye.
Doug!
Yes, sir.
We have to make a stop in L.A.
And keep it off the manifest.
Yes, sir.
Pull over.
She stopped.
Corner of Alderton
and Davis.
It's a gas station.
CHLOE:
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's me.
Hold on.
Okay, switched over
to my own VPN. Now they can't
monitor either end
of the conversation.
Do you have the walkie?
Yeah. Hang on.
All right, what
do I do with it?
Tune to proprietary
channel 17,
turn the sensitivity
up all the way.
See if you pick up
a pilot signal.
Okay, hold on.
( high-pitched squeal )
Wow. Do you hear that?
That's what I figured--
they put a tracker on you.
I found it. All right, Chloe,
I got it. Thank you.
Audrey, you need
to disable your phone
by taking the battery out
as soon as you can.
All right,
I have to wait
for a call from Jack
and then I will.
Okay.
( sighs )
Yes.
Sir, it's almost time.
The press conference.
That's right.
Mr. President,
if I could
have a moment...
Uh, I should be done
with my statement
shortly, Hal.
This is potentially
time sensitive, sir.
I just got an alert
that a warrant
has been issued for Jack Bauer.
Thank you, Aaron.
Yes, sir.
What about the warrant?
Well, it's an executive
branch warrant.
I didn't issue it, so it
must have come from you.
That's right, it came from me.
Well, as you've
put me in charge
of overseeing CTU and the
Homeland Security transfer,
don't you think
you should have discussed it
with me first?
I appreciate everything
you've done today, Hal,
but the last time I checked,
I was still Commander in Chief.
Of course, Mr. President,
but Jack Bauer?
It doesn't
make any sense.
We should be treating
that man like a hero.
I've gone over the logs.
Walt Cummings has confessed
that he arranged Palmer's
assassination, framing Bauer.
Well, clearly,
Cummings was protecting Bauer.
Why?
I don't know why.
But the fact remains
I have received confirmation
from Intelligence sources
that Jack Bauer was,
without question, the shooter.
Which sources?
That's enough!
I'm not going to stand here
and have my orders challenged.
You have concerns, Hal.
We'll sort this all out
once Bauer's in custody.
Does that suit you?
Yes, sir.
Good.
Mom?
( water running )
( sobbing )
( sobbing continues )
Amy?
Sweetheart, it's okay.
( groaning )
Hold on. I'm coming.
( sobbing continues )
Hold on, sweetheart,
I'm coming.
( groaning )
Mom! Mom!
Mommy.
WOMAN:
911. What's your emergency?
My mom-- she passed out.
I can't wake her up.
Calm down. Tell me your name.
Amy. My mom's name is Evelyn.
What's your mom's last name?
Martin.
Her name's Evelyn Martin.
All right, honey,
now tell me where you are.
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
MAN:
Sir, a call is coming in
to the 911 operator
from a Motel 6
on Porter Valley Drive
requesting medical assistance
for an Evelyn Martin.
LOGAN:
My fellow Americans, it is with
great relief that I announce
that the terrorist threat
our nation faced today is over.
More than an hour ago, federal
counter-terrorist agents,
under my direction,
thwarted the latest attack
on innocent civilians,
the nature of which was kept
secret due to national security.
This was done with the public's
best interest in mind.
He really did it.
Ma'am?
Charles.
He stopped the terrorists,
the treaty was signed.
He said he would
ride out this crisis,
and everything
would be okay.
And it is.
I should have trusted him.
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong, Aaron?
I'm just a little battle worn.
LOGAN:
They attempted to derail
the historic accord...
Jack, why are we
stopping here?
There's too many military
checkpoints in the area.
They'll stop our car.
We have to go the rest
of the way on foot.
How far is the bank from here?
About a quarter of a mile
that way.
( phone ringing )
Be right back.
Aaron, it's Jack.
Jack, are you aware
President Logan's
issued a warrant for your arrest
for your role
in David Palmer's assassination?
No, but that makes sense.
The Vice President's not the one
who's behind this, is he?
No, it's Logan.
They're going to have
every agency
and the military
looking for you.
And Logan is the only one
who can call them off.
As soon as we have
the evidence in hand,
We're gonna pass it off
to Secretary of Defense Heller.
After that,
it's not gonna matter.
Is there anything I
can do for you, Jack?
Keep your eyes open
and watch your back.
Will do.
Get out of the car.
Come on.
Let's go.
Move, move.
( vehicle approaching )
( whispers ):
Take cover, go!
Not a word.
WOMAN:
Ms. Hayes, Valerie Harris
is on line two for you.
She says it's urgent.
Valerie, what's happening?
We lost Audrey Raines.
What?
She found the tracker
and transferred it
to a DWP truck
at a gas station.
Damn it. How did
she find it?
She's got
no field experience.
I don't know.
The only reason
we discovered it
is the DWP guy stopped to
check a faulty power line.
All right, hold your position
and wait for my instructions.
Will do.
MILES:
Papazian.
Audrey Raines
ditched her transponder.
I need you to redirect satellite
surveillance and track her.
I can redirect CalTrans
and maybe one SAT-LINK,
but the rest are dedicated
to finding Bauer.
Following Audrey should lead us
right to Bauer.
Just get it done and tell me
when you've got something.
I'm on it.
Against the wall.
Watch him.
Just do what he says, Carl.
Do what he says and you'll
be home before you know it.
Right.
What's the emergency procedure
to enter the bank?
I have 30 seconds
to put my key in
the alarm panel,
then I enter my code.
You enter the wrong code
and alert the police,
all I have to do is make
one call, your wife is dead.
You understand me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Where's the vault?
Take us around the back,
stay away from the windows.
How do I open it?
There's a 12-digit code, but
it's a timed unlock procedure,
which allows enough
time for the police
to arrive in the event
that someone should
trigger the silent alarm.
Write the code down for me.
Take him over to one of
the desks, keep an eye on him.
I know you.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
You're David Palmer's brother.
I saw you on TV
this morning.
You were there when he was shot.
Now, what the hell
are you doing in my bank?
And who is he?
Listen, I know it's
absurd to ask you
to trust me under
these circumstances,
but believe me,
you don't want to know.
Oh, come on.
You threaten me with a gun,
you kidnap me,
you're robbing my bank.
Now, I deserve to know
what the hell is going on here.
Fine.
Jack and I believe
there's evidence inside
of one of your safety deposit
boxes that's gonna prove
who was behind the assassination
of my brother, okay?
JACK:
Wayne.
What's going on?
What do you want
me to say, Jack?
He recognized me.
It's all right.
Mr. Mossman,
how long is the delay
before the vault opens?
Five minutes.
Is that true what he said?
Is that why you two are here?
Yes.
Why didn't you just wait
till morning, get a subpoena?
The people that are behind this
will never let it go that far.
They've already tried to kill me
twice tonight, Carl.
And they're gonna try again
the very first chance they get.
( sniffs )
( moans )
Mom.
MAN:
Miss Martin,
you're in shock.
But you're going
to be okay.
You know my name?
( silenced gunshots )
Where's Bauer?
( screams )
You did?
Well, that's good.
I'm glad.
I'll get back to you.
I thought
you went to bed.
No.
I, uh, watched you
with the press.
Well, um, that was Morry,
and he thought
it went pretty well.
Good.
But that doesn't
begin to describe it.
Charles, you have had
to deal with
more crisis today
than any president
in an entire term.
You...
were magnificent.
Magnificent.
Well, I like the sound of that.
Especially coming from you.
I'm so proud of you.
I hope I haven't embarrassed you
too much as your First Lady.
Stop. No.
Don't be ridiculous.
I mean,
you walked up to the
edge a couple times,
but nobody noticed.
I'll try to find a compliment
in there somewhere.
I'm sorry, Marty.
I didn't...
Wow.
I was so selfish today.
No.
You had so much
on your plate,
you didn't need me
piling more on.
No, I...
Please don't
say anything.
Just accept my apology.
I do.
I do, I accept
your apology.
( phone ringing )
I have to take this privately.
Who is it?
Now, what difference
does it make?
Please, Marty.
I thought the crisis was over.
I thought you and I...
( phone ringing )
All right.
Yes.
We know where Bauer is.
Evelyn gave him up.
Well, then take care of it.
My men are heading there now.
Good.
Let me know when it's done.
I'm sorry, honey.
I guess I haven't gotten used
to the idea that...
that the crisis is over.
When what's done?
What?
You just said,
"Let me know when it's done."
Oh, that was Jamey.
I asked her to write me
a radio speech
for tomorrow morning.
We found Audrey Raines.
Where?
She's heading north
toward Mulholland.
Connect me with Harris.
( phone rings )
Harris.
Valerie,
we have a fix on Raines.
She's heading
toward the Sepulveda Pass,
coming up on Mulholland.
Copy that.
Let's go.
( starts engine )
( tires screeching )
Chloe?
Do you have a minute?
No.
What is it?
I was assigned to
log all satellite
and ground video activity,
but part of the vector
is locked out.
Locked out?
What do you mean?
I mean, someone's
taken control of one
of the satellites
using a class one
priority override.
Do you know anything about it?
No.
I'll look into it.
Thanks.
( sighs )
Crap.
All points are covered, sir.
The perimeter is secure.
Do you have a visual?
I did, briefly.
All right, listen.
You tell your men the instant,
and I mean the instant
that Bauer steps outside
that bank building
you take him down.
Then, kill the others
and secure the recording.
( buzzer sounds )
Which one is it?
Twenty-three.
MOSSMAN:
Mr. Palmer,
I admired your brother
a great deal.
He was a great man.
Thank you.
HENDERSON ( on tape ):
It had to be done, sir.
LOGAN:
I decide what needs to
be done, Mr. Henderson.
I never authorized you
to kill David Palmer.
Palmer was nosing around.
He'd have found out
about your involvement.
For God's sake, sir,
he called your wife.
I can handle my wife.
Right now, my concern
is keeping this operation
from collapsing
like a house of cards.
You're protected, sir.
That's president Logan's voice.
Every thread ends
with Cummings.
He thinks he's running this,
And you need
to keep playing it that way.
I know my part,
Mr. Henderson.
You just do
as you're told.
Oh, my God.
We got what we need.
Mr. Mossman,
I'm sorry we put you
and your wife through this.
It'll be safer for
you to stay here now.
Could you please
let us out?
Like to help if I can.
I've come this far.
We're gonna need
to borrow your car
a little longer.
MOSSMAN:
Sure, it's insured.
Wait. There's someone inside.
Mr. Mossman, get
back in the vault now.
Is there any other way out
of here besides the front door?
No, front door only--
security reasons.
Damn it.
Both of you stay here.
I'll be right back.
Henderson's men
are taking up positions.
There's no other way out-- we're
gonna have to turn ourselves in.
They didn't come here to arrest
us; they came here to kill us.
What are they
waiting for?
All the windows
are bulletproof.
They're waiting for us
to leave the building.
So what are you gonna do?
How do you trip
the silent alarm?
I have a key, but you trip
that alarm, LAPD
will be here
within a few minutes.
That's exactly what I want.
Henderson's men
outnumber us.
We leave this building now,
we lose.
Jack, if you call the cops,
they're gonna get the recording
when we're taken into custody.
We won't be taken into custody.
As soon as Henderson finds out
the LAPD have arrived,
he's gonna have his men
engage them.
He doesn't want the police
to have the recording any more
than he wants us to have it.
So they start shooting
at each other.
How does that
help us?
We have to try
and use that as a diversion.
It's our only way out.
Trigger the alarm.
Be right back.
Valerie.
The feed should be coming
through to your laptop now.
I've got her.
She's heading west on Chandler.
How close are you
to Audrey's car?
About two miles.
Close the gap to one mile.
Affirmative.
Something's wrong.
The feed's breaking up.
We're experiencing
the same difficulty
with our signal--
hold on.
What's going on?
I don't know.
The satellite's
positioned correctly.
I'm tracing
the corruption.
It's the server.
What is it?
O'Brian's gone.
* *
What were you doing?
What?
Are you kidding?
If you really want the details,
I'll write you a report.
Let's go, now.
MOSSMAN:
The police should be here
any minute.
Mr. Mossman, like I said before,
it might be safer
for you to stay
here in the bank.
No, these guys find me,
they assume I know
about the recording,
they'd probably
kill me, right?
I'll take my chances with you.
I want you to stay as close
to Mr. Palmer as you can.
I'll provide cover fire.
Once we leave the bank,
you break left.
Yes, sir.
Cooper, what's your status?
No change,
they still haven't come out.
Must have seen you, damn it.
Tell your men to move in
immediately.
The cops are here.
We can't let them have Bauer;
take 'em down.
Yes, sir.
This is LAPD!
Drop your weapons!
Engage! Engage!
( heavy gunfire )
Let's go.
( heavy gunfire continues )
( gunfire continues )
( rapid gunfire )
Need to go
to the police car now-- move!
( gunfire continues )
JACK:
He's been hit!
( tires screeching )
( bullets ricocheting )
( heavy gunfire continues )
How is he doing?
He's dead.
Damn it.
( phone rings )
Jack, where are you?
I'm on my way to you.
Did your father agree to meet?
Yes, he's landing
at Van Nuys Airport
in about 15 minutes.
I'm there now.
Good, we got the evidence.
Have you listened to it?
Yeah, there's no doubt
it's Logan.
You understand what this means.
We're talking about taking down
the President
of the United States.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FORD.
Built for the road ahead.
www.tvsubtitles.net