Coordinates for the targets--
upload them into the missiles.
Begin the
launch countdown.
How much time
do you need to cancel
the launch sequence?
I won't know for
certain till I see
how the targeting
software is configured.
We're going to keep Bierko
and his men out of here,
so you can finish this.
CHLOE:
Ten seconds to launch.
It's done.
( over radio ):
The launch sequence is canceled.
You were never really
going to let me go, were you?
JACK:
No.
You were responsible
for the deaths
of David Palmer
and Tony Almeida
and Michelle Dessler.
I'm going after Logan.
What do you mean,
"going after Logan"?
I'll fill you in
on the details later.
Right now, I need you
to walk me through
modifying some field
communications equipment.
Who is this guy?
Morris O'Brian,
Chloe's ex-husband.
I need some com unit
modifications.
Can you do that
without talking?
I could, but it would be
a terrible waste of my charm.
Jack Bauer's on
his way here now.
He's going to confront
your husband directly.
But Charles is leaving
for the airfield immediately.
You have to find
a way to stall him.
There's a helicopter
waiting for me.
Let it wait.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
You're the president.
Aaron said
the recording you had
implicating the president
was destroyed.
Yes.
NOVICK:
Without it, you can't
mount a case.
I'm working with someone
inside CTU.
They're setting up
a digital uplink.
If I can get Logan
to acknowledge
everything that he's done today,
it's going to be
all the evidence we need.
I need to get on that chopper.
PIERCE:
I don't see how that's
gonna be possible.
If Logan doesn't confess,
how far are you actually
willing to go?
As far as I have to.
Ah...
Here, let me get
this for you.
Watch your hair.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I got a flight suit.
Go ahead.
Did you make it to the
Secret Service outbuilding?
Yeah.
I think Morris and I
may have a way
to pull the copilot
from the flight.
What about the
reassignment protocol?
Working on it.
Mike Novick will have
to verify the pilot codes.
It should take him
about one minute.
Chloe, hold on
a second.
I'm switching over
to com.
Okay.
Do you copy?
Yeah.
I'll get back to you as soon
as I'm on the chopper.
Mike Novick's
going to call.
Morris.
Yes, sweetheart?
I need you to do
one more thing.
Some guy from Central
just called.
Says your packet's
messed up.
I got that
straightened out Monday.
I guess not.
He wants to
talk to you.
Now?
Right now. He had
me patch you through
to the Secret
Service outbuilding.
Mike.
I've delayed him
as long as I can.
He'll be there in a few minutes.
Have you heard anything
from Jack Bauer yet?
He should be in
the Secret Service
outbuilding. I'm sending him
the necessary documents now.
There's not much time.
I understand.
PIERCE:
Yeah, Mike.
The reassignment protocol
and authorization
should be coming through to you.
He'll need both.
How are we
doing for time?
Hurry.
Hello.
John.
Aaron.
I thought you transferred out.
Not quite yet.
Some guy from
Central called,
said my packet's
all messed...
Don't worry
about him.
Carruth has been relieved.
I guess there was something
wrong with his packet.
Ron Franklin.
There's my protocol.
This is not bad,
but it needs to
be more positive,
like, uh...
Jack Bauer is
on the helicopter.
You have to find an excuse
not to get on board.
LOGAN:
Um... Carolyn, do you
have the itinerary?
MARTHA:
Charles?
Excuse me. Could
I talk to you
for a second?
Absolutely.
Will you excuse us
for a second?
I know it sounds silly,
but I didn't bring
my medication.
and I just, I just want
to have it with me.
Of course. Of course.
We'll send
somebody
back for it.
No, no, no.
I don't want to delay you.
I'll be along later.
Besides, Charles,
I-I'm thinking that
when you land,
it would be better
if I wasn't with you.
Why?
This is your moment, Charles.
I-I think that...
when you step out
of that helicopter alone,
after saving the country,
that is an image that
history will never forget.
All right.
Thank you, Marti.
But don't be
far behind me, now.
I won't.
Thank you.
Captain.
I can fly this thing
if I have to,
which leaves you
with one of two choices.
You either do what I say and you
live, or you don't
and you die for nothing.
You understand me?
I want you to wait until
I give you my command, then
follow these
instructions slowly.
You're going to disconnect
your helmet from
the communications system.
Then I want you
to rip out the mic cable,
take your helmet off
and stow it.
Do it now.
I'll know if you deviate
from your flight plan.
Mr. President!
I have a message for you
from the White House!
LOGAN:
What the hell are you doing?!
Put these on!
You.
This is Jack.
Do you copy?
I'm here, Jack.
Where are you?
We just left the ranch.
I have Logan with me.
Is Morris standing by
with the equipment?
He's on his way. I'll
let him know you're airborne.
Make sure the pilot
takes heading 2-8-6
for two miles,
then breaks south.
Captain!
I want you to follow
heading 2-8-6
for two miles,
then break south.
Once you break south, there
should be an industrial park.
There's an abandoned
printing press facility
that you can use.
I'll get back to you.
Copy that.
What are you
trying to do, Jack?
Whatever it is,
you know you won't
get away with it.
Are you going to kill me?
I suppose you want
some sort of revenge.
I understand that.
Bad things happened.
I didn't want them to happen.
People who worked for me--
they-they went too far.
They did things
that they thought
I wanted them to do,
but they were wrong.
You have to understand.
I have always
acted in the country's
best interest.
But you're just trying
to get even.
Do you realize
what effect this will have
on the American people?
This day has been trying enough,
and now the President
is being attacked.
If you want
to do what's right,
you will turn this
thing around and go back.
Damn it, Bauer, say something!
Hello.
Morris.
Yes, love.
The helicopter is landing
in an industrial park
one mile due east
of where you are.
Head over there.
Okay, now, I give this guy
what we worked on,
and then I'm out, right?
Yes, but make sure
you have him call me
when you do
the hand-off.
All right.
Thanks.
Shut it down!
Your safety belt.
Move towards the door slowly.
Come on. Move!
Come on.
Move inside. Go.
Jack, maybe we can work
something out.
There's still time.
What do you want?
I can help you
get away from here
with enough money
to start a new life,
maybe find that daughter
of yours.
Try to work something out.
Whatever you want,
it's yours.
You have my word.
Your word.
Jack, I'm the President
of the United States.
I'm not, I'm not
carrying any weapons.
Don't you make a sound.
Hey.
Give me the case.
Jack Bauer.
I should have known that.
Modified equipment.
Yeah.
Oh, that's President Logan,
Jack.
Get out of here.
Yeah.
Chloe wants you to call her.
Go.
Yeah, Jack?
I have him.
All right.
I've just checked
the response deployment.
You have less than ten minutes
until they're on you.
Fine.
Listen, Jack.
I don't mean to put
any added pressure on you,
but if you don't have
a confession by then,
we'll all be arrested
for treason.
Is this some kind
of broadcast?
What is this?
I would like to know.
Is this an assassination?
A confession.
Don't count on it.
I know you're good
at extracting information.
I know that you're good
at torture.
I saw what you did
with Walt Cummings.
I think you'll be
surprised to find out
that I'm a little tougher
than that.
Take a seat.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, Jack.
I want to make sure that
you have good reception.
Who you talking to?
Are those your
friends at CTU?
You know you're putting them
in danger, as well.
Coming through
fine, Jack.
Okay, good.
My people can't be
far behind, Jack.
There's still time to get away.
Take it.
The plan involving the Sentox
nerve gas,
it was designed
to fool the terrorists
and the Russians.
Whether or not you formulated
the plan is irrelevant.
You authorized it.
You're delusional.
David Palmer uncovered
evidence of this plan.
When he started
asking questions,
he was assassinated.
Other people were killed
to cover that murder up.
Men and women who served this
country with distinction;
people that I worked with;
friends of mine.
No, you're wrong.
This is all a pack of lies.
The terrorists discovered
your deception.
And they deployed
Sentox nerve gas
on American soil.
Every American
who died today
as a result
of terrorist activity
is another murder that
you're accountable for.
And before you leave here,
you're going to admit it.
I suppose if you hurt me
enough, Jack,
I'll say whatever you want,
but that won't make it
the truth.
And everybody who watches this
will know that perfectly well.
What are the names
of your co-conspirators?
There are no co-conspirators,
because there is no...
Walt Cummings,
Christopher Henderson,
James Nathanson
have all admitted
to being part
of this conspiracy!
Now they are dead!
Right before
Christopher Henderson died
he acknowledged that
there were others!
What are their names?!
A man will say anything
under torture.
This won't mean a thing.
Mr. Logan, I'm not going
to torture you,
but you are going
to tell me what
I want to know.
Or so help me God,
I will kill you.
A year and a half ago,
I was warned
that my life was in danger
by someone within
the government.
I was told the only
way I could stay alive
was to create the illusion
that I was dead.
I was forced to deceive
people that I loved.
My only daughter
will never forgive me.
As I see the depth
of your corruption unfold,
I have no doubt
that you are that
source of danger.
David Palmer
was a great man.
And he was
a great president.
He was also my friend.
He tried to warn me
about you
and now he is dead.
Other people tried
to help me
and they are dead, too.
So, Mr. Logan, I hope
you understand
I have absolutely
nothing to lose.
You are going
to be held accountable
for your part
of everything that
happened today.
You are not going to be able
to hide behind the presidency.
Right here, right now,
you are going
to face justice!
And make no mistake
about this, this
is personal.
And if you think
for a second
that I am scared
to put a bullet
in your brain,
you don't know me.
I'm going to ask you
one last time,
who are your
co-conspirators?
You have until
the count of three,
or I will kill you.
One...
You make me a martyr, I'll go
down in history with Lincoln
and Kennedy, but you'll go down
with John Wilkes Booth
and Lee Harvey Oswald.
Is that what you want?
Two!
You're a man of honor.
How can you assassinate
a president of the
United States
in front
of the entire world?
If you love your country,
you won't pull the trigger.
Three!
You can't do it, can you?
No, Jack,
it's all right.
Jack, it's all right.
It's all right.
It's all right that you can't.
I'm the president.
Jack, they're here.
AGENT:
Lay flat on your stomach!
Put your hands
out in front of you!
Extend your arms!
Mr. President,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
I actually feel sorry
for that man.
He's delusional.
It would be better
if he were put
in some sort
of solitary confinement
for the time being.
Jack Bauer
wasn't able to get
the President to confess,
Mrs. Logan.
I'm sorry.
Why not?
What happened?
I'm not sure
of the details.
Bauer's in custody.
Gentlemen.
Thank you.
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
That will be all.
Thank you so much.
If I could just get you
to come this way. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
David...
Marti, don't
do this to me now.
You killed him.
You're a murderer.
Stop.
You are!
You're a criminal!
My wife is not well.
Would you please
escort her?
Get off me!
Don't you touch me!
Escort her into
the hangar, please.
You don't know what he did!
He's not fit to be president!
It is a sacrilege for him to be
even speaking David's name!
Don't...!
No!
I want to make sure
that she's all right.
Has the hangar
been cleared?
Yes, sir.
All secure.
It's empty.
Good.
Let them know that
I'll be back in a moment.
Yes, Mr. President.
You're not wearing some kind
of listening device, are you?
What are you
talking about?
I have to watch you
now, Marti.
You said that
I was a good liar,
but I am nothing
compared to you.
Charles...! Stop it!
Stop it!
Charles...
Aah!
Yeah, Marti.
Tell me the truth.
You're hurting me.
You don't know
what pain is.
I'm on to you, Marti.
I should've seen it
from the first,
but I wanted to believe
that you still cared for me.
Making love to me was
just a ploy, wasn't it?
Took a lot of planning
to get Jack Bauer
on that helicopter.
You were part of
that plan, weren't you?
It was your job
to delay me, wasn't it?
Wasn't it?!
Please...
They used you
so Jack Bauer
could get to me.
Come on, Marti.
Admit it,
you were part of it.
Yes. Yes.
Why?
Why...?
Why did you help them?
Because you killed
David Palmer.
I told you I didn't realize
that was going to happen.
Your people killed him
to protect you.
You covered it up,
that's just as bad.
I covered it up
because I had to.
Oh, and then others
died to cover that up.
That's right, for
the good of the country.
You sold nerve gas
to terrorists.
You're insane.
You're insane!
I did it
for the good of the country
as I saw it at the time.
You're such a hypocrite.
After your little
performance this morning,
you're in no position
to call me a hypocrite.
And I will tell you
something else--
if you blow up like this
one more time...
I will fill you
so full of drugs,
you won't even remember
your own name.
And then I will ship you
off to an asylum
and you can stay there
for the rest of your life.
Are we clear?
My fellow Americans,
this has been a terrible day
in the history of this country--
and yet at the same time,
a triumphant day,
because in the end,
we won a significant victory
over the forces of chaos
and terror.
We have preserved and protected
our way of life,
despite the loss
of innocent American lives.
I'll start the transmission
in one minute.
Is the Attorney General there?
I'm here, Ms. O'Brian.
I certainly hope
this recording is as important
as you claim it is.
Chloe, what's this about?
I set up
a conference call with
the Attorney General.
He's on speakerphone now.
Are you serious?
I'm very serious.
Mr. Attorney General,
this is Karen Hayes,
Homeland Security.
Bill Buchanan, CTU.
Sir, I apologize. Ms. O'Brian
placed this call without
authorization from me.
I'm sorry I had to do that.
We had to do things
under the radar
to protect you all in case
things went wrong.
In case what things
went wrong?
I think it would help
if I just played the recording.
HAYES:
What recording?
It's a conversation that took
place five minutes ago
between the President
and his wife.
How could you
possibly have a recording
of something like that?
Sir, an agent named Jack Bauer
placed a listening device
on the President shortly
before this conversation.
Bauer? Isn't he the one
that's under arrest?
CHLOE:
I'm going to play
the recording now.
I don't want
to listen to it.
Ms. O'Brian, at the very least,
this constitutes
an egregious violation
of privacy,
and we're talking about
the President.
MARTHA ( sobbing ):
...'cause you killed
David Palmer.
LOGAN:
I told you, I didn't realize
that was going to happen.
Your people killed him
to protect you.
You covered it up,
that's just as bad.
I covered it up
because I had to.
Oh, and then others
died to cover that up!
That's right, for
the good of the country.
You sold nerve gas
to terrorists.
You're insane.
You're insane!
A poet once said,
"No man is an island."
On a day like this, we can feel
the truth of those words.
Any untimely death is a tragedy.
Yet some men embody such
greatness of character
that their death
serves as a unifying force
for those who remain behind.
David Palmer was such a man.
A great President,
a great American--
and on a more personal note--
a wonderful friend.
He'll be missed...
( cell phone rings )
...more than words
can express...
Holtzman.
Yes, sir.
We take this moment to
remember with appreciation...
With all due respect,
Mr. Attorney General,
are you sure this isn't
some kind of mistake?
Yes, sir.
I understand, sir.
I'll do exactly as you say.
LOGAN:
...combination of wisdom,
strength and moral courage,
this country might have not
survived in its present form.
It's very appropriate that David
Palmer will be laid to rest
in Arlington Cemetery,
for he was a soldier
in the truest sense.
He was a man whose courage rose
in direct proportion
to the threats
his country faced.
In closing, I would ask
that the country
observe a national day
of mourning
for one of
the greatest Americans
this nation will ever see.
Thank you very much.
Federal marshall.
Would you please
come with us?
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
You came very close
to disrupting my speech.
BROWN:
On behalf of President Logan,
I wish to thank you all
very much for joining us.
I am sorry, but out of respect
for today's...
Those are ridiculous
accusations.
Excuse me.
If I may, sir?
You've probably never seen
one of these, Mr. President.
It's a micro-transmitter.
Agent Clark, arrest these men
and get them the hell
out of here.
I'm sorry.
Mr. President.
We have our orders.
You take...!
You take your orders
from me.
Not anymore.
After you, sir.
OFFICER:
Attention!
Aim, fire!
OFFICER:
Attention!
Aim,
fire!
Attention!
Aim,
fire!
Present arms.
Sir.
Give me a second.
Hey.
Thank God you're safe.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Jack, when I heard
you kidnapped the
President...
I was just trying
to get him to give me
a direct confession.
Jack...
How much longer
do you need to stay here?
Not much longer. They can
debrief me tomorrow.
You sure?
I can't believe
you're really,
you're really here.
Agent Bauer,
excuse me, but there's
a call for you
from your daughter.
From my daughter?
Yes, sir. A Kim Bauer.
It's been put through
to a land line
just inside that door.
Thank you.
I'll be right back.
I promise.
Take as long
as you need.
I'm not going anywhere.
I love you.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Kim?
Any word on Logan?
No. My guess
is he'll try
to cut a deal.
He'll resign
without a fight
in exchange for clemency.
He doesn't deserve clemency.
No, but the country
doesn't deserve
a long impeachment
process, either,
with everything
that's happened.
In any event, we can expect
Hal Gordon to be sworn in
as president soon.
Which means this
will probably be
the last time
I see this place.
I don't think so.
Not if I have anything
to do with it,
and I will.
You'll be back here
running CTU.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
When I came in here
last night to save the day,
I was a little bit
condescending and tactless,
to say the least.
I had no idea
what you were up against.
I'm sorry.
No. No need to apologize.
Mistakes were made.
You were right to come
in with a firm hand.
Well, I better go.
Karen.
I was thinking
of getting some breakfast
before going home.
I have to go over to Division
for one last briefing.
Bureaucracy.
Rain check?
Sure.
Chloe,
really good work today.
You, too.
I found this
in Edgar's possessions.
I thought you should
have it.
Thanks.
Hey.
What's all
this, then?
A friend of mine
who died today.
You, um, do you
want to talk about it?
Yeah? Come on.
Jack?
Oh, my God.
Agent Davis,
Jack Bauer's missing!
Attention, all units.
We have a missing agent:
Jack Bauer.
I repeat, we have
a missing agent: Jack Bauer.
...the lower level.
Put three men
on perimeter search.
Report back.
You surely must
be aware, Mr. Bauer,
that China has a long memory.
Only 18 months ago,
you invaded
our territory
and killed our consul.
Did you really think
that we would forget, hmm?
I know how this works.
I need to make one phone call.
Please...
just one phone call.
Kill me.
Just...
kill me.
Kill you?
You're far too valuable
to kill, Mr. Bauer.
Cync by QQ
www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net