Jack, this is hard for me.
The Chinese have proof
that you led the assault
on their consulate.
And now the Chinese want me.
That's right.
Listen to me very carefully.
The man they sent to take you
into custody
has orders to kill you.
Orders from who?
Someone in Logan's camp.
Bill Spaulding,
Secret Service.
I have orders to take
Jack Bauer into custody.
I intend to execute
those orders.
Jack!
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Jack!
Give me the epinephrine.
CHLOE:
I hope it's not too late.
He really looks dead.
Come on, Jack!
Come on, Jack, damn it!
Hey.
All right, Chloe, I need you
to run interference
with the local coroner.
Make sure
their database
synchs up with Jack's
information.
That won't cover the autopsy.
There's not going
to be an autopsy.
They wanted Jack dead,
now he's dead.
Mr. President,
you saved my life.
PALMER:
I'm only sorry it came to this.
I just wanted to let you know
that I was out.
I'm glad.
Jack, you do understand
that when you hang up,
for all intents and purposes,
Jack Bauer is dead.
JACK:
I understand that, sir.
Mr. President,
it's been an honor.
Jim Nichols!
You're on pump number one.
Sterling Rush, Patrick Priest.
You're on pump
number four.
Phil Stone,
Greg Nelson,
you're on pump five.
Sorry, guys, that's
all I got today.
Hey, Frank?
Look, I-I know
I promised
you work today,
but...
pump seven went
off-line last night.
That's all right.
I'll try again tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow'll
be much better.
See you tomorrow.
ANCHORMAN:
The sun is shining,
but the air is cool
at President Logan's retreat,
where Russian President
Yuri Suvarov
is expected to arrive
later this morning.
Everything worked for me,
up until the chapter
on your first campaign.
I'm sorry, but I think
it's a little long-winded,
and I think that we can
cut that down by half.
You didn't hear a word
I just said, did you?
Yes, I was listening.
No, you weren't.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I can use a break.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
I mean you've
been distracted
ever since you
got to Los Angeles.
I don't know, it's...
It's like you're
somewhere else.
Writing my memoirs...
maybe it's put me in
a melancholy mood.
Is that all it is?
Yeah.
David... I'm
your brother.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
It's all right, really.
Okay.
Well, then let's
get back to work.
One more chapter,
and we'll take a break.
Why don't we jump down
to, um, Chapter Six?
There's going to be
a lot of questions
about your relationship
with Sherry.
David!
No, no, no, no, no...
Get help!
Stay with me.
Stay with me!
Get help!
Walt.
My chair?
Don't worry,
Mr. President.
I had it adjusted.
Good.
Adjusted?
Wait a minute.
What are we talking
about here?
Yuri Suvarov is
over six feet.
Russian President can't be
looking down on the President
of the United States
when the cameras roll.
That's a risky
proposition, Walt.
The press finds out
about it, and...
They won't.
Don't underestimate the power
of the image, Mike.
Stalin and Churchill,
they both sat
for FDR at Yalta.
This is the defining moment
of my administration.
We have to make sure
that the media
presents it the right way.
( phone rings )
I'll get it.
Yeah, put
him through.
Have you checked on my wife?
Ah, she's still
getting ready.
She'll be fine, sir.
Hmm.
I'm in contact with Dr. Hill.
I'd feel better if you would
check on her yourself.
She cannot have
one of her meltdowns today.
Look...
you're the only one
she listens to, Walt.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Mike?
Mike, what is it?
David Palmer's
been assassinated.
What?!
It just happened.
Oh, my God.
Where?
In L.A.
I don't believe this.
Mr. President, uh, CTU is
standing by
to brief you directly.
Whenever you're ready.
Make sure LAPD sets up
a hard perimeter.
They're sending everyone
they've got.
Where are they
on witnesses?
Nowhere yet.
Who's running search
and sweep?
Secret Service, but
they're shorthanded.
Narrow the search area.
Make sure ballistics runs
a line-of-fire
trajectory.
Sir, President Logan's ready.
I'll call ballistics.
Put the President through.
Mr. President.
Bill... not to diminish
the loss that we're all
feeling right now,
but I'm expecting the Russian
President very soon, so...
let's say what needs to be said.
Of course, sir.
Have you arrested
the person who did this?
Not yet, sir.
Then what do you have?
Sir, the damage inflicted
by the single shot indicates
that President Palmer was hit
by a 308-caliber bullet
fired from an adjacent building.
We've initiated an interagency
protocol, level five...
Don't... don't give me
protocols, Bill.
Give me results.
Whoever did this, I want them
dead or in custody
by the time
the Russians get here.
Yes, Mr. President.
But until we know more,
I would ask that you consider
postponing the signing
of the treaty, sir.
No. Absolutely not.
Mr. President, we can't
discount the possibility
that this attack
is somehow connected
to the arms agreement.
A former president
was assassinated 15 miles
from where you are.
And I'm sure
I don't need to explain
the significance of this day.
Do you realize what kind of
political and economic capital
I've spent just to get
the Russians to the table?
If we call this off,
they won't come back.
Spencer?
Spencer!
What?
Get out of my bed.
Yeah.
I had a good time
last night, too.
I'm serious.
This was a mistake.
Get out of here.
What do you mean, a mistake?
We had a great time.
I don't get involved with people
who work for me.
It's too late for that.
I would appreciate it
if you didn't tell
everybody at work about this.
I don't want everyone thinking
I'm some kind of slut.
Believe me, no one's ever going
to think that.
What's that supposed to mean?
You should lighten up, you know?
You'll live longer.
What are you doing?
When you quit overanalyzing
the situation,
I think you're
gonna find out
that you and I are
pretty good together.
So I'm telling you
advce, yes.
Yes, what?
I'll let you buy me dinner.
Get me drunk.
Have your way with me.
Anytime you want.
You know, um, arrogance
doesn't turn me on.
I've read that some
women respond to it,
but I'm just letting
you know, I don't.
What is it?
President Palmer's been shot.
He's dead.
REPORTER:
While it remains unclear
how the assassination
will impact today's
scheduled signing
of the arms treaty with Russia,
President Logan is expected
to make a statement shortly.
Again, if you are
just joining us,
former President David Palmer
has been assassinated.
We're going to take
a few moments now to look
at the former president's
great achievements.
Who is it?
WOMAN:
It's me, Frank.
Hey.
I saw your truck outside.
I thought you
were on today.
Oh, Ned didn't
need me this morning.
Hmm.
It's so terrible,
what happened.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Come on, I'm
making breakfast.
Okay.
Frank's gonna
join us.
Great.
Derek, stop it.
Morning.
Use a glass, please.
Here.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you something, Frank?
Yeah, sure.
That rig in Alaska you worked
on, what was that called again?
The Albatross.
And you were thereast year?
Yeah, why?
It's funny.
My friend's got a brother
who's been working
on that rig for five years
and he's never heard
of any Frank Flynn.
It's a big platform.
Yeah, well, my friend's brother
says everyone knows everyone.
What is this, an interrogation?
I just don't like being lied to.
Derek.
No, it's all right.
No one's lying to you, Derek.
When you're out there, a lot
of the guys just use nicknames.
DIANE:
Yeah.
What's your friend's
brother's name?
Eat your breakfast.
Yeah, I'm not hungry.
Sorry.
He's just kind of
protective of me.
But it's the best thing
in the world for him
to have a man around here.
Look, what he said about me
and Alaska...
You don't owe me an explanation.
I figure if you had wanted
l me about your past
you would have
told me already.
I trust my instincts.
And I trust you.
Former President David Palmer
was killed
just a short while ago.
Now, no information
has been released to the public
athis time,
but an independent source
has verified
that Palmer was in Los Angeles
visiting his brother
and former White...
Bill will call if he
needs us, you know that.
No, he won't.
Authorities are remaining
very tightlipped
as the LAPD and Secret Service
seal off the area,
and there has been no word on
whether this was an accident...
It's not our job.
Not anymore.
This is different.
Come on, Michelle.
I'm just as upset
as you are.
David Palmer meant
a lot to me, too.
But there are other people
at CTU who can handle this.
No one who was active
during the other attempts
onis life.
Tony, you and I worked up
suspect profiles.
We ran scenarios.
And theyAneth
our records on file.
They don't have
our experience.
I never once regretted
our decision to leave CTU.
But I don't want
to look back
on today and realize
I could have helped.
We're running a business here,
Michelle.
Rick Rosen is expecting us
to make a presentation
in less than an hour.
You can handle the meeting
on your own.
Michelle, don't do this.
It's Rick.
Leave me a message.
Yeah, Rick, it's Tony Almeida.
Look, I just wanted to call you
and let you know
that Michelle's not gonna be
able to make our meeting today.
She had to go someplace.
On second thought...
I'm going with her.
Did Jepson brief you
on what's happening?
Said there was
a car bombing.
Two former CTU agents were hit.
Yeah, their names are Michelle
Dessler and Tony Almeida.
You knew them?
Yeah.
We're data-mining
for a connection
between them
and President Palmer.
I sent the parameters
to your screen.
I'll get on it.
Yeah?
It's Edgar. Are you coming in?
, I just, I  paged
on a level five protocol,
X
of crse I'm coming in.
I wanted to give you aveeads up
before you got here.
Heads up?
It's bad, Chloe.
Yeah, President Palmer
was gunned down.
I'd say that's pretty bad.
It's not just him.
What are you talking about?
Someone planted a bomb in
Michelle Dessler's car.
What?
Michelle's dead.
He
Tony's not doing too good.
Doesn't make any sense.
They were retired.
Buchanan thinks it's lind
to Palmer somehow.
We're cross-referencing
everything we have on Palmer
with Tony and Michelle, to see
if we can find a connection,
anything they may
have had in common.
Chloe?
Go.
I'll call you back.
I'll call you back!
Why? Chloe?
Since I don't have
to go to work today,
I can take care of the fence
out back if you want.wa
Oh, that'd be great.
I can't thank you enough
for all the work
you've down around here.
It's t least
I could do.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Jack, I know
this isn't protocol.
Please don't hang up on me.
I need your help.
Uh, hold on,
I can barely hear you.
I don't have a very
good signal.
Excuse me.
What is it?
They got Tony and Michelle.
Michelle is dead.
Tony is in critical
condition.
Now they're gonna
kill me.
What are you
talking about?
There's four people
that know you're alive.
Three of them are down.
Jack, I'm the only one left.
This has to be about you.
It's the only thing the four
of us have in common.
What happened
to Tony tod Michelle.
There was a car bomb.
X
There was a guy outside my
apartment and he was chasing me.
Oh, my God.
Where is he now?
I think I lost him.
I'm at a pay phone.
I dumped my cell phone.
I don't know
what to do now.
Chloe, you need to go dark.
That means zero contact
with anyone.
Even CTU?
Especially CTU.
Whoever's behind this
is probably monitori them.
Someone out ther
knows I'm still alive.
Who?
I don't know, but that's
what we need to find out.
Right now, I want you to head
north out of Los Angeles.
There's  abandoned oil
refinery at Variel and Topanga.
I want you to wait
for me there
You can take cover
by the large storage tanks
at the north end of the field.
You're coming to L.A.?
Give me about
a half an ho.
Okay. Thanks.
Tony Almeida
is being medevaced in.
We have a trauma team standing
by to receive him in medical.
You're bringing him
to CTU?
If there's a second
attempt on his life,
we can't protect him
in a hospital.
This doesn't track.
Michelle and Tony have been
inactive for over a year.
Who'd want them dead?
Whoever wanted Palmer dead.
So we're assuming
they're connected.
The timing
was too close
to write it off
as a coincidence.
There is a connection.
Let's find it.
Sir, the DOD liaison is here.
I need to set her up
with the security
protocols for the summit.
I'll take care of it.
You have your assignments.
Send updates
directly to my screen.
Where is she?
She just cleared security.
Thank you.
Audrey.
Bill.
Must be hard for you
to be back here.
Thank you, Bill. I'm fine.
I'm sorry
about Michelle.
Walt Cummings briefed me
on the way over here.
He said that you
wanted to postpone
the signing of
the treaty.
President Logan
is making a mistake.
I don't disagree.
Have you let him
know that?
He's the President, Bill.
It's his call.
That's what
I'm afraid of.
He wants me to make sure
that your top priority is still
security for the summit.
Station Five is set up for you.
When you're situated,
we'll go over the revised
security protocol.
Great.
Thank you, Bill.
David Palmer was a man
of truth and of honor.
And his influence will be felt
for generations to come.
Our nation grieves
for its loss.
Martha and I offer
our deepest sympathy.
You look beautiful,
Mrs. Logan.
I look like a wedding cake.
Les start over.
Oh, you can get that.
Is Mrs. Logan ready?
Not quite.
You didn't tell her
about David Palmer?
No.
Thank you.
She'll take it hard
when she finds out.
They've been friends
for a long time.
You don't have to talk
about me like I'm not here.
Excuse us, Evelyn.
Martha...
I... I'm sorry.
Look, I know... I know I'm late.
I'm sorry.
I just... I'm having
a bad hair day.
Martha...
I've got som
very bad news.
But... it's not Charles,
is it?
No. No, he's fine.
He wanted to tell
you himself...
Well... what?
Walt, Walt...
well, what... what is it?
David Palmer
was assassinated.
No...
I'm sorry.
I know how close
you were.
When did this happen?
Less than an hour ago.
This morning?!
I...
I... I have to talk to Charles.
He's doing damage control,
trying to keep this
om pushing the treaty
off the front page.
No, no, oh, no, I have
to talk to him now.
No. He's doing a
press conference...
No!
Martha!
Agent North!
Call John, tell him
not to let Mrs. Logan
anywhere near the stage.
Yeah, give me Dr. Hill.
As I look back upon the deeds
of David Palmer--
not only one of this country's
greatest leaders,
but one of this world's
greatest men...
Our nation grieves
for its loss...
Mrs. Logan...
Let go of me.
Let go of me! Let go!
I can't let you...
...to President Palmer's
entire family.
MARTHA:
Would you get
away from me?
LOGAN:
And to them, I also pledge
the full resources
of this great nation
to find and to punish
those responsible.
AGENT:
No, no, no.
Get aw from me.
I can't let you go out there.
Don't-don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
Get away from me
now, or I swear
I will have your family
eating dog food out of a can.
Martha, stop it!
Mike, damn it, I
am the First Lady!
Tell your storm trooper
to stay away from me!
CUMMINGS:
Certainly.
I need to talk
to my husband.
Martha, look... he's in the
middle of a press conference
right now.
Hundreds of
millions of people
are watching him live.
LOGAN:
...interfere with my job
of making this country
more secure.
What is it, Martha?
What is so urgent?
LOGAN:
...I have decided to keep
my scheduled meeting
with the Russian president
Maybe I can help.
LOGAN:
Yuri Suvarov and I will sign
a comprehensive treaty
that promises
a new level of cooperation
between us and our Russian
friends in the war on terror.
Tell Charles I want to
see him when he's done.
Don't shoot me.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm sorry I followed you.
I'm just... I'm just worried
about my mother.
Get up.
Get up. Get up!
Damn it!
Come here.
You're going with me.
This is none
of my business.
This is none of
my business.
I won't tell anyone.
Just let me go, okay?
I really wish
I could, kid,
but I can't.
You're going with me.
Now get in the helicopter.
Frank, Frank,
come on, please.
Get into the helicopter.
Move!
BESSON:
Prep a sterile
cranial field.
I need access to the
right hemisphere.
I need to talk to Tony
before he goes
into surgery.
He's non-responsive.
According to the paramedic
on the chopper, he suffered
a closed head trauma
that's affected
his speech.
They're going to try
to insert a stint
to relieve the pressure.
Will he be able
to talk then?
The doctor doesn't know.
I want real time updates
on his progress.
We need Tony to
explain this.
What is it?
I may have found
a connection
between Tony and
David Palmer.
Tony's phone records?
One call in particular.
The last time Tony spoke
to President Palmer
was the day
that Jack Bauer was killed.
Pull the transcripts?
I tried, but the files
were corrupted.
What's he hiding?
Something about Jack's death.
DEREK:
Are you kidnapping me?
No!
Then where are you taking me?
Los Angeles.
Why?
Because I couldn't
leave you back there.
You'd have gone to the police,
and I couldn't let that happen.
But what is this about?
Who are you?
Someone who's not supposed
to still be alive.
Like some kind
of witness relocation thg?
Yeah, mething lith that.
So you were a criminal.
No. Listen, Dere the less
you know about me, the better.
So what are you going
to do with me?
DIANE:
Hello?
Diane, it's me.
Frank, I can
just barely hear you.
What's that noise?
I'm in a helicopter with Derek.
Derek?
Yeah. He's fine.
Listen, Diane, I need you
to pick him up
hiin Los Angeles for me.
Why is he with you?
I'll explain everything
as soon as I see you.
Frank, Frank,
what are you doing with Derek?
Diane, please
just do this for me.
I need you to get in a car a
and start driving now.
You're scaring me.
Heane, do you remember
this morning,
when you said
that you trusted me?
Right now, I need you
to trust me.
Derek's going to be fine.
Just do what I say.
I need you to get in a car
and start driving
towards Los Angeles.
Don't talk to anybody
about this.
And I'll get back to you
as soon as I can.
Frank?
I don't understand.
You're just going to
hand me back to my mom?
I thought you were worried
about me going to the police.
I have something to do
in Los Angeles.
Once it's done,
it doesn't matter.
FO
How are you doing?
I'm sorry, Charles.
I didn't mean
to make a scene.
I know that.
Dr. Hill says you haven't
been taking your medication.
I don't like the way
the pills make me feel.
Martie...
we just need to
get through today.
Charles...
the reason that I needed to...
eded to talk to you...
What is it, honey?
Go ahead.
I think...
that David was killed
because of something
he was about to tell me.
What are you talkiou aal?
He called me
yesterday.
He said he wanted
to meet with me.
Meet with you about what?
He said it concerned
national security,
and that it involved you.
Me?
Yes.
What else did he say?
Just that he would explain
when he saw me.
If this was so important,
why wouldn't he have
called me himself?
Well, Charles, you shut him
out of this White House
about 18 months ago.
You know that.
He had no real access.
Except through you.
You don't believe me.
I didn't s that.
You didn't need to.
Martha...
I am not
making this up.
I am not crazy;
I am not a fool,
Charles!
Martha...
it's going to
be all right.
I'm not making this up.
All right.
I'll have Walt look into it.
You will?
Yes.
Thank you.
But right now...
President Suvarov and his wife
are arriving in one hour.
I need you to be there.
I need you by my side.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Was she all right?
No, Walt, she's
not all right.
She's having another one
of her delusions.
She thinks that David
Palmer was killed
because of something he
was about to tell her.
She's imagining
she's in the middle of one
of her own conspiracy theories.
Well, what should we do?
Nothing.
Spenser, have you talked
to Chloe this morning?
No. Why?
She left her apartment
about a half hour ago.
She should've been here by now.
It's probably traffic.
She commutes
against traffic.
And she's not answering
her cell phone.
I wouldn't worry about it.
She sounded strange
when I talked to her.
She always sounds strange.
I'm gonna call Adamson, have him
run a locate on her cell.
Don't waste his time, Edgar.
She's fine.
I'm sure of it.
What makes you so sure?
It doesn't matter.
It does to me.
I saw her, okay?
Uh, about half an hour ago.
But I thought you said...
Forget what I said.
Where did you see her?
Man...
do you really need me
to spell it out for you?
Don't worry about Chloe.
She's fine, all right?
You can just let me out here.
There's nothing here.
Just pull over, please.
FO
I still don't
understand what this
is all about, Frank.
Will you please tell me
what's going on?
Please?
A friend of mine's
in trouble.
I needed to pick her up
in a hurry.
This is the only way
I could get to her quick enough.
X FO
HeFO
Chloe.
Jack!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
What's happening?
Why would anyone
want to kill the people
who know you're alive?
I don't know yet,
but we're gonna find out.
Right now, I need to get access
to CTU's archives
from a secure location--
can you help me do that?
I can't do it
from my laptop.
But there's a research
loft at Cal Tech.
I can get us in.
Who's that?
I'll explain as soon
as we're in the car.
I don't have a car.
I took a cab.
Come on, get in
the helicopter.
We got to go.
Derek, get back in.
X
( tires screech )
Jack?
What?
CHLOE:
It's them.
How did theydiind me?
I don't think
they ever lost you.
Come on.
What's going on, Frank?
Who are they?
What are we waiting
for? Take off!
We're not at speed!pe
We're not gonna make it.
Get out! Get out now,
and stay by the side
of the helicopter!
Here! Take him and go
into the refinery!
Find somewhere
to hide! Move!
Double back, cut him off.
Go through the
smoke screen;
I'm going around.
Hold your fire, Chloe!
Jack, what are you doing?
Let's get out of here.
Chloe, take Derek
and walk away.
Walk away now!
At the rate you're bleeding out,
you're not gonna make it
unless you get
medical attention.
You tell me
what I want to know,
and I will get you
to a hospital,
you understand me?
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
Four people knew I was alive.
This morning,
you tried to take them out.
Why are you
coming after me?
Palmer was my...
primary target.
They only cared
about Palmer.
The others were just
a diversion...
...to set you up,
maket look
like you did it.
Why'd they want
to kill Palmer?
To keep him from talking.
They had to
shut him up.
What'd he know?
HeI wasn't given
that information.
Only hired...
to take out the principle.
You're the one
that killed Palmer.
Yeah.
Who's behind this?
Oh...
I got my orders
through a code of silence.
We never use names,
you know that.
That's all I know.
Take me to a hospital.
Yeah.
Sync:FRM-xxy
-=http://www.1000fr.com=-
www.tvsubtitles.net