BIERKO:
We release the Sentox here
and 200,000 people die.
We need access to
the control room.
CHLOE:
Jack, Bierko will be ready
to deploy any minute.
JACK:
If we could ignite that gas
before it leaves the plant,
the Sentox will be incinerated.
JACK:
Bierko!
Give me a hand.
Organize an escort team.
You get him back
to CTU alive.
You got it.
I just word from the FAA
about a hijacking
aboard a diplomatic flight.
So, what?
Jack Bauer is the hijacker.
GRAHAM:
What was he doing
on that flight?
Looking for the recording
that implicates me
in David Palmer's death.
Order the plane down and grab
Bauer before he can hurt us.
We need to take him down now,
dead or alive.
Mr. President?
I don't care if Bauer's
making threats or not,
that plane has
to land immediately.
And when it lands,
I want my secret service detail
to take him into custody.
Sit down!
He has a gun!
Everybody just
stay in your seats!
Do what I tell you
and no one will get hurt!
Captain, this I Jack Bauer.
I'm speaking to you
on a discreet channel.
The person that I'm
looking for, the man
with the evidence
that I need, is
sitting next to you.
He's your copilot,
Scott Evans.
JACK ( over headset ):
You need to open the door.
Could you, uh, take the stick
for a second?
( captain grunts )
( struggling )
I'm the only one
who can fly this plane now!
Give me the recording.
Advise CTU I have the recording.
I'll be on the ground
in less than 15 minutes.
Bauer's got the evidence.
He is in control of the plane.
What do we do?
You are going to have to shoot
down that plane, Mr. President.
Otherwise, you'll go to prison
for treason and murder.
AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER:
Sierra Tango, cleared to flight
level 2-2-0, report reaching.
5-2-0, Sierra Tango descend
to flight level 2-2-0.
We can expect the
approach to Van Nuys.
Good.
This is Jack Bauer.
Can you patch me through
to Karen Hayes?
( over phone ):
Hold please.
I'm bleeding.
I think you broke my nose.
You'll get medical attention
as soon as we're on the ground.
Right now, your only concern
should be flying this plane.
( over intercom ):
Miss Hayes, I've got Jack Bauer
on line one.
Put him through.
Yes, Jack?
I've got the recording.
It was on the copilot.
The copilot?
Yeah, he was
working for Henderson.
The captain's unconscious,
but I've secured the copilot.
We're en route
back to Van Nuys airfield.
What's our ETA?
21 minutes.
We're going to be
on the ground in 21 minutes.
Karen, listen to me.
This recording proves
that President Logan
was complicit
in David Palmer's assassination.
It's imperative that we do not
let it fall into the hands
of anyone that is loyal
to the president.
As soon as we're on the ground,
I'm going to need you
to provide me with a safe
corridor back to CTU.
Jack, it's Bill.
I'm back here with Karen.
I'll explain everything later.
We can dispatch a team
to meet you at the airfield.
They can head off
any law enforcement,
take you
into protective custody.
Okay, good.
Bill, how is Audrey?
Curtis just brought her in.
She's in Medical
getting treated, but it looks
like she's going to be okay.
Thank God.
Okay, I'll get back to you
as soon as we're
on final approach.
All right.
Audrey.
I just got off the phone
with County General.
I have some great news.
Your father
survived the crash.
He's alive?
Yeah, one of our teams
picked him up
about 30 minutes ago
at the accident site.
He's still in ICU, but they
expect him to pull through.
Oh, my God.
We have a team
stationed at the hospital.
He'll be well-protected.
Thank you.
( phone rings )
I have to take this.
Curtis?
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
This is Manning.
Is Henderson secured?
He's in Holding
Room Three.
Good.
I need you to take a team
to pick up Jack.
Where is he?
He's on a plane heading towards
the Van Nuys airport.
ETA is 20 minutes.
Why is he on a plane?
He had to commandeer the plane
in order to secure the evidence
against President Logan.
I'll brief you
with the details en route.
Curtis, I cannot emphasize
strongly enough
the explosive nature of the
evidence that Jack is carrying.
I need you to put him
into protective custody
and bring him back here to CTU.
Understood.
President Logan will probably
send his men to retrieve it.
You've got to get
to Jack first.
We will. I'm heading out.
( phone rings )
Yes?
We have a solution
that will allow you
to order the plane shot down.
I sure as hell hope so.
I may be the president, but
there are protocols in place
that I can't
just ignore.
What we're proposing will
circumvent your protocols.
What is it?
We're going to simulate
a VCI distress signal.
It'll be broadcast on the
airplane's transponder code,
and it will appear to come
from Bauer's flight.
Hold on. What is
a VCI distress signal?
It's an emergency signal
indicating that there's a
hijacking in progress,
and that the perpetrators
intend to use the
aircraft as a weapon.
It'll give you the
pretext to shoot it down.
There really is no other
legitimate response
to this scenario, Mr. President.
All you need to do is appear
to struggle with the ethics
and then give the order.
Mr. President?
Fine.
All right.
You sound reluctant.
I can't believe
it's come to this.
I'm going to shoot
down a plane
full of innocent people.
None of us is happy
about this, Mr. President,
but you don't really
have a choice.
Bauer has evidence implicating
you in this conspiracy,
and I don't have to tell you
what the consequences will be
for all of us
if it's released.
We should contact Chloe
and bring her in.
We're going to
want her help
bringing Jack
back to CTU.
HAYES:
Fine.
Send an escort.
Karen, I appreciate this.
I know you're putting
everything on the line
to help us.
All I can say is
this recording better be
everything Jack
claims it is.
I know Jack.
I don't always agree
with his methods,
but I trust his judgment.
I'll go make that call.
What's going on?
What's Buchanan doing
out of Holding?
The situation
has changed, Miles.
There's some new intel.
I haven't seen anything.
What new intel?
I don't have time
to explain it right now.
What does that mean?
It means that I'll brief you
when I've got the chance.
Have you compiled the orders
for Bierko's transfer?
I'm still working on them.
Let me know
when you've got them.
What is it, Mike?
A situation has come up
regarding the hijacked plane.
Tell me what's happening.
The FAA just picked up
a VCI distress code.
It originated
from flight ST-520.
What's a VCI distress code?
The VCI is a coding system
that was recently installed
on all commercial airliners.
This particular code indicates
that a hijacking is underway,
and that the plane
is going to be used
to target installations
on the ground.
Oh, my God.
Admiral Kirkland
is standing by
on video-conference
from Point Mugu.
He's ready to brief
you with the details.
Admiral Kirkland,
I'm Mike Novick.
I have the
President here.
Mr. President.
Admiral. Mike's told me
about this VCI signal.
How could it have been sent
without Bauer's knowledge?
Most likely, one of the pilots
under duress secretly activated
the transponder code.
Let me get this straight.
At last report, Bauer was in
the passenger cabin.
Does this mean that
he's now in the cockpit
and that he's in control
of the plane?
It appears that way, sir.
( sighs )
What do we do, Admiral?
Sir, the protocols for this
scenario are clearly specified.
We're compelled
to take preemptive action.
What action?
The aircraft must be shot down.
We've already scrambled an F-18
out of Point Mugu.
We just need your approval
to engage.
There are over 50 people
on that plane, Admiral.
We have to think of the people
on the ground, Mr. President.
Over 20 million citizens live
in Los Angeles County,
each one of them
is now a potential target.
I don't believe this.
Mr. President, if
I can interject.
Admiral, it's hard for me
to accept
that Bauer intends to use
the aircraft as a weapon
against civilians.
From my briefing document,
Jack Bauer
is a distraught individual
with a history
of erratic behavior.
Jack Bauer has spent
his entire career
protecting American lives.
I think there's a reason
he's doing what he's doing.
What would that be?
I don't have the answer,
but we should at
least try to find out.
We don't have the time.
Mr. President, we
could have the F-18
shadow the aircraft.
We could issue
a standing order
to fire
only if the target deviates
from its present course.
That's not a viable option,
Mr. President.
Why not?
Right now, that plane
is over the desert.
In another 15 minutes,
it'll be above Los Angeles.
If we're forced
to shoot it down then,
there'll be facing massive
casualties on the ground.
And, Mr. President,
we must also consider
the possibility
that Bauer intends to attack
the Presidential Retreat.
The Retreat?
You're inside the target zone,
and Bauer's already been accused
of killing one president today.
The simple fact is, sir,
we don't know
what his intentions are.
Mr. President...
Mike. Stop.
I've made my decision.
Admiral, I'm authorizing you
to shoot down that plane.
Yes, sir.
Mr. President...
Mike, please.
Don't make this
any more difficult for me
than it already is.
Miss Hayes.
This just came in
over the interagency sub-net.
BUCHANAN:
What is it?
We have to alert Jack.
This is Bauer.
Jack, air traffic control just
received a VCI distress signal
from your aircraft.
That effectively authorizes
President Logan
to shoot you down.
Shoot us down?
BUCHANAN:
And F-18's been scrambled
out of Point Mugu, Jack.
You have eight to ten minutes
at best.
Can you patch me through
to the pilot
of the F-18?
No chance.
They're on a coded frequency.
We can try to get in touch
with the White House.
And tell them what?
They don't want to hear
anything I have to say.
Hold on.
We need to land this plane now.
We're 100 miles from
the nearest airport.
They just scrambled an F-18
to shoot us out of the sky.
We need to get
on the ground now!
You didn't hear me.
There's nowhere to land.
How much runway do you need?
At least 5,000 feet.
Bill, do you hear me?
Yeah, Jack.
I need you to look
for a stretch of freeway
5,000 feet long, straight enough
for us to land on.
I'll pull up maps
in the area, Jack.
It'll take a few seconds.
Get back to me as soon as
you've got something.
We can't land
on the freeway.
Yes, we can.
It's late, there's a curfew.
There won't be any cars
on the freeway.
Cuff your right hand
to the flight control, now.
All the way.
Start taking us down.
Do it now.
What's Chloe
O'Brian doing here?
I don't know.
You can go.
What's going on?
An F-18's been scrambled
to shoot down Jack's plane.
Can you open
up a socket
with the ATC radar
tracking plot?
Yeah, I think so.
Do it, Chloe.
We need to know
the exact amount of time
Jack has before the
fighter plane reaches him.
Okay.
Karen, look at this.
Two possible
landing sites.
I think this one's
the best shot.
I agree.
Let's get Jack on the phone.
I need to speak with you.
We need to make an
emergency landing.
Talk to your passengers
and get them ready.
What's happening?
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just get them ready.
Okay.
Listen up, everybody.
We're going to prepare
for an emergency landing.
The proper procedure...
It's Bauer.
Jack, it's Bill, I think
we found something.
Bill, hold
on one sec.
I want to put you
on speakerphone.
Go ahead.
It's a stretch
of the 118 freeway
between mile
marker 91 and 92.
There's about 4,000 feet,
then there's an overpass.
That's not long enough.
It's the best
we can do.
Copy that, Bill.
Hold on, give
me a second.
You can either try and land this
plane on the freeway or I will.
Give me the coordinates.
3-4-5-0.2 north
by 1-1-0-3-0.4 west.
We need to know
where that F-18 is.
Jack, it's Chloe.
I'm working on it.
CURTIS:
Manning.
We have the exact location
where Jack's putting down.
Go ahead.
It's the 118 freeway
between mile markers 91 and 92.
He should be
on the ground
within minutes.
Copy. We're redirecting.
118 freeway.
Copy.
Mr. President,
we're five minutes away.
I'm patching us in directly
with the pilot of the F-18.
Go ahead.
KIRKLAND:
Bravo One, this is
Admiral Kirkland.
You're on with the president
and myself.
Report status.
My radar is locked
onto the target.
Target is in a steep descent.
Maintaining radar lock-on.
Okay, I've got
the ATC radar plot.
Put it on the
main screen.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, the F-18
is within 15 miles.
They're not
gonna make it.
He's gonna be within the
missile range in two minutes.
You're not
descending fast enough.
If we increase the descent
rate, we won't be able
to pull out of the dive.
If we don't get on the ground
before that F-18 reaches us,
it's not gonna
matter. Descend now!
( people screaming )
SUE:
Put the oxygen masks on!
PILOT:
Target has increased angle
and rate of descent.
One minute from missile lock.
Jack, they're almost
within weapons range.
The aircraft
can't take this.
I have to pull up.
Not yet!
I can see the freeway!
Come on.
Okay, level up now! Now!
We can't pull out of the dive!
I need your help! Pull!
( alarm sounding )
Ground proximity alert.
20 seconds to missile lock.
Target's at 1,000 feet
and leveling.
Leveling?
PILOT:
Affirmative, sir.
What does that mean?
Target may be preparing to land.
The objective seems to be
the 118 freeway.
Lower the landing gear!
We're going too fast!
Lower it!
He's lowering his landing gear.
The F-18's in range.
I have missile lock.
KIRKLAND:
The aircraft is in
a landing profile, sir.
I recommend we abort.
What?
The parameters
have changed, sir.
I want that plane shot down!
Sir...
Order your man to fire, now!
Mr. President!
Admiral Kirkland is right.
The aircraft's not a threat.
There's no reason to do this.
I implore you to reconsider.
Abort.
Yes, sir.
But if they
don't land,
I want you to shoot that
plane down immediately!
Yes, Mr. President.
Bravo One, hold fire.
I repeat, hold fire.
Copy, base.
Bravo One holding fire.
We have Marine units
deployed in the area.
I want them to cordon off
the landing site
and apprehend Jack Bauer.
Yes, sir.
500 feet!
We're not gonna make it.
Come on.
CTU.
We've spotted the plane.
They're coming in for a landing.
We're heading towards them now.
I'm handing the controls
back to you!
Touch it down!
We're still going too fast!
( people screaming )
Target has touched down.
I'm clear.
Returning to base.
Bill, we made it.
We're down on the ground.
Jack, we've redirected Curtis
to your location.
He should be there
in a few minutes.
I'm just east
of the Balboa overpass.
Have him meet me there.
Send a secondary team
to pick up the copilot
and EMTs for the pilot.
Got it.
Get out of there, Jack!
Everyone, keep moving
to the rear
of the plane!
Exit from the rear, now!
You should have followed
through, Mr. President.
You should have ordered
that pilot to fire.
They were landing on a freeway.
I had no pretext
to shoot them down.
I had to abort.
It's going to be much harder
to contain now,
if not impossible.
Bauer's on the ground.
He won't get far.
Even before
the plane touched down,
I ordered two battalions
of Marines into the area.
They're cordoning off the
landing site, even as we speak.
Bauer...
has nowhere to run.
I hope you're right,
Mr. President.
This is our last chance.
If Bauer gets through...
I know.
I know what's at stake, Graham.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I have any news.
( sirens wailing )
( garbled radio transmission )
( cell phone rings )
Yeah.
Curtis, it's Jack!
Go ahead.
The Marines are moving in.
They're setting up a perimeter.
Where are you?
We're approaching your position
from the north.
Okay, I got you.
I'll meet you on the north side
of the freeway.
( garbled radio transmission )
They know I'm
still in the area.
We got to get
out of here.
Head south on Variel. Move.
Damn it.
You're gonna have to try
and talk your way
through the roadblock.
Get your hands up!
Hands where
we can see them.
We're federal agents.
Los Angeles
Counter Terrorist Unit.
We've been given orders
to detain everybody inside
this perimeter.
We're all on
the same team here, Commander.
We're trying to
apprehend the suspect
who hijacked that plane.
Jack Bauer?
That's right.
Now, let us
do our job.
I need to see individual ID's.
I'm gonna call this in.
We don't have time
for this, Commander.
The longer we sit here,
the better chance
Bauer has of slipping
through the net.
This will only take
a few minutes.
A few minutes is all Bauer needs
to escape.
We're not prepared
to let that happen.
Now we're moving out.
If you really want to fire
on federal agents,
that's your call.
Stand down.
Move out.
Stand down!
Head east for a while,
then turn south.
Yes, sir.
Buchanan.
It's Curtis.
We've got Jack,
and we're headed back in.
Okay, Curtis.
Marines are all over the place.
Barely got past one
of the patrols.
They must be taking
direct orders from Logan.
There's no other explanation.
We can't take the
chance of running
into any more
of these patrols.
We'll stick to
the back streets.
Understood.
( phone rings )
Hayes.
MILES:
I want to know what's going on.
Miles, I told you
I would tell you
when I felt the
time was right.
I'm sitting here
watching you work
with two people under arrest
for aiding and abetting
a federal fugitive.
If you don't talk to me,
I'll have to get my answers
somewhere else.
I'll be right there.
You can't tell him.
I can't hold him
off any longer.
You really think
that's a good idea?
I have to trust him.
He's been nothing but loyal.
I probably shouldn't have
kept him in the
dark this long.
I'll be right back.
I don't appreciate
being threatened, Miles.
And I don't appreciate
being shut out.
We've worked a lot
of years together, Karen,
and I have never wavered
in my allegiance.
I don't deserve this.
No, you don't.
Come with me.
Jack Bauer's
acquired evidence
implicating President Logan
in David Palmer's death.
Have you seen this evidence?
No, but Bauer's bringing it
here now.
What is it?
It's a recording
of a conversation
between the president
and an accomplice.
But you haven't heard it?
No.
And that's what you're doing
with Buchanan and O'Brian?
Covertly helping Bauer?
Yes.
For the past
three hours,
President Logan has done
everything in his power
to keep Jack from
getting back here alive.
You're working against the most
powerful man in the world,
and you haven't actually heard
the evidence.
This is why I didn't
talk to you, Miles.
Because you knew
I'd talk you out of it.
Yes, I know
what I'm doing is risky.
If I am wrong,
my career is over.
I could be brought
up on charges.
Not just your career, Karen.
I am doing this because
I believe
that Bauer is telling the truth.
But you don't know.
Okay, okay.
Let's say he is.
Let's say that recording
implicates Logan.
Then what are you going to do?
Are you going to arrest
the President
of the United States?
That will be up
to the attorney general.
You're depending on...
I'm sorry
to interrupt.
Yes.
They're ready
to move Bierko.
Thank you.
I'll be right out.
Look, I have to go over
the transfer protocols.
I know that what I'm asking
from you is difficult.
Everything rests with
what's on that recording.
Tell me what you need.
Bauer will be here any minute.
The best way for you to help
me is to go back out there
and keep things
running smoothly.
All right.
Miles?
It's imperative
this stay between us.
Of course.
Thank you.
We have a full
tactical complement,
enhanced ordinance package,
two vehicle escort.
Vladimir Bierko,
you're being transferred
to a primary holding facility
at our district headquarters.
Let me know the second
he arrives.
Understood. Let's move out.
Where the hell is Mike Novick?
SECRETARY:
He's moments away, sir.
You told me that
three minutes ago.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
I was on the phone
with Colonel Owens.
He's the Marine
field commander on the site.
Is Bauer in custody?
No, sir.
What happened?
As ordered, the Marines
sealed off a one-mile radius
around the landing site.
They've completed a sweep
of the area.
And?
And it's Colonel Owens'
estimation
that Bauer is no longer inside
the perimeter.
He got away.
It appears so, sir.
I can't believe this.
Uh, Mr. President,
it's only a matter of time
before Bauer's apprehended.
Sir, are you all right?
Thank you, Mike.
I need some
time alone now.
( door closes )
( phone ringing )
( phone continues ringing )
Jack, the attorney general's
on his way
to his office
right now.
He'll be ready for
a video conference
in ten minutes.
Okay, good.
Chloe, I want you to prepare
the recording for playback.
I want you to clean
it up and apply a
digital signature so
that we can establish
a chain of evidence.
Okay.
You need to work alone.
I don't want anyone else
near that recording.
You don't ever let
it out of your sight.
I won't.
You said I had ten minutes.
I'd like to see Audrey.
Of course.
She's in Medical.
Thank you.
Well, when will I be able
to speak with him?
All right, I understand.
Well, just let him know...
Can you please tell him
that his daughter called
and that...
she loves him very much.
Thank you.
It looks like
my dad's gonna be all right.
Yeah, I know, I heard.
Oh, God, I'm so glad to see you.
Me, too.
We did it.
We got the evidence.
Oh.
The attorney general's
going to hear it.
So it's over?
Yeah.
President Logan's going to pay
for David Palmer's
assassination.
Thank you.
Close your eyes.
I'm going to sit with
you for a minute.
( phone rings )
Yes.
LOGAN:
Graham.
I've been trying to reach you.
I know.
Bauer slipped
through the cordon,
didn't he?
Yes.
I've just been told that
the attorney general's office
received a phone call
from the director of CTU.
I think it's
fairly obvious
they're in possession
of the recording.
I think that phone
call was about you.
I didn't expect
it would to happen so soon.
I am sorry, Charles.
You don't
deserve this.
Listen, Graham, despite
how things turned out...
...I still believe that
we were in the right.
I still believe
that we acted
in the best interest
of the country.
And we have to keep
putting the country's well-being
ahead of our own.
The spectacle of a sitting
president on trial for murder
would be devastating.
Yes. Yes, it would.
Aside from the psychological
damage to the country,
a trial would expose
certain realities
that should never
see the light of day.
If only we could keep
such a trial from taking place.
That thought occurred to me,
as well.
I'm glad we agree.
I want you to know
I've taken steps to ensure
that you and your associates
won't be implicated
in any of this.
I appreciate that, Charles.
We all do.
There's nothing more to say.
I'm going to hang up now.
There are, uh, a few things I'd
like to take care of before...
Good-bye, Charles.
Good-bye, Graham.
Martha, may I come in?
Now you want to talk?
Marti, please?
What do you want?
Is there something else
you want to confess?
No.
I want to tell you
how sorry I am...
for everything.
When you forget to give me
something for my birthday,
that's when you
say you're sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
It was horribly wrong
and unforgivable.
I know that.
But what I can't live with
is the fact that I hurt you.
That's the last thing
I wanted to do.
Marti?
Marti, please.
That's the truth.
The truth.
( sniffles )
You know what really
gets me, Charles?
What?
That you had me
going for so long.
I had no idea you
were such a good liar.
If I wasn't so horrified by the
fact that I'm married to you,
I might actually be impressed.
( sighs )
* *
( phone ringing )
Yes.
SECRETARY:
I have an urgent call
for you, sir.
He says his name
is Miles Papazian from CTU.
I don't want to talk
to anyone from CTU.
He insists that you'll want
to speak to him.
He says it's about Jack Bauer.
Put him through.
You're on with the President.
MILES:
Mr. President?
Yes, go ahead.
You don't know me;
my name is Miles Papazian.
I work under Karen Hayes.
What is this about?
It's about a recording, sir,
that Jack Bauer
has just delivered here to CTU.
Sir, my understanding is
it's a recording
of a conversation of yours
that, if leaked,
could significantly compromise
national security.
Go on.
My superior, Ms. Hayes,
is working with Bauer
and Bill Buchanan.
Their intention
is to play the recording
for the attorney general.
Why are you telling me this?
Because, sir...
I feel compelled to intervene.
And I just I wanted to make sure
that you would approve.
I do, Mr. Papazian,
I do approve.
Listen, I'm going to text you...
my private number.
Let me know how it goes.
And, Miles...
...I promise you,
I won't forget this.
Thank you, sir.
That's all I wanted to hear.
Mr. President, I look forward
to speaking with you again soon.
* *
Karen wants to
know how long
before the
teleconference starts?
Five minutes--
get out of here, Miles.
We'll be ready?
Not if you keep
interrupting me.
I'm just doing my job, Chloe.
Well, if your job
is to slow things down, then
you're doing really good work.
I'll tell Karen
you'll be ready.
Thanks.
www.tvsubtitles.net