What we're doing here is
very simple.
We're going to release
a certain substance
so that it flows
into your pipelines.
Take the canisters to the main
distribution tank quickly.
Is Wayne Palmer dead yet?
No.
Explain.
We rolled his car,
but he survived and got away.
It was sloppy work,
we'll make it right.
Well, you damn well better.
You know what's at stake.
Get down!
( gunfire )
Get in the car.
It's the truth.
Audrey Raines was my contact
at the Department of Defense.
You met with her
face-to-face?
Yes.
Damn it, Audrey!
Tell me the truth!
I am
telling you the truth.
You already
lied to me once.
You tell me what you know
or I promise you this
will become very unpleasant.
Bill, we have a connection
between Collette Stenger
and Henderson.
She received eight calls from
him she didn't tell us about.
That voids her agreement,
it's off.
You have three seconds
to tell me
where the target is
or I will kill you.
Where is the target?!
A natural gas
distribution center.
Our analysts tell us
once the Sentox
hits the main tank,
it goes right
into the pipes
where it becomes
impossible to stop.
From there, it goes straight
into people's homes.
JACK:
Sentox is already
in the system.
Give me the C-4 and a timer,
then get
these people out of here.
Jack, what are you doing?
In order to deliver the Sentox,
it had to mix with natural gas.
If we can ignite that gas
before it leaves the plant,
the Sentox will be incinerated.
Bierko!
Jack, that's it,
the main tanks are going.
Get out!
BUCHANAN:
Jack, respond.
Curtis, Curtis, this is Audrey.
Any sign of Jack?
Nothing so far.
I've got men searching
the main tank area.
Fire and rescue units
just arrived.
They're assessing
the situation now.
Chloe, what are we getting
from the air monitors?
Come on, Jack.
Chloe.
Just minimal trace readings
of the nerve agent.
Well below danger levels.
It looks like the Sentox
was incinerated in the blast.
Jack's plan worked.
I'm going to brief
the White House.
Apprise me of any developments.
Miles.
Curtis, have we done a full
search of the area for Jack?
It's underway.
We know he hasn't gone out
the north exit.
CTU, Jack's okay.
Get a medical team
over here now!
Jack!
Give me a hand.
Bierko!
I need him conscious.
Yes, sir.
The nerve gas, did it
leave the plant?
There's no trace of it.
Explosion worked.
Good.
He's going into severe shock.
We need to transport him now.
I want him taken back
to CTU Medical.
Yes, sir.
Curtis, organize
an escort team.
You get him back to CTU alive.
You got it.
On my count.
Three, two, one.
Let's go.
( cell phone rings )
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
Is your line still secure?
Yes.
What's your status on Henderson?
Henderson's still
an active protocol.
You need to make him a priority.
Bill, listen to me.
I know Henderson.
He couldn't have planned this.
He's a soldier and a patriot.
However misguided, he believes
what he's doing right now
is right for this country.
He was willing to let his wife
die in order
to protect someone,
someone very powerful.
Who?
I don't know.
Bill, I'm scared.
I think this is bigger
than anything
we could ever have imagined.
Karen, you're not hearing me.
They managed to prevent
an attack,
but that doesn't negate the fact
that CTU's performance
has been comprised of
one misstep after another.
I'm not disputing that,
Mr. Vice President.
Then why the hesitation to carry
out your mandate
and have Homeland absorb CTU?
CTU is still actively
looking for
Christopher Henderson.
A shakeup right now
could hamper that search.
I'm not going to
hold up this takeover
because of a
procedural mop up.
Henderson will be caught,
you can be sure of that.
Is that understood?
Clearly.
Whatever bureaucratic hoops
you have to jump through,
that's your business.
Just get it done.
Yes, sir.
And keep me informed.
I guess we should
get started.
Buchanan is not going to take
this lying down.
Despite what
the vice president said,
CTU just saved a lot of lives.
If Buchanan mounts a challenge,
it will be seen in that light.
This action could be
easily reversed.
If we were to find someone
who would go on record
citing Buchanan's
mismanagement,
how he superseded
Lynn McGill's authority,
how he allowed CTU
to be compromised...
go a long way to mitigating
his successes,
give us the
protection we need.
Buchanan's people
are extremely loyal.
I'm not thinking
about a member of CTU.
I'm thinking
of Audrey Raines.
She was here
all morning,
she saw what went on.
And her loyalty is split
between CTU and DOD.
We could take
advantage of that.
Let me draft a statement
and present it to her.
BUCHANAN:
We're being
rolled up, Audrey.
Homeland's taking over.
That's impossible.
Karen told me herself.
No, they can't do that,
not after what you've
accomplished today.
I'd like to think we've earned
a reprieve, but I doubt it.
CTU is in the middle
of an investigation.
Henderson is still at large.
I know, it doesn't
make any sense.
Karen's taking orders
from Vice President Gardner.
He wants this to happen.
Why?
I've been asking myself
the same question.
HENDERSON:
Yeah.
Well, how in the hell
did you lose him?
Palmer knocked Cobb out
and retrieved his weapon.
We tried to pursue, but
someone came to Palmer's aid.
Who?
That's unclear.
They got away.
All right.
We're going to a fallback, scrub
the scene and get over here.
Yes, sir.
You're all right,
Mr. Palmer.
Just take it slow.
Aaron?
We're at
the presidential retreat.
Can you try to sit up?
I think we need to get
you looked at, sir.
No, no, Aaron, there's not
enough time for that.
I'm all right.
Then maybe you can explain
to me what's going on.
Why were those men
trying to kill you?
Because David had a source
inside the White House
and someone is trying to
prevent me from seeing her.
Who is this source?
Mrs. Logan's assistant.
Evelyn Martin?
Yeah.
Yeah, she and David were trading
e-mails.
Listen, Aaron,
I need to find out the content
of those messages.
I think David was killed because
of information Evelyn gave him.
Mrs. Logan,
I drafted a letter to
the families of the victims
at the Sunrise Hills Mall.
It's here for your review.
Thank you.
And your schedule's
there as well.
You have a 9:00 a.m.
with the press office
and the president
wants you in
on his morning briefing.
Evelyn...
you all right?
I'm fine.
Just tired.
It's been a long day.
I'm surprised any of us
got through it.
Oh, do you have your credentials
with you?
There's still
a curfew in place.
I have them with me.
Good.
Try to get some rest.
Good night.
Evelyn.
Hi.
I really need to talk to you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Palmer,
I need to go home.
Ma'am.
Please.
This won't take but a second.
You were sending e-mails
to my brother, Evelyn. Why?
Mr. Palmer, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I traced the IP account.
I traced it right
to your address,
so, yes, you do know
what I'm talking about.
I need to know
what you told David.
I didn't tell him anything.
Evelyn, I have the record
of your correspondence.
David deleted the content
on the messages,
but I know, Evelyn,
I know you were
in contact with him,
so please don't
lie to me again.
Tell me what I need to know.
Someone killed David--
they killed him--
and they just
tried to kill me.
Now, I think
they knew I was
coming here to see you.
So I think that means
we're both in danger, don't you?
Please, I have
to go now.
Tell me what I need!
Talk to me!
I can't.
They kidnapped my little girl.
They said they would
give Amy back to me
if I gave them
the evidence.
What evidence?
I have proof about
who is behind everything
that's happened today.
They're going to kill my baby.
Evelyn, okay...
They're going to kill...
Listen to me,
all right? Listen.
Even if you turn
over this evidence,
they're not
just going to
give you back
your daughter
and let you go.
That's not what
these people do.
Now, you've got to
trust me, Evelyn.
Please, talk to me.
If I may?
Mr. Palmer's right.
You know too much.
They'll kill you both.
I'll give you
the evidence that I have
if you get me back
my daughter.
I pulled up Henderson's work
records for the past ten years.
It's a lot of material.
I'll start data-mining,
see if there's anything
we can use
to track him down.
That's Chloe O'Brian.
SHARI:
Who are those people?
That's Jim Hill,
from Homeland.
I'm Jim Hill,
Homeland Security.
Could you show me
your station.
Chloe O'Brian?
Yeah?
I'm taking
over your station.
I'll need all your
relevant access codes.
Who are you?
What's going on here?
May I have your
attention, please?
These men and women
are from Homeland Security.
I've just authorized
a unit-wide backslash protocol.
CTU is being
absorbed by the Department
of Homeland Security.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I realize this is sudden,
and this has been
a very difficult day,
but let's all cooperate
to make this transition
as smooth as possible.
There is still work to be done.
Vladimir Bierko
is en route to CTU,
and Christopher Henderson
remains an open protocol.
Thank you.
Ms. Raines, would
you mind joining me
in the Situation Room?
Why?
We need to speak in private.
Fine.
( phone rings )
This is Bauer.
Jack, it's  Wayne Palmer.
Wayne.
Are you all right?
I just heard about that
explosion at the gas plant.
Yeah, I'm fine. Listen, Wayne,
I wish I could tell you
that all the people
that were responsible
for your brother's assassination
are in custody, but I can't.
Yeah, Well, maybe
I can help you with that.
How?
Jack, I'm at
President Logan's retreat.
I'm here with Evelyn Martin,
Mrs. Logan's personal assistant.
What does Evelyn Martin
have to do with this?
She says she has proof
there were other people involved
in the plot to kill my brother.
And I believe her.
Who?
She won't tell me.
Why not?
Her eight-year-old daughter's
been kidnapped.
They're going to kill her
unless Evelyn
hands over the evidence.
This has to be Henderson.
They're supposed
to call any minute
with a place to meet.
Okay. I want to be
on that call when it comes in.
CTU will provide
operational support.
We're going to need
a place to meet.
I passed an old barn about
a mile west of the retreat
off Service Road 19.
Service Road 19.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
See you then.
Jack's going to meet us.
We should go.
Evelyn, listen.
They may be watching you,
so I don't think
we should leave together.
What do you
want to do?
We'll separate.
Get to your car, and we'll
meet up in the parking lot.
I'll see you soon.
"...the acting director's
failure
"to enhance security measures,
especially in the light
"of the heightened
threat, effectively
"invited the subsequent attack
that resulted
in loss of personnel."
You can't possibly
expect me to sign this.
It's a complete
distortion of
today's event
designed to place blame
on Bill Buchanan and CTU.
But you would agree
that today's attacks
represent a serious
intelligence failure
that needs to be addressed.
Thanks to CTU,
hundreds of thousands
of people are alive
who would
otherwise be dead.
But, if CTU had been
operating effectively,
those people would never
have been at risk.
I couldn't more strongly
disagree with this statement.
Well, I'm disappointed
with your decision,
but I appreciate your loyalty.
Of course.
Oh, just to confirm.
As on-site liaison
for DOD,
you participated in today's
decision-making process.
What's your point?
Serious mistakes
were made here today
that resulted in the loss
of American lives.
It would be a shame
to see the taint
of CTU's mismanagement
spread to your agency...
and your career.
By signing this,
you isolate the fallout
for today's mistakes
to Bill Buchanan
and CTU...
where it belongs.
I'm proud of what we did
here today.
The people of
CTU are heroes,
especially Bill Buchanan.
This takeover
is completely unwarranted,
and I won't help you justify it.
( phone rings )
Hello.
Audrey, it's Jack.
Jack, where are you?
I'm on my way
to see Wayne Palmer.
Wayne Palmer?
Wayne just told me
that Evelyn Martin,
Senior Aide to the First Lady
has evidence that would prove
who was really behind
David Palmer's assassination,
but she won't
give the evidence to Wayne
because her daughter's
been kidnapped
in an effort to try
and keep her quiet.
I think Henderson's
behind this.
They want to
make a trade:
the evidence
for the girl.
My God, Jack.
Yeah, I'm going to need you
to retask a satellite
to those coordinates--
I'll have them in a few minutes.
Jack, that could be difficult
right now.
Why?
CTU is being rolled up.
Karen Hayes is
replacing everyone
with people
from Homeland.
What are you talking about?
That doesn't make sense.
I know.
Even if she has a reason
to, we're in the middle
of tracking down
Christopher Henderson.
We'll never be able to
bring her team up to speed.
I know she's taking orders from
Vice President Gardner himself.
Gardner.
Jack, maybe you should talk
to Karen directly.
No.
She's the one in control here.
When I was interrogating
Henderson,
it was obvious that he was
protecting someone,
someone very powerful.
He was willing to
let his wife die
rather than
give him up.
and now, all of a sudden,
Vice President Gardner
is shutting down CTU
when we're actually
in a position to
bring Henderson in?
Do you really think that
Gardner's involved with this?
We can't afford to take
the chance that he's not.
All right,
what do you want me to do?
I want you to get Chloe
to retask the satellite.
I'll get the coordinates
over to you.
Jack, Chloe has
been let go,
along with the rest
of her department.
Audrey, I need the satellite.
Just figure out a way
to get Chloe back on.
All right, all right,
I'll call you back.
MILES:
I could approach some of
the senior CTU staffers.
I told you,
that's a waste of time.
They're worried
about their jobs.
We could promise them
some security.
Excuse me.
I've reconsidered my position.
I'll sign your statement.
May I ask why the sudden change
of heart?
I don't necessarily agree
with everything
that is in the statement,
but I do see
the need to shield DOD
of any possible controversy
that could reflect
back on my father.
HAYES:
Miles.
Thank you.
I want one thing in return.
What's that?
That Chloe be kept on
and assigned to me.
Why Chloe?
I'm going to need
considerable
server access to compile
my report for DOD.
Chloe can help me finish it
in half the time.
There are other people
who can do that job.
I have a working relationship
with Chloe.
She's an asset
that you cannot afford to lose.
Do we have a deal?
Yes.
Good.
All right.
Evelyn Martin will be leaving
the presidential retreat
in a couple of minutes.
It's time to get going.
What about the girl?
( sighs )
I'll take care of her.
MAN ( over phone ):
Wayne Palmer.
I'm at my car.
No one's around.
We're on our way.
Okay.
I'm extremely uncomfortable
sending the two of you off
without protection.
Aaron, we've
been over this.
If you leave the
compound again,
we're going to risk
raising suspicion.
I know it, sir,
but I don't like it.
Wayne.
Well, this is a surprise.
We didn't know you were coming.
Are you here to
see the president?
No.
Mr. Palmer came here
to give me
a memento
from his brother.
It's a service medal.
Sorry, I just...
I knew you and the president
were going to be dealing
with this crisis today,
and I just...
I don't want you people
to feel obliged to see me.
There would never, ever be any
obligation on our part, Wayne,
especially under
the circumstances.
I just want
you to know
how sorry I am.
Your brother was one
of the greatest men
to ever occupy the office.
And his loss,
to all of us,
can't be expressed in words.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
And I know that the president
would also like
to express his condolences
to you personally.
That means a lot, sir,
but unfortunately
I have a plane to catch.
I'm, uh... flying David's body
back to Washington, so...
Oh, I understand.
Safe trip.
Thank you, sir.
I'll walk you out, sir.
Excuse me.
( typing )
CHLOE:
Mr. Buchanan.
Miss O'Brian,
we're not done here.
How can they get away
with this?
Chloe, this
is not over.
Just follow your instructions.
Oh, it sure seems over.
Everyone's getting fired.
I'm going to do everything I can
to get that order rescinded.
Once the details of what we
accomplished here today
are made public, I'm confident
we'll be back at our posts.
The best thing you can do
is stay focused
and follow your orders,
do you understand me?
Yes, sir.
It's going to be
all right.
O'Brian, don't transfer
your station to Valerie.
You got a pass.
I did?
Yeah. So get back to work.
I don't understand.
Why am I staying
and everybody else
is being let go?
Because Miss Raines
requested that you
keep your position.
What has Audrey Raines
have to do with this?
Miss Raines signed
a detailed statement
documenting the numerous
missteps made today by CTU.
And by you
in particular.
So, for the moment,
she gets what she wants,
and she wants O'Brian.
Audrey would never sign
anything like that.
AUDREY:
I did sign it, Bill.
Why?
Because it's the truth.
You realize this effectively
kills any chance we have
of rescinding that order.
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry.
O' Brian.
I got a call from a man
about an hour ago
who told me
that he had my daughter.
That if I wanted
to see her alive again,
that I would have to follow
his exact instructions.
Did he give you
proof he had her?
I talked to her.
She sounded so scared.
You told anybody else
about this?
I couldn't. He said that
if I did, he would know.
Evelyn, listen,
I know we have a deal.
And I'm going to do
everything I can
to get your
daughter back.
No, I told you before.
I can't tell you anything
until I have Amy back.
You called David
with this information.
Why him?
I knew him.
He and the First Lady
were friends.
He was truly a wonderful man.
Yes.
Yes, he was.
I still can't accept talking
about him in the past tense.
I just...
I just can't believe he's gone.
I told him this information
because I trusted him.
I never thought for a moment
that it would endanger him.
I have your brother's blood
on my hands,
and for that,
I will never forgive myself.
Evelyn, you did nothing wrong.
( cell phone rings )
It's them.
( speed dialing )
( cell phone rings )
Bauer.
Jack, the call's
coming through.
Patch me in.
( Touch-Tone beeps )
You're ready for this?
( phone beeps )
Hello.
What took you so long
to answer, Evelyn?
I was just passing
through security.
I just left the retreat.
HENDERSON:
Are you alone?
Yes.
Why was Wayne Palmer
at the retreat?
Wayne Palmer?
Please don't
waste my time.
He was there
for a reason,
and it wasn't to
drop off his resume.
I think he was there
to speak with you.
I didn't even know he was there.
I don't believe you.
I didn't see him.
Evelyn, if you're lying to me,
it's your daughter
who will suffer.
I'm telling you the truth.
Please, you have to believe me.
Did you bring what we discussed?
Yes.
Please, let me talk to Amy.
Very well.
All right, sweetheart,
this is your mommy.
Say hello.
Mommy?
It's me, honey.
Are you okay?
Uh-huh. Are you
coming to get me now?
Mommy's going
to be there real soon.
I want you to keep being brave.
Okay?
Promise me?
I promise.
I love you, my baby.
I love you, too.
Okay, that's enough,
sweetheart.
Very good.
Now take down this address.
4615 Tarpin Street.
Got it?
EVELYN:
Yes, I've got it.
( speed dialing )
( cell phone rings )
Hello?
Audrey, it's Jack.
I just got off the call.
It was Henderson.
Have you got Chloe
back on line?
Audrey?
Sorry, Jack.
Yes, Chloe's still here.
Okay, I'm going to give the
address for the satellite sweep.
All right, go ahead.
4615 Tarpin.
All right.
Give me a few minutes.
Chloe, I need you
to come with me.
Don't talk to me.
It's for Jack.
Jack?
Chloe,
Jack needs your help.
Please.
Fine.
What the hell's
going on?
I had to keep Karen
from replacing you.
That's why I signed
the document.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't understand.
Chloe, you're the only one
that Jack and I trust here.
Jack needs one
of the satellites retasked.
Why?
Here's the address.
We need a full infrared sweep.
I'm going to need
an explanation.
Chloe, I promise you,
I will give you one,
but right now we
need to hurry.
( vehicle approaching )
( car door slams shut )
( approaching footsteps )
Something's wrong.
Wayne.
Jack.
You all right?
Yeah.
It's good to see you.
Good to see you, too.
Evelyn,
my name is Jack Bauer.
I promise you, we're going
to get your daughter back.
Right now I need to
know what you know.
I already told them I wouldn't
give up any information
until I have my daughter.
Fine.
Excuse me for one second.
( dialing phone )
( over phone ):
Audrey Raines.
Audrey, it's Jack.
Let me speak to Chloe.
Okay, Jack, hold on.
Jack, you're
on speaker.
Jack, Audrey told me
what's happening.
I can't believe
the vice president's
involved in this.
Yeah, I know.
Where are we with the satellite?
It's coming up now.
I'm sending the
image to your PDA.
There are men
all over the place.
How many?
I'm counting ten.
Okay. I want you to keep
the satellite on target.
I want you to download
real-time images to my PDA.
CHLOE:
Okay.
Jack.
I'm going to go with Evelyn
in her car to make the exchange.
I want you to find
somewhere safe,
and I want you to stay there
until this
is over.
No, I'm going
with you.
I can't allow that.
This is going to be
extremely dangerous.
I was a Marine, Jack.
I know that, Wayne.
And you never
saw a combat.
There's a big difference
between training
to kill someone
and actually
having to do it.
I can't put you
in harm's way
out of respect
to your brother.
Your family needs you now.
These are the people
who killed my brother, Jack.
They shot a bullet
right through his neck,
and then he died in my arms.
Put yourself in my position.
Could you just walk away?
No.
Neither can I.
I'm coming with you, Jack.
( laughing )
Thank you for your support,
Mr. Prime Minister.
Give my regards to
your lovely wife.
We'll talk soon.
It's going to take me
better part of the day
to return all these phone calls.
That's wonderful,
Mr. President.
World leaders,
prominent Americans.
They're all lining up
to offer their congratulations.
Uh, sir, were you aware
that Wayne Palmer
was on the premises?
He was?
Yes, I just spoke with him,
not a half hour ago,
he just left.
You didn't speak with him?
No.
What was he doing here?
Well, he said he had
a memento from President Palmer
he wanted to give
to Aaron Pierce.
It was
a service medal.
That explains it.
David and Aaron
were very close.
I'm just surprised he didn't
want to speak with you.
Well, it's no secret
that his brother and I
had our share of
disagreements over the years.
It's possible Wayne harbors
ill feelings towards me.
That must be the reason.
You clear on the plan?
I don't think I can do this.
Evelyn, do you want to see
your little girl again?
Because these men
didn't hesitate
to kill President Palmer
and they're gonna hesitate
to kill you and your daughter
once they get what they want.
Right now, I am
your last chance.
We have to stick to the plan,
do you understand me?
Okay, once you have your
daughter in your arms...
I know what to do.
We are going to get her back.
Let's go.
( engine starts )
Call out testing--
one, two, three.
Testing,
Chloe, did you get that?
You're coming through now.
I'm refreshing your screen.
Okay, we're at the southeast
corner entrance.
Jack, there's
a tunnel through that door
that leads to a conveyor belt
that lets out
into the middle
of the plant.
Be careful, there's
a hostile at the exit.
Copy that.
Draw your weapon.
Let's go.
Bravo, check.
Have you got
a visual on the mark?
Negative, sir.
All units holding.
Copy.
This way.
( silenced gunshots )
Let's go.
Damn it,
there's too many of them.
We're running
out of time.
I'm gonna need you to take
out one of their guards
so I can climb to the top
of this structure
and take out the sniper.
He's about a hundred yards
north of here,
just on the other side
of the conveyor belt.
Can you do that?
Yeah. I can do it.
Wait. One of them's moving.
( silenced gunshots )
Go.
Mr. Palmer,
can you hear me?
Copy. I'm on the south side
of the lower belt moving west.
Continue to the end, your
target's to the north.
( silenced gunshots )
Jack, it's all clear.
( vehicle approaching )
This is Bravo.
I think I hear a car.
Vehicle headed north.
Single occupant, female, over.
HENDERSON:
Bravo, what have you got?
I repeat, Bravo,
what have you got?
Come in, Bravo.
( garbled transmission )
Say again.
I didn't get that.
I repeat, woman is alone...
( static hisses ):
...in the car.
Copy.
Chloe, we've
taken out four men.
Evelyn has moved
into position.
Wayne, I want you
to wait for my signal.
Copy.
We need Henderson alive.
Do not shoot to kill.
( cell phone ringing )
Yes?
Evelyn, open all the doors
and the trunk
of the car.
Very good, Evelyn.
Now go to the front of the car
and drop the keys
on the ground.
I have the evidence with me.
I want my daughter.
Bravo, hold your position.
I'm coming out.
I have a visual on
Henderson and the girl.
Okay, Evelyn,
give me the evidence.
I'll give you the evidence
once you give me Amy.
Come on, let her go.
Okay, honey, go see Mommy.
Mommy!
She's moving.
Give me the evidence, Evelyn.
Get down. Get down.
Bravo, check. Come in.
Bravo. Come in, Bravo.
( gunfire )
( screaming )
( gunfire continues )
Wayne, I didn't get him.
If you got a shot, take it.
( engine starting )
( grunting )
( gunfire )
Chloe, it's Jack.
Henderson escaped
in Evelyn's car.
Do you have him on satellite?
We saw it, Jack,
but he's leaving
the search grid.
We're thermal-scanning
the plant,
not the entire
neighborhood.
Well then reprogram it!
We can't lose him!
Is she all right?
Evelyn's been hit.
The bullet passed
right through.
It hasn't hit
an artery.
It's not serious, but it's
gonna have to be dressed.
Evelyn, you've got
your daughter back,
now tell me what
I need to know.
Who is behind this?
Is it the vice president?
Evelyn, is it
the vice president?
The vice president
has nothing to do with this.
You promised me you would
control the situation.
I didn't count on
Jack Bauer showing up, sir.
He outmaneuvered me.
Sir, Bauer and Wayne Palmer
won't be around long enough
to tell anybody else
what they know.
I'm putting together
another team.
I will handle this, sir,
I promise you.
I will not let you down.
See that you don't.
www.tvsubtitles.net