You're a traitor
to this country
and a disgrace
to your office.
Logan wants me dead
because
he thinks I know too much.
Logan had more to protect,
and you know that.
Aaron?
Ma'am, please stay
where you are.
( gunshot )
Bierko's escaped.
What?
How long ago?
Davis, Karen Hayes here.
What happened?
Our lead car got taken out
by an IED.
I overheard Bierko
talking to his men.
He said they're not finished.
I'm sure he said something
about a nerve gas canister.
Henderson set up Bierko
with the nerve gas
to begin with.
Trust me.
You're wasting your time.
He's not going
to help us.
He will if we offer him a deal.
What do you want?
I'll disappear just like you did
so they wouldn't
turn you over to the Chinese.
Anything less than Bierko's head
on a plate,
this deal is off.
Bierko's going to release
the Sentox gas soon.
We need to know where.
CHLOE:
It's a Russian submarine, Jack.
What is the armament package
on a Russian Delta-4 class sub?
Best of my knowledge, 12
Scorpion land-attack missiles.
They're fast and accurate,
carry multiple warheads.
One of them can take out
several city blocks.
Lieutenant, we believe
the Natalia
has been targeted
for a terrorist attack.
We think the terrorists
are after your missiles
on the sub.
You need to secure your vessel
and lock down your
weapons system immediately.
We have control
of the weapons system.
Vertical tubes are loaded
and ready.
I've flushed the Sentox.
The atmospheric readings
are all normal.
It's safe to breathe.
The coordinates
for the targets--
upload them
into the missiles.
Begin the launch
countdown.
Remove your masks.
We are close to finishing
what we started today.
I have identified
12 high-value targets:
financial centers,
transportation hubs,
high-population-density areas.
The Americans
will wake up this morning
to discover how steep a price
they've paid
for their alliance with Moscow.
What we're about
to accomplish today
will be remembered
by our countrymen forever.
( typing )
Ms. Raines.
Admiral Kirkland.
I understand you're reporting
some type of emergency at
the Port of Los Angeles?
In anticipation
of today's treaty
with the Russians,
the Russian submarine Natalia
is docked here
for inspection by the U.S. Navy.
I'm familiar with the exercise.
I authorized it myself.
Terrorists have seized control
of that submarine.
What? We haven't received any
distress signals from the crew.
Because they're dead, sir,
all of them,
including the Russian crew.
We believe the terrorists
have flooded
the sub's ventilation system
with Sentox nerve gas.
My God.
Sir, I don't mean to preempt
your protocols, but how long
will it take you
to scramble a flight of F-18s?
You're asking me
to sink the submarine?
Sir, these terrorists
are in control of 12
multiple-warhead missiles,
which they will use
against civilian targets
unless we stop them first.
I'll need all of this confirmed.
We have a team on the ground
that can confirm,
but now I need
to know precisely:
How long will it take for you
to scramble these fighters?
I'm sending you the estimated
approach vectors
and ETA for my F-18s.
I can have my fighter jets there
within 22 to 25 minutes.
We have a problem, sir.
According to our simulation,
Bierko will have
his missiles in the air
in less than 20 minutes.
Scrambling the jets right now,
but it seems to me as if this is
going to be up to your team
on the ground.
We have visual contact
with the sub.
Hatches are still closed.
Ship's been locked down.
Confirming one hostile topside,
standing guard.
Jack, Chloe's simulation
has Bierko firing those missiles
in less than 20 minutes.
Sooner than that if he's already
started programming targets.
The Navy won't be able
to intercept in time.
Jack, it's Audrey.
I just got off the phone
with Admiral Kirkland.
He's scrambling F-18s,
but they won't be
able to get them
in the air in time in order
to destroy the sub.
How far out are reinforcements?
Too far.
Additional tac teams
won't arrive until
after the missiles
have launched.
That means we have
to take Bierko down ourselves.
That's not a real option, Jack.
There are only four
entry points on that submarine.
We have to assume that
Bierko's locked them down
and is defending them.
AUDREY:
Jack, Bill's right.
We don't have the manpower
or the resources
to get on that sub.
We might.
Somebody just launched
a signal tube
off the starboard side.
What's a signal tube?
It's a radio beacon
crewmen can send
to the surface in
case of emergencies.
Chloe, if there
are friendlies inside,
they can help us
board the sub.
I want you to scan all
emergency frequencies.
On it.
Standing by.
Jack, just so
we're straight--
we stop Bierko,
my wife and I disappear
for good, with
your help, right?
Yeah.
One other thing.
If I'm going on that sub
with you, I need a firearm.
I'll cover you.
Well, that's what
I'm worried about.
I don't go anywhere undefended
against hostiles.
I still consider
you a hostile.
Jack, I don't get a gun,
I don't go in.
CHLOE:
Jack, you were right.
There's a survivor
on the submarine. He's sending
out a distress signal.
Can he receive
on this frequency?
Yeah.
Patch him through.
MAN:
I repeat. Petty Officer
Tim Rooney,
on Natalia K524.
Code seven. SOS.
We are under attack.
Petty Officer Rooney,
my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with the Counterterrorist
Unit, Los Angeles.
What the hell is going on, sir?
Everyone's dead.
And there are people
in the Control Room
trying to operate
the missile launch system.
Who the hell are they?
They're Russian
separatists.
They're the terrorists
that were responsible
for the attacks that
took place earlier today.
Does the Navy know
about this?
Yeah. They're sending
in fighters,
but I don't think they're
going to get here in time.
So what are we supposed to do?
Did anyone else from your crew
survive the attack?
No. I don't think so.
Where are you?
Lower Level,
Auxiliary Engineering.
I was down here
doing an inventory
when the alarms
went off.
The atmospheric gauges
red-lined.
It's a sealed compartment,
so I shut it down.
The men that attacked the ship,
were they wearing gas masks?
They were, but they took
them off a few minutes ago.
Okay, good.
That means they
flushed the Sentox
out of the air system.
You should be able
to move around freely.
Hold on one second.
Chloe?
Yes, Jack?
I want you to get me
the nearest entry point
to Petty Officer Rooney's
current position.
The closest hatch
is the forward escape hatch.
Copy that.
Petty Officer Rooney,
do you have a firearm?
No. The armory's
on the other side of the ship.
You need to find something
that you can use as a weapon.
I have a... I have
a utility tool.
It has a knife on it.
That'll work.
I want you to
make your way up
to the Upper Level.
Let me know when
you get there.
You still haven't told me
what it is you want me to do.
I need you to get
to the forward escape
hatch and let us in.
There's a man there guarding it.
Then you're going
to have to kill him.
Petty Officer Rooney?
I'm an engineer.
I... I'm not trained for that.
The men that commandeered
the Natalia
plan to use
its missiles and launch them
on civilian targets
unless we stop them.
You need to make your way
up to the Upper Level.
You need to do it now.
We are running out of time.
I'll contact you
when I get there.
Copy that.
We need to get closer
to the sub. Are you ready?
Jack, I know you got
Malina's .45 in that bag.
Now, give it to me.
Let's go.
We're generating a list
of potential targets, but
frankly, we have no idea
what Bierko
plans to hit.
Are we evacuating
these potential targets?
Don't have time. The missiles
will strike before we can
mobilize even small numbers
of people to the safe zones.
How could this happen, Mike?
How could these people
even access
a submarine
in the first place?
The sub was attacked
when it was being serviced
at a civilian port,
not on a Naval base
where security
would have been
more substantial.
There has to be a way
to destroy that sub
before Bierko can
launch those missiles.
F-18s are scrambling
as we speak.
According to the
latest estimates,
they're not going
to get there in time.
AARON:
Yes?
I'm still waiting
to talk to Mike Novick.
He's in some kind
of crisis meeting.
There's no telling
how long he'll be.
Then I should try to get
off the ranch on my own.
No. Without Mike's help,
you'll be seen.
Charles can't find out
you're still alive.
I'll call you as soon
as I get ahold of Mike.
Okay.
Jack, the missiles
will launch
in less than ten minutes.
Copy that.
How much time do you need
to cancel the launch sequence?
I won't know for
certain until I see
how the targeting
software is configured.
Jack, the Petty Officer
is coming back on.
Patch him through.
Petty Officer Rooney,
you're on with Jack Bauer.
JACK:
What's your position, son?
I'm 30 feet forward
of the hatch.
Have you got a visual of the
hostile guarding the hatch?
Yeah. He's still there.
What do you want me to do?
You need to kill him
without alerting the others.
Are you right-handed
or left-handed?
I'm right-handed.
I want you to approach him
from behind.
When you're within 18 inches,
I want you to take
your left hand,
put it on his mouth,
pull his head back
into your chest
exposing his neck.
Then I want you to take
your right hand
and slit his throat.
I... I don't, uh...
I don't know if I can
do this.
You don't have a choice, son.
I want you to visualize
the hostile down on
the ground, dead.
You cannot afford
to think about this, son.
You need to do it.
Jack, there's less
than six minutes
until the missile launch.
Petty Officer Rooney?
Okay, I can do this.
I have to do this.
Cut him deep,
and cut him fast.
Agent McCullough, cover us.
We're moving in
on the tower.
Go.
Petty Officer Rooney,
what is your status?
My status is, uh...
He's dead.
Did anyone hear you?
No, no one's coming.
Good. Open the hatch.
You ready?
Yeah.
I'll take out the guard.
Let's go.
All right, he's down.
We're going in.
Oh, no.
The sub's missile hatches
just opened.
I see them.
What does that mean
in terms of our time frame?
You have less than four minutes
until they launch.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
Which way is
the control room?
It's down that hall.
You lead, we'll follow.
Okay.
All right, the control room's
right down that hall.
BAUER:
I'm going to need your help
drawing the rest of the
hostiles out of the con.
What do you want
me to do?
Is there another way for you
to get to the other side
of the control room?
Yeah, I can go down
one level
and then come up
behind them.
Okay, when you get there, I want
you to create a diversion,
something loud.
Just make sure you get
them out of there.
When you do, I want you
to find somewhere
to lay low and stay there.
I do not want you
to engage them.
Do you understand me?
Yeah, I can do that.
Go.
With the last
three missiles,
make sure you overlap
these populations centers
in San Francisco.
Locking up
GPS coordinates,
sir.
Keep working.
Did you hear that?
Yes, sir.
Down there.
Come with me,
both of you.
The control room's
right behind us.
I have a visual
on one hostile.
Agent McCullough, I'm going
to move into position.
When he's directly
above me,
signal me
with the mirror.
CHLOE:
Jack, the missiles are armed.
Three minutes to launch.
We're all clear.
Jack, I'm gonna have to manually
reverse all these codes.
Do you have enough time?
I'll do my best.
I don't want to be in here
any more than you
if those F-18s
take out this sub.
We're going to keep Bierko
and his men out of here
so you can finish this.
Let's go.
( yells )
Agent McCullough's down.
Bierko and one hostile
remaining.
Henderson, what
is your status?
Jack, I need more time.
You've got to hold them off.
60 seconds until they launch.
( groaning )
Jack?
Hang on, Jack.
CHLOE:
30 seconds to launch.
( screaming )
It's almost there, Jack.
Four more seconds.
CHLOE:
Ten seconds.
It's done.
( bones cracking )
HENDERSON:
The launch sequence is canceled.
I repeat,
the launch sequence is canceled.
Audrey, recall the F-18's.
I'm on it.
Bierko's dead.
The submarine is secure.
HENDERSON:
Jack, are you okay?
Bill, I'm fine.
I'm getting a lot
of feedback.
Take me off the com.
Hold it, Jack.
Now lower your arms
real slow
and turn around.
You were never really going
to let me go, were you?
No.
( clicks )
Good for you, Jack.
You were responsible for
the deaths
of David Palmer, Tony Almeida
and Michelle Dessler.
They were friends of mine.
That's the way it works.
Identify yourself!
My name is Jack Bauer,
with the Counter-
Terrorist Unit, Los Angeles!
All the hostiles are dead!
Holster your weapons!
Sir, you need to contact
Bill Buchanan-- immediately.
Okay. Lieutenant, I need
access to a vehicle.
Petty Officer,
get me a vehicle-- now!
Thank you.
BUCHANAN:
Jack?
Yeah.
I've been told
the Navy's running
cleanup and security on the sub.
Yeah, they're here now.
Bill, Christopher
Henderson is dead.
What? What happened?
He fired on me.
I didn't have a choice.
Are you coming back to CTU?
Yeah, I'll be there soon.
All right, we'll see you then.
Chloe, the Navy needs our access
codes to our logs
so they can use them
for their report.
Can you pick up?
Yeah.
What codes do they need?
They don't. Get somewhere
where you won't be overheard.
I'll have to get that
from my screen.
Let me get back
to my station.
I'm here.
What's going on?
I'm not coming
back to CTU.
I'm going after Logan.
What do you mean,
going after Logan?
I'll fill you in
on the details later.
Right now I need you
to walk me through modifying
some field
communications equipment.
That's not exactly
my area, Jack.
Then you'll need
to get some help.
Chloe,
are you with me on this?
Yeah. What do you need?
Hold on, I'll give you a list.
Okay.
Thank you.
We're certain the missiles
no longer pose a threat?
Yes, Mr. President.
We have complete control
over the boat.
Vladimir Bierko and all his
known associates are dead
or in custody.
So then it's all over, Mike.
It's over.
( sighs )
I need to make a statement
before I go back to Washington.
About the successful
resolution of the crisis.
Yes.
And about David Palmer.
Sir?
David's casket is being flown
to Arlington for burial,
and I would like to say
a few words alongside it
at the airfield,
and then I'll fly
back to Washington.
I'll get to work
on it right away.
Good. Thank you, Mike.
For everything.
It's been a hell of a day.
Yes, sir.
It has.
Mike.
You need to come with me.
Come with you?
Please.
Oh, please.
Mrs. Logan,
have you been...?
No.
I've never been more sober.
Or more sane.
What's this about?
My husband.
What about him?
Mike, I know
you've been troubled
by Charles's actions today.
You know that something
is terribly, terribly wrong.
You just can't put
your finger on it.
Okay.
Tell me what this is about.
No, I'm going to show you.
It'll explain everything.
Please come.
The mission to retake the
submarine has been successful.
Hmm, so I understand.
You'll also be interested
to know Christopher Henderson
was killed during the operation.
You're certain of this?
CTU has confirmed
the information.
That's excellent.
But let's not fool
ourselves into thinking
that's the end
of all our problems.
There's still Bauer
to deal with.
Don't worry.
Mr. Bauer will
be taken care of.
Good.
Mike. Over here.
Aaron...
What happened to you?
Agent Adams tried to kill me.
On the president's orders.
That doesn't
make any sense.
Where is Agent Adams?
Mike, we need your help.
God.
What the hell's going on here?
The president had something
to do with this?
Everything.
He was involved
with everything
that happened today--
supplying the terrorists
with the nerve gas,
the murder of David Palmer.
( sighs )
But Walt Cummings?
Walt was just their scapegoat.
He didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered by a man
who works for Charles.
Charles told me
to be quiet.
For the good of the country.
Keep my mouth shut.
I can't do that.
Not anymore.
Do you have proof?
Jack Bauer was
in possession
of a recording
that implicated
the president.
That's why Logan
was willing
to go so far as to shoot
a plane full of people down--
because Jack was on it.
Well, where is
this recording?
It's been destroyed.
I didn't want
to believe it
either, Mike,
but it's the truth,
so help me God.
All right.
If this is true,
we need to find another way
to make a case
against the president.
You're right, but first
we have to get
Aaron off the ranch.
There can't be
a record of it.
All right. You're right.
We need to move fast.
I know the men at the
Western Gate well.
They won't stop and
inspect the vehicle
if I'm driving.
You'll hide in the back
out of sight.
Thank you, Mike.
Give me the keys.
Aaron.
I'll be fine.
I'll go somewhere where your
husband's people can't find me.
But will you let me know
that you're all right?
It's probably safer
if we don't have any contact.
Good-bye, Aaron.
Thank you.
Mike Novick.
Mike, it's Jack Bauer.
I know this is
an unusual request,
but I'm looking
for Aaron Pierce.
I've been trying
to reach him on his cell,
but he's not answering.
It's Jack Bauer.
He's trying
to find you.
Can you put him
on speaker?
Aaron's with me right
now, Jack. Hold on.
It's all right, Jack. You can
speak freely in front of Mike.
He knows what I know.
Aaron, where are you?
A few miles from the ranch.
What happened?
The president tried
to have me killed,
but Mrs. Logan
saved my life.
She and I both decided
to bring Mike
into this.
And I'm still
trying to process everything they told me.
This is a real
mess, Jack.
Mike, I'm calling Aaron
because I need his help.
I need yours, too.
Help with what?
Bringing President Logan
to justice.
Well, Aaron said
the recording you had
implicating the president
was destroyed. Is that true?
Yes.
Well, without it you
can't mount a case.
I can if I can get
a direct confession from Logan.
I'm working with someone
inside CTU.
They're setting up
a digital uplink.
If I can get Logan
to acknowledge everything
that he's done today,
it's going to be all the evidence
we need.
Jack, if you intend to
physically coerce the president
of the United States...
Mike, we need to do this now.
The longer we wait,
the more vulnerable we are.
President Logan tried to take me
out, just like he did Aaron.
I don't need to remind you
that he was responsible
for David Palmer's assassination
and a terrorist attack
on this country's soil.
He cannot be allowed
to remain in office,
not for one more day.
How long will it
take you to get here?
20 minutes.
That's too late.
President Logan
will be gone.
He's leaving for Washington
around that time.
Then you have to try
and delay him.
I'm not sure
I can do that.
Mike, just tell me you'll try.
All right.
But get here as fast as you can.
Okay. Thank you.
Yes, sir. I'll get on a plane
as soon as I finish
our debrief with the Navy.
Homeland's ordered me to
Washington
as soon as I file
the Bierko case.
Apparently, the request
came from the White House.
Logan's looking
for an excuse to clean house.
I'm sure I'll be next.
HAYES:
Come in.
Yes, Chloe.
Do you have
something?
I need an authorization code.
For what?
I need access to
a high-clearance
workstation.
You already have access.
It's for some new personnel.
What?
Morris?
You're bringing Morris back?
Yes.
Why, Chloe?
Because I'm still trying
to salvage something
from the recording
that Miles erased.
If anyone can do it,
it's Morris.
I didn't think Morris
was even on the government
payroll anymore.
He's not.
What's he doing?
He's selling women's
shoes in Beverly Hills.
What?
Is this a joke?
No. You know I wouldn't
have brought him in
if there was anyone
else I could call.
Please, Mr. Buchanan.
Thank you.
Bill...
It's going to be
all right.
Who is this guy?
Morris O'Brian.
Chloe's ex-husband.
No, no, not like that.
May I?
See, the beauty of the beast is
if you leave these fields blank,
it'll prompt you
for a code.
Ba-bing. See that?
You just saved
60 seconds.
Ten of those a day,
that's an extra cigarette break
or whatever it is you do
to take the edge off.
Morris.
What are you doing?
Just making your people
more efficient.
I noticed you picked
the most attractive one.
Wrong. You're the most
attractive one.
Here's your clearance.
I'm surprised you got
Bill Buchanan to sign off on me.
You know, this is a really
good opportunity for you.
Why don't you surprise me
and not totally screw it up?
Okay.
I'm going to pretend
that this will require
all my focus and attention,
even though we both know
I can do it in my sleep.
Sit down.
So where is this recording
you want me to resurrect?
Nothing. Forget it.
It's fried.
I'm missing something.
You said you wanted me to
salvage a digital recording.
That was an excuse.
I need some comm unit
modifications.
I need a certified digital
audio transfer rate of 6.8.
I can only get to 6.5.
Can you do that
without talking?
I could, but it'd be
a terrible waste of my charm.
Okay. I'm not
listening anymore.
Call me when you're done.
Thanks.
Behind me, you can see
preparations
as the casket bearing the body
of David Palmer
is due here shortly.
It will be met
by President Logan
who is scheduled
( knock on door )
to make a statement before
he flies back to Washington...
Is Aaron safe?
Yes.
Thank God.
I can't believe Charles
is going to do this.
He has David's blood
on his hand,
he has the audacity
to eulogize him
in front of
the whole world.
Mrs. Logan...
I said earlier
there was no way
to make a case against
your husband.
I was wrong.
Jack Bauer,
the former CTU agent,
contacted Aaron and me.
He's on his way here now.
What for?
He's going to confront
your husband directly.
Confront him?
What's he going to do?
Jack Bauer will do
whatever it takes
to compel your husband
to confess the truth.
He's the only one I know
who can do this.
When will he be here?
15 minutes.
But Charles is leaving
for the airfield immediately.
I know, I know, I tried
to delay him myself,
but he wouldn't
change his schedule.
That's why I'm coming to you.
I need you
to keep him here.
Martha...
if you want your husband
brought to justice,
this is our only chance.
You have to find
a way to stall him.
Aaron, it's good
to see you.
Same here, Jack.
Was Mike able to delay
the President?
He's trying.
But he had to ask
Mrs. Logan for some help.
The First Lady knows
what we intend to do?
She does.
Aaron...
can she be trusted?
She is with us, Jack...
100%.
Can you still get access
to the Secret Service
deployment grid?
I already have.
The way security has been beefed
up around the main building,
there's no way you're
going to be able
to get Logan alone there.
Is Marine One taking him
to the airfield?
No, this was last minute.
They're transporting him
by reduced detachment.
They're using
a Navy helicopter.
That's where this
has to happen.
I need to get on
that chopper.
I don't see how that's
going to be possible.
Aaron, you get me as close
to that helicopter as you can
and then we'll figure
it out from there.
All right.
Let's go.
Yes, I agree, Wayne Palmer
should be at the airfield.
But if you can't find him,
I'm not going to wait for him.
Yes, I'm leaving now.
Have a copy of my speech
on the chopper,
and I'll work on it
on the flight over.
I'll be out of your way
in a second.
I saw on your schedule
that you're meeting
David Palmer's
casket at the airfield.
If you came here to judge me,
Martha,
I really don't have time...
No, no.
That's not it.
I've had time
to reflect and I...
I think I owe you an apology.
All right.
I said some horrible things
to you.
I've had horrible things
said to me before...
and by you.
But there was one thing you
said that I can't get over.
What?
That I broke your heart...
and that you hated me.
Well, I wish I could
take those words back.
All I can ask now
is that you forgive me.
Please, Charles...
I don't know how
to respond, Marty.
I never expected you
to say anything like this.
I mean it, Charles, I...
I mean it,
I need you to forgive me.
You mean it now,
but you know how you are.
By tomorrow, I could be
the man you hate again.
I know.
It'll take time for me
to prove myself to you,
but the truth is...
even though sometimes
I don't understand you,
I still need you.
And I still love you.
And that will never
change, Charles.
Not tomorrow, not ever.
I need you, too, Marty.
Fly with me
to Washington.
We can spend
some time together.
On a plane surrounded
by Secret Service?
Why can't we just spend
a little more time here,
together, alone?
You know that's
not possible.
I have to go.
I had to go
five minutes ago.
Okay, Charles.
You go.
Come with me.
I have a better idea.
There's a helicopter
waiting for me.
Let it wait.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
You're the President.
Tell the helicopter
to stand by.
Yes.
Until I'm ready.
And make sure
I'm not disturbed.
It's clear.
( cell phone rings )
Yeah.
The President just notified
Secret Service
he's going
to be delayed.
How long?
He didn't say.
But Mrs. Logan knows we need
as much time as possible.
Jack...
if Logan doesn't confess,
how far are you actually
willing to go?
As far as I have to.
www.tvsubtitles.net