High Commander's log.
Make that "former"
high commander.
I am writing this so that future generations
will know
the truth.
It all began
two days ago.
Okay, where's
my shoes?
Oh well I think I saw one of them
right over there.
Harry received a message
from the big giant head
saying that I was
to be replaced
the very next night.
Cruelly, that was
the very night
that Mary
finally said,
"I care about you".
Mary, you understand
my every thought.
I understand. You've had
the milk. Why buy the cow?
No, I want you.
I want the cow.
But I was summoned
into the basement
to meet
my replacement.
And here I am
in this encasement.
No.
I must make
an erasement.
Ignoring all
military protocol,
he confined me
in this invisible box.
Oh, my god!
He's turned me
into a mime!
What's going on in that pan?
- I'm cooking sausages.
Those are links.
I like patties.
I'm sorry, sir.
- Sorry won't do.
Press that meat, soldier.
I like my links flat.
Who ate
my Strawberries?
What Strawberries?
- I had a pint of Strawberries in here
with a note
clearly marked mine.
I didn't take 'em.
- It wasn't me.
Man, them strawberries
was good eating.
It is becoming
all too clear
how my predecessor
chose to run things.
You will find things to be quite
different under my command, Tommy.
Uh, no, I'm Harry.
No, I've decided that from now
on you will be known as Tommy.
What about me?
You will be known
as Tommy, too.
But wait. Tommy and then the
number 2, or Tommy as well?
You will all be
known as Tommy!
And that's not all. Lieutenant?
- Sir!
From now on, you will wear skirts.
- Skirts?
Something long that
looks pretty when you twirl.
And stay away from pleats.
You know, nothing too fussy.
Okay.
Furthermore, when coupons arrive in the mail,
I get first dibs.
I may open a box of
cereal to get the prize,
but I do not then
have to eat...
the cereal.
The bathroom has been stocked
with two kinds of toilet paper.
I, and I alone,
get the quilted kind.
You will go to a barber.
I will go to a stylist.
But wait, wait, wait. We have
so much more hair than you do.
You will never
mention that again!
Have I made myself
clear, Tommy?
yes.
When someone asks you
what time it is,
you do not say
"it's time to die".
And, uh, where do I go for work?
- The university.
Ah. So I run
the university.
Not so much run.
You teach a physics class.
I'm a teacher?!
Were all the janitors' jobs taken?
Six months on this planet, and
that's all my predecessor achieved.
How pitiful.
He was spending a lot of time
on that whole Dr. Albright thing.
Ah, yes, Mary.
I've got plans
for her.
There's my girl.
I feel so pretty.
Now pay attention. I
have an assignment for you.
Lieutenant,
take this down.
I will require
the following items:
500 rolls of silver
reflective duct tape,
144 ceramic
custard cups,
one subatomic spectrometer,
and one turkey baster.
You see, I am building
the greatest incubator
these puny humans
have ever known.
And when it
is completed,
I will spawn
my own private army of...
of...
fuzzy easter chicks.
What are you looking at? You
have your assignment. Hop to it!
Can you give us a ride?
- No. The car is mine, and mine alone.
You're humans.
Use your feet.
You know, I was this
close to kicking his butt.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was gonna
kick his butt,
but, you know,
I figured you'd do it.
Well, when he comes back, I'm kicking his butt.
- All right.
What are you guys complaining about, huh?
I deserved his job. I
should be high commander.
I have the seniority.
I know the territory.
So why wasn't
I promoted, huh?
Because I'm the woman.
Once again, the woman
was passed over.
You want me to kick his butt?
- Harry,
there's not going to be any
butt-Kicking. He is high commander.
Like it or not,
we're sworn to follow him.
Anyway, maybe this mission
could use a little discipline.
Yeah, nice skirt,
Tommy.
All right, how do
you work a car?
See, it's the difference
between good fabric
and cheap fabric.
Then again,
my third husband liked 'em cheap.
Yes, yes, that's
fascinating.
Say, Dr. Solomon,
could you come over and give me a hand
with my lint trap?
No, I...
I'd love to really, but
I'm afraid it's impossible.
You see, I have
a bad back.
I think I know why
you're down here.
Same reason my second
husband used to come down here.
Bottle of scotch hidden
in the insulation.
Of course,
I always knew.
The pink fuzz in his beer gave him away.
Mrs. Dubcek.
- Mm-hmm.
Yes?
I need you
to do me a favour.
Could you go upstairs
and tell Sally
that I'm down here?
But if you see me
standing there..
and this is
very important..
don't say
anything to me.
Just take Sally aside
and whisper it to her.
Whatever you do,
make sure
"I" don't hear "you".
Come again?
Never mind.
Stop it.
Okay, here's the duct
tape. How much do we need?
500 rolls,
silver reflective.
Okay, well, how
about eight rolls
of sort of grayish?
- That's fine.
What do you think Dick's
doing now? You know, old Dick.
You don't think they reassigned
him to the brown planet, do you?
Ooh...
Dennis!
- Tom, Sally, Harry.
What are you guys
doing here?
We just had to pick up some duct tape here.
No, I mean, on Earth.
Oh. Well, we're
doing that thing where we're
supposed to be a human family.
I dodged
that assignment.
We've seen you on TV.
18 rebounds a game.
Don't people
suspect anything?
Look at you..
the hair, the tattoos.
Like you could be human.
They think I'm weird
or something.
I hear that.
Listen, Dennis,
I gotta ask you.
Madonna..
where is she from?
Detroit.
- Detroit, earth?
Nooooo!
Yeah, she's here.
She's here.
What about Michael Jordan?
- Robot.
I told you so. See?
- All right, all right.
Well, guys,
I gotta be going.
Proceed boldly
and with stealth.
Jam on.
I like what you've done with your desk.
Would you like me
to do it
to yours?
No.
I like it messy.
Bad girl.
So, Dr. Albright,
refresh my memory.
Have you and I...
had sex yet?
Why, yes,
I believe we have.
How was it?
It was... nice.
Next time, it won't be... so nice.
What did you do to him?
- I don't know, Nina.
Nina, where's that
comprehensive course syllabus?
You only asked me to do it 10
minutes ago. I'm not a machine.
Oh, pity.
What are you doing? Trying
to show off in front of her?
I don't have
to show off.
I just have to...
show up.
Isn't he naughty?
Old Dick would have never
ordered us out onto the roof.
Except for that one time he
Oh, well,
that time, sure.
A small fire has broken
out in the living room.
There's a fire
extinguisher next to the stove.
The stove is
in the kitchen.
Obviously.
This guy's
such a hard-ass.
May I remind you that that
hard-Ass is our high commander?
You're the weapons
expert.
Isn't there some way
to get rid of him?
No, we're stuck
with him.
We can't just frag him with a
grenade while he's taking a shower.
But listen, showers
accidentally explode all the time.
I didn't hear that, soldier.
He said that showers..
Shut up!
Thank you very much. The fire
extinguisher is now on fire.
I miss the old Dick.
- I miss the old Dick, too.
Well, missing him's not going
to bring him back.
I will admit that
the old Dick's methods were
a little different
than this Dick, but..
it's not up to us to
question his directives, okay,
He is in command,
and that's that.
He's...
he's just mean, and there's
nothing we can do about it.
Whoa, whoa.
You're getting all wet. Stop.
- Stop leaking.
No, you're right.
As Dick always
used to say,
never let 'em
see you leak.
The fire's out of control.
I'll be back in two hours.
I miss Dick.
What do you want?
What do you want?!
Stop it.
Stop it!
Hello.
Dr. Albright, dinner, my place, tonight.
Is that an invitation?
- No.
Well...
the cat thinks he has the mouse by the tail.
Yes, but sometimes
the cat likes to...
play with his prey
before he goes in
for the kill.
Well, the cat
may have claws,
but the mouse
is quick.
True,
but the mouse
will always fall
for the cheese.
The cat likes
a little cheese, too.
And milk,
and dead birds...
but he always
licks himself clean.
You were asking
me to dinner?
Uh, yes.
- I'll be there.
No, I'm the cat!
Here's the syllabus
that you wanted.
Why, this is
beautiful, Nina.
So...
exquisitely
beautiful.
Well, we got a new
toner cartridge..
don't be so modest.
I'll see you later.
All right.
Excuse me. There must be some mistake.
This classroom is mine.
Find your own.
Dr. Solomon, we were all
just waiting for our grades.
Oh, grades.
I didn't realize
teaching involved evaluation.
Very well.
You need your hair
straightened.
You're too short
for your face.
You have a museum-quality torso.
You... are harmless.
You will be spared and used to
carry and used to carry heavy things.
You..
- Dr. Solomon, we meant our letter grades.
I've decided
to give you all...
"d"s.
- We got "d"s.
Isn't this beautiful?
I mean, look at her,
reunited with
the birth mother
she never knew.
I love "Ricki lake".
The other day, this woman finally
came face-to-face with her stalker.
And he was so sweet,
she agreed to go
out on a date
with him.
Well, maybe if
I went on that show,
they would reunite
me with Dick..
Johnson.
Dick Johnson.
Little Dickie Johnson.
Stop looking at me.
And who is this
exquisite creature?
Uh... maybe you'd better
go downstairs, Mrs. Dubcek.
Mrs. Dubcek.
I will see you later,
Turn that
rubbish off.
From now on,
we watch only golf.
But I was going to watch
"the jerry springer show".
Transmission incoming
from the big giant head.
Warning, warning!
Danger, danger!
Due to
a clerical error,
your high commander may
have been accidentally replaced
by a disgruntled
former employee
of the big giant head.
He should be
considered armed
and extremely
unpleasant.
And remember, when you're
thinking of giant heads,
think of the big
giant head.
Resume normal
functions in three,
two, one.
All right,
what was it?
Wrong number.
- Oh.
Now shut up and get me that turkey baster!
Why don't you make me
get the turkey baster?
Hi, old Dick.
Dick!
- Harry!
Invisible box?
- Yeah.
Yes?
- What is the meaning of this?
I distinctly asked for
reflective duct tape.
Oh, about that, see,
that was all they had.
Typical. Did you get
the custard cups?
We didn't
so much get them, as failed..
to get them, sir.
Did you try jenny's
restaurant supply on fifth street?
They're not open to the general public.
- Oh.
That's right. Can't let
just anyone make custard.
No, of course not,
not on this planet, No,
no, that would
be too simple.
No, we have retail,
and we have wholesale.
We have pink packets
and blue packets,
republicans
and democrats,
and the party that
crazy midget started.
So many choices.
How they all love
their free will.
Everybody has
a different point of view.
There should be only
one point of view..
my point of view.
Well, I have a message
for these humans.
The buffet is
about to close..
forever.
What is it, boy?
I think he wants us
to follow him.
Dick!
- Dick!
Sally! No, look out!
There's an invisible..
oh, you guys,
there's
an invisible box.
www.tvsubtitles.net