And one, and two, and there you go,
that's it!
Feel the burn.
Well, hello,
strange baby.
Who's that?
Well I don't know, some baby.
That's no baby.
Babies are pink, and wrinkly,
and wear blankets. Dick,
you better come in here.
Who's this?
I don't know. Some baby.
What does it want?
Here, I'll find out.
What do you want?!
Hello, has anybody seen my..
there's
my little rug rat.
Mrs. Dubcek,
you had a baby.
He's my grandson,
I'm babysitting him.
My son and his wife are
spending the week at Caesar's palace.
Ah, Rome.
- Mmm.
Could I ask you folks
to do me a favour?
Could you watch the little guy
while I run out to the doctor's?
No.
- Yes, we'd be happy to.
Oh, great, great.
He's had his nap,
and he's just been changed.
What was he before?
Mrs. Dubcek,
why do you assume
that Sally will be taking
care of the baby?
Well, she's a woman.
Yet another perk.
I'll go get
his stuff.
Now he may be a little bit cranky,
he's got teeth coming in.
Well, don't worry,
we'll sign for them.
Permission to ask what the hell you just did.
It's an opportunity to observe
a brand-new human.
Besides, you always said
you wanted a baby.
Not this baby,
I want one of my own,
one I made
from scratch.
What's that smell?
Hey, I've been
working out.
Turn it off!
I can't.
- Then turn it down.
What?!
What do you want?
Are you hungry? Tommy,
entertain him till I get back.
Wait, what, I don't know what..
All right, kid,
I'll read you a story.
Um... "dingo boy
released from pound.
Burt Reynolds up in arms".
Look. It's a little dingo boy. See?
Move it.
- Hey, those are my croutons!
Let him buy
his own croutons.
Look, he's eating.
He likes the croutons, Harry.
They're
nummy num, yeah!
Why are you talking
like that to the baby?
I have my reasons.
Well, I'm off.
Dick, look. Mrs. Dubcek was right,
I am great with this kid.
Well, how hard could it
be? Look how cute he is.
He's screaming?
Why is he screaming?
Somebody make him stop.
Hey, he stopped.
See, I'm great with this kid,
and he hates you.
Give me that baby.
Damn!
See? You make him cry.
Nonsense, haven't you
ever heard of tears of joy?
Yeah.
Come on now. Wear the hat..
- No, no, no.
Come on.
It's Mary's going-away party.
She's only going to be
gone for three days.
Please wear the hat. Hat, hat, hat!
- No, no, no, no!
Hello.
Surprise!
- Surprise.
Mary, I miss you
already.
Now, Dick, you don't have
to throw me a surprise party
every time I go
to a conference.
You wouldn't be saying
that if Nina had worn her hat.
Oh, Nina...
here are my keys.
You know where I keep the fish food.
- Yes.
Nina's taking care of your fish?
Mary, shouldn't I be doing that?
a-ha...uh... Nina already
knows where I keep the food.
I see.
She already knows.
- Uh-huh.
It must make it a lot easier for you, then.
Well if you really want to do it..
- Oh Yes I do, I do!
Mary, I want to take care
of your fish desperately.
Really, Nina,
thank you so much.
Just doing my job.
I have fish, you know.
Do you?
- Mm-hmm, they're in my freezer.
Here you go, baby.
Well, he hated that.
When is Sally going to
get back with those diapers?
Oh, look! Some coming out
of his nose again.
It's like
he's got wetness
coming out of every hole in his body.
Dumb, wet baby.
Hey, he likes it.
Maybe not.
Suddenly it's not quite
so funny when I do it,
now, is it?
What? - It's a baby.
- Oh.
Oh, Mary, this means so much to me.
Yeah. Okay,
now let's go over this one more time.
The filter and the heater are automatic.
Don't touch them.
- Well, what if I need to touch them?
Why should you need
to touch them?
Well what if I want
Just don't
touch them.
Now, here's something
I like to do.
If the fish
have been good,
I like to reward them
with a little brine shrimp.
And if they're bad.
I'll make them watch while
I eat the brine shrimp.
Now, this might
sound silly,
but I'm very attached
to these fish.
Please don't
kill them.
You love your fish,
and I love you.
That's why I'm going
to love your fish.
Just feed them.
Don't touch
the filter!
Okay.
Hello?
What is the matter
with you two?
How many times do I have to go
over this? When that baby is asleep,
the phone is not to ring more than once.
Right. The one-ring rule.
That's right.
Harry, did you throw
applesauce all over the floor?
No, it was
the baby.
He made a cute
little design.
Mrs. Dubcek..
- Shh!
She won't be back until tomorrow.
- What?!
She said she was still woozy
from the medication,
that she got on the wrong bus and
woke up in a petting zoo in Cleveland.
Oh, that old excuse.
We get to keep the baby another day.
Oh, great.
And by the way,
it was me that spilled applesauce.
- It was?
No, it was
the baby.
I've been meaning to talk to you about that..
- Shh! I think I hear him
turning over.
I don't hear anything.
Of course you don't. You're a man.
How could
this happen?
That baby has taken
control of us.
The one with the least
intelligence is running the show.
This is getting old fast. There
are three of us and only one of him.
We're bigger than him
and way smarter.
We could take this baby.
Who's with me?
Come on, men.
One ring.
Hello, fish.
Look at you
in there.
What are you thinking? I
know what you're thinking.
Are you in the tank,
or am I?
Well, it's you,
stupid fish.
Here, I brought you
some presents..
a treasure chest filled
with gold doubloons,
a topless mermaid.
Try not to stare.
And, best of all,
I brought you
a new friend.
I call her snowflake
because she's soft
and delicate.
I thought you
might like it
if I read you
a night-night story.
It's called
"Tales of the Calypso:
secrets of
the ocean deep".
"Slowly, so slowly,
the day turned
to night.
The darkness
taunts the light
that dances
in the depths below.
Suddenly
and without warning,
danger strikes.
Octopus, octopus,
your children
are dying."
I want that. I want that.
I want that.
I want that. I want that. I want..
Harry, we're here to get
something for the baby.
We're not here to get something for you.
- Nuts.
Here, baby.
What about this one?
Where'd he go?
Oh, no!
Hold on, baby!
- No, Sally, you can't!
Let me go! I've got to save him.
Get a hold of yourself! It's a
bottomless ball pit of death!
I don't care!
That's my baby!
No!
Ohh, I've got him!
I've got him!
Hey, lady,
we only let children climb in the ball pit.
That is so sick.
Lieutenant,
you look like hell.
I mean the "locked in a car
wash overnight" kind of hell.
Yeah, it's this baby.
He ran me ragged
all day.
That insolent
little twerp.
He's gone too far. Tomorrow I'm
granting you a one-day furlough.
Go into town.
Get yourself a tattoo.
I can't. Tomorrow I'm
taking the baby to the park,
and then the zoo, and
then I'm taking him golfing.
I think he has
real talent.
I don't understand. You sound
like you're actually enjoying this.
I am.
I know I complained
at the start,
but this is the first
assignment I've had
where I really feel like
I'm using all of me.
It sounds crazy, but I
cannot do enough for him.
The more he needs me,
the more I need him.
I have a great idea.
Let's wake him up, then rock him back to sleep.
- No!
Why not?
- What's the matter with you?
It's as if this baby
has made you go all soft.
He's broken down your defenses.
I know.
He's my wittle bunny wabbit.
God, what kind of talk is
that? You're a weapons expert.
I'm still a warrior.
It's just now I'm the
protector, not the aggressor.
I've heard enough.
I'm going to sleep.
You can't. I've tucked him in your bed.
As high commander, I order
you to untuck him at once.
Dick, I'm not taking
orders from you anymore.
I'm taking orders
from a higher commander.
His rank: baby.
But wait!
Where am I going to sleep?
Use his room.
Fine.
Morning, children.
Hello, snowflake.
Where's everybody else?
Come out, come out!
Why, snowflake, you're
looking a little bloated.
Oh, my god!
You bad fish!
Bad, bad fish!
Where's that
brine shrimp?
See?
None for you!
Dick!
Mary, you've
come back early.
The conference was a
disaster. I had to get out of there.
Are you sure that was a good
idea? Maybe you should go back.
No. Besides,
I missed you.
Oh, I was so lone..
where's my fish?
Oh... there's your fish.
That's not my fish.
Sure, it is.
You killed my fish!
No, I didn't!
He did.
You jackass!
- Yeah, you jackass!
Hello, sweetheart.
Can you say
my name?
Sally.
- No.
Sal-ly.
No.
You know, you shouldn't try so hard.
Kids develop
at different rates.
And resistance is the
sign of an analytical mind.
Really?
- No.
Don't listen to him. You
know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to find
Mr. Sock monkey.
You like Mr. Sock monkey, right?
Sally!
Sally, I feel
just awful.
I've killed the fish of the woman I love.
- Uh-huh.
Mr. Sock monkey,
where are you?
Those fish were
everything to her.
I've got to find something to replace them.
Come on out, you argyle piece of crap!
- Sally? Hello?
She can't hear you. She
can only hear the baby.
Harry, have you seen
Mr. Sock monkey?
Why, no.
Why would
you ask me?
I haven't seen
him all day.
La, la-la,
la, la, la-la
It's probably
in the bedroom.
Call me if he
needs anything.
What am I
going to do?
Well, hello.
Sock monkey!
Give that to me!
Yes, yes,
you should do
just fine.
You might even fit
in the tank.
Mary? Mary, do you
remember how I killed your fish?
No.
- Well, I did,
but I brought you something to
make you feel better. Come on in!
Whose baby is that?
Mine.
Well, not for keeps.
It's really Sally's.
I mean, she got it
from Mrs. Dubcek.
Let's just call it
a rental.
Come on.
Play with it.
Dick you've got to take that
child back to its mother.
Come on.
Just hold him.
I guarantee you'll like it.
I'm serious.
Just take him for a spin around
the block, and then we'll talk.
There you are!
There "you" are.
I'll deal with you, as soon
as I deal with you, sweetie.
Come on, honey.
Come on, Dick!
Oh...
Why are you so angry?
- I'm not talking to you.
Oh, you found him.
Oh, good, now we can
stop looking.
I was going to bring
him right back lieutenant.
If I were a good mother, I'd
push you down those stairs.
You're not a mother.
Well technically, no, but that's going to change.
How?
- I've decided to keep the baby.
What?! - No!
You can't. He's not yours.
I'm willing to overlook that.
He needs me.
He's helpless.
And what am I!
You can't keep him. They
have rules about these things.
They have laws
about these things.
They have TV movies
Dick, I'm keeping him.
That's final.
Hello?  Anybody home?
- Oh, my god!
I have to hide him.
- What?
You're coming right back
in here this instant! Sally!
Thanks so much for watching my grandson.
I have been
to hell and back.
I won't bore you.
- You're too late.
Well, where is
my little fella?
Mrs. Dubcek, I'm
so glad you're here.
We're having a problem with our oven.
- What kind of problem?
How should I know? You're
a landlady. You tell us.
Harry, Show Mrs. Dubcek to the oven.
Stuff her in it if you have to.
Sally!
- Is she gone yet? - No!
Then we're not coming out.
I order you to think this through.
- Okay. Hmm, no!
Sally, no..
Your oven seems fine.
I'll just get my little
boy, and I'll be on my way.
So soon,
Mrs. Dubcek?
We've been living in this
attic for almost a year now,
and we know very little about you. Sit down.
Tell us everything about
yourself. Leave nothing out.
Please everything. Travel?
- Marriages. - Medical history.
Well, there's
a doctor in Mexico
that once said I had
the exact DNA of a lemur.
Ohh, that's fascinating.
I'll be right back.
Sally!
Well, here he is.
You have to go
home now, baby.
There's
my little man.
Bye, baby.
- Bye, Sally.
Aw! Come on,
sweetheart.
Oh, what a big boy
you are.
Were you a good boy? Yes!
Well,
thank god
he's gone.
I'm going
to miss him.
Excuse me. I'm going to go
take care of the other baby.
What was that
all about?
I thought you loved him.
- I do.
Then why did you suddenly give him back?
I guess I love him
enough to know that his
real mom needs him more than I do.
You know, when I
couldn't find him, I went crazy.
I couldn't put
his mother through that.
Why don't you have one of your own?
- That would be great.
Why don't you
go for it?
Yeah, right. And let this body go to hell?
Mary, we have
to talk.
You have a dog.
- Yes.
Mary I want everything to go
back to the way it was
before I killed
your fish.
I'm afraid that's going
to take some time.
I know what it means to lose
something that you care about,
and what I did was
very, very wrong.
Why do you have a dog?
Well, I went to the pet store
to buy you some new fish,
and I saw this cute little guy.
Oh, Dick, I can't
take care of a dog.
If you can love a fish,
you can love a dog.
Well, he is kind of cute.
Come here, boy.
Oh, look at him.
He loves you, Mary.
www.tvsubtitles.net