Oh Dick
- Oh Mary
We mustn't do this here.
- Yes, we must do it.
We can't!
- We can. I measured.
Oh! I have an early class tomorrow.
You hear what
she said, Dick?
She's got an early
class tomorrow.
Will you be quiet?
Can't you see I'm trying
to get to second base here?
Things have really changed
since she entered the picture.
Yeah, now we even have to act like
humans when we're by ourselves.
She's like
that Yoko woman
who ruined
her husband's band.
Oh, yeah.
Hey you remember that episode
where she convinced Ricky
that she could play
the bongos?
This bites.
So does she.
What?
The crust in your eyes,
it's still there.
Oh, no! no, don't touch it.
It's beautiful.
My god, you're
a morning person.
No.
No, I'm
a Mary person.
Oh! Oh, that's
so sweet.
I had the strangest dream
that your brother Harry
was curled up at our feet
in the middle of the night.
It won't happen again.
I'll finish dressing.
- Can I help you?
No.
Do you mind?
I am trying to sleep.
She slept over again?
- Slept? No.
Well, eventually,
but I think the innuendo
is delightfully clear.
Don't you see what's going on
here? She hogs the bathroom.
She leaves stuff in the sink for me to wash.
And last night
she forced us to watch
an A and E biography
on Susan Saint James.
What's your point, lieutenant?
- You let in an outsider.
She's getting in the way of this mission.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to observe her up close.
Well, she's
no Jo Anne Worley, but,
Quarters to her.
Hello, Tommy.
I really want the two of us to be friends.
Don't you have any friends of your own?
You're probably
very confused
about what's going on
between your father and me.
No, not really.
I have excellent hearing.
I just want you to know
that your father and I
are going to be seeing a
lot more of each other.
Oh, wow.
How much could possibly be left?
Well, gotta go.
See you at the office.
I have an idea.
Why don't I ride with you?
Ahh, I think it would be
a better idea
if we rode separately,
if you know what I mean.
I don't know what you mean.
Well, People might start thinking
that we're
sleeping together.
What?!
- We are.
We are, I swear.
Why can't you two
just ride together?
I need the car to go shopping.
- I need a ride downtown.
It's just not
a good idea.
Why not?
- This is exactly what I was talking about.
She has a car...
- It's really none of our business...
You know what?!
I don't want to
start a fight here.
I think it's okay for you
to ride with me today.
Yes!
- Come on.
What's this?
I won.
I won 150 dollars!
You don't
understand, lady.
You owe "us" 150 dollars.
Oh, I see. So you lure me
down here to collect my prize.
Then you pull the old
bait and switch.
I'll take care
of this.
Sally?
Hello, Don.
It's been a long time.
I thought you walked out
of my life for good.
I'm back. I ran into
trouble out there in the city.
The city is full of trouble.
I found this on my car.
Parked in
a handicap zone.
I'm sure you had
a good reason.
Yes. It was the closest spot to the store.
Works for me.
Consider this taken care of.
- Just like that?
Just like that.
Wow.
Sally, can I take
you out tonight?
'Kay.
No. Stop it.
- We're not in the office.
Behave yourself.
- Let's go back in the car.
No!
Not in the car, not in the bar,
not in the house,
not up your blouse.
I cannot touch you here or
there. I cannot touch you anywhere.
Judith!
Father rice.
Hello, Dr. Albright.
- Dr. Solomon and I
just ran into each other on the way in.
Dr. Suter.
What?
I said, Dr. Suter!
You again!
Here, here, do you need any help?
Get away from me.
Good for you!
Stay independent!
Dick, rumor has it,
that you and a certain
anthropology professor are..
uh... going
at it pretty good.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yeah, right.
I gotta get me
an anvil.
Harry, I need a ride.
No.
You know, I outrank you.
Oh. Well, in that case, no, sir.
Please?
Just give me a ride.
Look, come on. Can't you see that I'm busy?
What, is it
too much to ask
for a little time
for Harry?
I'll tell you what.
If the roadrunner wins
this next one, you take me.
But if he doesn't,
I'll never ask you again.
Okay, you're on.
I've seen this
next scheme before,
and it's far too brilliant to fail twice.
Let's go.
you're wrong.
- I'm right.
You're wrong.
- I'm not wrong.
You're wrong
about that, too.
There's no way to observe a
society without intruding.
One can't help but leave footprints.
Of course not.
I've seen your bipedal gait.
So let me get
this straight.
You're saying that you
could drop right out of the sky
into some strange culture and
walk amongst them unnoticed?
Yes!
Hypothetically.
Mary, you're an anthropologist,
back me up.
I'm afraid I'd have
to agree with Dr. Solomon.
Of course.
What was I thinking?
You're sleeping
with him.
This is a disaster, Dick.
Everybody's talking about us.
Oh, we're back
to that again.
You just
don't understand.
I've worked hard
to be taken seriously.
There was a time when I had a reputation.
For excellence?
Well, yes,
but in a very
specific category.
When I was a young
professor on the fast track,
there were things that I did.
Well what were you doing?
The Dean.
Is that like
the Watusi?
Sometimes.
There was this very prestigious job opening.
Did you get it?
No, I didn't
get the job,
but I did get
a nickname..
Dr. Mary Slutbunny.
Well, there's
your silver lining.
You just don't
get it, do you?
When a man has an office
romance, it doesn't affect his career.
But when a woman has one,
no one takes her seriously.
I don't understand.
I don't expect you to.
I need to be
alone tonight.
But I'm not
like that.
I take you seriously,
Dr. Slutbunny.
Sally, you look
beautiful.
Oh, Don, that's just
the doughnuts talking.
What you did today
was really powerful.
I mean you just snapped your
fingers and things fell into place.
Let's just keep that our
little secret, shall we?
Okay.
Would you like
another doughnut?
I don't know, are you sure you can afford it?
I get 'em for free,
all except
the cream-filled,
but all that will change
when I make detective.
That day
will come, Don.
We'll make it come.
And then...
we can eat
cream-Filled..
together.
One-David-niner. One-David-niner. Copy that.
2-18?
2-18.
What is it?
- It's a 2-18.
I have to go.
- Take me with you.
I can't.
- Please?
Let's ride.
- Oh, goody!
That was
so exhilarating, Don.
I've never been
on a raid before.
Come to think of it,
I've never held a criminal
off the roof of a warehouse by his ankles
until he screamed,
"mommy"!
Oh, mommy.
Sally, you make me
feel alive,
like I've dropped
a stun gun down my pants.
Hey, Don,
do it again.
Sally,
you're insatiable.
You're home
awfully late.
I had a great time tonight.
Dick, I think I've finally found my calling.
What?
I'm joining the police force.
Why?
Because I can make a difference.
I'm sorry, lieutenant,
but I forbid it.
Why?
Because you will make a difference.
Say you clean up Rutherford. What's next?
Cleveland.
- Exactly.
Then you clean up Ohio.
- That's the plan.
Soon, the entire Midwest
is crime-free.
What's going to happen
to all those people
whose income
depends on crime?
The lawyers, the insurance
companies, the 11:00 news?
Hell, the entire
fox network?
There are worldwide
implications here.
We're not supposed to
interfere with life on this planet.
Why can't I interfere with the planet? You do.
I do not!
What do you call what
you're doing with Dr. Albright?
That's different.
When you're in love with someone,
you're allowed to completely screw up their life.
That's what love is.
I understand.
I'll talk to Don.
Thank you,
lieutenant.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go to bed.
I can't be around you
with a nightstick right now.
Yes,
I seem to have
that effect on women.
Hey.
Would you please
take it outside?
If only I could be that spoon.
- Stop it.
You let me be
the spoon yesterday.
Cut it out.
- Come on!
Dick, we're
professionals.
We have reputations
to protect.
We're not kids anymore.
Oh, I see.
The looser the skin,
the tighter the behavior.
Is that it?
Just let me be the spoon once. Please?
Fine. Just this once.
You're about
a quart low.
From now on, I'm just going
to slide things under the door.
The two of you
haven't RSVP'd
the trustees' cocktail
reception tomorrow night.
Well, I can't speak
for Dr. Solomon,
but I'll be there.
Nina, can I ask you something?
Damn! I almost made it.
There's a man
and a woman,
and the woman won't let
the man near her in public.
The man is very frustrated. What should he do
when all he wants is climb to
the top of the engineering tower
and proclaim his love
for all the campus to hear?
Well I wouldn't do that if I were him.
Well why not?
Because Dr. Albright
would kill him dead.
Fine.
I won't.
I don't know what
came over her.
Same old story.
She wants more space.
I don't know how
to give it to her..
Wait...I've got it.
I'll go out and buy
two dozen roses,
and then I'll put a little
note on each rose that says,
"hope you're enjoying
your space".
Then I'll take one over every
hour on the hour and give it to her.
If she's not there, I'll
leave it on her doorstep.
No Dick, that doesn't sound
like a very good idea.
Look, do you
want her back,
or do you want her to think you're an idiot?
I want her back.
Well, you've got to play it cool.
You have to act like
you couldn't care less
whether she likes you or not.
But I do.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do!
Oh, right.
Maybe I don't.
There you go.
But I do!
- No!
Trust me, she'll come crawling back.
I know what
I'm talking about.
I've been married
five times.
Yeah, Women.
Or so I've heard.
I understand,
Mrs. Bittenson.
His tree is dropping fruit on your property.
It's just that the police
department can't do anything at this time
except dispatch three
black-And-whites asap
to that
dirtbag's house
and gas him until he picks
up every last one of those...
figs.
I'm sorry, Sally. You just
walked into a hornet's nest here.
You work so hard, officer Don.
Rusty, Rico.
Protect and serve.
That's what I do..
protect and serve.
I got something to tell you,
and it's going to hurt.
Then make it quick.
I can't join the force.
But you're so good.
I'm the best, but it's too
much power for one person to have.
I'd affect too many lives.
No, there's no power.
I do nothing. I'm completely ineffectual.
Here's your stick.
I'll never forget
you, Smokey.
You'll be back.
A woman like you
can't stay away.
Maybe.
Be careful
out there.
So are we sending
the squad cars
to collect those figs?
Um... no, no.
I'll just, um...
pick 'em up
on my way home.
Oh, my god.
Here he comes.
They're going to have a field day with this one.
It's okayDr Albright Just. Calm down.
Nina!
It's so good to see you,
and only you.
Oh, Dr. Solomon,
I've never seen you with
a turtleneck before.
His name is Harry.
Dr. Suter!
Oh, and Mrs. Sumner!
You look lovely
this evening.
Oh, well, thank..
no!
Mmm! This is great dip, Mrs. Sumner.
It's pâté.
This is great dip pâté.
What's she doing?
You don't care.
Oh... right.
Dick, is there
something..
Martini, dry. Not too dry. Moist, very moist.
I see.
You're punishing me.
Fine.
You're good.
- Smooth.
But it's so hard.
Stay strong big guy.
Trouble in
paradise, Mary?
Oh, shut up.
Don't you have
anything better to do?
Why don't you get a life so
I'll have somebody to talk about?
Ouch.
Oh, I love
these things.
May I?
This isn't metric,
is it?
I didn't know you played.
- No, I'm not playing, I'm adding.
Not the way I would have done it.
Whatever.
I'll never understand
this human obsession
with what other
people think.
I don't care
what anybody thinks.
You know, Harry, maybe you
should care just a little.
Sally, how did you leave it
with officer Don?
Open. I've never been
out with a guy like him.
I've been wined
and dined,
but I've never
been doughnut-ed.
I like it.
I'd like to be breaded
and deep fried.
And I don't care what
anybody thinks of it.
You're right Harry. The only voice that
matters is the one inside your head.
Ha! Which one?
Shut up.
Mary Albright
is mine!
Dick Solomon
You on the
roof, put down the bullhorn!
There have been
complaints.
Put down
the bullhorn!
Thanks, Don.
www.tvsubtitles.net