I have got..
the perfect
present for you.
A present? What for?
- Christmas.
What, you didn't
get me anything?
No, are you kidding? No.
Not get you anything, of course
I got you something. I, uh...
I got you the perfect
something, it's perfect,
and it's, uh,
it's really something.
You're so sweet.
All right,
we are wired.
Can I plug it in? Can I plug it in?
- Knock yourself out.
It's magnificent!
- You ain't seen nothing yet.
By the time I'm through
with this joint,
they're gonna be able to
see it from the shuttle.
Tommy!
Look what I got.
- A stick?
No!
It's a Christmas tree!
You'll see. All it needs is a little love.
Dick! Dick!
Dick you are not gonna believe
what we got at the mall. - A stick?
It's a Christmas tree!
That thing?
We are Solomons Harry.
We should have the biggest,
noblest tree in all of Ohio.
Forget the stick, Dick.
We found jobs.
The mall is full of them..
Christmas jobs.
You are lookin' at a
professional gift-wrapper.
And I am the executive
assistant to Mr. Santa Claus.
I've heard of him. He's the muckedy-
muck in charge of the whole shebang.
Yeah, well, I'm kind of
his right-hand elf.
This is wonderful.
It's a celebration.
Tommy, when did we
first land on this planet?
January 9th. It was a Tuesday,
exactly 8:30 P.M.
7:30 central.
Do you realize we're
coming up on our anniversary?
An earth year on earth, and
everything is finally coming together.
It's as if all of the
earth were throwing us a party.
Suddenly I feel
so... so...
human.
Same here. - Me too.
- I'm feeling kinda human here myself.
Oh guys.
"Snap"!
Oh great...now it's a stick.
Weeds.
Okay, Dick, it's time
to pick your secret Santa.
It's time to who
for wha-wha?
Pick a name,
that's who you buy a present for.
Presents? for Christmas?
The bowl is heavy.
Let's see who this is.
Let's play
secret Santa.
Dr. Anthony?
I barely know him.
Glansberg, Chilton,
lanell
Dick, you don't get to
choose your person. It's random.
You pick one name, and
it's a secret until the party.
Ohhh.
Well I picked
my name,
and whoever it is
hasn't the foggiest idea.
For now until the party,
their life will be a
topsy-turvy
labyrinth of mystery,
and intrigue.
For the love of god,
let him draw again.
Well, hello-ho-ho,
everybody,
and welcome to
Santa's toyland.
Presents, toys and fun
for children one to ninety one.
Oh, uh, please note that children
sixteen to ninety one,
should not sit
on Santa's lap.
Damn!
Thank you, and have
a happy and safe holiday,
from all of us here
at the Rutherford galleria.
Wow, you've been
shopping your butt off.
Yeah.
It's Christmas, right?
Oh, it's great, isn't it?
People buying stuff,
lugging bags around,
maxing out their credit cards.
It's like everyone in the
whole world is joined together
to embrace
financial ruin.
Merry Christmas.
- Thank you,
and have a happy and safe
holiday from all of us here
at the Rutherford
galleria!
Merry Christmas.
She's coin-operated.
She says she has
the perfect gift for me,
and I have no idea
what to get her.
Her name is
August Lefler.
Well, I don't
know August..
well, aren't you supposed to
have some kind of list or something?
Well, I'm afraid I left my
list up in the north pole.
Oh, great! Can't you have your
wife fax it to you or something?
I can't screw this up!
Well, Tommy..
look,
you want to make
this August chick happy,
you're gonna have to drop some cold,
hard cash, you know what I'm Sayin'?
On what? Listen, pork butt,
I need model numbers here.
Get a haircut.
You look like a girl.
What again?
The root must be
somewhere upstairs.
Ooh, is that the gift
you got for Judith?
Or... whoever it was
you happened to pick?
Yes.
- There's a $20 limit.
I know.
I went a little over.
A hundred and twenty
dollars over.
It's easy to get
carried away, isn't it?
You know, a few years ago,
I made a batch
of my famous rum balls
for Christmas.
They were so popular that
this year, just on a whim,
I made 20 batches, enough
for the whole department.
Mmm. It's funny that you
would have that much rum around.
It's the holidays, Nina.
- Yes, Nina, it's the holidays.
My dad would go out and get the
biggest Christmas tree he could find.
We'd go caroling, open our house
to the neighborhood.
All that sharing
and generosity..
It's so beautiful.
Look how generous I am.
I am Christmas!
Hello, and happy holidays from all of us here..
- Where's my package?
I'm supposed to say the whole
thing. Hello, and happy holidays..
Excuse me. I was.. I was.. I was here first.
Excuse me.
I'm just picking up.
Wo wo wo, come on, people. You're
supposed to be happy. This is shopping.
Yeah, well, I'm fed up.
Where the hell's January already?
What is wrong
with you people?
This isn't about
buying gifts at all.
This is about viciousness and
ruthlessness and aggression, and...
usually I like
all those things, but...
but now, it's just
really ruining Christmas.
Just wrap!
awww.
Oh, don't worry,
boys and girls.
Santa will be
right back
after he takes care
of some personal business.
On the toilet.
Oh, what are they feeding
these kids? They weigh a ton!
Well, you know, I think part of the
problem is we're feeding 'em candy.
Maybe if we could give
them celery or some kinda...
Oh... Santa.
What are you..I mean..
it's.. you..
Noooo!
"Oh Tannenbaum, Oh Tannenbaum..
..that's "Christmas tree"
in German"
Now this is a Christmas tree.
Hey, hey, buddy, can I help you?
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, officer!
"Peace on earth, goodwill
toward men".. what a crock!
Nine hundred dollars
in fines,
and they confiscated
your chain saw?
And have you ever
felt a taser?
It's not nearly as much fun as it looks.
What a bunch
of hypocrites!
Apparently, the
Christmas spirit doesn't apply
when you're trespassing and vandalising.
Oh, let's face it,
Christmas is a sham.
How can humans take
something like shopping,
something pure
and natural and good,
and turn it into
something so ugly?
This is not a holiday,
this is torture.
They know exactly what they
want, but they won't tell you.
No-o...they make you guess.
This is just
so "Earth".
Humans.. I don't want to play
any of their reindeer games.
"fa, la, la, la, la la, la, la, la"
'tis the season to be jolly...
Oh, listen to them.
Singing like idiots. Why did we
want to be like humans anyway?
That's better.
And so we see that
that B equals,
2a over delta,
which equals k times mass over 2 pi delta,
and therefore..
Leon?
What are you passing around?
- Oh, Caryn made them.
Yeah, they're Christmas cookies.
- Oh, how christmasy.
All sparkly,
red and green.
Oh, look.
One of Santa's reindeer.
Watch him fly.
And look,
a little Christmas bell.
"Ding, dong"
I don't even know
what this is.
It was a snowman.
No, it was butter
and sugar and sprinkles,
all wrapped up in empty
sentiment and holiday hypocrisy.
Ho! Ho, ho, ho,
ho, ho, ho, ho!
Where do you think you're going?
- It's Christmas break.
It is not "Christmas break" until I say it is.
Not until you've completed the
following remedial assignment.
You will write
a 15-page dissertation
on wave physics and its
relation to electromagnetic radiation.
Oh, and a five-point bonus
if you can tell me
how the hell Santa delivers
all those toys in one night.
It's to be typewritten and on
my desk no later than 6:00.
Tonight?
- But it's December 23rd.
Yeah, it's
Christmas eve eve.
Ohh, it is?
Well, tough tinsel.
Thank you and have a happy, safe holiday
from all of us here at the Rutherford galleria.
Bye-bye, now.
Hey, Tommy.
- I finally found something for August.
Oh, perfume. Is this what she wants?
- I don't know.
So I also got her a portable Cd player.
- Oh, she likes CDs.
I don't know. So I got
her earrings...
oh, yeah, and a cellular phone
and a belt.
How did you afford
all this stuff?
You know that jar of pennies I have in my room?
- Yeah.
It's where I hide
Dick's credit card.
Bartender,
two fingers, no fat.
I believed in him.
I thought we were
bringing joy to the world.
I was gonna move
to the north pole
to work in his
toy factory.
Well, look what
the cat dragged in.
You got a lot of guts
coming in here, fat boy.
Do I know you?
Oh, don't get cute
with me, Kringle.
If that is
your real name.
Hey, what's
your problem?
You're my problem!
So what are you
gonna do?
Get one of your reindeer
to kick me to death?
Hey, take it easy, take it easy.
- Oh, mind your..
Whoa!
Wait a second.
But you.. he..
Is there a problem?
Jingle bell,
jingle bell jingle bell rock...
you know, this is the only
time of year I like white music.
What do you think, Nina?
Mmm.
Too much egg
Needs more Nog?
- Yep.
Mmm, that is
good!
Rum ball?
- Oh, spare me.
You better be nice to me if
you want your stocking stuffed.
Hey!
There will be no holiday cheer,
Nina, while there's work to be done.
Work? On Christmas eve eve?
I'll need all the grades for my 10:00 class
broken down and re-
tabulated for the whole semester.
On Christmas eve eve?
- Yes.
Dick, we need somebody tall
to hang the boughs of holly.
Fa, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, no.
I guess I'd like the plaid..
- We're out of everything
but green foil
and happy snowmen.
Well, it's for my mom, so..
- You got your mom a dust miser?
How nice.. the gift
that keeps on sucking.
I just didn't know what to get her.
- Yeah, apparently not.
Wait a second.
Where was that.. here you go.
A foot massager. The woman
needs a break, for crying out loud.
Gosh, thanks.
- You're welcome.
Hey, that's my foot massager.
- Oh, poor baby.
Who's it for?
- My wife.
Wow, real romantic.
Here, wait a second.
Ah! Some exotic
bath oils.
You can turn your wife
into a slip 'n' slide. - Thanks.
That.. that was for my boyfriend.
Unless you have
a better idea.
As a matter of fact,
I do. Here.
International beer basket
from the liquor locker.
Oh, yeah! Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
This is fun.
Hey, uh, diamond tennis
bracelet. Who wants one?
All this laughing,
opening their
little presents..
who needs Christmas
anyway?
I say, "bug Humbar".
You mean,
"bah, humbug".
Bah" what?
- You said, "bug Humbar".
And?
- Well, what does "bug Humbar" mean?
Well, what does "bah, humbug" mean?
- Forget it.
Here,
Merry Christmas.
You bought me a gift?
- Yeah.
So you were my secret Santa?
I was not your secret Santa.
I just happen to love
Christmas. Now, open your damn present!
Well, what is it?
- It's a travel mug.
What's it for?
So you don't spill coffee
in your lap every morning.
You noticed?
Uh, yeah.
I need this.
- You're welcome.
Nina...
forget the work.
Go to the party.
Are you sure?
- Yes. Have a good time.
And Nina,
M..merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas,
Dr. Solomon.
Where are those rum
dreidels I made for Dr. Schwartz?
Mary, look what
Nina gave me!
I'm not talking to you.
You're ruining my Christmas.
No, no, that was the old Dick. I
think I've actually got the spirit.
I want to be a part
of Christmas now.
Well, pah, dum,
a, dum, pum.
Here you go, Dr. Solomon.
- Dr. Solomon.
Your papers?
- Sorry we're late. Don't take points off.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
- What are you doing? We worked on those!
And in the spirit of Christmas
, I'm not even gonna read them.
I'm gonna give you
all Cs!
"Cs"?
- Yes!
Oh, what the hell,
it's Christmas. C-pluses!
Go, go, all of you,
trim your stockings
and stuff your trees!
Merry Christmas!
God bless us,
every one.
Judith! Judith!
Judith, come in here!
Judith, I'm your secret Santa.
Get out.
Here. Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
And happy new year.
- Same to you.
May your holiday be
filled with lords a-leaping,
ladies dancing,
pipers piping,
drummers drumming,
geese a-laying,
swans a-swimming.
- That will do.
Five golden rings!
I know I've had
a lot of rum balls,
but that was
really sweet.
It's just wonderful.
I thought Christmas was all
about stress and hostility
and handcuffs
and Miranda rights.
But no, it's more.
It's so much more!
It's about giving
and sharing
and just...
being human.
Come on, the party's
still going on,
and I've saved a special dance for you.
Ohh.
That weed
grew back again.
It's mistletoe.
- Mistletoe?
Yeah.
- Well, what's it for?
I'll show you.
Merry Christmas.
- Oh, merry Christmas to you.
But what's
the mistletoe for?
Dick!
Ohh.
Ah, well I don't know
how the real Santa's
gonna slide down
this thing,
but he will.
Ah, what a lovely way to mark
our first anniversary on earth,
our first anniversary
as humans.
Do you think we'll ever really
know everything there is to know
about being human?
Merry Christmas, Tommy.
This?
I made it myself.
It's the two of us. See?
What I got for you
is so much better
than this!
I mean, it is a joke
how much better
my stuff is
than this!
Which I love.
www.tvsubtitles.net