I love these Saturdays
in the park.
The soft grass,
the chirping birds,
the "eyewitness
news" team.
Save the park!
Makes you want to scream at the
top of your lungs like those people.
Let's eat
over there!
No! I prefer this table! It's in the shade!
Hey, look!
A butterfly!
Hey, look, Sally!
It's your friend Don!
Sally.
- Don.
A word to the wise. There's
trouble in the park today.
Trouble? Uh-oh. I
better take care of my baby.
What is it?
- Sometimes a wrinkle runs through the city,
and it rears up
on its haunches
like an ugly monkey
ready to strike.
Don, you always
have your finger
up the pulse
of danger.
Save the park! Save the park!
Save the park!
Hey, man, you want
to sign this petition?
The town's going
to destroy bates park.
Uh... maybe in
a little while.
There's no time, the dozers are on their way.
Okay. I've chained myself to the tree.
Oh!
- Sir, sir, excuse me.
Is it true you've chained
yourself to that tree?
Yes, that's exactly
what I've done.
So you won't
free yourself
even though the city
bulldozers are on their way?
No, I cannot
do that.
He may be an organized protester,
he may be a rogue
mountain man,
but one thing's
for sure-
he may be a hero.
We got it.
Is it on
the right channel?
Some of the
stories we're tracking at this hour:
A fire breaks out in a nursing home...
- Ooh!
a search for survivors
continues at the Parma Heights mudslide,
and in our Science Watch,
a vet performs an operation
that allows a cat to smile
for the first time.
Aww!
That's the happiest cat
in the world.
Tonight's top story:
a protest in Bates Park.
Look! I'm on TV!
- You're wearing my shirt. My shirt's on television.
That's exactly what I've done.
Hello?
Yes, Harry Solomon
lives here.
Okay.
Hold on.
Harry has
a phone call.
A phone call.
My first phone call.
How do I look?
- You look fine.
Hello.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
I'll have to talk it over with my family.
Okay. Bye.
Who was that?
- It's a member from the independent party.
They saw me on TV. They want
me to run for city council.
What's city council?
I think it's
some sort of council
here in the city.
Council? According to my
civics class, that's government.
Oh, Oh, this is big.
This is big. We do not
want to get involved in this.
This will allow us to get on
the inside, see how it works.
What about our vow not to
alter the course of the planet?
Please. It's only politics.
We dive in, master it,
grab a few votes, get a
little action. Nobody gets hurt.
Harry, call those people
back and tell them you'll run.
Right you're the boss.
- Sally, Tommy,
you advise Harry
on his campaign.
I'm going to register to vote.
- Shouldn't we all vote?
No. We don't want
to arouse suspicion.
One in four
seems right.
Here's a list of candidates and referendums.
So you're all set. You come
back here in two weeks to vote.
Right. And how many times do I get to vote?
One time.
And it doesn't matter
that I'm brilliant?
No.
Have you noticed
how tall I am?
We all get
one vote.
So your opinion counts equally with mine?
- You got it.
You're awfully smug for a man
who works at a folding table.
Okay, let's see.
For mayor,
Heckie Mulligan.
Hmm, funny name.
I like that in a Mayor.
Heckie Mulligan?
How can you vote for Heckie
Mulligan? Nina, can you believe that?
How do you know I'm not voting for Mulligan?
I thought you
were a democrat.
Why do you think I'm a
democrat? Because I'm black?
Go ahead, vote for Mulligan.
- I'm not voting for Mulligan.
Wait,
I don't understand.
Why are you getting
so worked up over politics?
It's simple. You vote for the
best, the best man wins.
Or woman.
Oh that's priceless.
What, Heckie's
a woman?
Frank Gansmiller.
Glad to know you.
Hey, Betty, the new speed bump
keeping the teenagers away?
Great, good.
Norma, Tom, Patty,
Cathy, Carl.
Too bad about
that warehouse fire.
I'm glad to hear
"the insurance" came through.
Harry Solomon.
I've never seen you
before in my life.
Hi, I'm
Harry Solomon,
a simple mind
for a simple people.
I can't believe
Dr. Solomon
is letting his brother
run against Gansmiller.
No one can dig up the dirt like Gansmiller.
- The man's a backhoe.
It's a piece
of equipment.
Don?
- Sally, what brings you here?
My brother threw his head into the ring.
You mean his hat?
- Yeah, sure, his hat.
What brings you here?
- Oh, the usual.
Looking for trouble,
making sure it doesn't happen.
Punch?
- Take your best shot.
Frank Gansmiller.
- Dick Solomon.
Nice to know you, Dick.
- I feel it only fair to warn you
that your challenger is my brother
Harry, and I am not easily swayed.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Mary, this is Frank Gansmiller.
This must be the little lady?
This must be the little man.
Mary.
Dick, it's all right,
as long as Mary
turns out to vote.
Although I don't know if you're old enough to vote.
- Yes, she is.
She's 44.
Mr. Gansmiller-
Frank, when I do vote,
it won't be for you.
Mary, Dick,
let me get serious
for just a moment.
"Why should I vote for
Frank Gansmiller?" You ask.
I didn't ask.
Mary won't let me get away
with anything, will she, Dick?
Not a thing, Frank.
Why should I vote for
Frank Gansmiller, Frank?
Good question, Dick.
Because I want
to take money
out of the drug
dealers' pockets
and give it back
to the people.
Oh, Frank's right. I want
some of that drug money.
All right, everybody. It's
time to hear from our candidates.
First up, our incumbent,
Frank Gansmiller.
Thank you.
No, no.
You know what?
You all know me.
Let's give the new kid a chance.
- Yes, yes.
This is a great man.
- Dick, sit.
Thank you,
fellow...
Rutherfordonianites.
Anyway, I'm here
because of
all you people,
Men, Women.
Of course,
if I had my way,
there'd be
like a lot more women.
You know, on any given day, I
see maybe one, two women, tops.
I want to see
more women.
Everywhere I go,
More women in the workplace, yes!
Okay.
Vote Harry S. Solomon.
The "S" stands
for know-how.
I'm sorry,
Snow-How.
Turn it off.
I've seen enough.
All right, whatta you got on him?
Nothing, he's clean.
Nothing, must have
something rotten in his past?
He's human, isn't he?
- I've done every background check personally.
There's nothing.
It's like he...
fell out of the sky.
What about drinking?
- No.
Gambling?
Bad checks? Tax evasion?
- No.
Pornography, drug addiction, bad hairpiece?
No!
Zero divided by zero,
zip, nada, bubkiss.
Bubkiss huh?
What does
"bubkiss" mean?
Nothing.
- Yeah, I thought so.
You know,
it's almost
as if he were...
Amish.
Damn!
No past, no experience, no record,
the perfect
candidate.
Wait a minute.
What about that sister of his?
- You leave her out of it!
Ooh!
Copper's got
a girlfriend.
Should there be a toll on
the Cherry street bridge?
Well, I never use it.
Yes.
- Yes.
But what if I
start using it?
No.
- Smart money on No.
What am I thinking? There's
nothing good on cherry street.
Yes.
No!
No-
Yes!
A resounding No-Yes.
Okay, let's move on
to the candidates.
This should be
a no-brainer.
City council, district nine? Harry Solomon.
Yaaaa?
What? Don't tell me
you're voting for Gansmiller.
Don't tell me you're voting for Harry.
- Yes, I'm voting for Harry.
Then you're voting wrong.
- There's no such thing as voting wrong.
Yes, there is.
You're doing it.
You're making a mockery of this
whole election by voting wrong.
It's my vote I get to use it any way I want.
What's the point of having a
democracy if people go around voting wrong?
In my opinion,
democracy is doing just fine the way it is.
Well, your opinion
is wrong!
I can't believe you're
voting against your own brother.
Ha, just watch me.
- Dick!
You're not going
to vote for me?
Well, that hurts.
And I know
because I feel
your pain.
But Harry Solomon
is not worried...
because Harry
Solomon knows
that Harry Solomon
can win.
How can you
possibly win?
Because Harry
Solomon appeals
to both sides.
Vote for Harry Solomon.
- Ow!
Hi!
- Hey, Mrs. Dubcek. You want a button?
Yeah! I'm glad Harry is standing up
for good old-fashioned
family values.
You could learn from
this lesson, Sally.
Never date a guy if he's
not good to his wife and kids.
Don.
- Sally.
We have to talk.
Your brother is playing with
matches, and that's how fires start.
I know my way
around a hose.
This election
could turn ugly,
very ugly.
I shouldn't be telling you
this, but I had to warn you.
You're the only thing in
my life that isn't dirty.
A girl can't stay clean
forever in a town like this.
Don't talk
like that, Sally.
You've got a great pair of
getaway sticks. Now use 'em.
Come on, Don.
Be straight with me.
You owe me
that much.
Follow the money, Sally,
follow the money.
Solomon.
Gansmiller.
Glad you came.
- Wow.
That's something I don't hear very often.
Solomon, this election
means a lot.
What do you say
we cut a deal?
Well, what sort
of deal?
You drop out of the race,
I'll make you building inspector.
Why do I want to be
building inspector?
Because when the building
inspector looks the other way,
he gets an envelope.
Well, what if the building
inspector doesn't look the other way?
He always looks
the other way.
Well, what's so special
the other way?
The envelope.
- Well, what's in the envelope?
I don't have to tell you
what's in the envelope.
Well you don't have to, but I
sure would appreciate it.
Look, what will it take
you to drop out of this race?
Well, don't ask me. I'm not
the one who makes the decisions.
You aren't?
- No, never have, never will.
I just sort of
follow orders.
Whose?
- Well, we sort of have a leader.
"We"?
- The Family.
The "Family".
Thank you, Solomon.
Thank you very much.
Harry Solomon?
How much do we
really know about him?
He claims to be
a family man,
but what kind
of family?
There's no hard proof
that the Solomons are linked
to the Gambinis, the Genoveses,
and the Corleones,
but is that a risk
you're willing to take?
Harry Solomon-
an offer you can refuse.
Paid for by decent, God-
fearing citizens for Gansmiller.
Don't say that.
We can't be in the mob,
we're from Ohio.
That's terrible.
Oh, Dick, Dick, Dick,
Dick, Dick, Dick, Dick.
Dick, Dick.
You are so out of the game.
That was a gimme.
He mentioned my name like 20
times. That was great publicity.
But he's a liar.
Dick, let me talk to you
like you're a two-year-old.
You know how when you see
a commercial for Cheerios,
and they keep
showing you Cheerios,
and you really
want Cheerios...
do we have
any cheerios?
Right next to the
embarassing defeatios.
What?
- Nothing, sir.
I'm sorry
I'm late, sir.
What are you doing?
- I'm kissing your ring.
I'm not wearing a ring.
- I'm sorry.
Please don't
have me whacked.
Whacked? What kind of nonsense is this?
Well, sir, we just want to
pay you the proper respects.
We didn't know.
- Know what?
About your family connections, Don Solomon.
It's that stupid ad. It's
a complete and utter lie.
I would hope you people
would know better.
Good, because I've had all I can
take of this election foolishness.
Aaaaaaah!
This is ridiculous!
Your political system
is a sham!
It's nothing but lies
and propaganda.
Look what it's
done to you.
You can't even tell who's
good or bad or right or wrong.
Give me science.
At least with physics,
you know when you have the right answer.
- I never do.
Cannoli?
Oh, I'll be so glad
when this election is over.
Here. Do something with this.
I'm so confused. I hardly
even know what I'm doing.
You're sitting
on your cannoli.
Look! Who did this!
Everything's
out of control!
What's wrong?
- What's wrong? I'll tell you what's wrong.
I'm trying to vote
my conscience,
and I can't even
hear it anymore.
I have only two choices
for city council,
a professional liar
and my brother, the joke.
Neither of them should
even be running for office.
There is no choice. My only
choice is not to vote at all.
Democracy is horrible,
absolutely horrible!
You're so right.
Democracy is the worst form
of government there is,
except for all
of the others...
and that is exactly
why you have to vote.
No!
- Yes!
If you don't vote,
you can't complain.
Complaining is
all I have left.
The system
isn't perfect,
but it's important
to participate,
even if you
get it wrong.
Just go to the polls and
do what you think is right.
Things were so much
simpler where I come from.
There's only one
big giant office,
and whoever outruns
the fireball wins.
Oh, god, I hope
I did the right thing.
And the
results for city council are in.
The incumbent, Frank
Gansmiller, is the winner.
So I would be...
The loser.
Okay, okay.
I'd like to thank you all for supporting..
all righty.
Harry, I want you to
know that I voted for you.
And to top
off this night of firsts,
there was also
one write-in vote
for a Dr. Mary Albright.
That self-serving Bitch.
I just had to come over
and say great job, kid.
It was a tough
campaign all around.
Glad to see no one
went negative.
Is that envelope job
still available?
No.
Tough luck, kiddo,
but your family's
better off.
You spend your life around
garbage, you start to stink.
I don't like the taste
of losing, Don.
It tastes
like a bad egg.
You know, the kind that gives you the burps.
During this election,
I've done some things, Sally,
some things I'm
not so proud of.
Did I know better?
Sure.
But it's this...
this town,
this crazy town.
Makes you want
to brush your teeth.
You're in luck.
I'm packing.
So, Dr. Solomon, did you
hear someone voted for me?
Yes, I think I did
hear that somewhere.
I wonder where that vote could have come from.
- Who knows?
It is a secret
ballot.
It was me, Dr. Albright.
I voted for you.
No, you didn't!
How do you know?
It was a secret ballot.
Damn!
I think we should vote
for who's high commander.
Sure. We're in a democracy.
- Can we vote for ourselves?
Of course. I vote for me.
- I vote for me.
I vote for me.
High commander breaks the tie, I win.
Wait, wait, Let's vote again.
This time I vote for Harry.
This is America, you've
got to wait four years.
That's not fair.
- Whoa!
God bless America.
www.tvsubtitles.net