Last time on Third Rock From The Sun.
After
trapping me in an invisible box,
my evil replacement continued his
diabolical plot to rule the world.
Not knowing
his true identity,
my beloved Mary made a date
with the scoundrel.
But just as I thought my
plight was lost forever,
my entrapment was cleverly
discovered by my stellar crew.
Oh, you guys,
there's
an invisible box.
Ow! Wow,
that smarts!
You're going to look hideous tomorrow.
- You think?
Yeah. There's this girl
I knew. She hit her nose.
Dustin Hoffman.
- Mr. Randell's coming over.
Hello! I'm trapped in a box here.
Okay.
Well, let's see. Anybody know how
to open one of these things?
Well, we know we can't
smash it open with our heads.
Tommy, go get a hammer.
- Nobody's getting a hammer.
Get a hammer. That's an order.
- I'm sorry, sir,
but you can't
give us orders.
Of all the insolent..
Dick you are no longer the high commander.
Sorry...
but if we let you out of
that box, well, that's mutiny.
Oh, mutiny shmutiny.
Big, fat dutiny.
Now, I'm sick of
the new Dick.
This Dick,
he's one of us.
So maybe he's
not perfect,
maybe his leadership
skills verge on the pathetic,
and maybe his incompetence
has made our mission the
laughingstock of the entire Galaxy.
I think you've made your point.
No, I haven't made my point.
The point is that he's always
been there for the three of us,
and it's time the three
of us take a stand for him.
Aha, sure sure. That's easy for you to say.
You don't have
the responsibility I do.
If we let him out and the
big giant head gets wind of it,
who do you think's going to take
the fall? The information officer?
The transmitter?
I don't think so. It's going
to be me, the woman. Typical.
Sally!
Think of all we've been through together.
When brad dumped you,
who ordered you
to drink
yourself silly
until you had completely
drowned your feelings for him?
You did.
And when I ran over
your foot with the car,
who drove you
to the hospital
the very next day?
You did.
And when you were hungry
that day in the park,
who stole that little girl's ice cream cone.
Tommy did that.
- It was my idea.
It was.
- True.
Sir, you're right.
I can't let you
rot in this box.
I've got to get you out
of here. Come on, guys.
Blood is thicker than water.
- It is?
I think.
- It's not as thick as peanut butter.
It's a pretty thick substance.
- Chunky peanut butter?
Get me
out of here!
The lighting is romantic,
the champagne chilled.
And now for some...
erotic literature.
"Make sure the 2x4 studs are
cleated to the floor plates
before applying
the wallboard".
Perfect.
yoo-hoo!
- Come on up.
Oh! I like what you've done with the place.
Just wait
until you see..
the bedroom.
Tonight...
is about pleasure,
a journey into the...
taboo.
I will let nothing..
destroy the mood.
Nothing.
I've seen these.
Lieutenant!
Ah, clap off, huh?
You made it!
- I'm free! I'm free!
Tommy, thank you!
I'm free! Freedom! Freedom!
There's so much
I've missed..
fresh air, the smell
of bacon frying,
watching talk shows
with Harry.
I didn't miss jerry
springer's biker chick makeover, did I?
It was Tuesday.
- Oh, damn!
Sally, why are you wearing that
skirt? It makes you look frumpy.
I knew it!
That Dick upstairs said
this look worked for me.
You know, I hate him.
- He crashed the rambler.
He changed
my name to Tommy.
Where does that leave you?
- He calls me Tommy, too.
Is that Tommy and the number, 2..?
- I don't know.
The guy's a major head case.
- I've heard enough.
No one dictates
humiliating and irrational edicts
to my family.
That's my job.
Now, come on.
Oh, oh, oh!
And nobody better have
touched my strawberries.
Mary.
What's she doing
with him?
Looks like he's plugging her pie hole.
I think she
likes it, Dick.
Dick?
- Dick?
Dick.
- Come on, Dick.
What does she
see in him? I mean..
Sure, he's gorgeous, but... it's
all part of his depraved scheme.
How dare he!
How dare she.
Did what we have
mean nothing to her?
Wait.
She thinks he's me.
But he's going to get her
Because he's deceiving her!
And she'll be his forever. In a way, mine.
But she likes..
but he.. I oughta..
but, she, I..
- Dick, hey, snap out of it!
You have to take action.
- You're right. I've got it!
We're moving to Florida.
- What?!
It's warm all the time. The
land is cheap. And the fishing..
bass as big
as your arm.
We're not going anywhere.
Now you listen to me.
This afternoon when I was with
Albright arranging this date..
you arranged this date?
- Yeah, but the point is..
you set this up? What are you, his pimp?
If you'd let me finish, I'll expl..
- You of all people..
Dick, get a grip and
listen to her for a second.
The point is Dick, that I tried
to talk her out of this date,
but she wouldn't listen to me because..
and don't
ask me why..
she has some sort of
emotional attachment to you.
She said that?
She cares about you so much,
she is upstairs about to
have sex with another man.
She would do that for me?
If you don't stop her.
You're right. That tyrant has gone too far.
I must defeat that man!
- All right!
I should have done
that earlier.
Okay, here's the plan.
Tommy, Harry, you stay here.
Sally, watch my back while I
make a run for the bathroom.
Okay, then what?
- I use the bathroom.
I've been stuck in a box for two days.
Hold on.
Enough.
I think my tongue
has a Charley horse.
Well, saddle up.
We're going for another ride.
What is going on? Last
time, you were so fast.
Why don't we
just get to it?
"It"?
What?
You know...it.
Oh, it.
You'll get it,
all right.
You'll get
all of it
that you want.
It is..on..it's way.
Come on, Dick.
He's taking forever.
Who's taking forever?
Toilet duck.
He's tackling
our stubborn buildup.
Lieutenant, you're the
woman. I need to know about "it".
It what?
- You know, it.
Oh, it.
Um...ahh...let's get some privacy.
Okay, well, um...
uh... it's, uh
it's kind of involved.
Um...
yeah?
Eww.
Really?
No.
Hmm. And women
like that?
They love it.
And to think, all this time I
was just walking around on them.
Mary!
- Dick.
Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary.
- Oh, that's more like it.
I want you so bad.
You've got to escape.
You want me to try and get away?
- You must.
Oh, let me go!
Let me go!
How's that?
Get out!
- What?
If you clear the hedge, you'll be fine.
- What is wrong with you?
Nothing. Everything. You
know I'll never leave you.
Dick.
- I've got to go now. You remember Tommy.
Tell her about the swim team.
- Swim team?
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the former
high commander.
It seems that I've
underestimated your..
stupidity.
That was your
first mistake.
Here's your second.
Look over there.
Where?
What's going on?
Dick is acting so strangely.
Listen, Dr. Albright.
Dick, he's got a lot of
baggage. It's an internal struggle.
Stop!
Ha!
Stop pulling my hair !
- I'll pull it if I want !
That poor thing.
I didn't know.
No, you couldn't know,
'cause he's been afraid.
See, he's been lonely
for such
a long time.
And as the years
went by,
he fell into despair
and lost all hope.
For what woman
could ever learn to love a beast.
Give me a second, okay?
I'll be right back.
Why aren't you helping him?
- Which one?
When I pull him up,
brain him with the gnome.
Gotcha.
I got him, Dick!
- Now help me get him into the chair.
Here. .
Tie him up good.
Tie him down tight
Which one is it?
Tie him up, or tie him down?
Both, Harry.
Hurry! We've got to get him
out of here before Mary sees him.
What are we going to do with him?
Let's take him to the
rambler and put him in the trunk,
like they do on that show, "homicide".
"homicide"?
"Life on the street."
- Oh, yeah.
Great idea. Tommy, Harry, run
down and clean out the trunk.
You got it.
- All right.
We'll be
right back, sir.
Don't be long...
Tommy.
Don't tire yourself
out, commander.
I want you to witness
the destruction my little device
wreaks on
the world you love so well.
What have you done
to our toaster?
It's not a toaster.
It's an incubator.
When I press
this button,
millions of spores will be
released into the atmosphere,
spawning
a whole new race,
a race
of groveling drones.
They will think alike
and talk alike.
At times, they'll
even walk alike.
And I will be father
to them all.
What will happen to Mary?
- Oh, don't worry.
I'm not using
this on her.
I'm going to take care
of her personally.
I'm going in there
and putting my feet
in her purse
again and again
and again.
You're insane!
And not Gallagher insane, just insane!
We cleaned out
the rambler, Dick.
Oh! You were able to use the gray duct tape.
Run!
No!
Stay...stay and witness my moment of glory.
as I impregnate
the entire
population of Ohio
with my demon progeny.
Uh, even the men?
Okay, not the men.
Not little girls?
- No, no, not them.
What about elderly women?
- I don't think so.
What about women who are already pregnant?
Oh shut up, all of you!
Okay, so, apparently,
I won't be impregnating
the entire
population of Ohio,
but all fertile women
of childbearing age
who are not currently
pregnant, and that's a lot.
We're talking
lots of women here
who will soon
find themselves
now pregnant
by me.
It's as easy as one...
two...
three.
Yes !
Yes, that
will show him.
Not that I care...but er..
show who?
Your father, that unfeeling purple tube
who gave you life but wouldn't give you love.
You know nothing
of my father.
So why don't you
just shut up?
'Cause you
don't know him.
You don't have
to defend him.
You can't change the past.
You have to live in the now.
This is the '90s,
girlfriend.
All I ever wanted
was approval.
Is it any wonder
I wet my bed?
I'm with you.
Your father's got you all caught up
in his emotional red tape,
and you need to cut yourself free.
What would you say
if I told you
that your father
was here tonight?
Come on out!
What?
I'm just kidding.
He's not really here.
I think you need to go
home and face him.
Let the cycle
of pain end here.
You're so right!
That's it.
Let it out.
Let it all out.
Hey, guys.
- Dennis, what are you doing here?
Long story.
I got a weird vibe from you guys yesterday.
Something wrong?
We could have used you about an hour ago.
What happened?
I got mobbed by all these people.
I gotta find a better disguise.
Why don't you try women's clothing?
Tried it.
Doesn't work.
Dennis, could you
do us a favour?
Could you escort that
guy back to the home world?
Why not? I'm going that way anyway.
I've got a present for the big giant head.
What is it?
Big giant nose ring.
Come on, come on.
Thank you, all.
I feel that I've made
a big breakthrough here.
Well, remember...
nobody's going
to respect you,
until you learn
to respect yourself.
Bed wetter.
And, Dennis, could you dispose of this
while you're at it?
You did it!
Oh, no, not just me,
lieutenant.
I had a little help from my friends.
- Oh, stop.
Ricki lake, jerry springer, and Sally Jessy.
Now listen up,
everyone.
I know that in the past I worried
that we watch too much television.
Well, all
I can say is,
god bless television
and the many ways
in which television
enriches our lives.
From now on,
I order you
to watch
more television
than ever before.
aye, aye, sir!
What are we waiting for?
Tommy call the hut and get a pizza
Harry, warm up that television.
You got it.
....and, Sally,
go get yourself a decent pair of pants.
Oh thank you, sir.
Dr. Albright, the last time we were out here,
you said
something to me didn't you?.
You cared about me.
Is that still true?
Of course it's true.
Because over the last couple of
days, you've seen me at my worst.
That's what being
together is about.
If we're going to
have a relationship,
I want to have it
with all of you,
and that includes
the dark side.
You know, I care
about you, too.
You've made that
very clear.
So what do
we do now?
Well, it's been
a long night, but
why don't you just put
your arm around me,
and we'll look up
at the stars?
The stars, yes.
They look like lovers
locked in a celestial embrace.
Why don't you just
look at those trees?
The trees,
they look like lovers,
their limbs exploring
and fondling each other.
How about we look at
that couple in the window?
Wow! They're going
at it like trees.
Harry, is there
something different about you?
You've lost weight.
- Nope.
Is that a new shirt?
Oh, wait! You shaved off your beard.
- Nope. I never had one.
It's something.
You got
a haircut.
You're getting warmer.
www.tvsubtitles.net