You know, Mr. Randell,
we've only been out on six dates, but
already I feel comfortable with you.
You make me feel
so feminine,
which is ironic 'cause I
could snap your neck like a twig.
Thanks.
Oh, Mr. Randell.
Sally, do you want to
go back to my apartment?
Oh, I know what's
going to happen there,
We'll continue to kiss
and touch and kiss and touch
just like the movies, and
all of a sudden the scene ends,
and we're in the park
eating hot dogs and laughing.
That's such a Sally thing to say.
You're never
what I expect.
Yeah, like that time you
didn't have to pay for dinner
'cause I got us thrown
out of the sizzler.
Like that, yeah.
- But that's what you like about me, right?
Right, right, right, right, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
But now it's
starting to, um...
I don't know..
irritate me.
I'm not the perfect woman?
This close, really.
Just a couple, three,
four things you could change.
Maybe let me be in control
sometimes, just a little.
Well, you're going
to see a whole new me.
God, I hate that.
It's gone.
Oh... I should have
let you do that.
Whoopsy doodle.
Good-bye, basket
of kittens.
I can only pray that
next month's photo
will bring us a fraction
of the joy and whimsy...
...that you did.
Thank you,
bank of Rutherford.
What? That's a monkey playing golf.
I know, but he's
putting with a driver.
You never see
yourself clearly
until you see yourself
through your lover's eyes.
I am red freakin' hot!
Good for you.
And I'm a loud, destructive,
irritating pain in the butt.
Mr. Randell's not crazy
about me anymore, Dick.
Sally, don't tell me you're
failing at your relationship.
How could you?
I don't know.
I thought I had this
whole woman thing aced.
My performance has been
technically flawless.
He wants me
to change.
Well Sally, here on earth,
humans change for their lovers.
August and I always
accommodate each other's wants and needs.
For example, I stopped
wearing old spice,
and she's stopped telling
me to stop wearing old spice.
Oh...don't compare
my mature relationships
to your little
"tigerbeat" tryst.
Yeah, she's right.
Tommy, adults have far more
complicated problems.
Although, come to think of it,
Dr. Albright and I are adults,
and we have none.
I have struck gold with
her, grabbed the prize,
hit the jackpot.
Ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding!
You're a winner.
You didn't win.
You lucked out.
Love doesn't just
drop into your lap.
You've got to
force it there.
I don't know, Dick. I'm beginning
to wonder if I've got what it takes.
Of course you've got what
it takes. You're a warrior lieutenant,
and this is the battle of the sexes.
You can win it!
You know, I envy you.
Everybody in this house
has got somebody except me.
But when I do make
my love connection,
lady beware.
I change for no one.
Harry, you sound
like an idiot.
And that will
never change.
Tommy?
Let's say
I got into this
horrible car crash,
and I wasn't
really hurt,
but my hair fell out
from the shock.
Would you
still like me?
What about the eyebrows?
- Gone.
Yeah, sure, I'd still
like you, of course.
It would take a couple
of days to get used to.
Did you see the monkey?
- I saw the monkey.
What if my sight
went next?
I'm bald,
with no eyebrows,
and I can't see. Would
you still go out with me?
I'd stand by you.
Of course, you
wouldn't know it.
Why don't you go out and
find your own girlfriend?
With my schedule, where
would I find the time?
Oh, my god. I have got
the most brilliant idea.
You should contact
a video dating service.
You think?
- Yes! August, that's genius.
In fact, I bet they're open right now.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
There is a woman out
there with my name on her.
I will find her,
and nothing's
gonna to stop me,
unless I get distracted
by something shiny.
You look
lovely today.
Thank you.
And you like everything else about me, too?
- Yes.
Have I done anything to upset you?
- No.
Great, 'cause I'm really
trying to change for you, Kevin.
I have been so bad.
Have you decided
on a wine?
What do you feel like? Red or white?
I don't know. You decide.
We'll have
a bottle of merlot.
We're out of bread.
You want more bread?
I don't know.
You decide.
Is it cold in here,
or is it just me?
I don't know.
You decide.
Sally what are you doing?
I don't know, you decide.
If there's a problem here,
just say so.
Oh, there's no problem. I'm
just trying to please you.
Would you just drop this Okay?
Something's wrong, isn't it?
You like to play naive, but you
know exactly what you're doing.
Back up. Is naive a good
thing in a woman or a bad thing?
Are you trying to drag me
into some neofeminist debate?
I don't know.
You decide!
Fine.
I've decided.
Lunch is over.
Aw, listen, hun, there
are other fish in the sea.
I don't want to hear
about the specials, lady.
Hi, my name
is Harry Solomon.
My turn-ons are
sunshine, beach houses,
and baking bread
with my blouse off.
I wasn't rolling.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
All right, Harry.
This is all about just being yourself Okay.
I want you to just
relax, act natural,
and have fun, okay?
All right, here we go.
Okay.
I was brought up...
on the backstreets
learned to love
before I could eat
educated, ow-Ww!
At Woodstock
I'm a soul man!
Friday would be fine.
Yeah, I see no problem with..
I'll call you back.
Hello
- Heh-woh..
This is
Mr. Poopie bear.
Is this my wittle
bunny face doll?
Hi, Mr. Poopie bear.
Is wou happy?
I'd be happier if I was in a
big snuggle buggle with wou.
Snuggle, snuggle,
snuggle, snuggle,
snuggle, snuggle.
Oh.
- Heh-woh?
Heh-woh!
Oh, heh-woh.
Dick, I need to talk.
Well, sure.
- I just had a horrible lunch with Kevin.
Tell me what happened.
I tried to change for him,
and he still got mad at me.
I thought I'd done everything right.
- I'm sure you did.
What do you think he needs from me?
- Sally, sit down.
Honey, I'm a man,
and here's something
that I've learned.
How can I put this?
Men... are
completely incapable of..
talking about
relationships.
Here's two women.
Dump on them.
What does this
remind you of?
That time in Vienna.
That waiter,
those long walks.
- And this coffee.
Yeah.
What's going on?
Sally's tense, I'm taking her away
with flavored coffee.
Who am I kidding? I've
never even been to Vienna!
Well, this
is amaretto.
A broken heart
demands mocha mint!
I'm sorry.
You can't blame me...
Sally, what's wrong?
Look at these chairs.
I don't know if it's the
fabric, or the pattern,
or that Mr. Randell hates me,
or maybe we just need a couch.
The fabric is a bit loud.
- It's Mr. Randell.
Sally, please,
stop being so sad.
I'm not sad. I'm angry.
- Then why are you leaking?
I don't know!
It's a whole new leak.
My relationship with
Mr. Randell is broken.
No matter what I say to him, I can't fix it.
Stop saying,
and start doing.
You've got to
have more sex.
More? I've never had any, ever.
Ever?
Well...
there's the black fly
in your chardonnay.
You've got to start.
Sex fixes everything.
It's the neosporin
of Amore.
Uh... Dick, I don't
know about that.
August says it's very in
nowadays to save yourself for marriage.
Excuse me, could we please not
talk about marriage?
I can't even get through dinner with this guy.
Are you just going to give up?
He's just not happy
with me anymore Dick.
You think you can just walk
out of here and find another man?
I mean, really, just look at yourself.
- What?
Oh, those
comically long legs,
that blindingly shiny hair,
those unruly breasts.
All right!
I get the picture!
Sally, he seems
like a nice guy.
Maybe he'll do it
out of pity.
Are you sure?
Come here.
I know the thought of giving yourself
to someone is
at once frightening
and exciting, but embrace it.
Let go of yourself.
I mean, Dr. Albright dove right
in, and it was her first time.
Um... ahem..
coffee, anyone?
Look, maybe you need
a little something to uh..
to get you
in the mood.
I have a movie
that you can borrow.
"Homeward bound".
Is this supposed to help?
- Couldn't hurt.
The scene where the cat
falls off the wet log...
you'll notice that part of
the tape is a little worn.
Here.
Mocha mint for you.
Thanks, Tommy.
- Yeah.
You know, personally, I think
Dick's going a little
overboard with the whole thing.
You have to realize making love
to Mr. Randell is your decision.
You're right.
I'll do it.
I mean, what do I have to lose
except my virginity?
Good-bye, Mr. Hymen.
You're firing
our accountant?
Oh!
What do you look for
in the opposite sex, Harry?
Big bosoms...
and teeth.
Harry, you're so natural and so sincere,
not to mention your
features are positively chiseled.
Yeah yeah, I had no idea that
you prefer one large meal a day,
or that your favorite color is clear.
- Clear.
Tommy...
we have to talk.
- August, are you okay?
I'll be all right.
Fortunately, the hamster
didn't have rabies.
The hamster?
- The hamster that bit my nose off.
Yes, that's right,
Tommy,
my nose is gone.
So, I suppose you
want your ring back.
Uh... well, no.
Uh... can't they, like, stick it
back on somehow?
And that would be the only
way you'd continue to see me?
With my nose back,
that is?
No, I didn't say that. Uh...
uh... I guess we'll
just work through this
whole nose
thing together.
No!
- Surprise!
I never should have
doubted you, Tommy.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Hi, Sally.
- Hi.
I wasn't expecting
to see you.
Well, you know me,
little old
impulsive Sally.
I've decided we need to
take things to another level.
Sally, I think we have a lot of
issues that need to be resolved.
By another level,
I mean this.
We can put those issues on
the back burner for awhile.
I really want
to please you, Kevin.
You didn't have to stop
to tell me that.
This is going to fix
everything, right?
Well, it's going to fix
a couple of things.
If it's not going to fix
everything, why are we doing it?
Okay, this wasn't
my idea, Sally.
It wasn't mine, either.
It was my family's.
Your family convinced you
to sleep with me?
Yeah, we really think you're worth it.
What am I, some kind
of experiment?
You make that sound
like a bad thing.
Why does everything have
to be so difficult with you?
If I'm so damn difficult, why do
you want to have sex with me?
Because you're laying
on top of me.
That's your answer for everything.
- I give up.
You give up, good. That means I win.
- No, you don't win.
You win?
- I don't win, either.
No one wins?
- No.
This really sucks.
- Yes, it does.
I don't want to play anymore.
- Neither do I.
I think one of us
should leave.
And since this is
your apartment,
I guess that would be me.
Good-bye.
You know, I've...
never lost before.
I'm sorry.
Tell me
what happened.
I went over there to fix things,
and instead I ruined everything.
And the worst part is,
I'm still a virgin.
Oh, my god.
You're a virgin?
Yes, I know.
It's horrible.
No, no, no, no,
it's wonderful.
It is?
Yes. It's perfectly all right to
save yourself for the right man.
Like you did for Dick?
Yes.
The point is, breaking
up with Kevin was smart.
He wanted you to be
something you're not,
and you're fine
just the way you are.
I like you, Sally.
I didn't know
you liked me.
Well, I do.
You're a strong,
opinionated,
intelligent
young woman.
Unpredictable at times,
a little scary,
but, hell,
that's you.
That is me.
I like me, too, but why didn't Mr. Randell?
Well, he's just not the right guy
for you.
But you'll find someone.
I mean, just look at you.
Those legs, that hair..
Please! I've been dragged
through the muck enough today.
Just chalk this up
to experience.
Thanks, Dr. Albright.
You're so nice.
I always thought
you were such a bitch.
Oh, I am,
but, hell,
that's me.
Well, hello.
- Hi.
I gotta say,
I'm shocked.
That videotape
did not do you justice.
What videotape?
Oh.
That must be Lydia.
A little more knuckle hair
than I had hoped for, but..
a guy has got
to start somewhere.
You know what this coffee reminds me of?
That little cafe
in Amsterdam?
No, that I used the
coffee pot to drain the freon
out of the air
conditioner.
yeah.
It's a beautiful
morning, isn't it?
The birds are chirping.
The sky is blue.
You're awfully cheery,
considering you just lost your boyfriend.
I'm okay.
- You know, I feel sorry for you.
I mean, this afternoon,
I'm going shopping for drapes
with Dr. Albright,
and you'll be alone.
And tomorrow I'm taking Dr.
Albright to the recycling center,
and you'll be alone.
The way I look at it, Dick,
I'm embarking on an adventure.
The dating world is like
a huge food court for me,
and I can take my little
red tray anywhere I like.
I don't follow.
Well, you see, Dick,
it's like, with you,
you know you're going to
have grilled cheese every day,
day after day
after day
after day.
But me, tonight
I might go Italian,
tomorrow, Greek.
Next week, who knows?
Mexican, Chinese..
hot dog on a stick.
Hey, Harry,
come on, it's singles day at the mall.
Lock and load.
Grilled cheese.
Tommy,
We're late.
Enjoy your lunch.
Yeah, you, too.
God, I love
grilled cheese.
Yeah.
I could eat it
every day.
Day after day after day after day.
Hey, do you have
any sliced tomatoes?
Yes!
Yes, we do!
Perfect mate has hundreds
of compatible people for you.
Let's go.
My name is Sally,
and I'm strong, loud,
opinionated, and aggresive.
I'm a big, angry virgin,
and I'm happy about it.
Oh, and I also enjoy walking
barefoot in the sand,
and the poems
of Rod McKuen.
So, if you're
man enough for me,
let's make a date.
www.tvsubtitles.net