Oh, it's that thing again.
I have a name.
Football, I thought
they canceled that in January.
Well, guess they
brought it back.
I still don't see the
point. What's it all about?
Well from what I understand, they
try to kill whoever has the ball.
Those two guys in the
middle seem awfully... intimate.
Yeah, they've been going
at it the whole game.
Yeah, they should
just get a room.
Is there any upside?
Well, if you make it down to the big poles,
you get to dance.
Dance?
And if you're really good, you win a trip
to some fruitbowl.
But only the best
dancers make it.
See ya.
- Whoa. Where are you going?
I have Glee club practice.
- Glee club?
Yeah.
Oh I see, you've changed your mission.
Now you're researching
what it's like to be a girl.
For your information, Glee
club is not just for girls.
Yeah, it's also for Geeks and Nancy boys.
Hey!
Oh, he's dancing.
- This is obviously a waste of time.
Go do something with one of
your girlfriends. That's an order.
Fine!
Wait a minute.
I don't have
any girlfriends.
You and me, sister.
You and me.
They are so good.
They ought to be.
They've been playing
the same damn song
for the past
six hours.
They're a marching band.
Why don't they march?
Preferably
into the ocean.
Oh come on Dick,
don't tell me you're not excited
about the homecoming
weekend.
You know, between
the Pendleton badgers
and Ohio western
mustangs.
Oh, it's football.
Everywhere I turn,
it's football, football,
big, fat shmutball.
Well, forgive me,
Mr. Intellectual.
God forbid you should come
down from your ivory tower
for four quarters.
Four quarters? I don't care
what you pay me, I'm not going.
It's bad enough
there was a giant
papier maché rodent
blocking my parking spot
this morning.
You mean
Pendleton J. Badger.
What does
the "j" stand for?
Nothing.
Nothing starts with "N".
It's just a kooky initial.
"Q" is kookier.
Why isn't it
Pendleton Q. Badger?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask him?
Anyway, I got us
great seats.
It's not just
a sporting event.
It's a long-standing
tradition..
Pendleton versus
Ohio western.
You know, if you really
want to defeat them,
the secret is right in
front of you.. the giant badger.
It's a Trojan float.
Load our team in. We push
it up to their school walls.
And they say, "look.
A friendly giant badger.
Let's bring it inside."
Later, that night,
they fall asleep,
and "Whammo"!
It could work.
It's not
very sportsmanlike.
Well, I'll admit it
doesn't involve any dancing
or homoerotic
butt-Slapping.
Although, you never know what
goes on inside a giant badger.
"Bali hai"
"may call you"
"any night"
"any day"
"here am I"
"your special island"
"come away"
"Bali hai"
That was really, um...
better.
Everyone take a seat.
You know, you mustn't
be afraid to sing
from your heart, from
your mind, from your body.
Music is the sound
your soul makes.
Try it like this.
"You'll hear me
call you"
"singing through
the sunshine"
"sweet and clear as can be"
"here am I"
"come to me"
"here am I, come to me"
"here am I
come to me"
"Bali hai"
Okay, now who would like to
stand up and try it like that?
Tommy.
Nina, how's it going?
Well I'm kind of busy..
Great..um..Listen, um...
we're friends, aren't we?
- Yeah, sure.
Good, 'cause I've decided we're best
friends. You got a problem with that?
Uh... no.
- Thanks, Nina.
I finally have a
girlfriend. You're my first one.
Oh, Sally, I am?
Why? Is that weird?
- Oh, no.
No, no. it's tough making
friends with women.
You're telling me. I can barely stand myself.
So, uh... what do you
want to do now, girlfriend?
You want to go shopping
or talk about cramps?
Shopping.
- Ok
And, for Monday, I want
you to read and outline
chapters eight
through 24.
Except for chapter 12
which you will refute in a 10-
page treatise with illustrations.
Oh, come on.
Dr. Solomon, it's homecoming weekend.
- Yeah, the big game.
Oh, yes, I forgot.
God forbid that your intellectual
development should get in the way of
"the Big Game".
What could be more
important than "the Big Game"?
The fate of mankind
rests on the outcome of
"the Big Game".
Is he being sarcastic?
Oh, and I've got
news for you.
The "j" in Pendleton J.
Badger, it's meaningless.
Dr. Solomon, you've insulted my intelligence,
my religion,
and my family,
and that's okay.
But there's one thing you
cannot insult, and that's the badgers
because there's something you
don't even know about a badger, man.
When they dig holes,
they do it for a reason.
And their teeth, they're really
sharp when they're very young.
So I'm going to that game, and I
don't care if you fail me for it.
But you're
already failing.
Okay, as long as we
see eye to eye, then.
I just don't see
why you care so much about
a team that has
no chance of winning.
Why are you so passionate
about a lost cause?
Ohio western's
record is 6-1.
They're going to win, why
don't you root for them?
But we go to Pendleton,
we're the badgers,
and the badgers are us, we're
us, not them, they're them.
We're us with the..
don't you get it?
No, why didn't you
just go to western?
Because we...
choked on our S.A.T.s.
That skirt was really cute, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
And there were those shoes
that looked so great on you.
Thank you. So, this is where you live.
Oh, Nina, I'm glad you're
here, get me some coffee.
We're not at the office,
I'm here with Sally.
Yeah, that's right, she's
my friend, my best friend.
If she's going to get anybody
coffee, it's going to be me.
We'll see about that.
Nina,
who are you going to get
coffee for? Sally or me?
Okay, I have to go
home and feed my cat.
I didn't know you had a cat.
- I'm going to go buy one.
I'll call you in 10 minutes.
- Okay.
According to
the "Daily Badgerian",
over 45,000 alumni
will return to Pendleton
for the homecoming game.
You'd think that
after four years
they'd want to put the
experience behind them.
All I know is, my friend
Nina and I are going together.
We bought new outfits.
I think I'm going to go, too.
Really?
It's not that I'm being sucked in,
it's purely scientific.
And who knows?
Pendleton might win.
That would be
Da Bomb.
You heard me.
Da Bomb!
Dick, can I talk to you for a second?
- What is it?
I met this woman that I really
like, and I think she likes me,
but she's
a little older..
31.
But Tommy, do you really think a woman of
that age would be
interested in you?
Sure.
- Wow! Good job.
What's your first move?
I don't know, I want to take
her someplace special, but..
Excuse me.
What about August?
She'll understand. She's a good kid.
You know, there's a word
for what you're doing here.
Oh, right. It's called trading up.
Guys, guess what.
I went to the stadium
to see if I could get a
job as a vendor for the game.
Did you get it?
No. I didn't have enough
experience to sell hot dogs.
So they hired me
as a security guard.
hi.
- hi, Tommy.
Sunny d?
Thank you.
You know, Tommy,
you may think I haven't noticed,
but I really think you're
making a lot of progress.
I'm trying.
I know you are,
and it'll pay off, trust me.
I'm counting on it.
Oh Miss, Miss  Frost,
I got you something else.
It's a ticket to the
homecoming Pendleton game.
The Mustangs-badger game?
- Yeah.
That's very sweet,
but I couldn't accept a gift.
Oh no, but my dad, he gets
them for free.
He works
at the university.
They pay him squat,
so they give him perks.
Well, thank you,
Tommy.
Man on first.
Hey, buy us
a couple of beers?
Sure.
So, you girls going
to the big game?
We don't want to talk
to you. We're just broke.
This is so strange. I feel
this gnawing in my stomach.
I told you, this is not the place
for oysters Rockefeller.
No, it feels
more like tension.
I'm not sure, but I think I might actually
be nervous about the game.
Nervous? There's nothing
to be nervous about
because the badgers
are going to win!
Badgers beat the Mustangs?
In your dreams!
Go ahead, laugh now
'cause you're going to be crying tomorrow.
Oh I don't think so,
we're going to beat you a million to one!
Oh, yeah, right, right,
you're going to score
2,380 touchdowns a minute.
You're not going
to score anything.
These aren't the same badgers
you pushed around last year.
Oh, really?
Yeah. We've got a bunch of fifth year seniors,
and they bulked up
like crazy.
ooh!
Yeah! and they've got heart.
Yeah, one each.
Yeah.
- Yeah? Well, I got bad news for you, lady.
She's no lady, she's a
badger. Show them your teeth Mary.
Oh, yeah? Well, you're going down.
And you know why?
- Why?
Because badgers suck.
Badgers don't suck, they bite!
You guys are nuts.
Nuts like a Badger!
- Yeah!
Hurry!
What? What?
The western team bus
is just pulling up!
Oh, my god.
This glass is cold.
All right...
let's just drop
the axe there, little buddy.
I said drop it!
August, there's something
I have to tell you.
What is it?
Well I never thought I'd say these words,
but I'm in love with another woman.
Who is it Tommy?
It's Miss Frost.
Miss Frost,
the glee club teacher?
I'm afraid so,
it just happened.
I understand.
You gotta do
what you gotta do.
You're not
upset or jealous?
No.
Not at all.
I hope you two will be
very happy together.
Oh, there's something
I have to tell you, too.
I've been seeing
Val Kilmer.
Really?
Oh, I'm glad
you've got someone.
Whew!
We're very
pleased, attendance is 19,438.
We'll beat ya!
We'll eat ya!
We'll bite ya!
We'll claw ya!
We'll beat ya!
We'll eat ya!
Go, badgers!
Oh Mary, you were so right.
I feel great!
I just feel
tingly all over,
and that's not just
the lead paint talking.
You really went all out, didn't you?
- Yeah.
Bug and pitman did it. They
didn't want to, but I made them.
It goes all the way down, you know.
[You'Il be happy to know the
homecoming queen, is recovering nicely]
Tommy.
Oh, Miss. Frost.
What a coincidence.
"Corn Dog"?
Well, hello,
Mrs. Sumner.
How's the Dean?
- He's fine, thank you.
Excellent. I'm afraid I'm going to
have to look in that bag.
What?
Uh, uh...
Oh, binoculars, huh?
And exactly who is it that
you were planning on looking at?
Because around here we got a little
thing called right to privacy.
Okay, spread 'em, lady.
- Oh!
This is Solomon.
I need a canine unit.
[ We request that
you stop throwing things
at the Pendleton band]
Please, god, block
the extra point!
I promise I'll never ask
for anything else!
Screw Mary's
shut-In grandmother!
Just block that kick!
Yes, yes, yes!
Aw!
- Yeah!
There is no god!
What do you think
about your badgers now?
Up yours, buddy. Quick,
Dick, give him the finger.
Yeah!...Ooooooh!
What the hell's
the matter with you?!
I don't get it,
our guys don't advance.
They're in a constant
state of retreat.
I can't watch this
anymore.
23 get up here!
Get in there and remind
them we're going "that way".
23, get back here.
Excuse me, lady.
Hey, I'm the coach.
Oh, yeah?
So you're the idiot who's
running this team into the ground.
That's me, you got a problem with that?
Yeah, as a matter
of fact, I do.
Let me tell you
what you can do.
Take that pretty little body of
yours, and march it up to the bleachers,
and park it.
I was just about to say
the same thing to you.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
- Yeah!
Why are your guys
throwing the ball?
Your throwing guy's too
short to see over the fat guys.
You need to run left,
it's their weak side.
What do we do after that,
Miss Schottenheimer?
You do it again,
they won't expect it.
She's right, coach.
You shut up, or
I'll quit fixing your grades.
No.
No, no.
Oh, god, no!
Yeah, now that's a play.
You heard the lady.
If you get any more
of those good ideas,
you mark 'em down on this pad for me.
- Can do.
You're doing
a hell of a job.
Yeah!
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
Apparently.
[Pendleton recovers the fumble
on the Mustangs 30-yard line]
Okay, everybody!
Here, come on,
let's try another one.
Sine, cosine,
cosine, sine!
Three-point-one-four- one-
five-Nine! Now you try it.
sine, cosine, cosine, sine!
Three-point-one-four-
one-Five..
What? What happened? What happened?
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Let's keep it down!
All right,
who threw that?
who threw that one?
Okay..
[Pendleton wins, I
can't believe it. Pendleton wins]
Hey, Nina,
look what they gave me
for winning.
Ooh, steak sandwiches.
Miss. Frost, I'm pretty
sure we can work this out.
Tommy, there
is no we.
There can't be,
and I'm not just
talking legally.
Well, then why did you spend
all that time singing to me,
luring me like a siren
to my destruction?
I'm a singing
teacher, Tommy.
I sing.
I didn't mean to give you
the wrong impression.
Look, I think you'd be better
off with a girl your own age.
Yeah. So what's your mother look like?
Listen.
Can you hear them celebrating?
Ah, yes, The happy sounds
of cars overturning
and stores
being looted.
I love the smell
of burning rubber.
It smells like victory.
- A sweet victory.
You know,
it's amazing.
There we were,
thousands of total strangers
all pulling together,
trying to transfer
our collective strength
to a tiny group
of young men
that we didn't
even know.
We cheered for them,
and they won for us.
I've never felt such a
feeling of joy and camaraderie.
The only sad part is that
everyone couldn't share it.
Someone had to lose.
I feel for
the mustang fans.
Ah, screw 'em.
You're right.
Badgers rule!
- Yeah!
Okay, lovebirds,
party's over.
Let's, uh...
take it inside.
Mustangs give
you problems.
you grief.
Mustangs give
you trouble,
but the badgers
got the teeth.
We're bad
We're bad-gers!
Not beavers
Not hamsters
Not gerbils
Not lancers
We're bad
We're bad-gers!
www.tvsubtitles.net