Oh, hi, Nina.
Would you stand up on the
desk and adjust that vent?
It's blowing
right in my face.
Uh, yeah. I'll get
to that real soon.
Until then,
you just do it yourself.
Fair enough.
Oh hi, Dick. Would you adjust my vent?
With Nina
in the room?
Get up on the desk
and adjust my vent.
Oh, of course. Nina, please leave the room.
- No problem.
I can't reach it
from here.
Put your foot on the chair.
Are you sure?
It's.. it's wobbly.
Well, I'll hold it down.
- Well, all right.
A little further.
- Okay.
Ah, there, how's that?
- Hold on, I'll check.
My foot!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
It should have been you!
That should do it,
Dr. Solomon.
Well, that's unbelievable.
I feel no pain.
Well you may feel some
discomfort when the shock wears off.
No. Obviously, the fall has
made me impervious to pain.
You should go home and try to stay
off your foot as much as possible.
Keep it elevated,
keep ice on it.
Just use good judgment.
I have
excellent judgment.
Yep.
In fact, Nina,
hand me the staple gun.
Call me if you need me.
Oh, thank you, doctor.
I'Il take him home right now.
I can drive myself.
- Oh! Don't be silly! It's the least I can do.
I'll take you home, come
back here, pick up my car,
go to the drug store, the grocery
store, pick up anything you need.
Okay.
- I'll just bring the car around, okay?
Wha.. why is she
doing this?
Sit back and relax.
You're in pain,
she knows she caused it,
she feels guilty.
Wha.. why should she
be guilty? I'm not in pain.
I have a superhuman
threshold for pain.
And wha-lah!
Harry?
I'm in my room!
This isn't a room. This is a
shower curtain in a hall way.
Is that so? Then why
are my linens here?
Because your linens fell off
the washing machine.
I'm sick of sleeping
on the washing machine.
Oh, sure, a vibrating
bed impresses the ladies...
but I want my own room! Dick
said that I could have one.
No. Dick said that under no
circumstances could you have your own room.
Let's not quibble
over semantics.
Besides, you guys
have your own rooms.
I sleep in a storage space
behind Dick's chimney.
And my room is an uninsulated
alcove overlooking a toilet.
Room with a view...
rub it in.
Harry, you can't
sleep in the hallway!
Home wrecker!
What's wrong?!
She hurt me!
- It was an accident!
Oh an accident?
We can make accidents
happen too, lady.
Here, let me
elevate that foot.
No touching!
Ooh, what did my body
ever do to deserve this?
What did I ever do to you?!
Mary, turn it off!
Well I can't. The doctor said he
doesn't give drugs for a sprain.
But that's good news,
isn't it? It's not broken.
Well I heard sometimes a sprain
can be worse than a break.
Oh, is that one worse?!
- Yes, it is! Much worse!
Well, I said
I was sorry!
Can I fix you
something to eat?
Just fix my foot! I don't care
if I starve, just fix my foot!
I.. I'll get you
some ice.
Look at my foot.
It's one big boo-boo.
Dick, you sound pretty pathetic.
Is it pathetic
to sprain your foot,
worse than anybody ever in the
history of the world. Sally!
Sorry, Dick. But you know
nothing about earth pain
until you've been
a woman, okay?
One week every month, I feel like
I got a pair of pliers in my pants.
You got a boo-boo? I'm in
the national guard of pain.
What was I thinking? I am
so stupid! I am so stupid!
Mary seems to understand
my pain.
Dick?
I too understand your pain.
It's right here.
Ah, crespin,
two boxes?
Rupsin, johnny,
one box.
Solomon?
Fifteen?
You really think you can sell
fifteen boxes of chocolate?
Sell?
That's right.
After school, on the weekends..
until every bar of chocolate is sold.
No one's gonna wanna
buy this crap!
It doesn't even have raisins!
I'll give you raisins.
- Or Nougat!
I'm gonna nougat you, Solomon!
What do I get
for selling this crap?
You get the satisfaction
of helping to pay to
send the band
to Washington!
Now how's that for compensation?!
- Oh, all right, cool.
That's that.
I'm Gonna practise some ball passing.
I want half of you
over there,
half of you over there,
the other half
come with me.
I brought you some soup.
Let me just fix
this foot here.
Eat your soup.
- Okay.
Mmm, this tastes
sumptuous.
My mother used to make this soup
for me whenever I ..
Did she always serve it
this cold?
I'll heat it up some more.
- Thank you, Mary.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
- Oh...
no, but, could you also
get me some crackers?
Sure.
Are you okay?
- Oyster crackers?
Mary,
I just wanted to say,
I'm so happy that it was
you who hurt me so horribly.
All right. I'll be right back
with your soup and crackers.
Oyster crackers!
My god!
I have a magic foot!
Sally, what are you doing?
- Eating your soup.
Well, you can't do that!
- It's not that terrible.
You put a bunch of oyster
crackers in it, you can barely taste it.
Don't eat all of these!
Dick is lying in there hurt.
Well I'm fine and I'm hungry. Besides,
I'm not the one who broke his foot.
Sprained.
Have a little compassion,
Sally.
We're healthy.
We have to help him.
I say he's lame.
Shoot him.
And wha-lah!
Harry, what are you
doing in here?
Dancing to the natural
sounds of plumbing.
Okay, well, get out 'cause
I've got to use the bathroom.
You can't kick me
out of my own room!
Okay, pilgrim.
It's your funeral.
Oh, dear god!
No, no, no, no, no!
Hi, my name's
Tommy Solomon.
I'm selling chocolate bars to send
the high school band to Washington.
Hey, fat guy! Is this a dream or what?!
Candy door to door..
Hi, father.
I'm trying to sell
these chocolate bars,
so the high school band
can go to Washington.
And learn
about Christianity.
And... become priests.
Fine then.
They'll stay here in Rutherford
and worship Satan!
Now this is
what I call a room.
I've got everything
a man could need.
A piece of plywood, the gnome,
a very thin blanket,
no food,
and my new friend, the crow.
Hi neighbour!
Not exactly the house
warming gift I hoped for.
But you can't
pick your neighbours.
Tommy,
make me a sandwich.
You have a sandwich
right there.
I know, but Mary cut it
in half, and not diagonally,
and that hurts my foot.
Well, you can chalk it up to me
being a teenager, but I just don't care.
Mary won't be back from the
colouring book store for half an hour.
You know, this day
has been hell!
I think I met
one nice guy all day.
Well, how many bars did he buy?
Oh, none. But he sold me
this nice set of encyclopedias.
Tommy?
Tommy, it's an emergency!
I need the remote!
Sally.
God, what?
- I can't reach the remote.
It's right there!
- But I can't get to it, Sally.
So?!
- Oh, lieutenant
Do you know what it's like
to feel helpless?
To be robbed
of your freedom by an injury?
To be a burden
on your family?
Oh, god,
how you must hate me!
I'm.. experiencing
the strangest sensation.
I feel bad
that you feel bad and..
even though I know
it'll be annoying,
I just can't seem to fight it.
Dick, can I get you anything?!
Make me a sandwich
and cut it diagonally.
Okay.
Oh, you forgot
the remote!
My foot!
It's better!
No!
Go on, doctor.
Give it to me straight.
The ankle looks great.
Are you sure?
- Yes, you're all better.
Don't you think you should
break it and set it again
just to make sure
it heals properly?
No.
Doctor, you don't understand.
The moment I sprained
that foot,
my life went
from VCR to VCR plus!
You've got to help me!
Dick?
The ankle is healed.
I won't be treated this way
by your heartless H.M.O.
I demand control
of my treatment options!
Because it's not the length of our time here
that matters, it's the quality of our lives!
And if you're not qualified
to break my foot,
then by god, I'll find
a doctor who will!
So you're telling me that in
this colourful, monochrome wrapper
is a bar of chocolate?
- That's right.
Delicious chocolate.
Now, how far would you walk
for a bar of chocolate?
To get a bar of chocolate, or at
the request of a bar of chocolate?
To get.
- Oh, 53 miles.
Well, now you can have
chocolate in your own home.
In my own home?!
That's right. Now, how much
would you pay for that?
For my own home,
or for a bar of chocolate?
Bar of chocolate.
- Ah..
Well, we tried.
Owww!
Excuse me,
my friend hurt his leg.
Could you help us out
and buy a chocolate bar?
Oh, Nina...
I can't tell you
how good it is
to be among people
who brush their own teeth.
You're not
brushing his teeth?
Do I have any messages?
One o'clock, Dr. Solomon called. He
wants to know where you are.
Oh, god.
- 1.05, Dr. Solomon called again.
His foot feels hot. Doesn't know if
that's a good thing or a bad thing.
1.12, Dr. Solomon called. He's hungry.
Can you make him a personal pan pizza?
1.17. Dr. Solomon called.
Wants to know if you've forgotten
that you were the one that hurt his foot.
Hello?
No, you have
the wrong number.
Oh, your foot hurts?
Have you tried
hitting it with a hammer?
I've cold called, I've direct mailed.
I can't afford a pay-per-view
special.  Nothing works.
This isn't my problem, buddy.
Well, just help out an incredibly
screwed kid and buy a chocolate bar.
If I bought every stupid
thing that came to my door..
Tommy, forget it.
The guy's not buying anything.
..I'd be living up to my pledge to
help every kid who came to my door.
Cash or check?
- How 'bout both?
Oh, come on!
That is just so cheap!
God!
I really want some candy!
What is that?
- 93.9, the wave.
The best of the '70s,
'80s and today.
Well, I know what it is,
but where is it coming from?
From my new tree
entertainment system!
Oh, look!
The squirrels are getting it on
to Marvin Gaye.
So it's nice up there?
- Only the best room in the house.
See you later, Dick.
- But.. but..
wha.. wha..
oh, Sally?
Thank god you're here.
You know how I hate
asking for your help,
but could you just please
do me this one little favour?
- What?
I want to see Harry's
cool tree house. Carry me?
No way.
Oh, please, Sally?
There's so little joy in my life.
- No.
But Sally, I ask you
for so little!
Can you just once..
- No!
You're right.
What good is a tree house visit
when death is only moments away?
What?
- Tonight's meal may be my last.
And you know
what that means?
Mexican night!
I think I hate you, Dick.
Tommy, Harry! We gotta go back to the store!
It's Mexican night!
- Oh great!
You know what is so weird,
Dick?
I don't know if it's, uh,
what you're saying or...
how you're saying it,
but, um...
all that stuff that used
to make me want to help you,
well, now it's just
pissing me off!
Oh, and Sally?
- What?!
Corn tortillas,
not flour.
Si, Señor.
No way!
You guys!
You gotta see this!
Ohh, I should have known.
What are you looking at?
That bastard!
There goes Mexican night.
- Oh, it's Mexican night all right.
Mexican prison night.
I say we stick a bucket
on his head,
and whack him with a bat like a piñata
and we don't stop till candy comes out!
Tommy, Harry, let's go!
- Wait a minute, Sally!
What about me? He's taken
advantage of me worse than any of you.
He made me cut up his food
and feed it to him.
He made me sing to his foot!
He made me take
his temperature...
the hard way.
Besides, I don't think you
have what it takes to get even.
I have a metal bucket
and three softball bats.
That's a pretty good start.
Ooh, oh. Hi.
The, uh.. the ladder
appears to be disconnected.
Funny how that happened, eh?
That must be painful
up there on that ladder
with that terrible,
terrible sprain.
Ah, yeah...It.. it hurts a lot.
Hey, Dick, how did you
get up there?
Well, uh...
you know how it is.
No, tell us.
- Could one of you just, uh...
grab the end of the ladder
and pull it in?
Gee, I don't know.
It's awfully far. My arms hurt
Well...
why don't you let me down
and I'll have a look at them?
Admit it, Dick!
You're a liar!
you manipulated us!
You tortured us!
It just happened!
It's nobody's fault!
Okay, okay, okay!
It's my fault.
You fortitude just felt so good.
So appropriate.
I'm sorry.
That's better.
Wow, now that's
gotta hurt.
Not as much as that.
All right!
Everybody line up
into a circle.
Solomon!
- Sorry I'm late, coach.
Hey, anybody who can sell 15 boxes of
chocolate in my class can be a little tardy.
What's your secret,
champ?
Well,
you know I...
kept thinking about
sending the band to Washington.
Well, they're gonna owe you some real
thanks when they get back next week.
Well..they're coming back?
Well, yeah.
All right,
which one of you tools
sold enough chocolate
to buy them a return ticket?!
Eh? Hey, you look at me when
I'm talking to you! Come here!
Guilt is like a belly button
that doesn't even collect lint.
It's a wasted emotion that just
nags and nags and nags and nags..
until Dick falls
out of the tree.
Maybe guilt is some kind of
ancient guidance system.
A stealth emotion
designed to make people
help each other out
even if they don't want to.
If I could just break that code,
I could get you all to serve me.
You don't need guilt
to get anyone to serve you.
We proved that
when we were selling candy.
All you need to do
is remind people they like sex.
Oh. Wouldn't it be scary if
sex and guilt were connected?
Sex and guilt
connected!
Harry, you're an idiot!
- I know.
Dick, I've been watching TV and I
think you can walk without these crutches.
No, I can't.
This man says
that he cannot walk,
but I say
that he can.
I say I feel the spirit
in Dick Solomon.
Now stand up and walk.
- But my foot is broken.
Oh, foot's broken.
Those are just words!
Now deep inside
and walk, my brother!
Walk!
- Aah!
Stay in bed, my brother.
Stay in bed.
www.tvsubtitles.net