Dick, I need a favour.
- Uh, not now, Tommy.
I'm doing research. I'm finding out
what happens when the spit hits the fan.
No, Dick, look,
this is important.
Take a look at this.
- Actors on acting?
Yeah. You know how you're
always trying to find new ways
to explore
the human feelings?
Ah, "Using Your Emotional Memory",
"The search for emotional truth
will stimulate
your emotional juices".
"Emotional juices"?
I love my juices.
This is exciting!
Yeah, I knew you'd like it, that's why I
volunteered you to direct our school play.
Me, direct? As in, control?
- Yeah, it's Romeo and Juliet.
August wants to play Juliet, and if
you direct, you can cast me as Romeo.
I'll do it!
That's so great, 'cause there
are some major make-out scenes.
And also some really
powerful emotional stuff.
I get to die.
I can just see it now
on the Marquee..
"Dick Solomon directs
a Dick Solomon production
of Dick Solomon's
Romeo and Juliet."
Yeah, whatever.
- Hmm.
"Naturally, an actor must
play the truth of the scene,
and not indulge
in emotion for its own sake."
Well, anyone knows that.
I didn't know you were interested in acting.
Well, yes I am, but what I
really want to do is direct.
I'm not saying
that I couldn't act.
I could be very convincing.
Light comedy..
horror..
tragedy.
Morning.
- Look, Mary!
I'm distraught!
Or am I?
Okay. You have a registered letter.
- Oh, what is it?
Damn, damn, damn, damn!
I owe fifteen hundred
dollars in parking tickets.
So they finally
caught up with you.
Guess I'll have
to dip into my savings.
Oh, no, no, I couldn't bear to
let you do that. I'll pay them.
You will?
- No. I'm acting!
Lo, and resolve itself
Dick!
Dick, guess what?
Ms. Dubcek's give me
all her old junk.
Yeah, I've got some friends
dropping by I haven't seen in 10 years,
and I'm cleaning out
the place.
There's some really great stuff in here.
Dr. Solomon,
if you want to come down,
I'll let you rummage through my tchotchkes.
- Oh, I'm..
I'm flattered Mrs. Dubcek, but
I think of you more as a friend.
What are you watching?
- Oh, it's Hamlet with Lawrence Oliver.
I've watched it
three times already.
Huh.. I like the way
he makes his voice
go up and down like that.
- I know.
It makes everything
he says sound so...
fruity?
No, important!
- Oh.
Hey, guys. You still
watching that stuff?
It's not "stuff,"
it's Hamlet.
Yeah, but why do they have to talk
that way? I can't follow the story.
Hamlet? The story is as old as time.
Pretty-boy son has a rich
daddy and a good-looking mommy.
The uncle knocks off daddy, marries mommy,
and he cuts pretty boy
out of the action.
So junior goes crazy
and he kills them all.
Not a pretty story,
but there it is.
Isn't that the plot
to the lion king?
Oh, please!
I need your help, Don. I'm in a bit of a scrape.
- Figures.
Dames like you
always attract trouble.
I got another parking ticket.
Can you fix it, Don, or...
am I leaning
too hard?
Go ahead
and lean, baby.
Don'll make
the ticket go away.
What?
You can make parking tickets disappear?
Of course he can. Don
has connections downtown.
Why..I have a friend who has
some parking tickets.
I can't always..
- Don can fix it, right?
Well, uh..
- Right?
Sure.
- Oh, this is just great!
Oh, I can't wait
to tell Mary.
Some of you
will not be cast.
Those will be
the lucky ones.
Over the long and grueling
rehearsal period,
I will be your director,
your teacher, your mentor,
your mother, your father,
your lover!
My assistant, Nina,
will read your names.
Nina?
- Okay, um,
Timothy Mafferty..
he's reading Mercutio.
"True, I talk
of dreams, which..
yes, yes, yes,
of course.
But have you
tried it like this?
Make your voice go high,
and then suddenly
bring it down.
Here. "True, I speak of
dreams which are but children
of an idle
brain,
begot of nothing
but vain fan...
...tasies.
From now on, I want
everyone to try to speak that way.
Oh, and use
your hands a lot.
We're acting.
Remember that.
He was touched by an anvil.
Remind me never to ask
you for another favour again.
You weren't right for the role.
- Hey, How'd the audition go?
I lost the part. The director
didn't think I was good enough.
You were good. You had
delivery, presence, timing.
You just didn't have that
indefinable something extra.
I was just trying to score some points
with my girlfriend. Is that too much to ask?
Romeo and Juliet
is a Shakespearian tragedy,
and has nothing to do with a
horny teenager and his girlfriend.
Go ahead,
Dr. Albright.
Hello, Don. Dr. Solomon thought you
might be able to help me with this.
Well, I have been known
to bend a few..
You have fifteen hundred dollars in fines.
And, "Poof", they're gone.
I can't "Poof" this many tickets.
One more, and she'd
be in handcuffs.
I was going to pay them.
- What happened?
I didn't.
Well, maybe if you got
a lenient judge,
he might reduce
the fine.
Your court date is
on the 27th.
Twenty-seventh.. oh.
Judge Debelko.
Sounds bad. Is it bad?
- It's bad.
You'd be better off
with Judge Conti.
Now, when I go to court,
should I apologise
to Judge Conti
or just show some remorse?
Actually, it might be helpful
if you'd show some cleavage.
He can't be serious.
- Trust me.
We're gonna paint your face and hike
your puppies.
I know what I'm doing, right Don?
"O Romeo, Romeo,
wherefore art thou"
yes, yes.
Very lovely.
Darling, what are you playing?
Fear, love, lust?
Because the audience
is playing boredom.
I'm playing Juliet,
and it's really hard for me
to concentrate when you..
Props? Where's props?
What?
This candlestick is
18th-century English.
Shakespeare was English.
- True.
But the play
is set in Verona.
Please, Tommy, I'm struggling to
wring a performance out of this
ragtag company of mannequins
from the junior miss department.
I can't do your job too. In the
future I suggest you leave it lay.
Now, everyone watch once
again as I act out the play
in its entirety.
Nina, Nina,
read me in.
Curtain rises.
A big, pompous blowhard
flounces
on to the stage.
Listen, I'm really sorry
you had to be the prop guy,
'cause, you know, if you were cast
as romeo,
we could have done
some serious making out.
We.. we could make out
right now.
With the prop guy?
Ha! Sorry.
Hey, what you making?
An authentic renaissance sleeping potion.
Now I just have to find an
15th-Century Italian vial.
Oh, Well, I find
Galileo "Vile".
Well, this is
the final box.
I am beat.
- Oh, thank you. You want some juice?
Oh, please. I'll have to introduce
you to my friends when they drop by.
They're lovely,
very nice.
There's Diane
and her husband..and Jimmy.
Jimmy's an old flame. I
knew he'd come back for more.
Come back
for more what?
I said, "come back
for more what"?
What happened?
Oh, great! You let her drink the prop?
Well, at least
we know it works.
I beg for justice, which
thou, prince, must give.
Romeo slew Tybalt,
Romeo must not live.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
You are Lady Capulet.
Your kinsman Tybalt has
been killed! He's dead!
You're asking for justice, not extra
pickles on your happy burger. Justice!
You're supposed to act!
Now bleed! Just act! Now act!
I can't act, Dr. Solomon.
- Yes, you can!
I can't..
I can't act.
Do your lines.
Now, now!
I beg for justice,
which thou, prince,
must give.
Romeo slew Tybalt,
Romeo must not live.
I want everyone to take
a good look at Cheryl,
because Cheryl,
is an actor.
Hello?
Damn it, voice mail.
Hello, Dr. Albright?
This is sergeant..
this is a friend..
with a message.
Don't come to court today.
There's been a change in plans.
Next,
Dr. Mary Albright?
Here your honour.
Sally, didn't you
get my messages?
What messages?
They switched judges.
I've been calling all morning.
You're charged with fifteen hundred
dollars in outstanding fines.
How do you plead?
All I can say
is I'm so sorry,
and I throw myself
on the mercy of the court.
Really.
Dr. Albright, will you
please approach this bench?
You have a very big bench.
I don't know what this
little charade is about.
We're trying to influence you.
- Sergeant, please remove that woman.
Doesn't he know who you are?
You have a gun, Don! Use it!
Dr. Albright, you "have"
influenced this court.
Really?
I am fining you the full amount,
plus court costs,
plus five hundred dollars for contempt.
Next.
But your honour..
- Next.
Thank you so much!
The one time that I can help the woman I
love, and your friend Don falls through!
It was just an ironic
twist of fate. Don't blame Don.
I don't want you hanging around that
police station any more, you hear me?
Fine, I'll go to his place.
- Oh, no, you won't.
Oh, yes, I will!
You hold it right there,
I'm not finished with you yet.
Oh, uh, hey, Mrs. Dubcek,
would you mind..
My god, she's dead!
Oh, what is it?
Oh, her.
She's not dead.
- But she's cold. She's not breathing.
Oh, you guys.
She's fine.
She drank the potion.
The sleeping potion?
From Romeo and Juliet?
Well, guess we can take her
downstairs until she comes to.
Here, Harry, get her feet.
Sally, help with the door.
Hi, baby, it's us!
Hi!
- Get her inside! Get her inside!
Who are those people?
Oh, well, um, it's Diane,
and her husband and Jimmy,
an old flame
coming back for more.
This is just great!
Didn't you make an antidote?
Hmm, is there one
in the play?
If they see her like this, the
spit is really gonna hit the fan.
What are we gonna do?
- Wait! I have a brilliant idea.
Harry, did you know that in a
theater of Shakespeare's day
the women's roles were played by men?
- Really?
Yeah, and they also tied up
bears and threw rocks at 'em.
It's the role of a
lifetime Harry, an actor's dream.
Come on, let's get her in the bathroom.
- I don't want to!
Dick, you can't pass Harry off
as Mrs. Dubcek! They'll know!
Ah! You forget, they
haven't seen her in over 10 years.
Besides, Harry has a secret weapon.
- What?
A great director!
Hello?
Anybody home?
Uh, no, nobody's here. Why don't
we go into the living room, okay?
Yeah, this way. Right,
move along. Faster.
Okay, right there.
Why don't you take a seat,
make yourself comfortable?
I can't believe
she got somebody
to pay rent
for this crap-hole.
Yeah, every month.
- Yeah,
and we just love Mrs. Dubcek.
- Ohh.
Even more
since the accident.
"Accident"?
Yes. Changed her, considerably.
Uh, and, uh, she refused
the estrogen therapy, yeah.
But don't mention it to her.
She's very sensitive.
Is there a bathroom around..
- No!
We use the one at the gas station.
- Yeah.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Talk to them.
What is taking so long?
Whoa, mama!
Do you mind? An
actor needs time to prepare.
Dick, I don't think I can do this.
It's show time! Now, let's go.
Oh, and Harry,
remember,
you're going out there a
youngster, but you're coming back a star
Now let's go.
Mamie honey!
Well,
I see you've met
my tenants.
Oh, uh, we love
Mrs. Dubcek.
Hi, Mamie.
- Lovely tattoo. Very nice.
I don't blame you
for being distant,
not after what
we went through.
She and Jimmy
used to be engaged.
Oh, you're Jimmy!
She mentioned you
just the other evening.
I just wanted
to say thanks,
for kicking me out
all those years ago.
That was the wake-up call that
finally got me off the sauce.
Aww!
- That's so sweet.
Forgive me?
Sure.
Stop it, stop it,
stop it!
I'm sorry. She had
something crawling up her chin.
Why don't you all
go downstairs,
and, uh, get
reacquainted?
Mrs. Dubcek,
there we are.
Bye, bye, now. Bye, bye. Bye, bye, now.
Manhandle me again,
and you'll answer to Jimmy.
We are breathing.
All right!
Which one of you
jamokes is Solomon?
That would be I.
- You're out.
Out? Who are you?
- I'm coach Mafferty.
My wife's with the P.T.A.
And there's a lot of complaints
that these kids are coming home
with low self-esteem, and they're
wetting their beds and stuff like that.
So you're looking at the new director!
- This is unacceptable.
Sorry, Spielberg,
you're out.
No, no.
Do not weep for me.
I humbly quit the stage.
No, no,
no tears.
The theater is
a cruel Mistress.
Adieu, adieu.
Remember me.
Okay kids,
let's huddle up.
Alright let's back it up to, "I pray
you good Mercutio, let's retire".
Okay, now, who's
playing Mercutio?
Uh, coach Mafferty,
if I may,
I think there is someone
here who can play Mercutio.
Aah!
I am hurt!
Aye, aye,
a scratch, a scratch.
Marriage is enough.
'Twill serve.
Ask for me tomorrow
and you will find me
a grave
man.
Romeo, brave Mercutio is dead.
A plague o'
both your houses,
for they have made
worms' meat...
of me-e-e!
Romeo..
- I have it,
and soundly too.
Your... houses!
I'm dead now.
Well, here it is.. the
review in my high school paper.
You've got a review?
Ah, ha, ha ha!
"Dick Solomon's
over-the-top performance,
gave new meaning
to the word 'Tragedy".
I have redefined
my art,
and so I retire.
- No!
No, no, please, please. To go any
further would jeopardize the mission.
Tommy, hang up
my codpiece.
Dick, I'm not your
prop lackey anymore.
Besides, as of next month, your
codpiece turns into Sancho Panza's hat.
I wonder
what Don's doing?
"Don". I never want to hear the name
"Don" mentioned in this house again.
Now, that's
an order!
Hi, there.
What am I doing
on the roof?
Don't you know, we were about
to ask you the same thing.
You should be inside,
Mrs. Dubcek, let us help you.
Oh, Don. Don?
Why should the name "Don"
make Dick so angry?
Sally?
- Who's there?
I would tell you, but my name
is so offensive to your family,
I dare not
speak it aloud.
Don, if they found you,
there's no telling
what they'd do to you.
I'm okay.
I have night's cloak
to hide me
from their eyes.
And if thou love me,
let them find me here.
My life were better
ended by their hate,
than death prolonged
wanting of thy love.
Wow, that's
so romantic.
Ah, well,
I wrote it myself.
I've asked you back here
for a reason.
You seem like an intelligent woman,
so I'm going to make you an offer.
I will lower the fines,
remove the contempt charge,
and eliminate the court
costs on one condition.
You have to promise me
that you will spend
the weekend with me
at a hotel in Chicago.
The Ambassador East?
- The Sheraton.
No.
www.tvsubtitles.net