44 across, "men are from
Mars, women are from..."
let's see, five letters
starting with V.
Ah! "Vegas".
Dick! Dick, look who
I met outside.. Michel.
Michelle?
You're a girl?
No, he's from France.
- Hello.
Michel asked me to take
a picture of him
standing next to that statue
of general Rufus Putnam.
Oh did you make him put his
finger in the general's nose?
Oui.
"Oui."
That means yes.
Mary! Nina!
This is Sally's delightful
new French guy, Michel.
Ah. Mary, Nina.
Your names could be French.
I took three years
of French in high school
and I can't remember
a thing.
No no no,
I am in America,
I am the one
who needs to learn, hmm?
Okay.
Oh! Michel, how do you say "
nice to meet you" in French?
Enchanté.
- Enchanté.
Okay, how do you say, five,
five, five, o, one, eight, nine?
Cinq, cinq, cinq,
zéro, Un, huit, neuf.
Okay, you might want
to write that down.
Nina!
Michel,
we should be going.
Yeah, it was fantastic
to meet you all.
Oh, yeah. Oh.
He is so charming.
Ow! Oui!
On my foot I have a big,
painful, oozing blister.
A blister!
So Michel, what time is
it in France right now?
Uh... 4:00 A.M.
Wow, it's so early.
You have been
so wonderful to me, Sally.
I never meet
a woman like you.
And you never will again.
You are not only
beautiful, you are kind..
but more beautiful right?
- Yes.
So, um, how long are you
planning on staying in Rutherford?
Sally, I.. I love this place,
I would like to stay very much,
but your government
is... not so nice.
Except for Abraham Lincoln.
Yes, nice man,
very very nice man.
But...
your country is not safe
for someone like me.
Uh... there is only one
safe way for me to stay here,
kind girl.
I need to get married.
Sally?
Would you marry me?
Yeow! Damn!
Hot diggity dog!,
Oh man, oh man, oh mama!
It's just that... nobody
has ever asked me that before.
Oui.
- Oh!
You're what?!
- I'm getting married.
Why are you doing this?
Two reasons, I'm a woman,
and he asked me.
Lieutenant, aren't you
forgetting something?
You're right, the wedding announcement!
No no! The mission.
Dick, this is my mission. It's
what women are supposed to do,
get married, have babies, hire
total strangers to raise them,
and then wonder
where they went wrong.
Very true.
It happened so quickly. How
did he know it was time to ask?
He's a man,
men know these things.
But I'm a man.
Am I missing something?
You? Never.
- No flies on you.
Dick, trust me,
I know what I'm doing.
Besides, I've dated
more than any of you.
But by no stretch
of the imagination
have you been
the most promiscuous.
Trust me, high commander,
Michel's a great guy.
Plus he's loaded, look.
He's giving me $5,000, he
wants to marry me so badly.
2,000 upfront and the rest
when the deal's done.
As a gift?
- No no, Tommy...
this is what's known
as a dowry.
It's an old-world marriage
custom and Michel is from there.
Maybe if we hold out,
he'll throw in a goat or two.
And the best part of everything is
I get to have a wedding, you know?
Big white dress,
long veil, crappy band.
Ah. It will be a day
I'll always remember.
Okay, there's work
to be done!
Harry, I want you to find me
something old, something new,
something borrowed,
something blue, go!
Tommy! Get me a deal on flowers!
- Flowers!
Dick! Your job is to sit back,
and just get overwhelmed
by the whole process, okay?
Hi, can I help you
with something?
Yeah, my sister is getting
married, she needs flowers.
Ah, anything in mind?
- Cheap.
Ah. You know what?
I have a sample bouquet from
a wedding we did yesterday.
Something like this maybe?
Yeah yeah, that's nice,
but it doesn't really uh...
pop, you know what I'm saying?
I was thinking something
maybe a little more like this,
and maybe a spray of these..
oh, these are great.
Could you hand me
the ribbon back there?
No, the ivory.
Let's see.
Now this rocks.
Young man, you have
quite a knack for this.
Flowers eh? Cool.
She's getting married.
- Oh, that's so romantic!
She just met him!
- I wish I'd have met him first.
Dick, do you have
a problem with this?
No, why should I? Sally's
fulfilling her purpose as a woman.
Oh, please, Dick,
not every woman
feels her life is incomplete
until she got a man.
Well, hasn't your life
been better since you met me?
Yes. But we've taken the time
to learn about each other.
And we've learned a lot
We've been together over a
year, we're not getting married.
Certainly not.
- We've never even discussed it.
You never brought it up.
- Neither have you.
We're talking
about it now.
I have a phone call to make.
- Me too.
Whoa, beautiful flowers.
- Oh, thanks, I arranged them.
Really?
You did a great job.
Ah-ah, don't touch. You don't
want to over-bunch the vase.
Each flower has to be
allowed to have its own moment.
Oh, yeah, moment.
Erm, my uncle wally owns
a flower shop in Florida.
His roommate Jasper,
helps him run it.
So, you think he'll
pass it down to his kids?
No, I think the legacy stopped
right there in south beach. Sorry.
See, this is the third set of
little people you've sent me,
and once again they bear no
resemblance to me or my future husband.
Get it right!
Sally! I got it,
everything you asked for.
Oh, what a relief!
Something old..
a radial, courtesy
of the alley.
Something new..
a tub of Vaseline with
an unbroken seal. Sweet!
Something borrowed..
a cup of sea salt
from Miss Dubcek.
And finally, the piece
de resistenance..
something blue..
a lifesaver!
Minty.
That's perfect, Harry.
Ooh! Those are beautiful!
Oh thanks, I was tempted
to use willow branches,
but they seemed
a bit stark.
You're very artistic.
- Yeah, I'm sure that's the word.
Hello, Sally.
- Hey.
I heard the news.
Wow!
It happened so suddenly.
Cut to the chase, Mary.
Sally, she thinks you're crazy.
What?!
- No, I didn't say that.
It's.. it's just
that I'm concerned.
I want the best for you and
this all happened so quickly.
Mary, you are
so transparent.
You're jealous.
- What?
You are.
- You are! - Yeah.
You wanna get married too.
- You do!
Well sure, when I'm ready.
- And you don't think I'm ready?
Well, I just think
you should wait.
Until when? I'm middle-aged and I
have to walk out of the bedroom
backwards so my husband
won't see my ripply butt?
Oh, stop.
Mary!
That's what you do!
Okay. I guess this was
none of my business.
You're doing it again!
I'm sorry I even tried.
No wait, Dr. Albright.
Wait wait wait!
Look. Look, just.. here.
Sit down here, okay?
It's just that I got so...
damn arrogant, you know,
that I got proposed to.
I mean, it's like I finally got
something I can lord over other women.
And that's not right, no.
- No.
I want you to be happy
for me, Mary.
I'd like you to be
in my wedding.
Bridesmaid?
Better. I want you to
be my maid of honour.
My bitter old maid
of honour.
Gentlemen, how do you know
when it's time to get married?
Right when that little
stick thing turns blue.
I mean, do you get married when the
relationship stops to be about sex
and starts becoming deeper?
Deeper than sex?
I just don't know
if I'm ready.
Dr. Albright is tightening the old
matrimonial chokehold, isn't she?
Oh I wish. Unfortunately
she wants to get married.
I guess I'm just
gonna have to ask her.
Well why don't you buy yourself some
time by giving her an engagement ring?
A ring?
- Sure, something big and showy, you know.
It proves how much you care for her and
that way you can drag it out for years.
So I just tag her,
put her on the shelf,
so I can pick her up whenever I
want like.. like human layaway?
I like it.
I like that one.
- Hmm, it's very you.
Sally, I've been
an insensitive clod.
Yeah, I'm used
to that by now.
No no. Not to you,
to Dr. Albright,
which is why I've decided
to ask her to marry me.
Good for you.
Thank you.
And as high commander,
my wedding is
more important than yours.
So I get to go first.
What?!
You horrible,
horrible man!
Why do you wanna rain
on my parade?
The one chance
I get to feel special,
and you want
to take it away from me!
I want to be the bride!
Me, bride!
I.. I'm sorry, forgive me.
I'm being selfish.
You're right.
You should go first.
You've already ordered your cake and...
I haven't even popped
the question yet.
Now stop crying.
There's my girl...
and what a big girl
you are.
And soon I'll have to
give you away to another man.
And what a pretty bride
you'll make.
"Where are you going,
my little one, little one"
my baby, my own"
"Turn around
and you're tiny"
"turn around
and you're grown"
and you're a young wife"
"with babes of your own".
To you, Dr. Solomon.
- To me.
You are a great American.
In France, it would be
very hard to find a man,
that would accept money
for his sister.
And it was
impossible in Wisconsin.
Hmm, yeah.
She's all yours now. I bet you
can't wait to sleep with her.
Pardon?
- You know, the big night, la nuit grande.
No no no,
professor Solomon,
this is a legal arrangement
only, I will not touch your sister.
No, You have to!
She's dying to!
Are you positive?
Of course, it's like those
sneakers ads say, "just do her".
You are a very
strange family...
but strange in a way...
I can accept, huh?
Salut!
- A votre santé. - D'accord.
Oh, don't push.
I'll buzz you in.
Wait to push.
I'll buzz, then you push.
Listen to me!
Wait for the buzzer
to stop!
And they wonder why old
downtown Rutherford is dead.
You can't get
into the stores!
Good morning, sir,
lovely day.
Yes. Is there
something I can show you?
Engagement rings
for women.
Oh, excellent, excellent.
Diamond engagements
are right over here.
Uh... we'll start small.
Ooh, this one looks nice.
How much is it?
Ah-ha, that one is...
three thousand dollars.
For a diamond!
Where I come from, we use
the big ones for doorstops!
Sir, you mustn't think
in terms of price.
The ring is a symbol.
- A symbol?
Yes, the circular shape
represents never-ending love.
Circular shape...
Great!
I'll give her my watch.
Knickers?
- They're crushed velvet.
Nice, do you... like them?
I made them.
Tommy...kiss me.
Err... do you wanna
go out to the rambler?
There's a few minutes
before this whole procession.
No, I was just
checking something.
Hey! Hey, don't start
the mower
unless you're ready
to cut the grass!
Oh, Sally...
you look so beautiful,
so exquisite, so..
bold!
You, my lucky lady, are
in charge of that train.
Hey, Harry.
Um... who's that?
Sally, meet
blind Joe Slocum.
He's old, I borrowed him
from the tip top club,
and he plays the blues.
Okay, so what do you have that's new?
- He's my new friend.
So are you of the
bride's family or the groom's?
Neither, I am with the
immigration and naturalisation service.
I have reason to believe that there is
an illegal alien in the wedding party.
Really?
Mary.
There's something I've got to ask
you before this whole thing starts.
Oh Dick, not again.
You're on Sally's left,
and remember, no skipping
down the aisle.
Can I borrow
a toothbrush?
There is the most adorable man
out there with the government.
He's looking for aliens.
Thank you, Miss Dubcek.
Now go out there and hypnotise
him with your feminine wiles.
Never been a problem. Oh!
- Okay.
Family meeting!
Family meeting.
Where?
- Are you sure?
I've got to see Michel.
No, wait wait wait!
wait wait wait...
What's going on?
- They're white.
I'm...I'm so sorry, Michel,
but I can't marry you.
- What?!
I'm sorry.
But I need to get married,
they'll send me back. I'm an alien.
What?
I'm an alien.
Wow, okay.
See this is never gonna work
because... I'm an alien too.
What? Then.. then what is the point of this?
- I don't know.
Then give me back
my money.
Well I can't,
I spent it on the dress.
What? But..
Pull yourself
together, man.
Listen, somebody's here looking for you.
Now come with us and we'll protect you.
No! No no no no, I am sick
of you and your crazy people.
Crazy people!
You're crazy!
Hey, you!
Come on, Albright.
Oh, Mary, uh..
we're leaving town.
No particular reason,
you know, call of the road.
Oh, Dick, you shouldn't
be embarrassed.
Michel's the one
who got arrested.
They got Michel!
Oh!
The other guy from
immigration. It was an ugly fight.
The French tend to kick
a lot when frightened.
Immigration?
Yeah, they said they'll be sending
him back to France in the morning.
Of course, he's from
another country!
That's why he's an Alien.
Alien from France.
- Oh.
Not a quivering purple tube
from a distant galaxy,
sent to study humankind.
What? I said "not".
I'm sorry, Sally.
It's all right, you know. I
got the cake, I got the dress,
I got almost all the way
to the altar.
But you didn't get married.
- I know, but what the heck.
Hey, as long as we're all
dressed up, who wants to go bowling?
Tommy, Harry,
grab my train.
She made
a beautiful bride.
She'll make
a beautiful bowler.
Mary.
There's something I've been
wanting to ask you for several days now.
I thought about it long and hard
and I know it's the right thing to do.
Mary...
will you wear my watch?
I can't wear this.
Oh, I see...
I thought it's
what you wanted.
It's just too big.
I know it's a big step,
but don't you think that maybe
someday you might want to wear it?
Well... maybe if..
if I gain
a lot of weight.
Cake?
Some white irises,
Gerber daisies,
and a sprig of eucalyptus
for balance and scent.
Cool, what you doing?
Yeah, I'm making a centerpiece
for the football team.
Really?
- Yeah, it'll go great on their training table.
I can't wait to see their
faces when they see this baby.
Ooh, it's fun to stay
at the Y.M.C.A.
www.tvsubtitles.net