So I said to her,
"hey mom your birthday
was last month,
hoist it up yourself".
I don't get it,
what are they laughing at?
Anyway, I'm not saying
my mom is overweight,
she's got that
flabby skin under her arm.
You know what I'm talking about.
Well, the other day this wind picks up,
this stuff starts jiggling
out dropped a tricycle
I lost when I was seven.
Excuse me.
Perhaps you can help me out. Those
things you said about your mother,
I don't understand
why they're considered funny.
Well, um..
- Is it because
the toned arms that once
cradled you securely
now have large deposits
of cellulite hanging from them?
Is aging funny?
- If you think about it..
And you, is it all the
alcohol you're consuming
that makes it okay to laugh at
the expense of your loved ones?
He's right!
I love my fat mama!
And you're
a bad man!
Dr. Albright,
have you ever lost
a tricycle in your mother?
Please Dick,
I am in a cruddy mood.
This fundraiser is turning out
to be a nightmare.
Well, why are you laughing? You
just said you were in a cruddy mood.
Oh, it's these jokes
Ben Littmeyer gave me at lunch.
Ben Littmeyer,
from the sociology department?
Yes, oh he has
the best sense of humour.
I finally convinced him
to host the fundraiser.
Well, why didn't you
ask me to do it?
I have a wonderful
sense of humour.
Nina, come in here.
I have a wonderful
sense of humour, don't I?
Ohhh.
See?
- Oh!
This is an important
fundraiser for Pendleton,
and Ben can get those fat
cats to cough up some cash.
Well I can make
a fat cat cough.
I can even
make him vomit.
Thanks Dick, but Ben
already said yes.
You don't think I'm funny?
Oh Dick, you're loving,
and intelligent, and sexy..
and funny?
- Oh! I have a class!
I am funny! I am funny!
I am!
What happened
to your coat?
I don't know
what happened to it,
so Mrs. Dubcek let me
borrow this one.
Sweet woman.
So you lost your coat?
Oh tough break.
I lost more
than a coat, Tommy!
I lost a friend,
a buddy,
a companion, who kept me
warm when it was cold
and warmer
when it was really
sort of too hot
to be wearing a coat.
Tommy,
look, you're
the information officer.
What do you know about this
thing they call a sense of humour?
All I know is,
that's not it.
Lieutenant,
I need your help.
I need you to find out
what's funny.
Oh I can't,
I've got to build this..
I ran out of room
for my shoes.
Well this is more important,
it's about me!
Well how am I supposed
to know what's funny?
What's so important about
a sense of humour anyway?
Oh come on Tommy.
Having a sense of humor
is having the power,
to transform someone's mood,
to lift his spirit.
You give it to someone you
love when she really needs it.
And I just found out today, that
Marys been getting it from another man.
Dick, I think this whole
being funny thing is just innate.
What do you think, lieutenant?
- What do I think?
I think either you got it or you don't.
Look what you just did!
What's wrong
with you guys?
Come on! Wake up you two, come on!
How am I ever gonna
find out what's funny?
No I don't get it. Give me
an example of what's funny.
Okay let's see.
I thought the movie
Emma was really funny.
What was funny about it?
Didn't you get it?
It was full of irony.
Okay, so irony's funny.
Sure, because someone says something,
and the opposite is actually true.
Oh okay, like when you
told me Emma was gonna be
a really great movie, when
actually it sucked out loud?
Well, apparently, irony is a
little too sophisticated for you.
Either that or you don't know
what's funny either.
I... don't know
what's funny?
I'll have you know,
at camp,
I was voted
"Miss Whimsy".
Why, was Miss Irony killed
in a canoe accident?
Hi, Dick.
- Oh, uh, Mary.
Just doing some reading.
Some physics reading,
you know.
Okay.
Say, uh,
an amusing joke
just came to me
you know,
out of the blue.
Knock, knock.
Okay.
Who's there?
Who's there you say?
Nina!
Nina who?
Ah Nina, she's right here!
Please let me host
that fundraiser!
No!
- Oh!
Ben Littmeyer just called, he's
gonna be a few minutes late for lunch.
Oh, another lunch
with Ben.
I see.
How funny for you.
Well, would you like to join us,
we could make it a threesome?
I don't go that way Mary.
Fine!
And last but not least,
garlic gum.
Oh, uh, Harry,
how would you like a nice
piece of perfectly ordinary gum?
Okay.
Mmm, garlicky.
Well, I had
a great day.
I haven't learned a thing about
comedy, and August and I had a huge fight.
Oh well, how would you
like a nice doughnut?
from this bag
labeled "donuts".
Ahh! You touched doggy doody!
Since when is doggy
doody made in Taiwan?
They have dogs
in Taiwan.. big ones.
Funny, right?
- I don't know. You know,
I don't think I'm ever
gonna see my coat again.
Okay, Harry, why don't you sit down,
you'll feel a lot better?
Right here.
Excuse me.
Damn!
You know, at least
I can take comfort
in knowing that
I treated my coat well.
Such as yesterday.
It was hot on the bus.
I took it off
and folded it neatly
and placed it
under the shade of my seat.
What?
You left it on the bus.
No-o-o!
You know they have a lost and found Harry.
Oh you mean I might
see my coat again?
Oh I am so happy.
Dick, I've been thinking
about this "humour" thing.
Why don't you try what
those guys on TV do?
Everybody says they're funny?
- Oh, yeah, those guys!
You know..
The McLaughlin group?
No.
They're not funny
at all!
Oh, hello Dick.
- Hello Ben.
I'm waiting for Mary.
I'm sleeping with Mary.
Oh. Okay.
So from what I've heard, you're
quite the professor funnypants.
Well, I..
- It's seems that you have Mary
wrapped around
your little funny bone.
But I can assure you,
I am a far tougher...
bone wrapperer
I think I'll wait
outside.
Make me laugh funny man.
Well, I'm not
a comedian.
It's just that funny things,
just seem to happen to me.
Oh really, like what?
Well, like last week,
I was at a bus stop,
and it suddenly
started raining, pouring.
And I look over
and I see this
gorgeous grad student,
and she's looking at me,
like a kid with braces,
looking at a candy apple.
Mmm, no, not funny.
Well, I'm about
to say hello,
when I suddenly realize, that
my hair has flipped forward.
Here I am standing in the
rain, with my very own awning.
Well, finally
the bus arrived,
and the door opened,
the compressor kicked in,
and this, this, European
weave of mine
got sucked
right into the bus!
Well,
there I was,
in front of
this beautiful girl,
and chasing that bus,
and chasing my hair..
up and down,
chasing!
And I couldn't..I just.. oh!
Oh! Oh!
This is not good.
Yes, Yes, it is!
The bus stole your hair!
Call 911!
911!
Mary was so right
about you Ben!
What's going on?
Ben's been telling me the funniest story,
about the bus,
and the girl, and the..
Call 911!
You've heard this one before!
I'm telling you, Ben's
heart stopping temporarily
was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
He's getting
some much-needed bed rest,
and I'm emceeing
the fundraiser tomorrow night.
How did you manage that?
I promised Dr. Albright
I'd stick to Ben's script.
Are you gonna?
- No.
All right, next up on open-
mike night, very funny man,
put your hands together
for Dick Solomon.
Thank you!
Thanks a lot!
Thank you so much!
Now,
I'm gonna
tell you some jokes.
Joke one:
I went fishing
last week.
My permit said
I could only catch five.
Oh, I caught five,
all right, as in 35.
Was that funny?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
But you know..
pot-stickers,
what are they all about?
Haa-haa!
Okay, joke number two:
Some termites..
I mean, huge termites..
ate my house last night.
Uh, it's gone.
It's completely gone.
That's it.
That's the joke.
Really suck.
- Really.
Where are you going? Wait.
Wait. Where are you going?
Hey, look! A bald guy. Am I right?
Haa-haa!
So, who do you think's
funny in our class?
Um, Alan Gimball.
Alan Gimball? Why?
- 'Cause he's 20.
Oh, so.. so you think
dumb people are funny?
If they're
that dumb, yeah.
You know who I think is funny?
David Barrett.
Oh, yeah, he's hysterical.
- He is so clever.
I meant because
he looks like a big dork.
What?
All right, let's install this baby.
- Sweet!
Did you measure the shelves?
- Yes.
Did you measure the closet?
Did you measure the door?
- Damn!
Listen, if it's
storage you're after,
you can put it in the
hall closet downstairs.
Let me go and get
the door for you.
All right,here,
keep it sideways.
Uh, Dubcek, hold it.
- What?
I got it, I got it,
no problem, no problem
Hello? Yeah just a second.
Harry, for you.
Hello.
Wrong number.
She took it down
herself.
Ah, it's all right.
You had the guts to get up
there, you know? It takes time.
I have to be funny
by tomorrow night!
You're not
gonna make it.
I don't know
what to do!
Well, don't over-think it,
you know, just,
talk about things
you know. That's what I do.
Yeah. You make fun of
your poor mother's flabby arms.
Hey, those flabby-arm
jokes made her the most
popular senior
in Fort Meyers, Florida.
You.. you mean,
she doesn't hate you for it?
Hate me? No.
She loves me for it.
It's a joke.
You mean,
tricycles don't really
fall out of her arms?
Uh, no.
Oh my god!
Of course they don't!
I mean, just think how
flabby her arms would have to be
for a tricycle to be up in
there, and for so many years.
And she didn't even notice it,
not even when she took a shower.
That's hysterical.
I get it.
I get the joke!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
This should be fun.
Um, I'd like to welcome
you all here tonight.
Before we go
any further,
I think that we should all
acknowledge the sensational job,
that my esteemed colleague,
Dr. Mary Albright has done
in organizing this truly
worthwhile event. Dr. Albright.
Don't you love Dr. Albright?
I know I do.
Now, I know many
of you are wondering,
what's with her
long sleeves?
Well, I'll tell you.
It's to cover up
her flabby arms.
She shook them the other day,
and the dead sea scrolls fell out.
She's, uh.. she's quite old also, you see.
But you know,
as sweet and wonderful,
as Dr. Albright is,
she can also be
somewhat domineering,
power-hungry
and hostile,
and I think I finally
figured out why.
Dr. Albright,
while you may not have
a man's genitalia,
at least you have
his razor stubble.
Oh, oh, oh! Oh!
And there's Nina.
Nina is Dr. Albright's
assistant.
Nina, stand up, stand up.
Come on, stand up.
Show everybody
how you put the "Ass"
in "Assistant".
I left my coat on the bus.
- Can you describe it?
Yes, it had eight wheels,
hard plastic seats,
and when it stopped,
it went, "sh-h-h-h"
Harry, he means the coat.
- Oh, oh!
Um, well, it kind of looked
like this one, only it was furry..
don't have it.
Next.
Night Eddie.
- See you Monday.
He's got my coat.
- Harry, be a man.
Hey, Mister,
that's my coat.
No it isn't.
- Yeah, that's his coat.
If it's his coat,
how come I'm wearing it?
Good point.
Hey babes.
Good morning Dick, did you sleep well?
Once the adrenaline wore off,
like a baby.
You know when you've been riding
the bullet train to "yuk-ville",
it's kind of hard to slow down.
I've been up all night
faxing jokes to Leno.
What have we here?
Eleven
banana cream pies!
One for every letter in my name. Am I right?
Right.
Oh girls. You shouldn't have.
Oh, we had to.
Really.
You were so funny last night.
- Ohh.
I was wondering
if you could help us out?
Oh I'd be delighted
to share my...
comedic expertise.
We who are clowns are
known for our generosity.
Maybe you can help us settle
an argument we were having.
Shoot.
What's funnier?
This...
or this?
Or... is two
at once funny?
How about...
this?
Is this funny?
I think...
this.
You are so right!
That is funny!
Thank you so much
for helping us.
I'm glad I could
be of service.
Now if you'll
excuse me,
I have a class
to teach.
You know, it's
a remarkable feeling
to be able to make
someone else laugh.
It's almost as if
you have the power
to get inside their brain,
and tickle it.
I can do that
with a chopstick.
Imagine how different
war would be,
if instead of trying
to kill each other,
people just showed up
armed with jokes.
But you could still
have guns, right?
Because, you know,
eventually you'd stop laughing,
and want to get on
with the killing.
You know what I found out?
Humour's subjective.
What do you mean?
Well, I thought the fact that
no one was laughing at you
at the comedy club
was hysterical.
Oh, I loved that.
No no.
No, that wasn't funny.
See?
- Which is also ironic.
You were at a comedy club,
and no one was laughing.
Hey shut up all of you!
Well I think I'm gonna take my
furry little friend for a walk.
He's been locked
in the basement all week.
You know, why do they
call it a "fur coat" anyway?
It's not made of fur,
and it's not a coat.
Uh, actually Harry,
it's both those things.
It was a joke.
Ohh!
Good night everybody.
www.tvsubtitles.net