The big day
is tomorrow,
And these turkeys seem to
know what's coming their way.
It's the end
of the world!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
What's going on?
Dick!
There's a terrible
crisis.
We were at the store,
and the place was a madhouse.
People were cramming
everything they could into their carts,
especially these giant
balls of butter.
I got one
for each of us.
I'm telling you,
something is up.
The radio said the
airports were jammed
with people trying
to get out of town.
As a matter of fact, I just
saw a report on a turkey ranch,
and those birds were
talking apocalypse.
Apocalypse?
- Well, more like "apocalopolis".
What does this
all mean?
Well, I have a thought..
we're all gonna die!
All right,
let's not panic.
Tonight we'll turn off the
lights and hunker down in the kitchen.
Tomorrow morning I'll make a run to the
university and find out what's going on.
Police and secure the perimeter!
- What?
Lock the doors!
- Oh, yeah!
Hello? Hello? Mary!
Mary!
Mary, what have they done to your hair?
Speak to me, Mary!
Dr. Solomon, what are you doing here?
I'm trying
to find Mary,
but she's probably
already dead!
Are you sure she's not
home eating a big meal,
celebrating
the holiday?
"Holiday"?
What do you mean, "holiday"?
It's thanksgiving.
- Ohh!
So it's not
the apocalypse.
It's.. what
did you call it?
Thanksgiving.
You should be home with your
loved ones around a dinner table,
giving thanks
for what you've got.
But.. well, why
are you here?
Yeah, well, I took
St. Patrick's day off.
For six months.
So Mary isn't dead?
- Probably not.
She's giving thanks.
- That's right.
With her loved ones.
- Yeah.
But.. but..
but that's me!
Go on home.
Have a beer.
Take a nap.
You'll feel like
a human being.
Well, of course I will,
'cause that's what I am,
a human being.
Overlooking
the holidays was simply..
human error.
Oh, Dick! We gotta
get out of here!
It's gotten worse. They've
stopped delivering the mail.
Of course they have.
Someone's taken over the airwaves.
There's a terrifying parade on every channel!
Of course there is.
I got the gnome! I got the gnome!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Slow down there,
speedboat.
It's just thanksgiving.
"thanks-what-ing"?
- Thanksgiving, it's a holiday.
Like big, giant
head day?
Similar, except nobody
gets thrown into the sun.
It's a national holiday.
Everybody gets to take the day off.
Except for Sally.
What?
She has to go into the kitchen
and make an enormous feast.
Great. Our first holiday
on earth, and I got to cook.
And then after we eat,
we have to give thanks.
To me, for cooking?
Ohh!
Sally.
No, we have to give
thanks for something bigger,
Something more important,
something like..
well, not this, but
something like how good looking I am.
Maybe if we just run it
through, it'll hit us.
Why should we
run through anything?
'Cause I called Mary,
she's coming over.
But what if we get it wrong?
It'll give us away.
Now, look, men.
When we first landed on this
planet, we didn't know squat.
We didn't even know what
the word "squat" meant.
And we had to find out the hard way.
- And it hurt.
All we have to do is find a
human example and follow it.
Hello, hello, everybody!
- Mrs. Dubcek.
Close enough.
Happy thanksgiving, everybody
. This is my daughter, Vicki.
Oh, I didn't know
Mrs. Dubcek had a..
I mean, hello-o-o-o-o.
Hi. You have
great hair.
So, uh, what are you
ladies doing for thanksgiving?
We're going off to the beef 'n' griddle.
- Oh, no, you're not.
You're coming over to our house to help us.
Uh, celebrate.
Yeah, we don't know what we're doing.
What do you say, Vick?
- I say, what the hell?
Then "What the hell"
it is.
Turkey, no turkey.
Turkey...
and no turkey.
Oh, Harry, you've got a real
childlike innocence about you.
It's very sexy.
Turkey.
Wow, this is the ugliest
lingerie I've ever seen.
But buckles.
- Mmm.
Oh, that? No.
That's just a costume I
wore in a thanksgiving play
I did in junior high.
I was a pilgrim,
and every time I wore it,
I put everybody in
the thanksgiving mood.
Tommy?
- What?
You heard what she said.
Forget it, Dick,
I'm not putting that thing on.
Once again, you let us down.
- What are you talking about?
You're the information officer. You should
have prepped us for this holiday weeks ago,
and now you won't
wear the costume!
Is there any end
to your treachery?
Look Dick, if it's a holiday, why
don't you just take the day off my back.
Oh, I will.
I will not allow my disappointment
in you to destroy this festival,
even though the costume would put
us all in the thanksgiving mood.
Yeah, well, it'll put me
in the crappy mood!
You're always in the crappy
mood.
Now, come on, put it on!
- No!
Put it on!
Happy thanksgiving!
Oh, happy thanksgiving,
Mary.
Put it on!
- No!
Ever since we got here, I can't do
anything right for you. Why is that?
Don't use use that tone of voice with me, old man.
- Oh! I'm going for a walk.
Oh, fine! And don't come
back until you're damn
ready to sit down with your
family and have fun!
Uh...Dubcek, so what am I
supposed to do with this thing?
You stick your hand right up
there and yank out its guts.
What's the point?
It's already dead.
That's how it's done.
- All right.
Sally, look who's here.
I thought you might
need a little help cooking.
Why? Don't you think she's ever cooked a
thanksgiving dinner before?
Is that what you think?
Yeah, you don't think I've ever
cooked a thanksgiving dinner before?
No, I didn't say that.
- Because thanksgiving is not new to us.
And we're certainly
not new to thanksgiving.
So, when's dinner, three o-clock?
Today?
- Three! On the dot!
All right, move it. Uh,
Dubcek, take out the relish tray,
and Mary, hold this.
Okay, now, does the fork go
on the right or on the left?
Well,
this goes here,
and this goes here.
Are those the rules?
Oh, forget about
the rules, Harry!
Just put whatever you want to
put wherever you want to put it.
Can I put my shirts
in my underwear drawer?
Go wild.
Okay.
Maybe you should rub it with a
little margarine before you put it in.
You heard the woman.
Rub that bird.
I don't think so. All it
needs is a little salt.
No margarine!
Heavy on the salt!
If you want
the skin to crisp..
Want skin crisp now.
Want you dead now.
Dick, my grandmother
had a saying..
"Get out of the kitchen before
I burn you with a hot spoon".
Your grandmother had
a rapier wit.
She did.
Dick, get out
of the kitchen!
And she was mean too.
Are you open?
- 'Course we're open. It's thanksgiving.
Excuse me. This game's not
three-Dimensional, is it?
Uh, yeah. Uh, you want to play some 8-ball?
What's 8-ball?
- Don't worry, we're not very good either.
Harry, you should see the
beautiful turkey Sally has in the kitchen.
Oh, there's a turkey here?
- Oh, it's enormous!
I want to see it!
You murdered it!
Although we are very familiar with this
tradition, it never ceases to appall us.
Well, I did it.
Here it is, folks..
the perfect turkey!
Shouldn't we wait
for Tommy?
We're starting
without him.
Well, but I poured some
grape juice in a wine glass,
and who's gonna sit
at the kids' table?
Doesn't matter.
Fine, okay. Thanksgiving's ruined. Hack away.
Oh, no, no, I..
I couldn't make the
first hack. Mary, you hack.
Before we hack the turkey,
shouldn't someone give thanks?
Uh, here we all are,
gathered together for a
completely authentic thanksgiving dinner,
perfect in every way.
I just want to say
I am thankful
that we are all here
to feast on this dead bird.
We're not all here.
Tommy's not here.
Thank you so much
for bringing that up!
Thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Don't worry. Tommy will be back.
- Thank you!
Hey. Excuse me.
I'd like to add
a little something,
if I may.
Uh, I just
feel that
this year I have so much to be thankful for.
That thing under my armpit
went away.
And when I was
working at wal-mart
and that big stack of boxes fell on me.
I got workman's comp for
eight months, and that's..
that's twice as much
as my normal salary, so...
guess you'd
have to say that
god has been
very, very good to me.
Let's eat!
You know, I left because
they don't appreciate me.
And I do a lot for those
guys. 6 ball, corner pocket.
I mean, they just don't
understand how difficult it is to be a kid.
I mean, I do a lot at home, but you have
to have a life outside work too, you know.
7 ball, side pocket.
I mean, occasionally I screw
up. I'm only trying to be human.
But whatever I do, it's
never enough for those people.
8 ball, three banks,
back pocket.
You know what I mean?
That's game.
Tommy,
they're hard on you
because they love you.
Yeah, at least
you've got somebody.
My father used to take me
out to the shed every Friday,
whether I deserved it
or not.
Why?
Because he cared.
He just wanted to make me strong, that's all.
I should go home
and thank him.
Well, why don't you?
I can't afford to,
you've got all my money!
Here, take it.
Go home.
Oh, Tommy, man!
You're the best!
I love you, man!
I love you!
Hey, Frank..
- Hold on.
Hi, dad,
it's Francis.
What are you doing?
It's tradition.
I like it.
What's the matter
with us, Harry?
I'm gettin' drowsy,
and I can't
fight it.
I feel like
I'm gonna explode.
I'm gonna
ex-uh-pul-lode!
Stay with me, Harry.
I'll save you.
No!
Save yourself!
Harry!
Harry, can you
hear me?
Harry!
It's Dick! Come back to
me! Come back to me, Harry!
Dick?
- Harry!
Talk to me!
What's for dessert?
Wow, your mother's
refrigerator
is far more spacious
than ours.
Did you get enough
to eat Pumpkin?
Well, that depends on
what you're talking about.
And what do you think
I'm talkin' about?
Yams.
Oh, I got yams for ya.
Don't you want to put a
little mini marshmallow on that?
Yahtzee.
No, Dick, that wasn't Yahtzee,
that was two of a kind.
Yahtzee.
- No, that's not a Yahtzee.
Five in a row.
They lost
the instructions.
Tommy knows how to play.
- Well, Tommy's not here.
Yahtzee.
It's too bad. He would
have really liked my stuffing.
Well, he should have
put on the pilgrim costume.
Why didn't you put on
the pilgrim costume?
You're the one who wanted to show off
and have a big, stupid thanksgiving.
That's not why I had a big, stupid
thanksgiving. I did it for all of you.
Oh, admit it, Dick..
everything is about you.
What about you? You had a good time.
Oh, yeah, if you call spending
a whole day in the kitchen
with these two
jabbermouths a good time.
Hey! One of those
jabbermouths is his girlfriend!
Yeah!
I have had it with all of you!
This holiday is over!
- Oh, I see! Well!
Now I have something to give
thanks for. Thanks for nothing!
This is why I go
to the beef 'n' griddle.
I've never felt
this way before.
this sticky before.
Harry,
I got to go home
to Orlando tomorrow.
But I'll be back.
You know, I like you, Harry. You're..
you're not like
the other guys.
Ah.
No, ma'am.
Do you, uh.. do you think
we could make it work?
Oh, I don't know.
I'm pretty tired.
I meant us, Harry.
I definitely think
that "us" could work.
Me too.
Your family's a little
strange, though.
Ha! Your Mother's
Mrs. Dubcek.
Oh, Mary, I'm so sorry about everything.
What?
- Oh the tension, the fighting,
the lumpy gravy.
- Yeah.
You give and you give
and you give
until you just
can't give anymore.
Mmm. Same thing
happens at my house.
This happens at your house?
- Why should my house be any different
than 99% of all
the homes in America?
What about the other
one percent?
Connecticut.
Hey, guys.
- Tommy, you're back.
Oh, I'll leave
you two alone.
Sorry I left
like that.
No, that's all right.
I don't think it was your fault.
I found out
something pretty cool.
You know how you tried to
make this a special day,
but all the resentment I
had for you came spewing out
and we ended up spending the
whole day avoiding each other?
Yeah.
- It's normal.
I was gonna tell you
the same thing!
Yeah, the screaming, the
fighting, the exploding resentments..
that's what
thanksgiving is!
So we did get it right.
- Yeah.
Nailed it.
- Oh, yeah.
Tommy.
I've never felt
so content.
I look around
this room and I see
nothing but
familiar faces.
Well, some are more
familiar than others.
I barely know you.
But it doesn't matter,
because tonight
you're all family,
and this has been
the perfect thanksgiving.
And now for
the perfect dessert.
Surprise!
Well..I guess not everyone
likes jell-O.
Listen, Dick, we better not let another
one of these big holidays sneak up on us.
Oh, don't worry,
lieutenant, after this one,
there couldn't possibly
be another one for months.
You know, after cooking that huge
dinner tonight, I think I deserve a break.
What do you plan to do?
- I think...
tomorrow I'm gonna spend a
nice, peaceful day at the mall.
Really?
I hear there's a sale.
Really? Goody!
www.tvsubtitles.net