(Kim) No!
(Dan) Keep moving.
(Dan) Shut up!
Put her down. Put her down.
(Rick) Keep movin'.
(Dan) Shut up! Let's go. Come on, keep goin'.
- We have to go back.
- She's dead.
- You don't know that.
- Get in!
- Take it easy.
- You better decide whose side you're on!
We can't just leave her
in the middle of the street.
Nina...
- Nina, l know you're upset.
- Of course l'm upset. What do you expect?
Sorry. Look, the reason why l had to leave
the office is because l got a call from Walsh.
He was meeting one of our agents,
Scott Baylor. He said he had evidence...
That led you to me, l know.
But you should have thought it through.
Nina, listen to me. Richard Walsh is dead.
- What?
- He was shot. l watched him die.
What is going on?
He was killed cos he had proof that people
within our agency are behind the Palmer hit.
- Who?
- l don't know yet.
Right before Richard died
he gave me that key card.
l'm hoping that's going to tell us.
Jamey's trying to break it down now.
- You trust Jamey?
- He did. l trust you.
The three of us have to work together.
From this point forward we have to
assume that we can trust nobody else.
- l understand.
- Good.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Work the card with Jamey.
l have to make a call.
Agent Pierce wanted to talk to you.
- Fine. Give me a minute.
- lt's very important.
A minute.
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
- Find anything out?
lt's barely been half an hour
since you told me.
l need you to find out the source of this story.
Not first thing in the morning, now.
This can't be done over the phone.
l have to talk to some people in person.
l wanna hear something by four.
- You've gotta let me...
- (hangs up)
- Where were you?
- l went for a drive.
A drive? Alone, at this time of night?
- l just needed to get away for a while.
- Away from what?
Everything.
They haven't told you, have they?
There's been an assassination threat.
- That's what all the fuss is about?
- Yes.
l thought it was something serious.
Jack. l'm screening the passenger list.
Something doesn't add up here.
- What?
- 2B. Manifest shows an empty seat.
So?
According to the ticketing file, first class
was full. Plus there was a waiting list.
Why would the plane take off
with an empty seat?
This is good.
What time does Rayburn get in?
- Six.
- Wake him up. Bring him in now.
Jack.
OK. We've got something off the key card.
The encryption is complex. l've asked
Jamey to isolate sectors. She's extracted one.
Just part of one.
That's it, just an address?
What's that got to do with Palmer?
- lt doesn't say.
- Crosscheck it with his schedule.
- He's not going anywhere near it.
- Has he been near it since he came here?
No.
How about previous visits?
Connection to family members?
l can check. lt'll take time.
No. Let's see what
we can peel off. Start in here.
Just the address on San Fernando Road.
How long will it take you to access
the next level? Minutes or hours?
- Hours, most likely.
- We don't have hours.
l'll check out the address myself.
- You want some backup?
- No. l need you here.
- What's wrong?
- l can't access our decryption software.
Phones are down, too.
lt's a lockdown.
lt's Mason. Hide the key card.
l'll handle this.
Hello, Nina. These men are with lnternal
lnvestigations. You are in official lockdown.
- By what authority?
- District Office.
We're trying to stop an assassination. Can't
you find anything better to do than this?
Two agents died tonight. A lockdown's
standard procedure until we get answers.
- Where's Jack?
- l don't know.
Station two, coming your way.
Lockdown. Nobody leaves.
- Lockdown? Are you serious?
- No, l'm kidding.
- l gotta get some work from the car.
- You know the drill.
Fine. You take the keys.
All right. l assume you're all
familiar with lockdown procedures.
You remain in the building.
All communications will be monitored.
Any incoming calls without
secure access codes will be blocked.
ln the meantime, continue to work on the
systems available until notified otherwise.
Who called them in, Tony? You?
Yeah, me.
- Why?
- Somebody had to. Jack's out of control.
Meaning what?
Two agents are down.
Jack was there when it happened.
You can't believe he was involved in that.
Tell you the truth,
l don't know what to believe.
l'd hate to think this has
anything to do with me.
- You think what you want.
- (Mason) Could be here for quite a while.
He got past me.
All right, Nina, where'd he go?
l already told you, l don't know.
You let me know, we can
get things up and running.
l'm really sorry, George. l can't help you out.
Mm-hm. Me, too.
Senator, could l have a word with you?
l'm not sure you appreciate
the seriousness of this threat.
l get serious threats every morning.
With all due respect, this one's different.
lt's a pro from overseas.
- Who's behind it?
- We don't know.
But as l'm sure you're aware, an airliner
exploded an hour and a half ago outside LA.
- No survivors.
- There's some connection?
Again, we don't know. We're looking into it.
What do we know?
That these are serious people,
and they want you dead, today.
- What about my family?
- The threat is against you only.
But of course we'll increase
security for your family as well.
The main thing is your schedule.
Today's primary day.
l'm not gonna hide in my hotel room.
Understood, but we recommend some
changes. The breakfast, for example.
The breakfast is important. The top labour
leaders in the state are gonna be there.
We're trying to keep you alive.
And l'm trying to win an election.
(door opens)
Mom said you wanted to see me.
Wanted to make sure you're all right.
Why are you up?
lf l'm not sleeping by three, l'm not sleeping.
l was gonna watch some tube.
Wanna join me?
- Anything on this time of night?
- Nothing good.
l guess l'll pass.
Heard about the threat.
Don't worry about it.
They'll take good care of me.
They better.
You better get some rest.
l'm telling you, we have
to go back and get Janet.
Are you gonna tell
your girlfriend to shut her mouth?
- She's probably dead.
- What if she's not? She might need help.
Why do you always do what he tells you?
Why don't you think for yourself?
- Just leave it alone, OK?
- l can't. She's my friend.
You know, she may be right after all.
We should go back.
lf she's alive, she can lD us.
- We have to shut her up for good.
- What?! What are you saying?
You're gonna kill her?
You're gonna kill Janet, huh? Huh?
Close her mouth. Now!
l'm not gonna let you tie me up! No!
Sounds like she's gonna tie you up.
(Teri) l just hope the girls are still there.
(siren)
Oh, no.
l don't believe this.
Stay in your car, sir. Back in the car.
Keep your hands where l can see 'em.
- Do you know how fast you were drivin'?
- Yes. Our daughters are missing.
We got a phone call.
We're on our way to pick them up.
- Licence and registration.
- Did you hear what l said?
Officer, my name is Teri Bauer.
He's telling the truth.
We really could use your help. My daughter
just phoned from Platt's Auto Body.
Different last names.
One's married, one's not.
l just called 911 15 minutes ago.
Verify it if you want.
- You know what? l'm gonna do that.
- Yeah. Why don't you do that?
- Listen...
- l said remain in the car.
l understand that. Can we speed things up?
Write us a ticket so we can go?
The woman asked me to verify the 911.
That's what l'm trying to do.
You know, you are a real
piece of work. You know that?
- My daughter is in trouble. We're finished.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Take it easy.
- (cop) Relax, everyone. Whoa.
- (York) Get your hands off me!
No. Stop. Don't do that.
Please, don't do this.
Ma'am, he just disobeyed
a direct order from a police officer.
- l'm afraid l'll have to place him under arrest.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
You know Richard Walsh was killed tonight.
Scott Baylor, too.
Did you know Jack was there
when it happened?
l don't know anything about it.
- And you have no idea where he is now?
- No.
- You're making a big mistake, Nina.
- No, you are.
When this lockdown is over,
l'll talk with the Double l team,
about some highly irregular banking
transactions traced to your account.
Trust me, the trouble Jack's in, my bank
accounts won't even raise an eyebrow.
He's going down, Nina. But that doesn't
mean you have to go down with him.
True love is a beautiful thing, but...
why go to extremes?
l know about the affair.
l mean, Jack talks about it all the time.
- Sure he does.
- How else would l know about it?
See, it is possible that Jack's not
the shining knight you think he is.
You wanna try again?
Where's Jack now?
(cop) This is Mary-138. Need a
transportation unit at the Fifth Street bridge.
- (phone rings)
- (cop) Ma'am. OK. Please, ma'am.
(radio) 1-M-38.
Repeat location with full request.
(cop) 1-Mary-38. l need a transportation unit.
(phone rings)
lt's Teri. Leave a message,
and l'll callyou back.
Honey, it's me. l'm just checking up
on Kim. l'll call you back soon.
Don't move.
Dammit!
2-Adam-14. Reporting shots fired at
18166 San Fernando Road. Request backup.
(radio) 2-Adam-14.
Backup on the way, 18166 San Fernando.
Stop! Police!
- Hold it right there!
- Federal agent.
- Your badge. Nice and slow.
- Putting my gun down.
- CTU? What the hell is that?
- Counter Terrorist Unit.
This guy is not waiting for me, so you
better shoot me or help me, but decide now.
- All right, l'll help you.
- l'm picking up my gun.
Easy.
You be careful with that gun. l need him alive.
Throw me your flashlight.
(phone rings)
(Jack) Take cover.
- (radio) 2-Adam-14. Backup's on the way.
- 2-Adam-14. Copy.
Turn off your radio.
- l wish you hadn't called for backup.
- Why?
Cops have to play by the rules.
l'll have to break a few with this guy.
Who is he?
So to sum it up, Jack leaves his wife,
shacks up with you for a while,
gets bored, and then moves back home,
leaving you out in the cold.
My personal life is not your concern.
- lt is if it affects your work.
- lt doesn't affect my work.
How long have you been with
the agency, Nina? Six years, seven?
Seven years.
l remember when you first joined.
You were goin' places. Everybody knew it.
lt hasn't quite happened
for you yet, has it?
- You ever wonder why?
- l've done all right.
But you could have done so much better.
You had a great reputation once.
You know what your reputation is now?
Jack's flunky. His lapdog.
This is your chance
to get back on track, Nina.
He's a loose cannon.
Rules don't apply to Jack Bauer.
He does what he wants when he wants,
and he doesn't care whose life it affects.
He shot me with a trank gun,
for God's sakes.
- You withheld information.
- l was following orders.
Maybe he's following orders
you don't know about.
He violated lockdown,
and he left you holding the bag.
lf he cared about you,
he wouldn't have put you in that position.
Let me ask you, would you
have done that to him?
Fact is, l'm just asking you to do
your job and tell me where he is.
l don't know.
(squeaking)
(Jack) Get down! Get down!
(in Spanish)
(janitor) Sí. Bueno.
(sobs)
- (Rick) Maybe she's dead after all.
- (Dan) We have to be sure.
- Let's just put her in the van.
- No.
- Dan...
- Shut up!
(siren)
Move it!
Yeah?
- Mason's gonna wanna talk to you.
- What do you want me to say?
Jack's made it clear that
the three of us work in confidence.
- But doesn't Mason supersede Jack?
- No, no.
What we're doing came from Walsh.
George will say anything to get you to talk.
Do not be intimidated by him.
OK.
Cross me.
(creaking)
(running footsteps)
- The other building.
- Jeez, this place is like a maze.
(Carl) All right. l've got a name.
George Ferragamo. Know him?
Yeah. l know the name.
You find anything else, leave
a message on the 802 number only.
OK. You got it.
Thanks, Carl.
You've been spending an awful lot of time
behind closed doors, making phone calls.
- Have l?
- What's going on, David?
Phone call earlier tonight
from Maureen Kingsley.
She's digging up old history.
Bad history.
Just tell me.
She claims that Keith
murdered the boy who raped Nicole.
What?
Well, first, Lyle Gibson
was no boy. He was 19.
Second, he killed himself.
The coroner's report proved it.
- Maureen has new evidence.
- What evidence?
l put Carl on it.
He came up with a name. George Ferragamo.
That's the therapist Keith went to.
What about him?
- He claims that...
- Not that Keith confessed in therapy?
- Apparently.
- Well, then he's lying.
- You've gotta get our lawyers on this.
- Yeah, l know. l will.
- But, you know...
- What is it, David?
l just don't understand it.
Maureen's always been very responsible,
one of the few real professionals left.
Well, l'd call this unprofessional.
David!
David, you can't seriously think
that our son might be a killer?
No, of course not.
- Look, l apologised.
- You don't get it, do you?
- You've committed a serious crime.
- Officer, please.
Clearly he's upset. We both are.
lf you could just give us a break, please.
- (radio) 1-Mary-38.
- 1-Mary-38. Go.
1-Mary-38. That emergency call was placed at
that location approximately 30 minutes ago.
Copy. Thanks.
That still doesn't justify you
disobeying a police officer.
ldiot!
- Ground units'll be on their way.
- l need him now to claim jurisdiction.
- Where do you want me?
- Keep him pinned down at the exit.
l'll try and go round
the other side. Don't hit him.
- l won't.
- Don't hit me either.
(loudhailer) This is the police.
Drop your weapon.
¡Dios mío! ¡Por favor! ¡Por favor!
- l told you to stay put!
- Yo no hice nada.
(man) Over here!
- You want me, come and get me.
- (cop) Don't do it! He'll kill both of us!
(cop) Don't do it!
Come out! Drop the gun!
Don't!
Step out where l can see you
and throw down the gun.
(cop) Don't do it!
- l'll drop the gun, but you've gotta relax.
- Don't do it.
Shut up. Put down the gun.
Speak English, asshole!
l'm putting down the gun!
The gun's going down.
Good work. Throw me your cuffs.
Oh, my God.
(Teri) l think it might be up here,
somewhere to the right.
(York) Yeah, maybe.
(York) There's someone up ahead. Maybe
they saw something. Roll down your window.
Excuse me. Could you tell me
what happened here, please?
- lt might involve our children.
- You shouldn't let your children come here.
Yeah, l know. But could you just
please tell me what happened?
Girl was hit by a car.
Do you know where they took her?
St Mark's is closest.
Was she alive?
- She didn't look good.
- Go, go, go, go.
(Dan) Hey, it's Gaines.
- Where's the other one?
- She was a problem, so we killed her.
- The body?
- No one'll find it.
- She been any trouble?
- Not at all.
You're with me now.
Be good, you'll be back at the mall
in a day or two. Be bad, you won't. Clear?
- Mm-hm.
- Good.
Agent Farrell, come with me, please.
Jamey.
l've already told these men,
l don't know anything.
Tryin' to protect Jack and Nina?
Don't be naive.
Sit.
Let me tell you how the game is played.
First thing they do is to tell you
that you're the only one they can trust.
That's flattering, and it makes
you trust them in return. All right?
Then they get you to do
something you shouldn't.
Say you don't know where
Jack went, for example.
The next thing you know, Jack's gone,
Nina's stonewalling,
and you're in the hot seat.
Sound familiar?
Hey, you're being used.
l've seen it a million times.
lf you help me out, l'll help you out.
lf you hold out...
(phone rings)
Mason.
Really? Good. l'm on my way.
Seems our boy's surfaced. His name
popped up on a police frequency.
- Not that l'm surprised.
- ls he in trouble?
Off the record, just out of curiosity,
what's so special about Jack Bauer?
All right, we've found Bauer.
We're pulling out. Lockdown's over.
Hope you give some thought
to what we talked about.
(man) Call it in as a DOA.
Everything checked out. Here you go.
What was her name?
Jessie Hampton.
Know anything about this guy?
- No. l gotta take him in for questioning.
- Maybe you didn't notice, he killed a cop.
- But there's something else at stake here.
- Not to me. Not to these guys.
All right.
Can l at least have a few minutes with him?
Guys.
Thank you.
Get up.
lf you tell me who you are,
l might be able to help you.
- Don't let them take me. lf they do, l'm dead.
- They seem in control.
l'm not worried about them.
- Who are you worried about?
- You spring me, then l talk.
- That's not gonna happen.
- That's too bad...
Bauer.
Bauer. How do you know my name?
(cop) Time's up.
l know more than that. lf you ever wanna see
your daughter again, get me outta this.
What do you know about my daughter?!
l'm fine! l'm fine!
l'm fine.
Visiontext Subtitles: Adrian lsaac
ENGLlSH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net