I would like you
to appear on television
and appeal to members
of Islamic communities
everywhere.
The majority
of your cabinet feels
that you're making
a tragic mistake.
The man has murdered
countless innocents,
and you are putting your hopes
for this country's safety
on him.
They will come after you.
I assure you of that.
We're talking about removing the
President of the United States.
We are in the middle
of a national crisis,
and he is in over his head.
He has brought
this on himself.
I need the president's
itinerary,
specifically in regards
to Assad's televised address.
Why do you need this?
The less you know,
the better.
Because of me,
Fayed has a device
that can arm all the bloody
suitcase nukes he was.s.
CHLOE:
You can't blame yourself.
When the next bomb goes off,
and thousands
of more people die,
everybody will remember
that I was the one
that made it possible.
CTU found me.
I needed to preoccupy them
with a bomb
to enable my escape.
The delivery system software
was programmed
for five detonations
at five high-priority targets.
Because of your carelessness,
we are now down to three.
More than enough for
our needs,Gredenko.
Our country lost the Cold War
because it was afraid
to use these weapons
against the Americans.
Today we will
correct that mistake,
and the Arabs will
take all the blame.
Marilyn, it is vital that
we find this man Gredenko.
If we retrace the route
that you took that night,
do you think that you
would recognize the house?
Maybe.
What's going on
with you and Jack?
He's looking for someone
he thinks I can help.
You mean Gredenko?
What do you know about him?
I followed Graem
to a house one night,
he met with some Russians.
Jack wants to take me
over there to see
if it can jog my memory.
PHILLIP:
Now you're not going
to take Jack to the house
where Graem met the Russians.
You're going to take him
to a different address.
Now you do this for me,
and I promise you
you will see Josh again.
If you don't, he dies.
Marilyn,
is any of this familiar?
MARILYN:
Yes. That's it.
The pale blue
house on the right.
JACK:
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Go! Go!
Bomb! Everyone out!
(automatic gunfire)
Come on, move, move, move!
Don't stop!
(phone rings)
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
BUCHANAN: What do you got?
We've been ambushed.
The house that Marilyn led us to
was wired with explosives.
Half my team is down--
I need you to send paramedics
to 9407 Hendry Place.
Bill, they knew
we were coming.
You mean Gredenko?
Yeah, I think so.
Right now I'm trying
to find Milo and Marilyn.
I think they're being
pursued by hostiles.
I'll have a team
there in ten minutes.
I'll monitor local bandwidth,
see what I can come up with.
Bill, hurry,
we need to find them.
(breathleMarilyn, come on, we've
I-I can't...got to keep moving.
You understand?
Come on, move.
Move!
Check the warehouse.
(labored breathing)
REPORTER: The fallout has
prevented emergency workers
from coming within
several miles
(phone ringing)
of ground zero, but survivors
are being treated
at local hospitals and makeshift
medical facilities
like the one behind me.
Local authorities continue
to urge people
to stay in their home
until further notice.
Yeah?
HACKER:
We took out the CTU team.
So is my son dead?
Yes, sir.
(sighing):
Right, well...
had to be done.
You have Marilyn?
No, sir, not yet.
Why not yet?
She escaped with someone
from CTU,
but we're tracking them now.
Damn it, Hacker.
We'll find her soon, sir.
The man she's with doesn't look
like a trained field agent.
Make sure you take her alive.
I need her to find Gredenko
so I can end this mess.
I understand, sir.
I'll call you as soon
as I have her.
(clattering)
Hey.
They know we're here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Marilyn, listen to me.
I'm going to cover you.
When I do, I want you to head
back towards the alley.
I want you to run as fast
and as far away from here
as you can, you understand me?
Okay.
The targets are right behind us.
Behind those Dumpsters.
Remember...
we need to take
that woman alive.
Just wait...
wait till I tell you.
Go!
(screaming)
I can't!
(cries out)
I told you to go!
I couldn't!
(groaning)
Let's go.
Wait! Wait!
Kill him.
(pained grunting)
(gunshots, Marilyn screams)
Drop your weapon!
Let her go!
Drop your weapon
or I will kill her.
If you wanted to kill her,
she'd be dead by now.
Now drop your weapon!
Or I will use mine!
Do it!
On your knees!
Now! Hands on your head!
Interlace your fingers!
Turn around and
face the fence!
Milo!
Let me see it.
(pained groaning)
The bullet went
through and through.
There's no arterial bleeding.
You're going to be okay.
CTU will be here in a minute.
Take this gun.
Make sure he doesn't move.
(whimpering)
(screams)
That call you took,
that was from Gredenko.
You tipped him off!
Now over half
my team is dead!
You don't understand.
What don't I understand?
That Gredenko knew
we were coming?
It wasn't Gredenko
on the phone.
Those aren't his men.
If those weren't Gredenko's
men, whose were they?
Who sent them?
Your father.
What are you talking about?
It's true, Jack.
I swear.
Your father called me
in the car.
My father?
He told me to lead you
to that house.
He said if I didn't...
he said he'd killed Graem,
and that if he had to,
he would kill Josh.
I'm sorry.
He has my son.
(sobbing)
Marilyn.
Do you have the address
to Gredenko's safe house?
(mouthing)
I need you to give it to me now.
I can't.
Not until I have my son.
I will help you get Josh back,
but I need that address now.
Gredenko is our only chance of
recovering the nuclear weapons.
You saw what happened in
Valencia earlier today.
This is going to be worse.
Please.
Just give me the address.
I recognized the house
once we were driving.
It's on Glascoe-- 9421.
Don't move.
(phone rings)
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
I've got the correct address
for Gredenko's safe house.
9421 Glascoe.
Turner's team will
be there any minute.
You run point on this.
No, I want you to send me a
smaller team to my location.
I'm at an industrial park
on Pine, just south of Oxford.
Make sure the team
brings me a vehicle
with a full tactical kit.
Then they're gngng to have
to transfer Milo back to CTU.
He's been shot,
but he's not critical.
I want you to divert
the rest of the team
to the address on Glascoe--
have them initiate the attack.
Get back to me as soon as soon
you've got Gredenko in custody.
Jack, what's going on?
I'll explain everything later.
That's not good enough.
Bill, please.
Just trust me.
This is personal.
Jack!
--Hi.
Hey.
Did you finish the vectors?
No.
You know, if you're having
trouble, I can help you.
I'm not having trouble.
I'm just not finished,
and I don't want this to turn
into another conversation
about whether or not I'm okay.
I'm sorry, love.
It's all right, but if you can't
talk to me, then you should talk
to a staff psychologist
or your sponsor.
I don't need a shrink.
I don't want to talk to my
sponsor, I'll be fine.
We just heard from Jack.
Marilyn Bauer's safe, and she
gave us Gredenko's location.
Milo was shot
during the operation,
but he's going to be okay.
What happened?
He held off three
armed hostiles
until Jack could get there.
From what I understand,
he's going to be up
for a commendation.
Morris, when Milo gets here,
I want you to debrief him
as soon as medical
gives you the okay.
Yeah, yeah, I'll debrief him,
and thanks for rubbing
that salt in the wounds.
What are you talking about?
The nukes are armed
because I'm a coward,
and now you want me to listen
to Milo talk about
what a bloody hero he is. Agh!
Coincidence?
It'll be taken care of, thanks.
Taken care of.
We're coordinating the Gredenko
operation from here.
Tac teams
are moving in on his location.
I'll be right there.
Obviously I pushed you
back to work too soon.
I'll have someone
from district relieve you.
No, no, that would
just make me feel worse.
Look, I need a few minutes--
I'll be fine.
I'm going to take a walk.
I'll cover for you,
but you need to be
back here
before we launch.
Yeah, I will.
Give me the phone;
we need to make the call.
Scramble collar
has to be enabled.
(indistinct communication
over police radio)
(beeping)
(distant siren blaring)
Give us a second, please.
Does he know where Phillip
is holding Josh?
No.
I'm gonna have to
force my father's hand.
Meaning what?
He's gonna call my father,
tell him he's
apprehended you,
but that you won't give
him Gredenko's location
until he takes you
to see your son.
What if Phillip refuses?
Then you have
to stay firm.
Tell him it's not a negotiation,
no matter what he threatens.
Jack, you're asking me
to put Josh's life at risk.
Josh's life is at risk.
Trust me, my father is not
going to give away his location
unless he thinks he has to.
Is that what this is about--
finding Phillip?
Josh is secondary?
My father will
have Josh with him.
Marilyn, I will do
everything in my power
to make sure
your son is safe.
How do you know
he won't betray us?
He wants to live.
Let's go.
You don't want to watch this.
You know, Josh...
your father
was very proud of you.
He used to tell me
how blessed he felt
knowing everything that he
was working so hard to build
would be left in
such good hands.
Do we really have to talk
about this right now, Grandpa?
No... of course not.
He loved you very much.
Remember, I'll be able to hear
both sides of this conversation.
You're set.
Dial.
(phone speed-dialing)
(phone rings)
Do you have her?
Yeah... but we
took casualties.
I'm on my own now.
Are you assembling another team
to take out Gredenko?
Yeah, I am, but she's refusing
to tell me where Gredenko is
until she sees her son.
Put her on.
I did what you asked,
now where's Josh?
Marilyn, look,
I know you're frightened,
but this doesn't
have to end badly.
If you help me
find Gredenko,
we can all survive
this, as a family.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I just want my son.
I'm just saying, you made
your deal with Graem.
Now make a deal with me.
With enough time,
you and I... and Josh
can rebuild whatever is left
of this family.
After all, the legacy
I'm trying to preserve
will someday be his.
We can do this.
But first, you have to tell me
where Gredenko is.
Only after this man
takes me to see my son.
Bringing you here will only
complicate things,
and I need Gredenko now.
Tell me where he is.
No.
You may have misunderstood
my offer as a sign of weakness,
so let me
make it perfectly clear.
If you do not help me,
I see no future
for you or Josh.
I will walk
into the next room,
and I will kill him.
Right now.
Tell me... or Josh dies.
I will not tell you
what you want to know
until I have my son.
Give him back the phone.
(sobbing)
Yeah?
Bring her to me
at the Grandmont Hotel.
Room 2132.
We're on our way.
We got the address.
You did great.
Cuff him,
put him in the back.
(sniffles)
(handcuffs clicking)
Josh?
Uh, I'm just gonna
go downstairs
to get a soda.
Did you want anything?
No, thanks.
Did you look
in the minibar?
Uh, yeah, but there really
wasn't anything that I wanted.
Why don't you call
room service?
Well, I just feel like
getting out.
Josh...
Don't even
think about it.
No one's life is worth
the destruction
of everything I've built.
Now step away from the door.
--I was beginning
to worry.
Meeting went long.
Here's the President's
itinerary.
Oh, good.
This will work.
So when...
when does all this happen?
Now.
I need you to
authorize clearance
for someone to get
inside the bunker.
Once he's inside,
he'll carry the ball.
"Carry the ball"?
You mean, kill the President.
Sir, I would like to think
that we are beyond the point
of second-guessing ourselves.
This President has
endangered the lives
of millions of people.
You do not need to tell me
what the stakes are here.
So who is this person
we're putting inside?
He's a security specialist,
private sector,
but I've already put in
a request
for him to advise my group
on civil response options.
He has level two clearance;
I just need you upgrade him.
They will trace this thing
right back to me.
No. You won't even
be investigated.
We have a cover.
A cover? Who?
Assad.
Assad?
You're trying to make it
look like he did this?
Sir, all you need to do is
call in your authorization code.
(phone ringing)
That's all the information
you need on him.
Yeah, Dan.
Mr. Lennox, the President
has asked to see you.
Okay, tell the President
I will be with him in a moment.
Sir, our man will be here
within the hour.
Call me when you're done
with the President.
Tom, come in.
You asked to see me, sir?
Yes, I'd like to hear
your thoughts about something.
My thoughts on what, sir?
Assad's speech.
He's going live
in less than one hour,
and before I give him
my thoughts,
I wanted to hear yours.
Is there a problem?
Uh, no, sir, it's just...
What?
I assumed you were no longer
interested in my opinion, sir.
Tom, I still value
your judgment,
and if I've made you feel
otherwise, I apologize.
All right, sir.
How much longer?
I'm not sure.
I have to recalculate
the profile
for two of the target cities.
Hurry.
I don't want to be
exposed like this
any longer than necessary.
You think the authorities know
we're working with Fayed?
If they don't, they will soon.
WOMAN (harried):
I was in my kitchen
when I saw the flash.
I turned to look out my window,
and it just exploded,
all the windows.
There was glass everywhere.
And then there was this sound.
It was so loud.
Oh, man.
Hell of a day, huh?
Yeah, you could say that.
Can I get you anything else?
No.
Yeah.
Whiskey. Plain, single malt.
What kind?
That kind.
This?
Yeah.
And these.
Okay.
(register drawer opening)
Your change?
Keep it.
(grunts)
(sobbing)
(retching)
(phone rings)
MORRIS:
I'm on my way.
From where?
I told you, I went out
for a walk.
The Tac Team is about
to move in on Gredenko.
I need you at
your station.
I'm on my way.
Morris...
(sobbing)
Come with me.
I want you to put this on,
under your clothes.
It's just a precaution.
(frustrated grunt)
My hands are shaking.
Here.
I'm going to do everything
I can to get him back.
He's the only reason
I stayed with Graem...
He was the only good thing
I had left since...
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Get out.
(grunts)
You do exactly
what I tell you.
You understand me?
--Hey, Milo?
Hey.
How are you
holding up?
(groans)... They say
I'm going to be okay.
(sighs) It's...
So what happened?
I was stupid.
They don't pay me to be
a field agent.
Well, maybe
they should,
because, uh...
you protected Marilyn Bauer.
That's what I heard.
I had no idea
what I was doing.
The whole thing
just happened so fast.
You don't have to downplay
it to make me fell better.
You don't have
to do that.
Okay.
Uh...
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Well done.
Thanks.
I'm going to push Assad
to make these changes.
Your suggestions are
all excellent, Tom.
Oh? Just doing my job,
Mr. President.
I'd like you to be there
when he delivers this.
I will be, sir.
If you'll excuse me,
I have a briefing
with Senator Benson.
Of course, Tom.
(phone beeps)
Melinda?
I have some notes that need
to be taken to Assad.
MELINDA (over intercom):
Yes, Mr. President.
(quietly):
What did the president want?
He asked me to review
Assad's speech.
Which he'll never get
the chance to deliver.
Listen, sir... you need
to authorize that clearance.
Our man will be here
any minute.
It's in the works.
It's just taking a while
to complete the authorization.
All right, well, we need it
before he's here.
I will call security again.
I will phone you back
if there's any problem.
Meanwhile,
go meet with him.
This is Tom Lennox.
I need to speak to the ranking
Secret Service agent on site.
MAN (over phone):
Agent Hollister.
Agent Hollister,
this is Tom Lennox.
I need to see you immediately.
Yes, sir.
I can meet you
as soon as I get someone
to man my position,
which should be
in about 15 minutes.
No, that's not soon enough.
I've got something to show you.
Where are you right now?
"B" Wing, room 17.
I'm on my way.
(groans)
Carson wondered
if you were playing us.
He said that he didn't want
to bring you into this,
but I defended you!
I said that
we could trust you.
I told him that you understood.
Nothing justifies the killing
of a president.
This president is giving us
no choice.
Don't do this.
(grunting):
It's already done.
(panting)
Yes, uh, this is Reed Pollock.
I have a message for Agent
Hollister from Mr. Lennox.
Yes. Could you please tell him
that the issue has been resolved
and that Mr. Lennox won't need
to meet with him.
MAN (over phone):
Yes, sir.
Okay. Thanks.
NADIA:
We just confirmed
Marilyn Bauer's intel.
The Glasgow house is owned
by a Russian shell corporation
that Gredenko has a hidden
interest in.
Is Turner's team in place?
They'll let me know
when they're ready to go.
Chloe,
lock satellite
and establish
a comm link.
Nadia.
(quietly):
Where were you? I told you
not to take too long.
Sorry.
Comm unit's operational,
but the backup module
needs to be reset.
You better go do it now; the
operation starts in two minutes.
(quietly):
Come with me.
Do you realize that after
everything we've been through
what a betrayal this is?
I was a little late.
Morris, I can smell it
on your breath.
Yes... I took a drink,
but I spat it out
straight away.
Please...
I swear.
Chloe, look at me.
Look at me.
I am stone-cold sober.
You're losing control.
You're placing other people's
lives in danger.
(sighs)
I'm going to have to tell
Buchanan.
After everything
that has happened...
(chuckles)...
something had to give.
The important thing is,
that I realized I didn't want
to throw everything away,
especially you,
especially you.
And I stopped myself,
and that is a little victory.
Right?
I swear, it will
never happen again.
Please don't tell Buchanan
because you're right--
me getting back to work
is the best medicine.
I'll be watching you
for the rest of the shift.
Fine.
Call your sponsor.
I will.
Turner's team is
taking final positions.
Chloe, open
the video link.
Hal, what's your status?
No sign of a lookout.
Windows are covered,
but we're good to go.
Commence at your discretion.
Ryan, is your team ready?
Yes, sir.
Okay, we're going in on three,
two, one.
Clear!
First sweep,
all clear, sir.
Roger that.
TURNER (over link):
Mr. Buchanan, there no sign
of Gredenko or anyone.
Hal, as soon as you've
completed a full sweep,
process the place
for evidence.
Yes, sir.
Chloe, text Jack's
cell phone,
tell him we don't have Gredenko.
(panting)
(phone vibrating)
Hold up here.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Don't even think about
trying to warn my father.
Once he sees that you
brought me here,
he's more likely
to shoot you than I am.
Do you understand me?
Yeah.
Both of you
go up to the door.
You knock; when he let's you in,
I'll follow.
Let's go.
Marilyn, get back.
Open the door.
Now, go.
Where the hell is
my father?
I don't know,
I swear.
Where's Josh?
Marilyn, just stay calm.
Put these on.
(phone rings)
Answer it;
put it on speaker.
Hello?
PHILLIP:
Hello, Marilyn.
Jack, even when you were young,
I learned never
to underestimate you.
I didn't want to hurt Josh.
You've forced my hand.
Take a look out the window,
the adjacent roof.
(gasps)
Oh, Phillip,
please don't!
JACK:
Dad...
you only have
one play left here,
that's to try and cut a deal
with the government.
Explain your connection
to the nuke; tell them
you'll try and help them in
exchange for immunity.
Right now that is
your only option.
You pull that trigger
and that option is gone.
Do you understand me? Gone.
I'm no fool, Jack.
They're never going
to give me immunity
after everything
I've done.
You don't know that.
You don't know that for sure!
Right now they are desperate.
But either way, for you,
this is over.
Dad, it's over!
There is no empire to protect.
There's no legacy left.
There is Marilyn, Josh and me;
that's it.
Please, Dad.
I know you don't want
to hurt Josh.
I'm the one you want.
You let Josh go...
I will surrender.
Come alone, unarmed,
and I'll let Josh go.
But if you bring anyone else
into this,
I will kill him.
I understand.
Hang up the phone.
(speed dialing)
WOMAN (over phone):
CTU.
This is Jack Bauer.
I need you to send a team
over to the Grandmont Hotel
to pick up a hostile.
He's been secured.
He's in room 2132.
Jack?
--Hey, I need to talk to you.
About what?
Morris.
Not here.
Look, he came and saw
me in the infirmary...
Look, I know he's been
a little shaky.
Has he been drinking?
You smelled it on his breath?
Yeah.
I did, too.
I already talked
to him about it.
He didn't metabolize
the alcohol.
the alcohol?
I know it sounds weird,
but it's true.
He took a drink
and he spit it back out.
How do you know?
Because he told me.
And you believe him?
I don't have
to believe him.
I was married to him-- if he
was drunk, I would know.
He's not drunk.
He's been sober
for three years.
I didn't know he
was an alcoholic.
Now you know.
And you don't think Buchanan
should know about this?
No. If he slips up again,
I will personally tell Buchanan.
Let's just leave it for now.
Okay.
Okay. I want you to wait here
for Josh.
Do you think your father
will keep his word?
As long as I keep mine.
You know how to use this?
Point and shoot.
Once I get Josh,
do you want me to call CTU
and tell them
to send help?
No.
I need to take care
of this myself.
Jack...
thank you.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Just wait here.
I'm unarmed!
Dad!
Come out! I am unarmed!
PHILLIP:
That's close enough.
Turn around.
Now show me that you're not
wearing an ankle holster.
Take one step toward me
for every step Josh takes away.
Josh.
Slowly.
Your mother's waiting for you
in the stairwell
around the corner. Go. Go!
That's it.
Oh, Josh!
Oh, God...
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Go.
I never meant
for this to happen, Jack.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't know how exactly,
but Gredenko found out
about my role in David Palmer's
assassination.
So... he blackmailed me,
forced me to cooperate.
So it was Gredenko who had you
divert some of the bombs
the company was responsible
for destroying?
He's a radical nationalist.
Told me that he wanted
to preserve some of the arsenal
for the day when the Soviet
Union would be reestablished.
I believed him because I had to.
When did you find out
he sold the bombs to Fayed?
Not until one of the bombs
was detonated in Valencia.
That's the truth?!
Absolutely.
I've been looking for Gredenko
ever since.
So that I could find out
what he knew about Fayed,
and stop all this.
I'm a patriot, Jack.
I never wanted any harm
to come to this country.
You want to lie to yourself,
you go ahead,
but stop lying to me!
You let all of this happen
just so you could cover up
what you did!
(wry chuckle)
You have all the smarts
that Graem never had.
You'd have handled
Gredenko before this
all got out of control.
You know, none of this
would have happened
if you hadn't turned your back
on me.
So that you could become--
what?--
a civil servant.
So...
your people will use Gredenko
to find this terrorist,
and the truth will come out
about all I've done.
We never got Gredenko.
Then all this was for nothing.
On your knees.
I didn't have to end
like this, Jack.
(gun chamber clicks)
You could've had it all.
I want you to know...
...I never wanted you to feel
like I had turned my back
on you.
That I had turned my back
on the family.
I just had to go my own way.
Do things for myself. I...
It was never good enough
for you.
I'm sorry.
Anyway...
I'm ready.
What are you waiting for?
Do it!
Damn you!
(phone rings)
Yes?
My name is Jack Bauer.
Who am I talking to?
You must've exhausted all
your options to find Gredenko.
Who is this?
It's Charles Logan, Jack.
I might be able to help you, but
we need to talk face-to-face.
Where are you?
I'm near the airport.
Good, you're local.
CTU knows where I am.
Come and see me, Jack,
as soon as possible
And come alone.
I'm looking forward to it.
www.tvsubtitles.net