JACK:
That's hyocine-pentothal.
You will experience a pain
I can't even describe.
At 8cc's, I run the risk
of inducing heart attack.
Four cc's!
That's 8cc's total, Jack.
His vitals are spiking
across the line.
Four cc's!
(screaming)
The connection you found
between Dad and Gredenko
had to do with a contract
that was awarded to us.
What did an ex-Russian general
have to do with the contract?
It was his job to release
the old nukes...
into the U.S.
for decommissioning.
He knows you didn't
tell him everything.
Yeah, and I won't.
You know I won't, Dad.
Have to be sure.
(muffled grunting)
(muffled screaming)
I would like you
to appear on television
and appeal to members
of Islamic communities
everywhere
to come forward with
any information regarding Fayed.
I certainly can't
reach out to them for help,
but I know you can.
Fayed has already
called me a traitor.
And many others will follow him
if there is even a suspicion
that I am an American puppet!
Not a puppet, a partner.
At least when it comes to
finding these nuclear weapons.
The President just rejected
every one of my proposals.
REED:
A change in leadership
is imperative to ensure
this nation's security.
I'm not talking about
holding hearings.
Something more... immediate
would have
to happen.
This is the engineer?
You've got the wrong man.
(grunts)
FAYED:
You're going to modify this
so that I can use it
to reprogram the bombs.
You will do it.
The question is
how much pain will be inflicted
on you before you comply.
(Morris screaming)
(gasping, screaming)
Stop!
I'll do it.
Arm it.
Very good.
(pumps shotgun)
TURNER:
Fayed's already gone.
The reprogramming device that
Fayed had me build for him,
if it's not here, it means
he took it with him.
And with it,
he can activate
the other bombs he has
anytime he wants.
(helicopter rotors whirring)
* *
(phone ringing)
Yes?
FAYED:
I have the arming device.
But I had to leave
one of the suitcases behind.
What happened?
CTU found me.
I needed to preoccupy them
with a bomb to enable my escape.
The delivery system software
was programmed
for five detonations
at five high-priority targets.
Because of your carelessness,
we are now down to three.
More than enough for
our needs, Gredenko.
You just make sure the delivery
system arrives on schedule.
The trucks have left Nevada,
and they'll reach the location
within two hours.
Good.
You can use the time you have
to reprogram
your targeting software.
Call me when it's completed.
(vehicle engine starts)
Since the FAA
was unable to track
Fayed's chopper, we have to
assume it set down somewhere
outside the containment area.
We may not know
where Fayed is,
but we do know he's in
possession of a device
that will enable
him to activate
the three remaining suitcase
nukes in his arsenal.
Our only potential lead
was uploaded
from the hard drive of a laptop
recovered at the scene
by Jack Bauer and his team.
Milo.
There was an e-mail fragment
I was able to restore
from the computer's hard drive;
it made reference to
recent communications between
Fayed and Dmitri Gredenko.
Gredenko is the former
Soviet general in charge
of turning over Russian nukes
to the U.S. for decommission.
Ultimately, he was the source of
the weapons Fayed now possesses.
So, clearly, Gredenko's
more involved in this
than we realized.
What's his interest
in helping Fayed?
Gredenko's an ultranationalist.
His desire to harm this country,
economically and otherwise,
is in sync with Fayed's.
Have we gotten any updated intel
on his location?
BUCHANAN:
Interpol just confirmed
he's no longer in Moscow.
Since the point
of origin
fingerprint on the
e-mail fragment
was Pacific time,
I think it's safe to assume
he's somewhere on the West
Coast, possibly Los Angeles.
Chloe, run a data sweep through
INS and customs channels.
See if we can track
how he got in the country.
(sighs softly)
Morris.
We have to take
him to Medical.
I just want to talk
to him for a minute.
Are you okay?
Give us ten minutes.
Bill.
Jack.
We able to pull anything
off the hard drive we found?
We have.
Apparently, Fayed's been in
contact with Dmitri Gredenko.
Gredenko?
It's looking
more and more like
he's been aiding
Fayed's operation all along.
You think he's here
in Los Angeles.
Evidence on the hard
drive points to that.
What leads do you have
on Gredenko?
Your father's company
was contracted
to dispose of the nukes
Gredenko was
to hand over.
My brother Graem
oversaw those contracts,
not my father.
He still might have
some information.
Okay, fine, I'll talk to him.
Where is he?
He went to see
your brother's body
in the morgue.
Okay, thanks.
Chloe, you all right?
Yeah.
Thank you for saving
Morris's life.
Yeah.
I'm really glad Fayed didn't
kill you this morning.
Me, too.
I have to talk
to my father.
I... just want to thank you
for everything.
* *
Dad.
Whatever your brother
may have done,
he didn't deserve this.
I didn't mean
for this to happen.
Yeah.
Well...
Dad, I'm sorry about Graem.
I am.
But right now,
CTU wants to know about
your connection
to Dmitri Gredenko.
What?
We believe that
he's working with Fayed.
They want to know
what you know about him.
He was the Russian liaison
on our government contract to
decommission Soviet nukes. Why?
What kind of dealings
did you have with him?
Couple of phone calls to
Moscow, that's about it.
Do you know of any contacts
that Gredenko might have
which would allow Fayed to move
the remaining four nukes?
Look, Jack, like I told you,
I had virtually no involvement.
Graem oversaw the project,
he dealt with Gredenko.
Whatever you need to know
died with him.
You know where Marilyn is?
No.
Why?
You gonna question her, too?
She's probably with Josh.
He's taking the death
of his father
pretty hard.
Leave them
alone, Jack.
Let them grieve
in peace.
I'll make a call to some
of the company executives.
About Gredenko.
Maybe Graem shared something
that I wasn't privy to.
Thank you.
DOCTOR:
Try to rest.
You're doing
very well.
You can go in now.
Morris?
How are you feeling?
Say something.
What is there to say?
You were tortured.
You held out as
long as you could.
I armed a nuclear bomb.
You had to.
Fayed was gonna kill you.
I wish to God he had.
Because of me,
Fayed has a device that can
arm all the bloody
suitcase nukes
he wants.
You can't blame yourself.
When the next bomb goes off, and
thousands of more people die,
everybody will remember
that I was the one
that made it possible.
That's not
gonna happen.
'Cause we're gonna find Fayed
and we're gonna stop him,
and none of this
will matter.
Are you any closer
to finding him?
No.
Just go, darling.
Go.
(phone rings)
Yes, Mr. Bauer?
We've got a problem.
Gredenko's here.
In L.A.?
Are you sure?
Yes.
Only, they don't
know where he is.
We've got to get to him
before they do.
If Gredenko
implicates me, everything--
the company I founded
and spent my life protecting--
it's over,
you understand?
Yes. I'll put a
team together.
I'll monitor
CTU from here.
If I hear of anything,
I'll call you.
Yes, sir.
I don't care
what you have to do.
You find Gredenko,
and you kill him.
Understood.
I talked to my father
about Gredenko.
He said he'd make
some inquiries, but I
think it's a dead end.
He doesn't
know anything.
The news from here
isn't much better.
But Milo managed to trace
the fragment he pulled off
Fayed's computer
to a local I.P. network.
It confirms Gredenko is
definitely here in L.A.
I've got my people
monitoring chatter,
data-mining
interagency backlogs
on Gredenko's activities
prior to going underground.
Right now,
that's all we can do.
Okay.
Have a seat, Jack.
What is it?
It's the toxicology report
on your brother's body.
Forensic evidence indicates that
the hyocine-pentathol
you administered to Graem
during his interrogation
caused his coronary.
There's something else.
I saw the field tape,
and Rick Burke's
report for Division.
He said you exceeded protocols,
even after he warned you
of dangerous levels.
That's true.
Agent Burke tried to warn me.
Then you pulled
a gun on him.
You must realize
how this looks, Jack.
Coming right after your
brother tried to kill you.
I lost control.
Because you found out he was
responsible for David Palmer's
assassination.
Yes, because I found out
about David Palmer's
assassination.
'Cause I found out
about everything.
I lost control.
I tried to tell you I didn't
think I could do this.
This job.
I wanted to kill my brother.
I wanted him dead.
I was standing over him...
and I looked up and I saw
my father in the doorway...
and everything just stopped.
I ordered Agent Burke
to shut down the IV, he did.
I thought we caught it in time.
Bill, I did not set out...
to kill my brother.
I swear to you.
I can adjust the report
before I send it
to Division.
No.
Jack...
an Internal Affairs
investigation
will impede our search
for Fayed and Gredenko.
Right now, you are
critical to that.
You cannot cover this up.
I ordered Agent Burke
to administer
the hyocine-pentathol.
I killed my brother.
Whatever the consequences are,
I accept them.
Bill...
do this right.
Okay.
--I'll submit the report as is.
--There is some difficulty
with my statement?
A little more emphasis
on religion,
and less on politics
than I expected.
Many of the people
you wish me to sway
have been persuaded
that our cause is a holy one.
I am not innocent
in this manipulation.
So I must address them
in these terms
if I am to enlist
their cooperation.
(knocking on glass)
Yes?
Excuse me, sir.
Vice President Daniels
is calling for you.
Would you like to take
it in your office?
No, I'll take it in here.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Noah?
Thank you for taking my call,
Mr. President.
I know you're pressed for time.
What can I do for you?
I'll get right to my point.
I've made no secret
of my disappointment
that you rejected
Tom Lennox's plan
for mass internment
of Arab nationals
in our country.
The plan did not delineate
country of origin, Noah.
It was nothing more than
a blanket proposal
to arrest and detain
thousands of Muslims
living here,
without due process
I might add.
Be that as it may, since,
as I understand it,
the terrorists
have now acquired
the capability to arm
the three remaining
nuclear weapons,
I'm asking you
to reconsider.
And I thought
I told you that
my decision was not
open for debate.
Well, that's unfortunate,
Mr. President,
since the majority
of your Cabinet feels
that you're making
a tragic mistake.
I respect that.
But I firmly believe
that our best
chance of stopping
further attacks will come
from the intelligence
drawn from Islamic communities.
And you hope to obtain that
by letting a known terrorist
leader address the world
on American airwaves.
The man has murdered
countless innocents
over the past 20 years,
and you are putting your hopes
for this country's
safety on him.
Not entirely...
but to the extent
that he can help us, yes.
Mr. President...
you approached me to be your
running mate because you knew
I could deliver voters
who questioned your...
experience,
who were afraid
that your Presidency
would be too weak
on national defense,
and I... assured them
otherwise, but now
you're proving them right.
There's a thin line between
conviction and stubbornness.
You can stand firm,
but just know that...
you're standing alone.
Are we done?
Clearly.
You are paying a very high price
for doing this.
Not as high as my country
will pay if I'm wrong.
As someone who has
alienated followers
by choosing
the unpopular course,
I suggest you tread carefully
among your people.
Mr. Assad, our cultures
are very different, sir.
It's not just a cultural
issue, Mr. President.
It's simple
human nature.
They will come after you.
I assure you of that.
You sure it's safe
to talk in here?
Yes, this area is
currently unmonitored.
All right.
You intimated you had some
sort of plan of dealing
with the President.
Palmer's refusal to implement
your proposals will
unquestionably lead
to the loss
of many more American lives.
And I, and many others like me
who love this country,
will not
stand by idly
and let that happen.
So what is it you propose?
I think you know.
I need to hear.
Definitive action.
We are in the middle
of a national crisis
and he is in over his head.
He's brought
this on himself.
Listen, before you start
reconsidering
and report me, just know
I will deny that we
ever had this conversation.
I'm not...
I'm not
reconsidering.
I know what you're saying
is necessary, I just...
cannot believe it has
come to this.
Who else is involved?
You don't need to know that.
I'd like to know
who I'm dealing with.
Right now you're
dealing with me.
Vice President Daniels,
is he involved?
No.
The vice president doesn't
know anything about this.
But we do know that he
shares our sentiment
in regard to the current
state of affairs,
and that he will
enact your initiatives
once he has the power to do so.
You seem pretty certain
this is going to work.
More so with your help.
I need the President's
itinerary.
Specifically, in regards
to Assad's televised address.
I do not have
the proper clearance.
I need you to access it.
Why? W-why do you need this?
Damn it, Reed.
We're talking about
removing the President
of the United States.
Do not keep me
in the dark here.
I never said
that I was
the architect of this.
I'm just a conduit.
Besides, for your sake, I think
that it is very important
that we maintain
a certain level
of plausible deniability.
The less you know,
the better.
I'll get you that itinerary.
--Marilyn.
Hi.
I heard you were with Josh,
I didn't want to disturb you.
Yeah, well, he's taking it
pretty hard.
He loved his
father very much.
I'm very sorry.
You don't owe me an apology.
Maybe they haven't told you
the circumstances
of Graem's heart attack.
They told me enough.
Look, Jack, I know the kind
of man Graem was.
Even if he did die because
of your interrogation,
I don't blame you.
I blame him.
The truth is, I've been trying
to leave Graem for years.
But he threatened
to take Josh away from me.
Said I'd never see him again.
Did Josh know
what he was like?
No.
I always tried to protect him
from the truth
about his father.
What have you told him
about his father's death?
Only that he had a heart attack.
That's enough for now.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, I have to go
back to work.
If there's anything
I can do.
Is it true there are more bombs
out there?
Yes.
Are you any closer
to finding them?
No, we've hit a road block.
Right now we're looking
for a Russian operative
who we believe is helping
the terrorists.
Graem knew him.
Russian?
A man named Gredenko.
You know him?
No.
Come here.
But you know something.
Maybe.
It was probably nothing.
It was months ago.
Marilyn, anything you
can tell us might help.
Graem was going out
a lot at night,
and, uh, he said
it was work related,
but I didn't believe him.
I thought he was having
an affair on me,
so one night I followed him.
It wasn't out
of jealousy.
It was... it was
for leverage.
Anything I could use against him
to get custody of Josh
if I left him.
Where did he go?
It was to a house in West L.A.
I went to the window.
The blinds were drawn,
but I could hear him inside
talking to some men.
They had Russian accents.
What were they saying?
I couldn't hear them
clearly enough,
and frankly, once I realized
he wasn't cheating on me,
I got in the car
and went home.
Do you remember the
address of the house?
No. Jack, I'm sorry,
I wasn't paying attention,
I was more concerned
about getting caught.
Marilyn, it is vital that
we find this man Gredenko.
If we retrace the route
that you took that night,
do you think that you would
recognize the house?
Maybe.
Maybe?
Yeah.
Yeah. I think so.
Wait right here.
Jack.
I think I might have
a lead on Gredenko.
It's a real shot
in the dark,
but right now
we don't have anything.
I wanted to know if I had your
permission to follow it up.
What do you got?
Hey, Marilyn.
Hey, Phillip.
How you doing?
I'm hanging in there.
What's going on with you
and Jack?
He's looking for someone.
He thinks I can help.
You mean Gredenko?
He questioned me about
the same thing earlier.
What do you know
about him?
Nothing really.
I followed Graem
to a house one night.
He, um, he met
with some Russians.
What house?
I don't know.
It was in West L.A.
Jack wants to take me
over there
to see if it can
jog my memory.
Phillip,
I don't know how long
this is gonna take.
And I can't leave
Josh alone.
Could you please stay with him?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Your Tac team's
assembling outside.
I'm sending Milo
along with you.
Milo? Why?
I want a
tech available
to pull intel
off any computers
we might find at
Gredenko's location.
Chloe will be running
point from here.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry about leaving
you, sweetheart.
But I'll be back
as soon as I'm done
helping Uncle Jack.
Helping him with what?
Where are you going?
I'll explain later.
Right now I want you
to stay here
with your grandfather,
all right?
Marilyn.
I was thinking maybe I would
take Josh back to my house.
Why?
Why can't you just wait
with him here until I get back?
Marilyn, look, he's
frightened of this place.
Understandably so.
I think he needs to be
in familiar surroundings
right now.
All right.
All right, I'll, um,
I'll clear it with
Mr. Buchanan.
Will you explain
things to Josh?
Yeah, sure.
All right, you listen
to your grandfather.
He's in charge.
Phillip, thank you.
Sure.
Sorry to take you away
from Josh.
All you need to do is
identify the house.
I promise you I will not
put you in any danger.
I know.
Mr. Buchanan,
I'd like it if Josh's
grandfather could take him back
to his house.
Of course.
We should go.
Bill, I'll be on comm.
We'll be leaving soon, Josh.
I have to make one phone call.
Just be a minute.
MAN (on phone):
Yes, sir.
Have your men find
and secure a house
in West L.A.
Fine.
I'll text you with the address.
--Morris, we have a lead.
Jack's sister-in-law
thinks she knows
where Gredenko is.
Jack and a Tac team are heading
over there now.
I need your help
running tactical.
Don't be ridiculous.
We're shorthanded.
So get your shirt on,
and let's go.
Running tactical
is what you do best,
why would you
need my help?
Oh... I get it.
You came in here
to give me a pep talk.
Get me back
working behind
that computer
and everything
will be tickety-boo.
Why don't you be a little
less obvious, Chloe.
I'm a coward, not an idiot.
Morris,
I know you've been
through a lot today,
but you're really starting
to piss me off.
Well, let's add that to
my list of failings.
Why did you do that?
I didn't want to.
Look...
if you're gonna try
and save a bloke...
save someone who's worth it.
Stop it, stop it.
Jack and his team are entering
a hostile situation
and they need CTU back up.
Yes, I can do it alone,
but there'd be less
chance of a mistake
if you would help.
So why don't you stop feeling
sorry for yourself
and get back to work!
Milo, we just passed
98th Street.
Roger that, Jack,
we're maintaining our position
six blocks behind you.
I can't imagine what you went
through in China, Jack.
When you were over there,
I thought about you.
I tried not to.
I guess, I've been trying not
to think about you
for over 20 years.
Marilyn, we don't need to talk
about this.
It was your father, wasn't it?
He drove you away.
Tried to pressure you
to work for his company.
Is that why you left,
and enlisted
in the military?
There were a
lot of reasons.
Was I one of them?
No.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Marilyn, it's me.
Don't say anything...
just listen.
I don't want Jack
to know I'm on the line.
Do you understand?
Okay.
You're involved in
something that's much bigger
than you can
possibly imagine.
So here's the deal.
Unless you do exactly
what I say...
I will hurt Josh.
If you don't
believe that,
you might want
to consider this...
Graem's death
was not an accident.
I killed him.
I want you to say,
"Thank you, Susan."
Thank you, Susan.
Now, you're not going
to take Jack to the house
where Graem
met the Russians--
you're going to take him
to a different address--
9407 Hindry Place.
You got it?
Yeah.
Good.
Now, you do this for me,
and I promise you,
you will see Josh again.
If you don't, he dies.
Okay.
9407 Hindry Place.
Do the right thing, Marilyn.
I already lost a son today.
Don't make me lose a grandson.
Good-bye, Susan.
Are you all right?
Fine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
That was my office.
A lot of the roads are still
shut because of the bomb.
Can we get home?
No. And no one knows seems to
know when they'll open up again.
Then what do we do?
We'll go to a hotel.
We can stay there
until they clear up.
Marilyn, is any
of this familiar?
Yes.
Jack?
What?
What is it?
It's nothing.
I thought I saw the house.
But I was wrong.
Oh, that was it.
Hindry Place.
Milo, we got a street.
Copy that, Jack.
Relaying it to CTU now.
How long before the new targets
are reprogrammed?
20 minutes.
You still think you can
trust the Arabs?
They serve their purpose.
Our country lost the Cold War
because it was afraid
to use these weapons
against the Americans.
Today we will correct
that mistake.
And the Arabs will take
all the blame.
--All right, we're on it.
Chloe.
Marilyn remembers the street
where she believes
her husband met with Gredenko.
Hindry Place.
That's a mile away from where
they're looking. Is she sure?
That's what she told Jack.
Pull up all access roads
in and out of the area.
I'm in the middle of
reconfiguring the uplink.
I'll put Morris on it.
Your call.
I know you're lying to me.
Just like my mom.
You're all treating me
like I'm just some
stupid little kid.
What are you talking about?
I want to know why my dad died.
What's your mother told you?
It was a heart attack.
I know, but...
I know he was
doing something
illegal or whatever.
But nobody's telling me
what it was, and I just
want to know.
Did it have to do with the nuke?
Look, Josh...
you're gonna hear a lot
of things about your father,
what he may or
may not have done.
I'm not gonna pretend
it's going to be
easy for you.
You know,
no matter what...
I'm gonna be
there for you.
That's it. The pale blue
house on the right.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
We've got an address.
9407 Hindry Place.
Initiate tactical
response with CTU.
Have them bring up the
schematics of the house.
Meet me in the alley
behind the target.
All right, I'm on it.
Hold on.
We're going after
the blue house.
Advise your men,
non-lethal force.
We need Gredenko alive.
Jack...
Marilyn, I want you to stay
in the tactical van.
You'll be safe there.
But, I have...
Jack, I've got the schematics.
There are two entrances.
One in the front,
one on the west
side of the house.
Okay, I'll contact
CTU as soon as
we've got Gredenko
in custody.
Milo, I want you
to stay with Marilyn.
Are your men ready?
We're set.
Let's go.
All teams go. Go!
Go! Go!
Bomb! Everyone out!
(loud explosion)
Oh!
Jack!
We've gotta go!
No! No!
Get in the van!
Get in the van
and close the door!
Jack? Jack, can you hear me?
(automatic gunfire)
(tires screeching)
Oh, they're coming!
Get out! Come on! Move! Move!
(screams)
Don't hit the woman!
We need her alive!
(gunshots blasting)
Move!
Move! Come on, come on! Move!
Go, go, go!
(grunting):
All agents report in.
All agents report in now.
Calling in for EMT.
www.tvsubtitles.net