-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
We-We're going t...
(grunts)
HAYES:
Get Medical right away!
LISA:
It is incontestable
Wayne Palmer
won't be able to continue his
duties as commander-in-chief.
I have the fate of the western
world and the lives
of millions of Americans
hanging in the balance,
and I can't...
stop thinking about you.
Bill Buchanan had Fayed
in custody...
and he let him go.
Karen Hayes put it
in a blue file over at Homeland.
Someone is going to have
to go down--
the farther from the
president, the better.
Are you asking me to resign?
HAYES:
No, Bill.
I have to fire you.
You should work with Milo,
you know, get cozy.
Don't be such a jealous jerk.
Um, the day I'm jealous
is the day I kill myself.
Is there anything else?
How about don't arm
nuclear bombs
for terrorists.
Sorry.
That's not how I feel.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not-- it just slipped
out of my mouth.
Morris!
You shouldn't have
any trouble running CTU.
I'm not the right
choice to take over.
You are the right choice.
Nothing will change
operationally.
Your objective remains the same:
bring in Jack Bauer
before he can hand over
the component to the Chinese.
Mr. Bauer.
Let's do this.
Audrey walks out of here alone.
As soon as I see that she
gets down near the bridge,
then I'll give you
the component.
DOYLE:
All right, this is
going down now, Nadia.
Jack is about to hand over
the component.
NADIA:
Mike, don't let that happen.
MAN:
Cheng and his men
have escaped from the hotel.
They're in three black Hummers,
heading north.
Agent Bauer,
get down!
Weapon is down!
Down on the ground
now!
Who is your commanding officer?
DOYLE:
I am, Jack.
I got to take
you into custody.
Where's the sub-circuit board?
Cheng's got it.
I was set to blow the building
and destroy the component
until you engaged us
in a firefight.
I had this handled.
Audrey, it's over.
It's all right,
you're safe.
Help me, Jack.
Please don't let
them do this to me.
Audrey!
They've done something to her.
You've got to help her, please.
(inaudible)
My God.
(helicopter propeller whirring)
Mr. Bauer, was this
the only C-4 that
was in the building?
Yes, that's everything;
the building's clean.
(sniffles)
Ms. Raines,
my name is Mike Doyle.
I'm a CTU field agent.
We're hoping
you saw or heard something
while Cheng was holding you...
something that could
lead us to him.
You're safe now,
Ms. Raines.
Jack bought your freedom
from the Chinese
with a component
that contains
highly sensitive
Russian technology.
Can you understand me,
Ms. Raines?
Help me, Jack.
Please don't let them
do this to me.
I want CHP to work with military
on roadblocks.
You need to set up three-
and five-mile perimeters
from Cheng's
last confirmed location.
I need satellite scans analyzed
and forwarded to me now.
(over phone):
The system's overloaded.
Yeah, I understand
the system's overloaded.
Those are your orders.
(knock at door)
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. Morris,
I read your request
for a transfer out of Comm.
Mm-hmm.
Is this because you
and Chloe had a fight?
Look, your facts
are essentially correct.
The why I don't see as being
anybody's business.
Look, Morris, you've had
a hard day-- we all have--
but... I really need you
on the floor.
So I'm sorry; your request
for a transfer is denied.
(conversing indistinctly)
You're new to the
job, and I'm just
trying to protect you
from being caught
in the middle
of a very awkward
professional situation.
You're asking me
to indulge
your private melodrama
while we're in the middle
of an international crisis.
Bill Buchanan said he'd
consider my request.
Did he tell you that?
Bill Buchanan
is not running CTU, I am.
I've made my decision.
Nadia...
Go back to your station, keep
your personal life to yourself.
You can deal with this tomorrow.
Nadia...
We're done here, Morris.
(phone rings)
Anything else you want to say?
Oh, yeah.
This is Nadia Yassir.
Nadia, it's Mike.
Do you have a lead on Cheng?
We're working on it.
How did it go
with Audrey Raines?
Not good.
What, she doesn't know anything
about Cheng?
Where he was holding her,
what he was doing?
She's completely
nonresponsive.
I'm not a shrink,
but whatever they did
to her in China...
it left her with some kind
of post-traumatic reaction.
Bring her back here.
District will want a specialist
to take a look at her.
Do you have any idea
what Jack was thinking?
Yeah. He had this
motel rigged with C-4.
He was going to take
this whole place down
as soon as Audrey was safe.
He was willing to
sacrifice his life to
get Audrey released?
And his plan would've worked
if I hadn't intervened.
You saved his life.
But I lost the component.
Jack went against a direct order
from the White House.
This was no one's fault
but his.
We're on our way back.
Stevenson, you take Ms. Raines.
I'll go with Bauer.
(helicopter propeller
whirring nearby)
Audrey!
DOYLE:
Jack, stop.
Where are you taking her?
To CTU, Jack, the same
place you're going.
Let me talk to her, just
for a couple of minutes, please.
You saw what condition
she's in, Jack.
I know her.
I know what she's been through.
I might be the only person
that can get through to her.
Please.
You're under arrest, Jack.
We'll discuss this back at CTU.
Put him in the
second chopper.
Mike! Let me talk to her now.
HAYES:
CTU is pouring
all their resources
into finding Cheng,
and this executive order
gives them authority to close
all ports and
border crossings.
We can't keep migrant workers
from crossing our borders
at will.
How the hell are we supposed to
stop a determined enemy agent?
Well, I think the point
is to slow him down, sir,
so that CTU
has more time to find him,
but I agree, Cheng
will find a way
to smuggle out the
Russian component
eventually.
So then Russia loses
its defensive edge against the
Chinese and Moscow blames us.
We will do everything in
our power to prevent that, sir.
(sighs)
(slams book)
Thank you.
Karen...
Yes.
Tom told me
about you and Bill,
how you had to...
fire him from CTU.
How did he take it?
Not well.
Karen.
Yes.
You and I have had our...
difficulties in the past,
but I want you to know that...
I value your role here
and that I appreciate
your sacrifice.
Thank you.
(knock at door)
Excuse me, sir.
What is it, Tom?
Russian President's
calling for you
in the telepresence suite.
He insisting on a face-to-face,
Did he say what he wants?
No, but he's on with the heads
of military
and intelligence services.
I want both of you
with me on this.
(gasps)
Palmer's still
in a coma.
Looks like Noah's going to be
acting president for some time.
Good for Noah.
And good for us.
The only thing he cares about
is pushing
his lunatic foreign agenda.
Any pending legislation
on spending...
you'll defer to me.
Now that he is
acting president,
we're going to have to
be even more careful
We will be.
I've got half an hour.
Let's stop talking.
President Suvarov,
you're on a secure conference
with Vice President Daniels.
President Suvarov.
Mr. Vice President.
You know my Chief of Staff,
Tom Lennox, and Karen Hayes,
my National
Security Advisor.
How can we help you?
Some very troubling news has
been brought to my attention.
What would that be?
The nuclear weapons
that fell into terrorists' hands
contained proprietary
Russian technology
that up until now
has only been available
to your government and mine.
I'm well aware of that, sir.
Then you are also
"well aware"
that an FB-sub-circuit board
from one of the weapons
is now in the possession of an
agent of the Chinese government.
Do you deny that, sir?
Mr. President,
all I'm prepared
to tell you is that...
we're in control
of the situation.
Mr. Vice President,
my generals have confirmed
that this component contains
information that will compromise
our defensive capabilities.
You must stop the Chinese from
leaving your country with it.
I don't appreciate being
dictated to, Mr. President.
Now, I don't need
to remind you
that it was a Russian general
who allowed those bombs
to enter the U.S.
in the first place,
the same Russian general
who conspired to detonate them.
That does not change
our grave concerns
about this development.
If you do not intercept
this component,
my generals have instructions
to initiate
an appropriate response.
Mr. President...
Good night, sir.
How the hell did the Russians
find out about this?!
Russian intelligence
must have been tracking it.
No, no, no, the information
circle is too tight.
Only select people
at the White House
and CTU even knew about this.
So you're saying there's a spy?
There is no other explanation.
I will start an immediate
internal investigation
into the White House staff.
I'll do the same
at CTU, sir.
What are your reads on Suvarov?
How seriously do
we take his threat?
Oh, I would say very, sir.
With the Chinese in possession
of the component,
the Russians will
need to extend
their defensive line
in Central Asia.
We have a military base
in the region.
Which the Russians
will have to target.
We will have to
respond in kind...
Which will escalate things
beyond just a regional conflict.
Give CTU whatever they need
to find this man Cheng.
(speaking Chinese)
OPERATIVE:
Yes?
I've interfaced the component.
You should have the schematics.
Yes, they've downloaded.
I'm running a diagnostic
on the component now.
Good. We'll be there
in less than an hour.
Wait.
(typing)
(sighs):
There's a problem.
What?
The circuit board is damaged.
Can you fix it?
No, not unless I have
The security override.
We don't have access
to that information.
Without it, this technology's
useless to us!
We'll have to find someone
who has the necessary expertise.
--LITTLE
I'm gonna take a quick shower.
Noah's waiting for me
to get back.
(shower running)
* *
(cell phone ringing)
Yes?
We're all set.
And the girl doesn't know
you're working for us?
Not a clue.
Good.
Morris.
Yeah?
I saw you arguing with Nadia.
Yeah.
Was it about us?
I asked for a transfer.
It was denied.
Why did you do that?
Because working with you
is becoming very uncomfortable.
I told you I was sorry.
You said I should stop
helping terrorists
arm nuclear bombs.
We've both said things
that we haven't mean before.
Yeah, I know.
But...
there's a line,
darling, and...
and you crossed it.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying that...
it's over.
There's no going back.
We're done.
Morris.
Look at me.
You don't have to do this.
We're done.
But, Morris...
(sniffles)
(sobbing quietly)
Nadia, the situation
has escalated with the Russians.
They know the Chinese
have the component,
and they're threatening
military action
unless we stop them from
taking it out of the country.
How did the
Russians find out?
A leak.
Tom Lennox is
looking into it here,
and he wants you to start
an investigation there.
I'll let Internal
Affairs know right away.
Now, what about
Audrey Raines?
Has she provided any information
that will lead us to Cheng?
Not yet,
but the psychiatric specialist
from District has just arrived.
So we're hoping he
can get her to talk.
Do you have any other leads?
Not at the moment.
That's unfortunate.
I cannot emphasize enough
how important it is
that we stop Cheng.
If you need more resources,
you need to let me know now.
Do you understand?
I will.
One more thing.
To be honest, Karen,
what we need is Bill Buchanan.
But there's a rumor
flying around you fired him.
Well, that's complicated, Nadia.
Not as far as
we're concerned.
You know more than anyone
how good he is at this job.
I don't see how something
like this could happen
when we're in
the middle of a crisis.
Look, I'm not at liberty
to discuss this.
Just keep me updated with
your progress on finding Cheng.
Dr. Bradley. I'm Nadia Yassir,
acting head of CTU.
We're under a time crunch now,
so I'd like to get started
with Ms. Raines
immediately.
She's being prepped in medical.
These men can take you there.
I'll join you shortly.
Thank you.
I want to hear your first
impressions as soon as possible.
Of course.
Nadia, Doyle and Jack
just landed.
Okay, have Doyle secure Bauer,
and then have him
meet me in medical.
Okay.
Can you leave us alone, please?
Thank you.
Ms. Raines.
Ms. Raines, I'm Dr. Bradley.
I'm here to perform a medical
evaluation to help you remember
whatever you can
about this man Cheng--
where you were held,
what you heard.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Come here. Look at this.
Please, you've got
to let me talk to her.
You know CTU's protocol.
You know how they're
gonna interrogate her.
They're gonna make her retreat
farther inside herself.
Please,
listen to me!
Sit down.
This will make it
more comfortable.
Mike.
Please, I'm
begging you.
Take care of her.
Jack's in
holding three.
How you doing?
White House is pressuring us
to find Cheng.
We have to hope
he can get some information
out of her.
(knocking)
Dr. Bradley,
this is Agent Doyle.
He was involved in
rescuing Ms. Raines.
Do you have a diagnosis?
My preliminary
is she's
a type three catatonic, capable
of following simple commands
and repeating words and basic
phrases, but otherwise,
utterly unresponsive.
Do you think
that you'll be able
to get the information
we need from her?
Within your timeframe?
Not without intervention.
What does that mean?
Ms. Raines is suffering from
severe psychological abuse,
amplified by pharmacological
agents, as evidenced by
more than 100 injection sites
on her arms, feet and groin.
It's gonna be next to
impossible to communicate
with her in
the near term unless
we essentially attempt
to shock her out of this state.
So they used drugs
to torture her,
and you're gonna give her more?
These are different compounds,
sir, used for different reasons.
What are the risks?
22 percent of patients
experience
cardiovascular events,
some of it
neurological.
In the most extreme
cases, death can occur.
We can't do this.
No, Doyle.
I am not
comfortable with
the high percentage
of adverse reactions either.
But this treatment
is the only way
you're gonna get anything
out of her in the time you have.
Maybe not. One of our agents,
Jack Bauer, has a long
history with her,
and the Chinese put him
through something similar.
Listen, it makes sense
to see what Jack
can draw from her before
we do anything riskier.
Doctor?
Yeah, I know who Jack Bauer is.
I read Ms. Raines' file
on the way over.
And in my opinion, contact
with him will more likely
upset her than
encourage her to talk.
But there's no chance
of her dying from it.
Let's give Jack
a chance with her.
With all due respect,
it's not your call, Ms. Yassir.
District has formally placed
Ms. Raines in my custody
and granted me the authority to
determine appropriate treatment.
I'm gonna begin preparing
for her treatment shortly.
I'll let you know
what the results are.
Good day.
You can't let him do this,
not without even
giving Jack a...
He has jurisdiction.
The hell with
jurisdiction!
There's nothing I can do.
You can do
what you know is right.
That's what Buchanan
would have done.
And that was uncalled for.
Well, I'm sorry.
What I meant to say is,
since you're acting director,
you can't be afraid
to step on toes.
Does that go
down better?
And part of being
acting director
is respecting
the chain of command.
But thank you for your advice.
--It's him.
(ringing continues)
Hi.
Where are you?
I'm... on my way out the door.
Well, get here as
quickly as you can.
There's a crisis.
Has there been
another threat?
Yes, but not from
the terrorists.
I'll fill you in
when you get here.
I'll be there
in less than 15.
Lisa...
I need you.
I need you, too.
I have to go.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Yes.
It's me.
What's my next move?
Thank you.
Yes.
I think I've identified
the leak, sir.
Is it here or at CTU?
Oh, it's very much here, sir.
I had NSA run
a data sort
on all White House phone calls
and e-mails
over the last two
and half hours.
That's when we found out
the sub-circuit board was
in play.
And?
During the same time frame,
one of our staffers called
a lobbyist,
Mark Bishop, three times.
Now, CIA had flagged
this Bishop two years ago
as having
"possible to likely contact
with Russian Intelligee
agents."
No further investigation
was done
due to lack of resources.
Which staffer are we talking
about here, Tom?
Lisa Miller, sir.
(scoffs)
I find it hard to believe
my Chief Aide is working
for the Russians.
I don't think she did
so knowingly, sir.
She wouldn't have called Bishop
from her phone.
Then I... I don't understand--
how is this man getting
information from her?
Well, so far...
we have found
credit card records
that show Ms. Miller and Bishop
staying at the same hotels,
on the same nights,
several times
over the past year.
Now, I think if we dig
a little deeper,
I'm sure that we will
find more evidence
that shows these two were
sleeping together.
Then we have a bigger problem
than you think, Tom.
Why is that, sir?
Because I'm sleeping
with her, too.
She...
She started working
for me
two years after my wife...
After Nancy
died, it...
At that time I didn't think
I'd ever feel anything
for another woman again,
but...
Lisa and I
became close,
then last year...
we were working
late one night, and...
Well, you understand
how these things happen, Tom.
Damn it.
What a fool I've been.
What the hell do I do, Tom?
You know, actually, sir,
handled correctly,
we may be able to turn this
situation to our advantage.
Mike, what's
happening out there?
Will they let me
speak to Audrey?
I tried to make
it happen, Jack,
but they're
not going for it.
Why not?
'Cause the shrink
who's treating her--
he doesn't think
it's a good idea.
Let me talk to him.
I wish
this guy was interested
in what other people had
to say, but he isn't.
Why?
He's got her
in medical, Jack,
and he's about to try
some protocol of his own
using big doses of drugs.
It could kill her, Jack.
Why did you uncuff me?
'Cause I think you need
to do something about it.
Make it look good.
Easy.
(grunts)
Vitals are strong.
I think she's ready.
Good.
Get her IV started.
Excuse me, sir,
you can't be in here.
Have you started
yet?
No.
What have you done to her?!
Nothing. Nothing.
Consider yourself
lucky.
You're Jack Bauer,
I recognize you
from her file.
You shouldn't be here.
Seeing you will only
make things worse.
Shut up!
(breathing heavily)
Audrey, I need you
to come with me.
I need you to come
with me now.
Please, come on.
(alarm blaring)
Just get me anything you can.
(blaring continues)
Milo, what's the location
of that alarm?
Clinic, Nadia,
exam room six,
where Audrey's
being treated.
Get me video feed.
She's gone.
Lock everything down.
Get me holding room three!
If we just let Jack talk
to Audrey,
none of this would
have happened.
--Okay, thank you.
Security's confirmed
that jack didn't pass
through any of the exits
before the lockdown.
He's still here
somewhere.
No one left sectors
A through K
they're clear.
All right,
so he's got to be on
the lower levels.
Have you checked
those video feeds?
Yes.
That's what I'm doing,
just takes a little bit of time.
I know, make it
take less time.
Where's Chloe?
Morris?
I don't... I'm not sure.
Doyle.
Have you found Jack?
No, not yet.
But I'd like to know how
he managed to overpower you?
I made a mistake,
I got too close.
Yeah, see, I don't think
it was a mistake.
You made it very clear
that you wanted
Jack to have a chance
with Audrey.
So, I think you went there
with the express purpose
of letting him overpower you
and then escaping
with your keycard.
I did what I think
is best for this operation
and for Audrey Raines.
I have him!
He's headed down
to the lower level.
But with everything locked down
he's only going to have access
to corridors L and M.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Let me know
if you find anything else.
And have Dr. Bradley
and Doyle meet me there.
Hold on.
Come on.
(beeping)
(grunting)
It's all right.
It's all right, I'm here.
I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going
to protect you.
to take care of you.
I promise.
I know you can recognize me.
I see it in your eyes.
It's me, Jack.
The men who hurt you,
they can't touch you now.
I won't allow it.
Right now, I need you
to try and remember.
I need you to remember
who you are.
Your name is
Audrey Raines.
You were born Audrey Louise
Heller in Albany, New York.
Your father was the Secretary
of Defense, James Heller.
Your mother's name
was Alicia.
She died
when you were nine.
Please, Audrey,
just try and remember.
(computer beeps)
Nadia, I've got Jack.
Room 237 was just sealed
from the inside.
They have to be in there.
I see the room now.
Damn it. It's disabled.
Get an entry team
down here now.
Need an entry team
at door 237.
The men
that were holding you,
when they called me
there were within an hour
of my motel.
When they moved you,
can you remember if,
if you took surface streets
or the freeway, anything
that can help us find them?
I want them to pay
for what they've done.
I know
what you've been through.
I know what it's like
to feel
like it's never going
to end...
to hate them that much,
and then need them...
to start blaming
yourself
for everything
that's happening to you.
But they can't hurt you
anymore.
You don't need to hide now.
It's over.
Please, Audrey, give me
some kind of a signal.
Anything, anything
that let's me know
you understand
what I'm saying, please.
Please!
It's all right, I'm...
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I know you're trying.
I love you with all my heart.
(sizzling)
I'm not going
to let them hurt you,
but they're going
to take you away
from me
for a little while.
There's nothing I can do
to stop that.
Audrey, we're out of time.
Is there anything
that you can tell me
that could help us find Cheng
or at least
where they were holding you?
Please.
Come here.
Come on.
Get down.
Jack, put your gun down.
You put your gun down!
Get him
out of here.
I'm not letting him take
Audrey back to medical.
Jack, you need
to lower your weapon.
Not until I get a guarantee
from you that Audrey is safe!
(quietly):
Bloomfield.
What'd you say?
JACK:
Did you hear that?
She said
"Bloomfield."
I asked her where she was being
held; she's trying to answer.
We don't know
if that represents
genuine communication.
"Bloomfield" could be
another programmed response
meaning nothing.
We'll soon find out.
Morris, did you get that?
Bloomfield: have
Chloe track it down,
keep Doyle in the loop.
MORRIS:
All right.
In the meantime, Dr. Bradley,
I'd like you to wait
for me in my office.
I'm not going anywhere;
she's my patient.
And she's my witness.
I suggest you go
with these men, Doctor.
Listen to me, Jack.
You have my word, I will
not let him touch her.
Please,
lower your weapon.
Audrey, please,
it's all right.
He's going
to take care of you.
Jack, I need you to go with
these men to Holding.
--Yes, of course, General.
I'll review the report
with the Vice President.
I'll get right
back to you.
Suvarov wasn't bluffing.
No, sir.
Air Force satellites confirm
the Russian Army is moving
large numbers of troops into
the Central Asian theater.
How long before they're
in range of our base?
They'll be within
strike range
within the hour, sir.
(door opens)
I'm sorry, Mr. Vice President,
I got back here
as soon as I could.
Forward General Wilkes' report
to the Joint Chiefs.
Let me know
their recommendations.
Yes, sir.
(door closes)
What's going on?
Why is Tom talking
to the Joint Chiefs?
Because the Russians know
the Chinese have
the component.
How did that happen?
Someone inside the Beltway has
been selling them information.
Someone with access.
A man named Mark Bishop.
Do you know him?
I believe he's a lobbyist.
Are you sure it's Bishop?
Yes.
We began monitoring
his phone calls
as soon as this came
to our attention.
Ten minutes ago, he called
a known Russian Intelligence
agent from his cell phone.
BISHOP (over recorder):
It's me.
What's my next move?
MAN:
It's imperative you
reach out to her
over the next few hours.
Find out if there are
any developments
with the component.
BISHOP:
I'll call her
and I'll access her PDA again,
see if she has any new e-mail.
MAN:
Very good.
So how well do you know
this man Bishop?
He's an acquaintance.
He consulted on a white paper
last year on defense spending.
Damn it, Lisa,
don't insult me
any more than you already have.
Bishop's been
passing intelligence
to the Russians that
he got from you.
I don't know if he
read your e-mails
or if you talked
about it in bed,
but the Russians know
about the component
and they're threatening
military action against us
if we don't get it
back from the Chinese.
I always knew you
were a good liar.
I just... I just didn't
think you could lie to me.
I guess I thought
too highly of myself.
I swear to you, I didn't know.
It's still treason,
which I don't need to remind
you is a capital offense.
You didn't just betray me,
you betrayed your country.
What do you want from me?
You're going to go
back to your boyfriend
and you're going
to make him believe
that we have the component back.
I can't do that.
You can and you will
do exactly
what Tom Lennox tells you to do.
And don't you even think
about trying to expose our...
relationship.
If you go there, I'll
have you declared
an enemy combatant.
Put you in solitary; it'll
be years before you speak
to anyone about anything.
Noah...
Are you all
right, sir?
I'm better now.
Secret Service is sending over
a team to work with her.
We'll get this going soon.
I've made arrangements
to take you away from here.
I'm going to look after you,
Audie, I promise.
You will get well
and you won't be alone.
I'll be right back, sweetheart.
Before I take my daughter,
I'd like to see Jack Bauer.
Where is he?
He's in Holding, sir.
Escort Mr. Heller to Holding.
Nadia, hey, did Audrey speak
when he was with her?
No, I don't think so.
Well, it turns out the name she
gave us might be a good lead.
There's a Bloomfield Copper
Company that used to have
a refining facility
in Jefferson Heights.
Forensics just found
oxidized copper particles
on her clothing.
You think that's where
Cheng was holding her?
Yeah, I think it might be
his base of operations.
LAPD's locking down
the building,
but I told them to stand
down till I get there.
Good work, Mike.
Thanks.
Mike.
You were right.
I should have stood up
to Dr. Bradley.
You did.
When it counted,
you stood up to him.
Mr. Secretary.
You've seen Audrey.
I made Audrey a promise,
I make the same promise to you.
I will take care of her
as long as it takes.
I will be there for her.
No, you won't, Jack.
Excuse me?
I don't want you to go
anywhere near my daughter
ever again.
Audrey went looking for you
and this is how she came back.
What's happened
to her is your fault.
I accept that responsibility,
but I can help her.
Stay away from her.
Mr. Secretary, earlier
I got through to Audrey.
I can do the same thing again.
I just need some time.
Please.
I'm warning you.
Stay away.
You're cursed, Jack.
Everything you touch,
one way or another,
ends up dead.
www.tvsubtitles.net