Congratulations, Tom.
It's an excellent plan.
It's about time someone
in this administration
stood up to these people.
Thank you very much,
Mr. Vice President.
The American-Muslim community
is our best
line of defense
against these terrorists.
Your plan...
would only hinder
the efforts of law enforcement
to stop Fayed.
I remain convinced
that implementing this plan
would be a terrible mistake.
15 minutes ago,
the NSA picked up a conversation
between McCarthy and Fayed.
McCarthy's found
another engineer
to arm the four remaining nukes.
CHLOE:
Oh, my God. It's Morris.
JACK:
Morris, it's a setup.
The engineer McCarthy's
looking for-- it's you.
(two gunshots)
Get out of the car or the
next one's in your head.
We're on our way.
We'll be waiting.
With my money?
FAYED:
You'll get paid as soon
as I have what I want.
I'm just delivering him.
You'll have to make him
cooperate.
How do I find McCarthy?!
Four cc's!
His vitals are spiking
across the line.
JACK:
Four cc's!
Jack, don't.
It has nothing
to do with McCarthy.
It has to do with Palmer.
David Palmer?
I gave the order
for his assassination.
JACK:
Not only was he responsible
for David Palmer's
assassination,
he directed
the entire conspiracy.
He was trying to protect
my father's company.
Then...
You told them about Palmer.
I had to give
them something,
make them think I cracked,
but I kept you out of it.
Dad, stick
to the plan.
Sometimes you have
to make adjustments.
My son's had a seizure!
PHILLIP:
If you people killed my son,
you're gonna regret it
for the rest of your life.
Chloe, it's Jack.
I'm en route to the ambush site.
You need to tell me which
direction they took Morris.
I'm bringing
it up now.
Jack, what are they
gonna do to him?
Chloe, they have to keep
him alive long enough
to try and make the
bombs operational.
That means
we've got time.
I need you to remain calm
and pull up the satellite now.
I'm trying;
the server's not responding.
That's 'cause
you're not
re-synching the
coordinates correctly.
I know what I'm doing.
Have you confirmed this
with the field team?
Yes.
Jack's on line 1.
Jack, it's Bill.
We just got word from the field
team at your brother's house.
Graem's dead, Jack.
What happened?
We'll know more
after an autopsy,
but all signs point
to cardiac arrest.
Because of the interrogation.
The medic on site believes
that was a factor.
My father know?
Yes, he was there.
But your sister-in-law
and nephew
were already en route to CTU
when it happened.
Bill, I'd really
appreciate it
if you would be the one
to break the news to her.
Of course, Jack.
Sir.
Stand by.
Chloe's starting to screw up.
She's worried
about Morris.
I think she's
losing it.
Chloe, have you accessed
the uplink yet?
Not yet.
Listen,
I know what you must be feeling,
but if there's a problem...
Get away from me!
There's not a problem!
The only problem is people
like you bothering me
when I'm trying
to do my job.
Chloe, give up
your post to Milo.
Leave me alone; I can do this!
Now.
Fine.
Jack, I've had
to relieve Chloe.
She's too distraught
to function.
You're on with Milo.
Jack, just give
me a second.
Okay, I got McCarthy
on satellite
13 minutes ago,
abducting Morris
in a silver Maserati
at the corner of Central
and Third.
I'm tracking them
to their current position.
All right, right now
McCarthy's at Adams
and 13th, heading west.
Copy that.
We should have a visual
in the next couple minutes.
How long is it gonna
take the TAC teams
to intercept McCarthy
on the ground?
I don't know.
We'll get back to you.
Where are we taking him?
Fayed will call soon.
Just relax. Drive.
I am relaxed.
I just want to get
this over with.
It's never gonna be over.
CTU knows
who you are.
They're already
looking for you.
Shut up.
Is that possible?
Don't listen to him.
He's bluffing.
So you're not Darren McCarthy,
arms dealer,
subcontracted
by BXJ Technologies.
CTU intercepted a transmission
about Fayed hiring
you to do this.
I said shut up!
Right.
We're handing him over
to Fayed as planned.
If I'm already
a marked man,
might as well get paid for it.
What about me?
He didn't say
they know about you.
And anyway, I'll take care
of you, like always.
(helicopter whirring overhead)
Chopper?
That's a chopper.
I got him. I got him.
We got a visual.
Turn left.
But why...
Just do what I say!
Just do it!
Swing back.
JACK:
They just took off.
They must have spotted us.
All right, I got them
turning north
onto Anders.
Go around them.
I, uh...
Go around them!
What?!
Just do it!
No!
Oh, my God.
Are they still there?
Yes.
Turn there!
We got a problem up here.
They're headed
to the 110 interchange.
Damn it. We just lost them.
Does CalTrans have any cameras
that are covering that area?
No.
Nothing.
TAC team is still
five minutes away.
Captain, I want you
to put me down now.
Do you know
what this is about?
Fayed, the man
you're taking me to,
is the terrorist who set off
the nuclear bomb in Valencia.
He has four more bombs.
But he needs me
to make them work,
so that he can kill tens of
thousands of innocent people.
And all you have to do
to stop that from happening
is to uncuff me.
McCarthy's right.
CTU doesn't know you exist.
For the love of God,
all of those people's
lives are on you.
Let's go.
Shouldn't I get my luggage?
Forget about the luggage!
Come on!
You did not tell me
this is about nuclear bombs.
What this is about
is about $7 million.
Now, get in the truck!
MILO:
Pressman.
They dumped the car.
They must have
switched vehicles.
From the underpass,
they could've merged
directly onto any one of
six local roads or highways.
There's no way
of tracking them
without knowing exactly
what vehicle they're in.
Damn it, Milo.
They could be anywhere!
The TAC team's here.
Get back to me.
Head south.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I have a new place
for us to meet.
Are you certain
you're not being followed?
Yeah.
What's the address?
4332 Florence Avenue,
apartment 621.
Have you got
my money?
Yes.
Turn on the GPS.
Apartment 621.
All right?
Don't forget it.
Okay, good.
It's not too far.
Yes, yes.
Thank God.
A bit excessive,
but you did
the right thing.
Now I've got to contact CTU
and give them...
Shut up!
Fayed wants you alive,
and whatever shape you're in
beyond that is up to you.
Oh, come on. What are you doing?
I am making $7 million.
And I can spend it without
having to worry about CTU.
--Listen...
I know you think I'm wrong,
and that I blindsided you
by not backing your proposals.
Correct on both counts, sir.
Tom, I have always
valued your counsel.
Ever since you showed up at my
home and convinced me to run,
spearheaded my campaign.
I mean, if it weren't for
you, I wouldn't be here.
But I do hope I can
still count on you
to help me implement
my polices.
AGENT DAN:
Excuse me, Mr. President.
The plane carrying
Hamri Al-Assad
has landed at Andrews
Air Force Base.
He'll be here soon.
Thank you.
We'll talk later.
(knocking)
Mr. Lennox?
Uh...
Everything's okay.
We're fine in here. Thank you.
What happened?
The President
just rejected every one
of my proposals right there
in front of the Cabinet.
Not only has he changed his mind
on the internment plan,
he is rolling back
on the detention facilities
that are already in place.
I thought... I thought
he was on board.
Well, so did I.
Now he's putting forth
his own agenda
to try and appease
the Muslim population.
Is he hoping that they're
going to cooperate
and help find the
nuclear weapons?
That's it! That's it!
And all he will succeed in doing
is to prove to the terrorists
that he does not have
the stomach
to do what is necessary
and inevitable.
Okay. Then you need to use your
influence to change his mind.
My...?
My influence?
You don't get it, do you, Reed?
I have no influence.
Not here.
Not in this administration.
No, I'm resigning.
Sir, that would be
a terrible mistake.
My mistake was to believe
that Wayne Palmer
has the courage and the vision
to fill this office.
Clearly, I overestimated him.
He is certainly not his brother.
Which makes it all the more
important that you stay.
Sir, you have the support
of a great many people here,
the least of which
is the Vice President.
Well, unfortunately,
the Vice President
is not the one in power.
And this country
is being led to slaughter
by the man who is.
No, uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
I can't, in good conscience,
be party to this. I can't.
Sir, sir, this is
a terrible mistake.
Reed, I cannot talk about this
any further.
Go now and draft
my letter of resignation
and bring it to me now
for me to sign.
Yes, sir.
CARSON:
Yes?
Yeah, it's Reed.
Palmer just shot down the Lennox
plan in the Cabinet meeting.
He's rejecting every one
of the initiatives.
Did you hear what I said?
I heard.
Looks like we have no choice.
We'll have to move ahead
with what we all talked about.
I realize it's extreme,
but under the circumstances,
I don't see any alternative.
Do you?
No. But there's a problem.
Tom Lennox is resigning.
When?
As soon as I write
his letter of resignation.
Carson, if he goes,
I lose my job.
And I lose my access.
Our plan is contingent on your
proximity to the President.
We need you in place.
I know, I am very
well aware of that,
but Tom Lennox is
determined to quit.
He might reconsider
if he knew what was coming.
I suppose I could
feel him out.
Then do it, carefully.
We have to protect ourselves.
Has anything turned up
on CalTrans?
Without knowing what vehicle
McCarthy switched in to,
it's going to take hours
to scan through frame grabs.
Stay on it. Right now,
it's all we've got.
Mrs. Bauer.
Yes?
I'm Bill Buchanan,
Director of Operations.
You must be Josh.
May I speak with you a moment?
Privately.
Um...
It's okay, Mom.
Okay.
What is it?
I'm very sorry
to have to tell you.
Your husband is dead.
How?
He appears to have suffered
a heart attack.
What did Jack do to him?
I assure you there'll be
a thorough investigation.
Your father-in-law is
accompanying Graem's body here
for an autopsy.
Unless you have an objection.
No.
I have to tell my son.
Of course.
Josh.
Your mother wants
to speak with you.
MARILYN:
He had a heart attack.
He died.
JOSH:
What? No.
Pressman.
It's Jack.
Let me speak to Buchanan.
Hold on.
Sir... Jack's on the line.
Jack?
Bill, we found McCarthy's body
less than three blocks away
from the interchange.
We intercepted a call from LAPD.
The witness said
the shooter was a female,
drove off with a male
fitting Morris's description
in a silver pickup.
Did the witness get
a license plate?
No. But McCarthy
received a call
just about five minutes ago.
The caller ID is blocked.
I need you to trace
the source of the call.
You think the call
came from Fayed?
Yeah.
I'll give it to Milo as soon
as you upload the phone's data.
It's on its way.
Knock.
MAN:
What do you want?
I'm Darren McCarthy's associate.
I've got your package.
Who are you?
Where's McCarthy?
He's waiting to
hear from me.
If he doesn't
get the money,
he gives you up.
This is the engineer?
Look, this... I don't know
what you're talking about.
I-I'm just a data analyst.
You've got the wrong man.
Look...
I've brought you
what you want.
Just give me the money,
and I'll go.
You'll get your money when
this man completes his task.
You work at CTU,
so you know I have four nuclear
suitcase bombs in my possession.
You may also know these bombs
need to be reprogrammed
before I can use them.
You are here to create a device
that will allow me to do so.
(quivering):
Well, not bloody likely, mate.
You're going to modify this
so that I can use it
to reprogram the bombs.
(inhales deeply):
No, I'm not.
--Bill, what's happening
with the phone trace?
BUCHANAN:
Milo's still
working on it, Jack.
What is it taking so long?
Checking into it now.
Milo...
what's your status?
All I've got is that the call
was made from a landline.
But the number
was routed through
at least a dozen
different servers,
and they keep cycling
back on each other.
(bangs table):
Come on!
Are you going to be able
to do this?
CHLOE:
Milo.
Let me try.
I know I screwed up earlier.
I wasn't thinking clearly,
but let me try this.
I need to.
All right.
The number strings are
caught in a loop matrix.
CHLOE:
Did you try running a
SatCom overlay filter?
That only works on cell-to-cell
communication.
This call was placed
from a hardline.
NSA recently started using
satellite carrier systems
as a backup for
all phone traffic.
You just have to reconfigure
the embedded decryption program
to... Got it.
That's it.
All right.
McCarthy's call was made
from an apartment building:
4332 Florence Avenue.
Did you copy that, Jack?
Yeah, do we know
which apartment?
No, there's no way to tell;
they tapped directly
into the building's
trunk line.
Our men are ready to move.
Have tactical meet us
over there.
Tell them to set up a perimeter.
Stay out of sight.
Understood.
Good work, Milo.
Sir, it wasn't me.
If you think she's ready,
bring her back in.
Mr. Al-Assad...
right this way.
I've checked out
your background.
And despite my
understandable skepticism,
I do believe you're serious
about wanting
this negotiated peace.
On my own terms, yes.
Let's table your terms
for the time being
while we discuss mine.
My country, sir...
has suffered a nuclear attack
by the very same terrorists
who used to follow you.
Thousands of innocent
Americans are dead
or dying as we speak.
I'm aware of the tragedy
in California, Mr. President.
I was there.
Then you understand,
that if Fayed
successfully detonates
any more nuclear weapons
on US soil,
there will be
no chance whatsoever
for a peace agreement.
The American people
are demanding
that we strike back.
And not just at organizations
such as yours,
but at the governments
that support them.
Now, if just one more nuke
goes off, one more,
we won't have a choice.
You understand me?
We're talking about war.
You don't have to tell me
what is at stake,
but I still don't understand
what you want from me.
I would like you
to appear on television
and make a public address
to the world.
Declare your intentions
for peace,
and appeal to members
of Islamic communities
everywhere to come forward
with any information
regarding Fayed.
You flatter me if you think
I hold sway over all Islam.
No, sir, not all.
Just the extremists who share
your hatred of the West.
I certainly can't reach out
to them for help,
but I know you can.
But perception is everything,
Mr. President.
So I must present my agenda
to my own people
in my own time,
not by appearing on American
television from The White House.
Fayed has already
called me a traitor,
and many others will follow him
if there is even a suspicion
that I am an American puppet.
Not a puppet,
a partner, at least
when it comes to finding
these nuclear weapons.
Now, that's what we have to be
for your peace initiative
to have any chance
of working,
so get used to it!
Now, between you
and me, sir,
I really don't give a damn
how and when you wanted
to present your agenda;
the time is now.
You want to lead
this peace initiative...
then lead.
Who's in command?
Agent Turner.
Agent Turner, what's the status
of your perimeter?
It's in place.
We've got agents
in plainclothes
covering the exits
to the building,
and we have three TAC teams
in position to move in
on your command.
Do you have confirmation
that Fayed's in the building?
Not directly, but
the building manager ID'd
Morris O'Brian entering
the building
with a woman less
than 20 minutes ago.
We assume the woman
is the driver
your witness saw
shoot McCarthy.
There are no cameras
in the building.
We don't know what apartment
or floor they're on.
CTU is patched in
and awaiting your word.
Thank you.
Turn it on.
Bill, it's Jack. Do you copy?
Yes, Jack. Go ahead.
I'm at the staging area.
We have a confirmation
that Morris is
inside the building.
We do not have
confirmation on Fayed.
There are no cameras
in the building.
Do have infrared satellite?
We can't get a live feed,
but we do have a satellite
in position uploading images
at five-minute intervals.
The latest scan shows 215 people
in the building,
spread out over six floors
and 112 apartments.
It's going to take too long
to go room by room.
We're going to have to
figure out another way ID them.
Is this building on the city's
emergency services grid?
Yes, Jack. All buildings over
ten units are required to.
Chloe, it's good
to have you back.
I'm to need you to get
into their system,
and trigger an
all-building fire alarm.
Okay, we just have to get past
their log-in screen.
Let me know
when you're ready.
Agent.
Please...
please, stop.
Just indicate you'll do what
I've asked, and we will stop.
People are leaving the building.
There really is a fire.
What do we do?
There's no fire.
CTU knows we're here.
I really need
to get out of here.
Shut up!
Up against the wall.
Your time is up!
I will use this
all over your body
until you die of
shock or blood loss.
Then I'll just find someone else
to do what I need.
Do you understand?
Look, please...
I don't care about the money.
I made a mistake.
Just let me get out of here.
Please.
So, you give up
the seven million, huh?
Yes.
Okay.
Oh!
Stop... stop!
I'll do it.
--Come in.
This memo says Palmer's
arranging
for Assad to make
a televised statement.
I heard.
Not only are we providing
free airtime
to a mass murderer
and a vowed enemy of democracy,
we are proving terrorism works.
You have my letter
of resignation?
No, sir, I don't.
Why not?
Because you can't resign
while this country is
being brought to the brink
of a nuclear holocaust
by a weak, misguided President.
Damn it, Reed. I explained...
I cannot get the President
to budge on policy.
There's nothing I can do
about this.
What if I told you that
the climate could change?
What does that even mean,
the climate?
Well, I'm just saying that
there are people who believe,
like you, that more
aggressive steps need
to be taken to crack down
on terrorism, both here
at home and abroad,
and that a change in leadership
is imperative
to ensure
this nation's security.
Um...
Who?
Excuse me, sir?
Who are these like-minded people
we're talking about?
I was... I'm just
speaking abstractly.
But you'd have
to agree that, uh...
your plan would have
all the support it needed
if the Vice President were the
man occupying the Oval Office.
Wait...
Now, I may dislike
the President's current course
of action.
I hardly think
it warrants his, his removal.
I'm not talking
about holding hearings.
Something more
immediate would have to happen.
Oh, my God...
You can't possibly be intimating
what I think you are.
I'm not intimating anything.
I'm just simply musing.
Careful.
That kind of musing
can get you thrown
into prison for treason.
Well, I'm sorry, sir,
that you've misunderstood me.
Yeah, I certainly hope so,
for your sake.
All right.
I think you have a letter
to draft for me.
FIREFIGHTER (on bullhorn):
You need to keep
a safe distance
away from the building
until we have determined
there is no danger.
Please move across the street
away from the building.
Anything from your men
on the ground?
They've looked at everyone
who's exited the building.
There's no sign
of Fayed or O'Brian.
If they were inside
when the alarm went off,
they're still in there.
Damn it.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, it's Bill.
Go ahead.
We've got the latest infrared.
We're mirroring it
to your screen.
Hold on.
I've got it.
I'm looking at it now.
Okay, there's three people
left in the apartments
on the second, fourth
and sixth floors.
We need to narrow that down.
Chloe, who's renting
those apartments?
Superimposing building
department schematics
and cross-referencing
with phone company
and police records now.
Okay, the woman on the second
floor is handicapped.
She probably didn't leave
because she can't.
The other two apartments
are occupied
by single males;
the man on the fourth floor
has been arrested
several times
for distribution of narcotics.
Fayed wouldn't use anyone
with a criminal record
to set up a safe house.
Our hostiles are
in the sixth floor apartment.
Get your men ready.
We're moving in.
All right, let's go!
How much longer?
I don't know.
McCarthy said this is
a few minutes' work
for an advanced programmer.
You're stalling for time.
I am not.
It'll be ready
in a minute.
Most everybody seems to have
evacuated the building.
Which is how they intend
to find us.
At this point it's only
a question of time.
Go.
It's done?
Yes.
Bring it.
You have the bombs here?
Just one.
Let's see if you did
your work correctly.
Arm it.
Arm it!
Very good.
Kill him.
Please, I did what
you asked, didn't I?
Now.
All agents sound off!
Clear.
AGENT:
We're clear.
We took a head count
of the bodies.
One hostile's missing;
we haven't found Fayed.
It's clear, sir.
Have your men maintain
the search for Fayed.
I want them to identify
every possible exit
from this apartment.
Yes, sir.
What's his status?
Unconscious, but alive.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Morris has been injured,
but he's alive.
Mr. Bauer, you need to see this.
(into earpiece):
CTU, this is Bauer.
--Jack, be careful.
The bomb has a fail-safe device
that prevents any forced entry.
Through the glass casing I have
two small metal plates slowly
converging on each other.
Those are the trigger plates,
Jack; once they touch
an electrical charge
will detonate the core
causing the nuke to explode.
How far apart are they?
Approximately three inches.
Okay, that gives us
only about three minutes.
There's a small metal box
to the right of it.
You need to carefully
unscrew the top of it.
Copy that.
AGENT TURNER:
Agent Bauer, we know
how Fayed got out.
They opened up a wall
in one of the closets
to get access to the building's
ventilation system.
From there, Fayed could get
to the basement,
and, in turn, the sewer tunnels.
Did you mobilize your teams
and set up a perimeter?
Yes, sir. But we believe
Fayed's already gone.
Witnesses report
a helicopter taking off
from a nearby field
a few minutes ago.
It appeared to be
a medical evac chopper,
so it got through our net.
Damn it.
The top's off.
Come on, Chloe.
We are running out of time.
Okay, under the gears
you should see four wires.
Short-circuit each of them.
That should stop
the left gear from rotating.
You can access the dip switches
underneath it
to open the case and manually
stop the trigger.
Okay, the left gear
stopped moving.
I see the dip switches.
They're all in the up position.
What's next?
Um...
Switch three and four
to the down position.
Nothing happened.
The case didn't open.
It didn't?
That's what I said.
It didn't open.
Hold on.
(bomb buzzing)
Chloe, we are
almost out of time.
Okay, I have an updated
schematic.
It wasn't switches
three and four.
You need to push four and five
to the down position,
and the cover will open.
Are you sure this time?
I'm about as sure as I'm going
to be before this bomb goes off.
It's done.
The bomb is disarmed.
Notify your men the
bomb's been deactivated.
It's over.
MORRIS:
It's not over.
What are you talking about?
The reprogramming device
that Fayed had me build for him.
If it's not here,
it means he took it with him.
And with it,
he can activate
the other bombs he has
anytime he wants.
You gave him something
that worked?
I'm sorry, Jack.
CTU, did you copy that?
BUCHANAN:
We got it, Jack.
Alert the President
immediately.
Organize two teams:
one to search the apartment,
one to search
around the building.
Agent O'Brian will tell you
what you're looking for.
Yes, sir.
You see this flash report
in from CTU?
I'm reading it now.
They let Fayed slip
through their fingers... again.
Apparently he now has
the capability
to arm these remaining
suitcase nukes.
This situation is
immeasurably worse.
You know my letter
of resignation?
Have you got that?
Yes, I just, uh...
I just finished
printing it.
I can bring it over
to you right now.
No, no, no.
No, just tear that up.
What?
Um...
That talk we were
having in my office,
I don't think
I misunderstood you.
And I...
would like to discuss
this... further.
Not on this phone.
I'll let you know
when I have a secure location.
www.tvsubtitles.net