Fayed has the bombs.
Where is he?
I don't know,
but I can help you find him.
RYAN:
Preparing the tracker now.
We can track the
isotope signature
up to 15 miles.
(inhales sharply)
MILO:
We are locked
on the isotope signature
that's being emitted
from Gredenko's arm.
You led them to me.
I had no choice.
I don't like it.
Something's wrong.
I'm heading in.
Which direction, Milo?
He stopped and entered
the building on the left.
He's right on the other side
of the door!
Oh, my God.
He cut off Gredenko's arm!
Ryan, move your men in now!
I want Fayed alive!
REPORTER:
But sources indicate
that the same terrorist cell
is most likely...
We're trapped.
This way.
I recognize him from the news!
He's the terrorist
they're looking for!
MAN:
Thatis him!
You bastard.
Back off!
Gredenko is not here.
I need you to lock down
the area
and initiate a search!
One of the Cabinet votes
is invalid.
The tally's seven to six
in favor of invoking
the 25th amendment
and removing President Palmer
from power.
I'm sorry, Wayne.
No, don't waste your apologies
on me
because I won't let you
steal the presidency.
As I'm sure you're aware, sir,
conspiracy to commit perjury
is a felony offense.
LISA:
My affidavit will push the court
to rule in your favor
so that you can do what's right
for this country.
NOAH:
You're right. Do it.
Turn it off.
Wayne, the Supreme Court
was just notified.
Daniels withdrew his suit.
You're still the President
of the United States.
President Palmer...
What?
He's about to go ahead
with the nuclear strike.
This makes no sense, sir!
It's what you risked your life
to stop!
Tom, I risked my life
to reassert my authority.
Mr. President...
...we have a successful launch.
Good.
Mr. President,
the missile is just
entering target's airspace.
Mr. President...
Tom, I said I was
done talking.
We both agreed
a nuclear strike is pointless,
Fayed's actions
are not state-sponsored
and his country
cannot be held
accountable for this.
Five minutes till impact.
The ambassador assured us
he country is doing
everything possible
to find those suitcase nukes.
They simply don't know anything!
Well, one way or another, Tom,
we're about to find out
if that's true.
(keypad beeps,
phone rings on line)
Buchanan.
HAYES: Bill, it's me.
Have you gotten anything
from Fayed?
Jack's interrogating
him now,
but frankly, he's not
optimistic about breaking him.
What's going on?
The president's gone ahead
with the missile strike.
He what?
He's launched it, Bill.
Why?
I don't know why.
He fought the vice president
to regain his office,
and now he's just going
ahead with Daniels' plan.
It doesn't make
any sense.
We've got to stop this.
Look, can I tell
the president
that you have a solid lead
from Fayed on the location
of the suitcase nukes?
If you're asking me
to provide a pretext
to bring the missile down,
Karen, I can't do that.
Fayed's not talking
and Gredenko's dead.
I don't have anything.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
I'll call you later.
Sir, we have confirmation
the radar's tagged
the missile.
They're scrambling fighters
and readying air defenses, sir.
Then they know we're coming.
Good.
Sir, I just got off
the phone with CTU.
Bauer's interrogating Fayed.
It's just a matter of time
before he has the location
of those bombs.
No, Karen, we can't afford
to wait longer.
Sir, we can't afford not to.
Please, why are you doing this?
Four minutes to impact,
Mr. President.
Mr. President...
(intercom beeps)
Yes?
Excuse me. We have the
ambassador on for the President.
This is President Palmer.
Mr. President, my government
has alerted me
of the nuclear weapon heading
toward my country.
That's correct, Mr. Ambassador.
We've made good on our threat.
For God sake, I implore you
to stop it!
On what grounds?
We have uncovered new
information regarding
your situation.
I'm listening.
We've identified a general
in our Central Command,
General Mohmar Habib,
who has also been in
contact with Fayed.
It's our belief
that he's been helping
orchestrate the attacks
on your country.
Have you arrested Habib?
Yes, yes. He's being
interrogated as we speak.
Please, you must
abort this attack
before it's too late.
Does Habib know the present
location of Fayed's
nuclear weapons?
It is my understanding
that the general's
last contact with Fayed
was during the drone operation.
He has no current knowledge
of the weapon's whereabouts
or their intended targets.
Mr. President,
two minutes to impact, sir.
Ambassador,
your government has
known about this man
for quite some time,
haven't they?
Mr. President, this
development has come
as a shock...
Stop lying to me!
That missile will hit
in less than two minutes,
Mr. Ambassador,
so please don't try
my patience again.
You must understand
the fragile political
climate of our country.
General Habib
is a high-ranking
military commander.
I really hope
protecting this man
was worth pushing us
to the brink of
World War III.
The missile will be aborted,
Mr. Ambassador.
But in the meantime,
I strongly suggest
you get me a full
dossier on General Habib.
I want a thorough update
on the progress
of his interrogation.
I'm also demanding
that you return here
to the White House immediately.
I want direct access
to you, sir,
for the duration
of this crisis.
As you wish,
Mr. President.
Commander, abort code:
Alpha-Zero-Delta-Nine.
Ditch it in the Gulf.
My God,
they were lying to us
all the time.
Withholding information
and you knew it.
I suspected it.
Well, I'll see that theVickery
sends a recovery team
to retrieve
that nuclear warhead.
That won't be necessary, Tom.
The president
ordered the launch
of a secondary missile on board
theVickery,
an unarmed one.
HAYES: What?
This was all a bluff?
The vice president was right.
Well, about one thing, anyway.
That it was going
to take a willingness
to strike back before
getting any real cooperation
from their government.
The difference is I wasn't
about to take innocent lives
to prove my point.
Now let's get
this information to CTU.
Perhaps it's the key
to breaking Fayed.
(grunts)
Gah!
This country is planning
a full retaliatory strike
against your people.
Now, I can stop it,
but tell me where the bombs are.
Where are the bombs?!
Fayed, this is over.
You lost.
Save your people.
Just tell me
where the bombs are.
Are you enjoying
yourself, Bauer?
As much as you enjoyed
butchering my little brother?
Your brother was responsible
for the death of dozens
of innocent lives.
Now you're responsible
for thousands.
Trust me, I haven't
begun to enjoy myself.
Go ahead.
You'll get nothing from me,
and you know it.
We'll see.
(gasps)
(coughing)
(whispering):
This is not working.
Let me have a go at him.
No. That's exactly
what he wants.
He knows he's lost.
He wants us to martyr him.
(cell phone ringing)
Hold on.
This is Bauer.
BUCHANAN:
Jack, it's Bill.
What's your status with Fayed?
Same as before.
We're getting nowhere.
I just got some new intel
from the White House.
Fayed's government
arrested one of its generals--
Mohmar Habib.
Apparently, he's
been running Fayed,
helping him coordinate
the attacks.
Then Habib would know
where Fayed's men are.
Unfortunately not.
He claims there's
been no contact
since the failed
drone attack.
They're interrogating him now.
Well, unless Habib's
going to give us
something more useful than that,
we still have no location
for these bombs.
We have to try something
more drastic.
How soon can you have
Fayed ready for transport?
Immediately, but...
You really think
you're going to be
remembered as some great martyr
for your people, Fayed?
Yeah, you blew up
a little city,
and you killed a lot
of people today.
But let's face it,
that's going to be of no
real political significance.
Let me tell you
what's going to happen.
Your number two guy,
once he realizes that
you're out of the picture,
he's going to take
those remaining suitcase nukes,
and he's going to blow up
a substantial target,
something that's really
going to hurt this country.
And if, by some
chance, he succeeds,
he's going to be the
hero of your jihad,
and you will be forgotten.
Is that what you want?
(scoffs)
Do you honestly believe
you can manipulate me
by playing on my vanity?
I serve the will of God.
No, you don't.
And if you don't believe me,
ask him when you meet him.
(cocks gun)
Agent Doyle, lower your weapon.
I said lower
your weapon!
Buchanan wants us
to transport Fayed
back to CTU.
We don't have time.
His men are probably
on the move.
The only way
we're going to break him
is with a
pharmaceutical package.
Burke is standing by.
We don't need Burke.
Just give me some time with him.
Those are your orders.
Agent Doyle,
do you have a problem?
No problem.
Good.
Get your men ready.
--LENNOX:
Excuse me, sir.
Here's the file on Habib.
Is this the complete dossier
on General Habib?
No, sir.
That's preliminary.
And I was told by
the ambassador's staff
that more will be forthcoming
and will be relayed
concurrently to CTU.
Good.
How soon before
the ambassador gets here?
Within 15 minutes.
Oh, and I spoke with
Secret Service.
They said your sister is on
her way back to the hospital
to be with Walid.
And she's going
to call you soon.
All right.
Thank you.
I did want to say,
your handling
of the crisis...
Tom, I know that
you're not happy
that you were kept in
the dark about the bluff.
But the Joint Chiefs
and I agreed
to keep the
plan closed.
That's not it.
I just want
to say I'm sorry...
I doubted your strength
and your leadership.
It's all right.
Well, respectfully, sir, no...
it's not all right.
Tom...
you and I go back
a long time,
so let's be honest
with each other.
You made it no secret
that you believed
the vice president
was better suited
to lead this country
through this crisis.
And I was wrong about that, sir.
No, if that missile had
detonated on foreign soil...
Russia, China, every nation
with a nuclear capability
might well have inserted
themselves into this.
No, this could have
been a world war.
Unfortunately, we're already
in a world war, Tom.
It's just taken me some time
to fully realize that.
If it hadn't have been for
Vice President Daniels
initiating that missile launch,
I would have no gambit
to play here.
And the ambassador would never
have come forward
with this intel on Habib.
I'm not David, Tom.
And I never will be.
But I am learning that who I am
is not so bad.
Yeah, well, we're all doing
some learning here today,
aren't we, sir?
Tom?
Daniels withdrew his challenge
to my competency very suddenly.
And from what I know,
without any
discernible reason.
Change of heart maybe.
Oh, something
must have changed it.
You have something on him,
don't you?
Sir, as chief of staff,
I'm here to inform you
and also
to protect you.
Those jobs don't always
work in combination.
JACK:
We're northbound on Washington.
ETA about 16 minutes.
Tell Agent Burke we're going
to need everything he's got.
Jack, what if this
doesn't work?
I've never found
pharmaceutical torture
all that effective.
I have.
If this is supposed to frighten
me, you're wasting your time.
I won't tell you a thing.
Whether you do or not,
I get to watch
you suffer.
Agent Doyle, I don't
want you talking...
Jack!
Watch out!
(tires screech)
Everybody okay?!
DOYLE:
Yeah.
They're trying to flank us
on both sides.
We're sitting ducks here.
Try and get Fayed out the back.
I'll cover you from this side.
DOYLE:
All right.
(automatic gunfire)
(speaking Arabic)
(yelling in Arabic)
We're clear.
Bill, it's Jack,
do you copy?
Bill, do you copy?
We're here, Jack.
The cover team
just picked up Fayed.
You think
he bought it?
We'll know soon enough.
JACK:
Is the A/V feed up yet?
We're almost there.
Agent Doyle, you're bleeding.
Oh, must have cut myself
in the crash.
Mike, do you need
medical assistance?
DOYLE:
Uh, negative, it's superficial,
but thanks for your concern.
Jack, I'm patching it
through to you now.
JACK:
Copy that.
JAMAL:
Talit, take evasive measures.
Keep off
the main streets.
(speaking Arabic)
My name is Jamal Nasawa.
We are with
the Al-Tahireen cell.
General Habib sent us.
The general?
Yes.
How did you find me?
Through contacts the general has
within the American
intelligence community.
He learned of your route
and ordered us to intercept.
He wants us
to help you rendezvous
with your men.
(breathing heavily)
Give me a gun.
(speaks softly)
I want to speak to him.
General Habib.
That's not possible
at the moment.
Why not?
The general is under tight
scrutiny by the government.
It's not safe.
He said he'll call us
when he can.
Fayed,
where do you want us
to take you?
I'll let you know
after I speak to the general.
As you wish.
Bill, did you copy that?
Fayed's not going anywhere
unless he talks
to General Habib.
I don't know
if I can make that happen, Jack.
We've got to make
that happen.
Otherwise, this play is
going to fall through.
We have no other way
to find the bombs.
I'll call
the White House.
--I've got Bill
Buchanan on the phone.
I'm patching
him through.
Bill, you're on speaker
with Tom Lennox and myself.
So what's the situation?
Jack Bauer wasn't able
to extract any information
from Fayed.
He considered it a dead end.
Consequently, we
implemented a plan intended
to trick Fayed
into leading us
to the location
of the suitcase nukes.
What sort of plan?
We staged a fake rescue of Fayed
by CTU agents posing as members
of a terrorist cell
with loyalties to Habib.
We hoped
that Fayed would lead us
to wherever his men
are holed up.
But he hasn't, right?
No, sir.
Fayed is stalling until he can
get confirmation from Habib
that these men are
taking orders from him.
He wants to speak
to the general, sir.
Habib is still being
interrogated, Bill.
We don't yet know how
cooperative he's being
or even if he will be.
I appreciate that, sir.
Our agents on the inside
are trying
to circumvent Fayed's request,
but Jack believes
Fayed will not lead us
to the location of the nukes
unless he speaks directly
to the general.
Where's the ambassador now?
He arrived a
few minutes ago.
Karen Hayes is meeting
him in the lounge.
All right.
I'll do my best to put pressure
on the ambassador, Bill.
Maybe they can force
Habib to make that call.
Keep doing what you can
on your end
just in case
I'm not successful.
Yes, sir,
we'll keep you apprised.
All right.
You know, sir, if this
ruse isn't working,
our time might be better
served getting the information
out of Fayed by more
conventional means.
Tom, if Jack Bauer says
that's a dead end,
then it's a dead end,
and I believe him.
Let's not keep
the ambassador waiting.
Oh! Are you all
right, sir?
I'm fine.
Ambassador.
Mr. President.
The Prime Minister has asked
me to convey his gratitude
to you for stopping the attack
on our country and his relief
that an international
catastrophe was
narrowly avoided.
Well, don't get
too comfortable,
Mr. Ambassador,
because there may be one yet.
Sit down.
Let me get right to the point.
At this very moment,
Abu Fayed is traveling
with a team of CTU agents
posing as a terrorist cell
allied with General Habib.
You have Fayed?
Yeah, we do, but we don't
have the suitcase nukes.
The problem is Fayed
will not rendezvous with his men
until he speaks to that
general, presumably to confirm
the legitimacy
of our undercover agents.
So we need that phone call
to take place now.
I appreciate your dilemma,
Mr. President,
and I will gladly
pass on your request.
But I'm not sure
the general would
be accommodating.
He's proven to be quite stubborn
throughout his interrogation.
Well, perhaps you should be
a little bit more persuasive.
I resent your tone.
I don't need you to tell me
how dire the situation is.
This is not a moment
for your indignation,
considering
it's your country's
own inactions that have brought
us to this point.
I can assure you,
every effort is being made
to get information
from him.
We have even
arrested his family.
Have you threatened
to kill them?
I beg your pardon?
Mr. President...
These are desperate times
for us, Mr. Ambassador.
I spared your country
a nuclear strike that
would have killed thousands.
What is your country
willing to do
to insure that
another bomb
does not go off in mine?
What you're suggesting
is barbaric.
I'm fully aware
of how your country treats
political dissidents.
So don't you dare
speak to me of barbarism.
Now I don't care
how you do it,
but General Habib
needs to call Fayed
and give him his orders
directly without
compromising CTU's operation.
You'll make the call now.
Nadia...
if General Habib makes
the call,
it'll be to
Jamal's phone,
but the general
doesn't speak English.
I'll set up a
separate channel
and translate
their conversation.
Milo, I need you to uplink
a proprietary channel
on socket D to my terminal.
I can't. I'm busy.
Why don't you just
do it yourself?
Because I don't have level five
security clearance.
Hasn't stopped you before,
now, has it?
Milo, is there something
on your mind?
I just don't get it.
A few hours ago, Doyle was
threatening you, hurting you.
You were barely talking
to me and now, what, you
two are best buddies?
Just because I showed concern
for an injured field agent
Concern...?
doesn't make us friends.
Milo, besides,
he might not as bad
as you think he is.
No. He is.
The guy is a creep
and a sadist.
You know what?
I don't have time for this.
I can have Chloe do it.
It's fine.
Wait, that's it? That's
all you're going to say?
Let go of me.
Psst.
I know it's none of my business,
but do we have
a bit of a problem?
No.
I'll set up your channel.
Thank you.
You all right, love?
Yeah. Thanks.
Don't mention it.
(labored breathing)
Pull into that garage up there.
We'll wait there.
JACK:
Stop right up here.
Fayed, I understand
your caution.
But we can't just sit
here while the Americans
are looking for us.
I told you-- we're not going any
further until the general calls.
Tell me, Jamal.
FAYED: If you take your orders
from General Habib as I do,
how is it I've never heard
of you or your cell?
This is going south, Jack.
Just be patient.
Don't be a fool, Fayed.
You know how this works.
Every cell is autonomous,
without the knowledge
of what the others are doing.
It is the only way
that we can protect ourselves
and our operations
should any of us get captured.
(phone rings)
Yes?
(speaking Arabic)
The general.
Alloo?
HABIB:
Fayed...
(speaking Arabic)
NADIA (over radio):
"Fayed, I can't speak long.
I suspect I'm being watched."
(Fayed speaking Arabic)
"So I was told."
General...
"General..."
"these men who rescued me,
did you send them?"
(speaking harshly in Arabic)
"Of course I sent them."
"Do you still
have the bombs?"
(speaking Arabic)
"There are two left.
They're with Halil
at a safe house."
(Habib speaking Arabic)
"Why haven't you used them?"
(Fayed speaking Arabic)
"The Russian Gredenko
failed to provide us
with the means to
a secondary target."
(speaking Arabic)
"You failed, Fayed."
"I should have sent Sameer
in your place."
(speaking Arabic)
"Are the bombs operational?"
"They are."
"Good."
"Connect with your men,
"get the bombs
ready to move out,
"call me back
at this number.
"By then, I will have chosen
a new target for you.
Do you understand?"
Na'am, General.
"Yes, General."
Are we good?
The safe house isn't far.
Head east toward
the 110 Freeway.
Target vehicle is moving.
Copy that, Jack.
Looks like it worked.
I'll let the White House know.
Let's go.
Mr. President?
Are you feeling
all right?
I'm fine, Karen.
Just a...
just a little tired.
Mr. President,
I just got word from CTU.
The general's phone call appears
to have satisfied Fayed.
He's leading them
to the safe house and the bombs.
Oh, thank God.
I'm pleased we were able
to help, Mr. President.
(Wayne clears throat)
(strained):
So am I.
Karen, would you please show
the ambassador
to his car.
Yes, Mr. President.
AMBASSADOR:
Forgive me, Mr. President,
but I believe you asked me
to remain here
until the crisis is resolved.
That won't be necessary
any longer.
Thank you again
for your cooperation.
Of course,
Mr. President.
You handled him well, sir.
(strained):
The door, Tom.
Excuse me, sir?
What...?
The door, lock it.
Mr. President...
No one can know.
Sir!
--All shadow teams
for Bauer and Doyle
have checked in
and are standing by.
They're ready to advance
the moment Fayed arrives
at the safe house.
No one moves until Jack calls
with confirmation
that the nukes are there.
Make sure Fayed's vehicle
and the follow car
have a wide berth.
No choppers in the area.
Nothing to tip Fayed off.
Right.
Sir...
I think we have a problem.
What is it?
I analyzed the transcript
between General Habib and Fayed.
There's an
inconsistency.
During the conversation,
the general mentioned
a man named Sameer.
That's right.
According to the
inter-agency database,
a Sameer Al-Afted served
on the general's staff
throughout the '90s.
He was later implicated
in money laundering
for various radical
organizations.
Well, that's probably the guy.
Yeah, well, the problem is,
Sameer Al-Afted was killed
two years ago in a raid
by Afghan forces.
But the general spoke about
him as if he were alive.
Okay, he could be referring
to another Sameer.
Or it could be a code.
I think the general
was trying to tell Fayed
that he was speaking
under duress.
I'd better warn
Jack and Doyle.
Nadia...
Good work.
Jack...
they're turning north
onto Adams.
Jack, we just detected
what might be a duress code
in the conversation between
General Habib and Fayed.
Give us the specifics.
The general mentioned sending
in a man named Sameer Al-Afted.
But Sameer's been dead
for two years.
Give me your phone,
we need to call Jamal.
Jack, if they're wrong,
you could blow this.
If they're right,
this is already over.
Now give me your phone!
(phone rings)
Yes?
JACK:
Jamal, this is Agent Bauer.
I'm in the follow vehicle
behind you.
I need you to listen
to me very carefully.
Go ahead.
We believe that General Habib
may have given Fayed
a duress signal.
Fayed might know
that this is a setup.
Jamal? Jamal, do you copy?
(static crackling)
Damn it, what the
hell just happened?
CTU, we just lost
video and audio.
They went into a tunnel
about a quarter of a mile ahead.
It may just be interference.
How long is it?
Checking.
It's only 120 yards long.
They should've come out
the other side by now.
Copy that.
Aerial One, this is Jack Bauer.
We have lost the target vehicle.
It entered a tunnel on Adams.
We need you to seal off
the north end. We're going in.
PILOT:
Roger. On our way.
We got a visual on
the target vehicle.
It stopped in the middle
of the tunnel.
We're going to engage.
(tires screeching)
Now.
Dead.
They're both dead.
Jamal's still alive.
Stay with him.
Call in a medic.
Aerial One, did you see anything
leave the north end
of the tunnel?
Aerial One, do you copy?
(door slams)
* *
(grunting)
(panting)
It's me. I'm on my way
to you now.
I'll explain when I get there.
(gears grinding)
(engine roaring)
Bill, it's Jack! Do you copy?!
Jack, go ahead.
Fayed is in a sanitation truck
headed east!
Jack, say again.
We didn't get that.
Damn it!
(transmission static)
Jack?
(static continues)
The signal's gone.
There's no contact
from Agent Doyle.
Aerial One says they're still
inside the tunnel.
Send the call
to audio forensics,
see if they can pull
what Jack said.
Chloe, replay the
satellite feed.
Back-time it 60 seconds.
Yes, sir.
Bill, this is Doyle.
I don't have
a twenty on Jack.
But I have a dead
body at the loading dock.
--Doctor, what is
happening to him?
His blood
pressure's dropped.
It's 80/40.
It could be any
number of things:
vascular damage from
the adrenaline shot,
intracranial swelling...
Mr. President?
We have to get you
down to Medical.
No.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
(groaning)
Just give me another
shot of adrenaline.
No, sir.
Another injection
would kill you.
I should never
have given you
that last one. I won't make
that mistake again, I'm sorry.
Sir, what are you doing?
I'm going back to work.
Would you please
listen to this man.
Let him perform some tests.
When this crisis is over, Tom,
and those nukes are secured.
In my opinion,
you won't last that long.
I might surprise you.
Mr. President...
if you don't get down
to Medical right now,
you can have my resignation.
I won't accept your resignation,
Arthur, so don't bother.
Now, please...
will you excuse us?
(labored breathing)
(whispering):
For God's sake,
talk some sense
into him, Tom.
It is his decision.
Tom...
call CTU.
I want to know
what's happening.
All right, sir.
All right.
HALIL:
What's going on, Brother Fayed?
What happened?
FAYED:
Gredenko betrayed us.
He led CTU right to me.
What?!
They may be tracking me.
It's not safe here.
Load the bombs onto the truck.
We're leaving.
Where are we going?
To finish this.
We're going to take out
downtown Los Angeles.
Let's move!
You wait here.
You guys, come with me.
(bones cracking, low groaning)
(gate and chains rattle)
(Fayed speaking Arabic)
(three gunshots)
(gunfire, men shouting)
(groaning)
(both grunting, shouting)
(grunting)
(pained shouting)
(pained groaning)
Say hello to your brother.
(choking)
(helicopter blades whirring)
Jack? Jack?
(panting)
You all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
How'd you find me?
Well, we tracked the
sanitation truck by satellite.
Bombs are on the table.
CTU, this is Doyle.
We're on site.
The bombs are secure,
and Jack's all right.
Repeat, the bombs are secure.
Damn, Jack.
Let's get you to Medical.
(groaning):
I'm fine.
(cell phone ringing)
Doyle.
(chamber clicks)
You got a call.
It's being routed
through CTU switchboard.
Thanks.
This is Bauer.
Hello? Hello?
WOMAN (over phone):
Jack...
are you there?
Can you hear me?
Audrey?
Help me, Jack.
Please, help me. You...
What the hell is going on?
Audrey, where are you?
CHENG:
Hello, Mr. Bauer.
Yes, Ms. Raines is alive.
If you wish her
to remain that way,
you will call me back
in ten minutes
at 310-597-3781
on a secure line.
If you make any attempt
to find our location,
she dies.
Cheng... Cheng!
(dial tone drones)
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net
www.tvsubtitles.net