-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
Yeah.
Mark Hauser?
Who's this?
You know who it is.
MARK:
I already gave you
what you asked for.
But your employer
has tightened security,
so the access I paid for
is no good.
It'll take some time to download
the new security protocols.
I'll give them 40 minutes.
Federal agent!
Down on the floor!
Bill, Hauser admitted
to selling Gredenko
the security specs for Edgemont
nuclear power facility.
Does Gredenko have the specs?
Not yet. He's going to pick
them up in about 20 minutes.
Hauser was wounded, but he's got
a brother that Gredenko knows.
We're going to use him
to go through
with the transaction.
You look nervous, Brady.
All teams,
take out your targets.
There's a third hostile
inside the vehicle!
You know who I am
and you know
what I'm going to do to you
unless you tell me
where the bombs are.
First my terms:
amnesty from
your government and a guarantee
I won't be returned to Russia.
Nadia's being processed
as an enemy combatant.
I don't know if I can accept
that she betrayed us.
She spied for Fayed?
I think we're wrong.
I hear you and Nadia Yassir
are friends.
Yeah. Why do you ask?
'Cause I came across
evidence
at the switching station
that proves Nadia's innocent.
You're clear, Nadia.
Admiral Smith,
is the Vickery ready to launch?
It's seconds from
optimal launch position,
Mr. Vice President.
Good, proceed
with the strike.
HAYES:
Vice President Daniels
is about to launch a nuclear
strike against the Middle East.
This strike is a complete
reversal of everything
your brother was working for.
You want Dr. Welton
to bring him out of the coma.
Yes.
(phone rings)
It's for you, sir.
Yes.
I've called off the strike,
Noah.
I'm resuming my duties
as Commander in Chief.
Inform Admiral Smith
and the others
there's to be no hostile action
without my direct
authorization.
It's apparent to me that
the president is still suffering
the effects
from the attack on his life.
I can't let him remain in power.
Get me the Attorney General.
LENNOX: Secretary Dawes,
can you see and hear me clearly?
Yes, I can.
What about Secretary Durant
and Attorney General Graves?
Their connections
are being set up now.
How about the president?
He should be arriving
any moment.
What are you doing?
I need to get up
from this wheelchair.
No, you need
to take care
of yourself.
Sandra, I can't afford
to look weak.
Roosevelt did just fine
from a wheelchair.
Listen, when I face Daniels,
I want to be on my feet.
Dr. Welton?
Yes, sir?
Can you give me a shot
of adrenaline?
Wayne.
I can.
It'll raise your
blood pressure,
which is not what
you need right now.
Could elevate
the risk...
(knocking)
Mr. President,
it is time.
Give us a few minutes, please.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me,
Mr. President.
Mr. President...
Just do it.
Now.
(phone beeps)
What do you have, Jack?
Gredenko offered us Fayed
in exchange for immunity
and a guarantee that we won't
extradite him back to Russia.
Bill, I don't trust him.
He rolled over
too easy.
What do you think
his play is?
I don't know yet.
Well, it's your call, Jack.
But you should know
what's happening in Washington.
President Palmer's
regained consciousness.
How is he?
Well enough to reassert
his claim on the presidency.
but Daniels is challenging
him under the 25th amendment
in large part
so he can go ahead
with the nuclear strike
against Fayed's country.
Does he have a chance
of winning?
It's unclear, but if Fayed
detonates another bomb,
no one will be able
to stand in Daniels' way.
If there's a challenge
for the presidency,
the immunity agreement
will have no authority.
It won't be binding.
Bill, you need to understand
that I have no intention
of honoring
this agreement.
Tell the Attorney General,
fill out the papers.
I'm calling him right now.
The president should be here
momentarily.
Mr. President.
Mr. President,
I know I speak
for everyone here in saying
how very happy I am to have you
with us again.
Let's proceed.
(Lennox clears throat)
LENNOX:
As you know, an attempt was made
to assassinate the president.
He sustained injuries so serious
that the doctors had
to induce a temporary coma
in order to relieve
the pressure on his brain.
In so doing,
they saved his life.
The question now is whether,
in the words
of the 25th amendment,
he is unable to discharge the
duties and powers of his office.
Mr. Lennox,
isn't this really
a medical question?
Well, to a degree it is,
but the 25th amendment
puts the final decision squarely
in the hands of the Cabinet.
May we hear medical testimony?
Yes, we may.
And to that end, let me bring in
the surgeon in charge
of the president's case.
Dr. Welton,
if you would, please.
The president has undergone
an ordeal,
but from a medical
point of view,
I believe the greatest danger
is passed.
His cognitive functions
are presenting normally.
I have every expectation
that President Palmer
will make a full recovery.
GILES:
Might the pressures
of the office
increase the possibility
of a relapse?
It's difficult to say.
It's certainly a possibility.
Can you estimate those chances?
I'm afraid I can't.
If you had a vote, Doctor,
how would you cast it?
This is precisely the question
which the Constitution
demands that
this Cabinet answer.
Thank you very much, Doctor.
Uh, Mr. President, I think now
would be an appropriate time
to address the Cabinet,
if you would, please.
The vice president initiated
this process
because I stopped him
from launching a nuclear strike
against the Middle East.
But this vote shouldn't be
about policy.
According to the Constitution,
you're judging me
to see if I am unable
to discharge the duties
of my office.
Well, as you can see,
and as you were just told
by my physician, I'm in complete
possession of my faculties,
and so to remove me
from this office
would be to betray
both your oath
and the American people
who voted me as their president.
All right, Mr. Vice President.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the Cabinet,
the 25th amendment
is purposely vague
on how you're supposed
to judge if a president
is unable to discharge
his duties.
It's open
to interpretation,
which is why
this is very much about
the president's policies
and his actions.
Here are the facts:
When a second nuclear attack
today spread radiation
over one of our major cities,
I decided
it was necessary to launch
a retaliatory strike
to show our enemies
that if attacked,
we would make them share
our pain.
Wayne Palmer's
first act upon regaining
consciousness
was to stop that strike;
to respond to the attack
by doing nothing.
In a time of war,
the president must be strong
enough in body and mind
to defend this country.
And I'm afraid
Wayne Palmer's actions
are the proof in this matter
that indeed,
he is unable
to discharge his duties.
All right,
time is of the essence,
so unless there's an objection,
I would like to recess
and then reconvene
for your vote in ten minutes.
--Any word on the
Cabinet vote?
No, they haven't
come back yet.
Look, Milo,
about what happened today,
let's just put it
behind us, okay?
Oh, which part,
the suspicion of terrorism
or the... the other thing?
The suspicion.
And the other thing?
Let's not worry about it
right now.
Let's try and get
through the day.
Okay.
I'm not going to
forget about the kiss,
and I don't think
you are, either.
(phone rings)
Nadia.
Nadia, it's Doyle.
Don't say my name,
just listen.
All right.
Okay. I need you to come up
to my office right now
and don't say anything
to anybody, just come.
On my way.
(sighs)
Have a seat.
Look, I know you and I
got off to kind of a bad start.
A bad start?
You assaulted me.
This country is under attack
by Islamic terrorists.
We had reason to believe there
was a mole in this building.
Starting with you wasn't racist.
It was common sense.
Oh, okay, so you're not
a racist, you're just a sadist.
You don't know me.
I think I do.
Why'd you call me here?
It turns out
there was no mole.
The terrorists were able
to hack into our system
'cause someone screwed up
and logged the wrong
security parameters.
I'm pretty sure
that someone was Milo,
and the proof
is on his computer.
I need someone to get it
without him noticing.
I can't do that.
Why? Is it 'cause
you're too busy
deciding if you want
to sleep with him?
Listen, if you don't get
the evidence for me,
I'm going to call a forensics
team, and they're going to come
and tear his system apart
as the entire floor watches.
And if they find what I think
they're going to find,
everyone gets to watch
Milo hauled out of this building
in handcuffs.
I'm sure it wasn't pleasant
when it happened to you.
But you're going to stand by
and watch it happen to him?
That's your idea
of being a friend.
So you want me to betray him
for his own good.
I promise you,
Milo will be better off
if you help me
than if you don't.
Your call.
If the Cabinet sides with you,
what are you going to do
about Daniels?
Unfortunately, Karen,
the Constitution doesn't
allow the president
to fire his
vice president.
No, but you can
marginalize him.
Karen's right.
Get him out of the bunker.
I would love to,
but Daniels has
way too many supporters,
and I can't afford
to alienate any one of them
right now.
Besides, I'd rather
have him somewhere
where I can keep an eye on him.
Mr. President,
the Cabinet's
reconvening.
Thank you.
HAYES:
All right, let's go.
Please, sit.
All right,
ladies and gentlemen
of the Cabinet,
let us now begin the vote.
Will those of you who believe
that President Palmer is able
to discharge his duties
please, at this time,
raise your hand.
Do we have any abstentions?
Uh, the vote is seven to seven.
LENNOX:
Mr. Attorney General,
what would be the next step?
Well, there's no need
for a next step.
The amendment requires
that the vice president
and a majority
of the Cabinet agree.
There is no majority
in the Cabinet.
It's split evenly.
President Palmer
remains in office.
NOAH:
It's not that simple--
one of the Cabinet votes
is invalid.
LENNOX:
Uh... sir,
wh-which vote is not valid?
National Security Advisor.
What are you
talking about?
She resigned.
I resumed my duties.
I don't agree.
And I haven't seen
any evidence
that you've been reinstated.
That is ridiculous!
I sat here with you
in a Cabinet meeting
less than one hour ago!
Ms. Hayes,
allowing you to sit in on
the meeting isn't the equivalent
of formally recognizing you
as National Security Advisor.
In fact, I did not
and do not so recognize you.
Oh, my God!
And if Ms. Hayes'
vote is invalid,
then the tally's seven to six
in favor of invoking the
25th amendment and removing...
President Palmer
from power.
I'm sorry, Wayne.
Noah, don't waste
your apologies on me,
because I won't let you
steal the presidency.
That's just not going to happen.
And what do you suggest?
The country has to be governed.
LENNOX:
Well, I would suggest,
sir, that this is
properly a matter
for the courts.
I concur.
We don't have time to go to...
GRAVES:
Mr. Vice President, if I may.
I agree with Mr. Lennox--
this is a legal question.
The Supreme Court
was in session this afternoon.
We can recall it and have them
render a decision regarding
the validity of the vote.
The whole matter could be
resolved in well under an hour.
Well, thank you,
Attorney General Graves.
Why don't you simply
get the process started,
and keep us advised
of your progress.
Certainly.
I think this meeting
is concluded.
(quietly):
Get my affidavit started.
Tom.
You know something?
I'm beginning to think
you're not on my side.
Well, sir, I'm on the side
of the United States of America,
and if you ever
thought otherwise,
you were very much mistaken.
--Gredenko's attorney approved
the immunity agreements.
Yeah, we're just waiting
for digital signatures.
All right.
I'll inform the attorney
general's office
it's on its way.
Thank you.
Milo.
What's up?
I'm having a problem
with my station--
it keeps telling me
to refresh
the system credentials.
Uh, it's the
hardware codes.
You have to reset them
in the machine room.
I can take care of it.
Thanks.
You okay?
Yeah.
(laughs softly)
Well, you were right.
Milo forgot to refresh
the security parameters.
The breach was his fault.
So when you tell District,
they can fire and maybe
even arrest him.
Which is why
I'm going
to alter the logs so
they'll never know.
(sighs):
This should work,
as long as they haven't
changed the password.
(beep)
There. It's done.
Why'd you do that?
'Cause all I care about
is finding those nukes,
and we have a better chance of
doing that with Milo on board,
whether he likes me or not.
"And mankind was naught
by a single nation."
You've read the Koran.
Yeah, and the Bible
and the Upanishads.
Anything I can get my hands on.
You're lucky--
you found your answers.
I'm looking for mine.
I'm going to get ready
to deploy.
What did Doyle want?
Nothing. We were just
reviewing some data sets.
Oh, your... system's back up.
Thanks.
(phone rings)
Buchanan.
HAYES:
Hi. It's me.
Hey, how did
the Cabinet vote go?
It was a tie, which, in effect,
means that Palmer's
still in office.
Good, that's good.
That's what we wanted.
Yes, well, Daniels is
contesting the vote.
He's saying that
mine is invalid.
Based on what?
Based on the fact
that I resigned,
and I was never
officially reinstated.
That's ridiculous.
You attended Cabinet meetings;
you had no replacement assigned.
How does he explain that?
I know, but maybe
he's right, Bill.
I did hand in my resignation.
Which was rescinded before
it was officially accepted.
Daniels knows that.
He's grasping at straws, Karen.
I'm so scared, Bill.
If he wins...
this will all be my fault.
Stop, stop.
It's desperate maneuvering
on his part,
Karen, nothing more.
He hasn't got a case.
And the Supreme Court
will agree.
Well, we're giving our arguments
in 15 minutes.
Call me as soon
as the decision is in.
Thank you for being there.
You don't have to thank me.
It's my job.
(laughs)
I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
I'll talk to you soon.
Bye.
(long sigh)
(Gredenko speaking Russian)
(man speaks Russian over phone)
Dasvidanya.
(snaps cell phone shut)
Good. My attorney
has verified the agreements.
Bill, we're set.
Gredenko's ready
to make the call.
All right, Jack,
we're standing by.
Doyle's got a team ready to go
as soon as Fayed tells Gredenko
where to meet him.
Copy that.
You try and warn Fayed
with anything you say
or how you say it,
and I will kill you
right here right now.
I believe you, Agent Bauer.
Make the call.
(phone rings)
Yes?
It's me.
Do you have the security
protocols for the power plant?
Yes.
Where do you want to meet?
Are you certain
you're not under surveillance?
Of course.
Do you think I'd be
calling you otherwise?
I can't allow another
one of your mistakes
to disrupt my plans
for the remaining two devices.
Do you want
the protocols or not?
Where are you right now?
Culver City.
Meet me at the Santa Monica Pier
in ten minutes.
GREDENKO:
Um, it may take me more time.
I won't wait.
Where do I find you?
Just be there.
I'll find you.
Give him the phone.
Bill, how long will
it take Doyle's team
to make it to the pier?
He's about 30 minutes out, Jack.
We'll make due with Ryan's team.
Put him in the vehicle.
Instructions from
the Supreme Court.
Our arguments have
to be submitted in writing,
in the next ten minutes.
Sandra's working
on our brief.
How's it coming?
I'm just about finished.
We have a strong case.
You resigned, and Daniels
was in charge
when you returned,
so the legal question is,
did he consent
to your reinstatement?
Of course he did.
And he made no objections when
you returned to the bunker,
you sat in his
first Cabinet meeting,
and he never questioned
your right to be there?
No, he didn't.
His own actions
prove our case.
Thank you...
for everything, Sandra.
My affidavit explains
everything--
that I never really intended
to reinstate Karen,
I was only allowing her
to perform her duties
temporarily, therefore,
she had no authority
to cast a vote
under the 25th amendment.
The problem is,
after Karen returned,
you treated her
as if she were still
National Security Advisor.
It's really a question of my
state of mind, though, isn't it?
Yes. And your state of mind
will be inferred
from your actions.
Doesn't sounds like you think
our chances are very good.
I don't.
Then I am... deeply afraid
for our country.
When the world sees
that Wayne Palmer
isn't willing to fight back,
our enemies will be encouraged.
These recent attacks will be
just the beginning.
America will be vulnerable
in a way it never has been.
There may be a way
to illuminate your state
of mind more explicitly.
I can swear an affidavit
that, earlier today,
you told me to
inform Karen Hayes
you had no intention
of reinstating her.
But that you were
going to allow her
to perform her duties
on a temporary basis only.
Then Wayne regained
consciousness
before I could have
that conversation with her.
Lisa, you're talking
about perjuring yourself
in front of the Supreme Court.
I'm aware that
it's perjury,
but the end
justifies the means.
My affidavit will
push the court to
rule in your favor
so that you can
do what's right
for this country.
You're right.
Do it.
Prepare your affidavit.
And, Lisa...
...thank you.
Yes, sir.
Kasim, Hassan, with me.
I'm meeting Gredenko.
I'll be back within the hour.
And if you're not?
Are you worried for me, Halil,
or just anxious
to take my place?
I think we're wasting time.
We have the bombs.
We should use them right now.
Gredenko's information
will enable us
to inflict damage
across half of California.
There's other target out there
that will result
in large amount of casualties
without the additional risk.
I've made my decision.
Let's go.
Come in.
Mr. Vice President,
I need to speak with you alone.
There is something in this room
you need to know about, sir.
Something in this room?
What are you
talking about?
This small object here
is a microtransmitter.
After you directed me
to lie to the ambassador
about the attempted
assassination,
I decided it was time
to protect myself.
Now it turns out I was
protecting the country as well.
Be careful, Tom.
Be very careful
what you try to do here.
Actually, sir, you are the one
who needs to be careful here.
LISA:
I'm aware that it's perjury,
but the end justifies the means.
My affidavit will push the court
to rule in your favor
so that you can do what's right
for this country.
NOAH:
You're right.
Do it.
Prepare your affidavit.
Turn it off.
As I'm sure you're aware, sir,
conspiracy to commit perjury
is a felony offense.
Now, I strongly urge you
to pick up that phone
and call the Supreme Court
and tell them that you have
withdrawn your affidavit,
and that of
Ms. Miller as well.
Tell them that you support
the vote of the Cabinet.
That you have
no further objections
to President Palmer
continuing his presidency.
You do understand
that I'm just trying
to do what's right
for this country.
Well, so am I, sir.
--Karen, I need
the launch protocols
the Joint Chiefs set up
with Vice President Daniels
along with chain
of command signing.
They just came over
from the Pentagon.
Everything is in place.
If the court sides with you,
you can cancel the strike
permanently.
I also need want an update
on the situation with Fayed.
(hoarsely):
Has CTU made any progress?
Yes, they have
Gredenko in custody.
The last time I talked to Bill,
they said they were going
to use him to lure Fayed
out in the open.
Who's running it?
Jack Bauer.
Good.
SANDRA:
Wayne.
The Supreme Court
was just notified
Daniels withdrew his suit.
What?
It's over.
He gave up before the
court had a chance
to make its decision.
Why?
I don't know.
I just know
that you're still
the President of
the United States.
(breathing heavily)
Let the Cabinet know
I won't take any action
against those who sided
with the vice president.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and, Karen,
tell Bill I want him to keep me
up to date on CTU's progress.
(breathing heavily)
Melinda.
Tell Dr. Welton I need
to see him, please.
I don't have a visual yet,
but Fayed won't show himself
until he sees Gredenko.
BUCHANAN:
Understood. Ryan,
what's your status
with Gredenko?
RYAN:
I've got
the audio transmitter set up.
I'm preparing
the tracker now.
Roll up your left sleeve.
JACK:
What's its range?
We can track the isotope's
signature up to 15 miles.
Copy that.
(winces)
Is it radioactive?
Yes.
It penetrates
into the bone.
It's got a half-life
of about 11 hours,
so you can forget about
trying to dig it out
or making a run for it.
He's good to go.
JACK: Bill.
How far out is Doyle's team?
About 20 minutes.
We can't wait.
Fayed was clear
about his timeline.
Ryan,
send in Gredenko.
Gredenko's moving now.
CHLOE: I'm getting
a clean audio signal
from the transmitter
on Gredenko.
And we are locked
on the isotope signature
that's being emitted
from Gredenko's arm.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Hello?
I have the gain on Gredenko's
transmitter up all the way.
There's no one
on the other end of the call.
He's reading something
off his phone.
It's a text message.
Fayed's made contact.
Everyone get ready.
Gredenko is heading south.
Milo, have you got him
on the tracker?
Yeah, he's still moving.
I'm heading in.
I'm going to follow him.
* *
I've lost audio signal.
I'm going to secondary channel.
There's no audio
on the secondary channel.
But he hasn't moved.
I don't like it.
Something's wrong.
You led them to me.
I had no choice.
But if you listen to me,
we'll both get
away from here alive.
Kasim.
Which direction, Milo?
I'm nearing the south end
of the pier.
That's where he stopped
and entered the building
on the left.
Is he still inside the room?
Yes, he's right on the other
side of the door.
I'm going in.
Milo, no one's in here.
Jack! The tracker's
showing the signal
right there
in the same room with you.
My God.
He cut off Gredenko's arm.
Ryan, move your men in now!
RYAN:
Roger that. Let's go.
Hold on.
I've picked up his blood trail.
Fayed,
their men will be coming
from the west side parking lot.
We should go this way.
Ryan, have your men circle back
to the east side of the pier.
Try and cut them off.
--Ryan, have you got anything?
Negative.
How far out
is Doyle's team?
20 minutes.
Have him set up a perimeter
as soon as he gets here.
Ryan, where are you?!
I'm pinned down!
Moving towards
you now.
Show me your head.
TV REPORTER:
But sources indicate that
the same terrorist
cell is most likely
responsible for the nuclear
explosion in Valencia...
We're trapped.
This way.
That's him.
I recognize him
from the news.
He's the terrorist
they're looking for.
MAN:
That is him.
You bastard.
Federal agent!
(two gunshots)
I am a federal agent!
I'm taking
this man into custody.
Now, back off!
Back off!
He shot my friend.
I'm sorry about your friend.
We'll get him medical attention.
Just stay back.
I hope your friend is dead.
Shut up!
Everybody out
of the bar now!
Move!
Gredenko is not here.
I need you to lock down the
area and initiate a search.
We have two men down.
One is a civilian, the other
is Fayed. He's in custody.
I need Medical
up here now.
All right, Jack. Good work.
Nadia, get me the president,
please.
I understand you're weak.
Another dose of
adrenaline will raise
your blood pressure
levels even higher,
to the point where we know
there'll be vascular damage.
And that's a risk
I'm willing to take.
Your well-being
is my responsibility.
And my responsibility, Doctor,
is to the well-being
of this country.
So give me another dose
so I can go back
to doing my job or I will find
someone else who will.
MELINDA:
Mr. President,
Bill Buchanan is on line one.
I'll take it.
Thank you, Arthur.
Yes, sir.
Bill.
Mr. President, I'm calling
to tell you that Jack
has Fayed in custody.
What about the bombs?
We haven't finished
the radiological scan yet,
so we can't confirm the bombs
are in the immediate vicinity.
Jack is going to interrogate
Fayed as soon as possible.
But there's no way of knowing
how long that will take
or how successful
that will be, right?
No, sir.
All right, Bill.
That's what I wanted to know.
Thank you, sir.
But since the case
was withdrawn,
the court has no reason
to retain the documents.
They should be sealed
and returned to me immediately.
Okay. Good. Thank you.
I was thinking
that maybe
it's time to
declare a truce.
Okay. Well... maybe it is.
You know, we both want the
same thing for this country--
what's good for the country.
We just don't always
agree on the means.
I would love to go forward
without the threats
and the intimidation.
Done.
Good.
One more thing.
Do you know why
the vice president
withdrew his suit
from the Supreme Court?
No. I have no idea. Why?
Well, one of
my aides saw you
with him before
it was announced.
I... I guess just put this down
to happy coincidence.
For now.
But someday I'd love to know
the realstory.
Okay. Some day.
(phone rings)
Lennox.
He...
This cannot be,
this has got to be some mistake.
I'm on my way.
President Palmer.
What?
He's about to go ahead
with the nuclear strike.
Mr. President.
If I may, sir.
I understand you're about
to launch the very strike
we just prevented Vice President
Daniels from launching.
That's right.
This makes no sense, sir.
I mean it's what
you risked your life to stop.
Tom, I risked my life
to reassert my authority.
I've got Vice President Daniels
calling me weak.
Even you thought the same thing.
I implore you, sir,
do not mistake being reckless
with being strong.
Tom, I am done talking.
Mr. President.
We have a successful launch.
Good.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net
www.tvsubtitles.net