Previously on 24.
The Americans know
our location.
We need to launch the
drone before they close in.
We'll find a way to deliver
the other two bombs.
Launch the drone.
- I can't find the drone.
- Readjust based on projected vectors.
I'm doing that now, General.
It's just not where it's supposed to be!
Until you find it, I'll have my
F-16s stay in a holding pattern.
We figured out how
the drone was able to
stay hidden from our satellites.
Whoever is piloting it
is able to anticipate our
repositioning directives.
How can he do that?
Our satellite data is being
relayed to the drone pilot
through a workstation here.
We have a leak.
We have to find out who's
subverting our system.
It is Nadia. The signature
trace matches her computer.
Surrender your station.
Who are you streaming
our satellite data to?
What?!
I will do what's necessary
to get the answers I need.
- Let her go.
- What the hell are you doing?
We got the drone
pilot's location.
We're not through
with her, Milo.
Jack, what's your status?
The drone pilot is down.
I'm at his controls now.
The target is San Francisco.
There is no way to deactivate
the bomb remotely.
I'm fighting a stall.
I'm losing control of the drone.
I need to find a
place to land it now.
None of the first responders in San
Francisco are reporting a detonation.
The bomb did not
go off on impact.
Move out! There's radioactive
material in this area!
We were able to take
control of the aircraft,
crash-landing it in an industrial
park at the edge of the city.
But in the process,
the bomb's nuclear core was compromised
and radioactive
material was released.
So what we're essentially
dealing with is a dirty bomb.
- Sir, it was a radiological spill.
- It was an attack on our nation.
I warned the ambassador, Tom.
We were led to believe that this
warning shot would be fired
only in response to the
detonation of a nuclear device.
They need to see with
their own eyes that
I will answer this threat with
an in-kind military response.
The order's given.
Launch the missile as
soon as they're in range.
Prep two units of fresh plasma.
You need to keep him alive.
Gredenko's got two more bombs out there.
Right now this man's
our only link to them.
Jack! I just talked to CTU.
There's a situation developing
where the drone went down.
What?
The casing on the nuclear bomb,
it cracked.
There's been some dispersal
into the atmosphere.
How bad is the fallout?
A dozen first-responders
were exposed to high levels,
but casualties
should be minimal.
Wind vectors are okay so far,
and they're starting to evacuate.
I want you to go through the pilot's
databases and electronic files.
I want you to see if you can
find any link to Gredenko.
Agent Bauer.
- He didn't make it.
- Damn it.
- Buchanan.
- Bill, it's Jack.
What did you get from
the drone pilot?
No, he's dead.
We've been running down
leads on this end.
So far nothing's
come up on Gredenko.
Doyle told me about the fallout,
but he said it was containable?
I'm afraid it's
not that simple.
The incident has created some serious
policy complications in Washington.
Like what?
Vice President Daniels has ordered a
nuclear strike against Fayed's country.
What's he trying to do,
start World War III?
That'll be seen as an act of aggression
against the entire Middle East.
Which is why we have to
find Fayed and Gredenko
before Daniels
launches the strike.
- When is it happening?
- Within the hour.
Bill, that doesn't give us
enough time to find Gredenko.
I'll get back to you.
Victor's still not answering.
Because the
Americans found him.
The bomb was supposed to hit
San Francisco ten minutes ago,
but there is
nothing on the news.
Even if you're right,
we are safe here.
Victor doesn't
know our location.
So we can continue
our operations safely.
What operation?
There is no operation.
It's over because of
you and your people.
No, Fayed, it isn't over.
We have two more bombs.
I have the bombs.
But you need me
to deliver them.
I'm the only one
who can give you the
targets you want.
Come on, come on, shoot me now,
or put down the gun.
- Yeah.
- Mark Hauser?
- Who's this?
- You know who it is.
I already gave you
what you asked for.
But your employer has
tightened security,
so the access I paid
for is no good.
- That's not my problem.
- It is your problem.
It became your problem the
moment you took my money.
It'll take some time to download
the new security protocols.
How much time?
Half an hour, maybe longer.
I can call you when it's ready.
- I'll be there in 40 minutes.
- Gredenko.
I'm hungry.
Knock yourself out.
There's peppers in here.
- You like peppers.
- Not red ones.
- I don't eat red food, Mark.
- Since when?
I don't like red food.
I'll take the
peppers out, okay?
You take care of me, Mark.
You always take care of me.
I do my best, Brady.
While I'm doing this,
I need you to do something for me.
Okay.
I need you to access some files
from the mainframe at my office.
- Can you do that?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
Nadia's being processed
as an enemy combatant.
She's being transferred to a
holding station in Temecula.
Sir, I don't know if I can
accept that she betrayed us,
that she spied for Fayed.
I think we're wrong.
This is not easy for any of us.
But the facts at hand indicate
she was streaming
intel from her station.
- Mr. Buchanan.
- What is it?
We may have caught a break.
What do you have?
I've been monitoring
everyone on our watch list
who's ever communicated with Gredenko
through phone calls or e-mails.
The filter algorithm flagged a call
that happened a few minutes ago.
Mark Hauser. He does security
consulting for energy companies.
His company has contracts with
dozens of chemical facilities--
oil fields,
pipelines and nuclear power plants.
Unfortunately the call was scrambled,
but we do have Hauser's address.
Get that address to Jack.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah, excuse us, guys.
While I was stripping data from
the drone pilot's hard drive,
I found this.
- What is it?
- Remote access module.
It's how the drone pilot
breached CTU's satellite grid.
No, the pilot got
into our system
because Nadia Yassir opened
the door and let him in.
No, she didn't.
This guy got in through one of the
radical web sites Nadia's
been monitoring.
The access module proves it.
Are you saying Nadia's system was
compromised and she didn't know it?
That's right.
That puts you in
a tough position,
considering you're the one who
led the witch hunt against her.
I followed standard protocols
based on the information that
was available at the time.
Well, Nadia might
not see it that way
when she takes it up with
the Justice Department.
You know,
once the dust settles today,
they might want to
make you an example.
Relax, Mike.
You took care of me in Denver,
and I still owe you for that.
But we're even now.
Copy that. I'll get back to
you as soon as we're there.
- We got a lead on Gredenko.
- How good a lead?
We'll know soon enough.
It's just a few miles from here.
I want you to put together a Tac Team,
we'll move out.
I need to stay behind.
We're still processing.
Fine.
Ryan, get your men together,
come with me.
Give us a minute, please.
Sandra?
How are you holding up?
I can't believe
this is happening.
It doesn't feel real.
I'm so sorry.
Sandra.
Unfortunately, I need to
ask you for your help.
There's an extremely volatile situation
developing at the White House.
Vice President Daniels
is about to launch
a nuclear strike
against the Middle East.
- A nuclear strike?
- Yes. And the cabinet is behind him.
I've tried arguing against it,
but no one's listening.
- Are they insane?
- No. They're just scared.
Before the attempted
assassination on your brother,
Wayne was reaching out to
the Middle East governments
to solicit their help in stopping Fayed.
And it was working.
This strike is a
complete reversal
of everything that
he was working for.
You want Dr.
Welton to bring him out of the coma.
Yes.
And I need your consent.
But the doctor said that
he needs to remain sedated
for a few days before
the swelling can subside.
Yeah, but we don't
have a few days.
Yeah, well,
even if Wayne regains consciousness,
we don't know what state he'll be in,
physically or mentally.
But we won't know
unless we try.
Sandra, I wouldn't dare
to ask you to risk this
if I did not think it was absolutely
necessary for the sake of our country.
- I'm sorry, I can't do it.
- Sandra, please.
I've already lost one brother.
I can't lose another one.
I know you did not ask
for this responsibility,
but like it or not,
it is yours.
Wayne Palmer is still the
president of our country.
He's the only one who can stop this from
happening, and you are the only one
who can give him the chance
to do what he believes in.
Give him that chance.
Ask yourself what Wayne
would want you to do.
I'll talk to Dr. Welton.
And God forgive
me if I'm wrong.
The USS Vickery has been detached
from carrier group Falcon,
which is currently on
patrol in the region.
Now, the Vickery will reach
launch position in 40 minutes.
So, in less than an hour,
we'll have made our point to the enemy?
Yes, Mr. Vice President.
The B-611 short-range tactical warhead
has a blast yield of 300 kilotons.
The message will
be loud and clear.
Very good, Admiral. Exemplary.
Tom, give us the damage and casualty
estimates you got from COMPLAN.
- Tom?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Is there a problem?
- No. No, no.
Um, this projection is,
of course,
based on theoretical models generated
at our nuclear facility in Alamogordo.
COMPLAN estimates a high range
of general damage by zone,
as well as multiple
casualty numbers
based on various
climate models.
- Now, should the...
- I'm sorry, Tom.
I need to step
out for a minute.
Carry on with the briefing.
Right. Uh,
should the enemy mount a response,
the potential does exist
for the US to be drawn
into a conflict in
which its troops...
What the hell does this mean,
they're taking him out of the coma?
Apparently, Sandra Palmer gave
her consent a few minutes ago.
- This is Karen Hayes.
- I don't know, sir.
I only found out about this because I
have a source inside the medical bay.
Put me through to Dr. Welton.
Okay. I've cut the
pentobarbital drip.
His metabolic rate's up,
and he's breathing on his own.
What about the
swelling in his brain?
No sign of
intracranial hypertension,
but it's still
too early to know
when or even if he'll
regain consciousness.
Dr. Welton, Vice President Daniels
on line one. He says it's urgent.
Dr. Welton,
what are you going to tell him?
The truth.
Mr. Vice President,
this is Dr. Welton.
I've just been told you're trying to
rouse the president out of his coma.
That's correct, sir.
I thought you induced the coma
to save the president's life.
Treating patients with head
trauma's a fluid process.
Sounds to me like you're risking the
life of the president of the
United States.
With careful monitoring,
we can minimize that risk.
- Let's cut the crap, Doctor.
- Sir?
We both know what's
going on here,
why Sandra Palmer wants
her brother conscious.
She's trying to subvert
my policy agenda.
Policy's not my concern.
Oh, I think you're
very concerned,
and I think you agree
with what she's doing,
and you're willing to risk the life
of the president to get it done.
So if you don't stop now,
I will compel you to stop.
With all due respect, sir,
the president's medical
treatment is not under...
- You'll do what I tell you.
- No, sir. I'm sorry, I will not.
I am required to follow the
wishes of Sandra Palmer.
You're free to take up
your concerns with her.
If the president dies or suffers any
permanent damage from your actions,
I will nail your
ass to the wall.
- Do you understand me?
- Perfectly, sir.
Chloe, I need that photo.
I need it now.
Sending now, Jack.
Team B,
advise when you're in position.
- Team B in position.
- Copy that.
I've got a positive ID.
Move in on the house now,
move in on the house now!
Federal agent!
Get on the floor!
- Don't move!
- Do what they say, Brady.
Put him in a chair.
Mark, Mark.
Take him in the
living room now.
- Let's go.
- He doesn't know anything.
- Shut up!
- Mark.
He's got some
arterial bleeding.
We need to get
him to a hospital.
We don't have time. Do whatever
you have to to stabilize him.
All right.
Let me have the room.
I know you're scared right now,
but everything's
going to be okay.
I want to see my brother.
I'm going to let you
see your brother,
but I need to ask you
some questions first.
- I'm not allowed.
- You're not allowed? Why?
Mark says,
don't talk to strangers.
I'm not a stranger.
I'm a police officer.
You can talk to me.
It's all right.
My name is Jack Bauer.
What's yours?
- Brady.
Brady, when we came in,
you were working on your computer.
What were you working on?
- Getting files.
- What kind of files?
I don't know.
Mark asked me to get through the IPC
firewall to set up a proxy server port.
- Oh.
- Can I see him now?
Soon.
I'm going to talk to him first,
and then you can see him, okay?
You're doing great, Brady.
Stay with him.
You were getting paid to give
Dmitri Gredenko information.
You used your brother to
get that information.
Now he's in a lot of trouble.
My brother's got
nothing to do with this.
That's not what he told me.
He doesn't...
he doesn't know what he's doing.
That's not how the Justice
Department's going to see it.
They're going to prosecute him
for treason unless I intervene.
Now I'll help your brother
because you and I both know
he didn't understand
what he was doing,
but you're going to have
to give me Gredenko.
What kind of information
were you selling him?
- Security specs.
- What security specs?
The Edgemont
nuclear power plant.
Bill, this is Connell Johnson.
He's on loan from District.
- Connell.
- Hey.
We swept the drone
pilot's system.
Most of the hard drives and
data files are encrypted.
Our digital forensics
people are expecting you.
We'll see what we can find.
Have you gotten anything
more from Nadia?
She still claims
she was set up.
- Is she in the building?
- Yeah.
She's being transferred
to a holding facility.
- Why do you ask?
- Just curious.
Sir, Jack's on line two.
He's got Hauser in custody.
Jack?
Bill, Hauser admitted
to selling Gredenko
the security specs for Edgemont
nuclear power facility.
- Does Gredenko have the specs?
- Not yet.
He's going to pick them
up in about 20 minutes.
- Can your team handle the grab?
- We've got a situation.
Hauser was wounded, but he's got
a brother that Gredenko knows.
We're going to use him to go
through with the transaction.
Right now, it's the best shot we've
got of getting Gredenko alive.
I'll get back to you as
soon as I've got anything.
Brady, we need to talk.
Are you really a policeman?
Yeah.
Then... my brother
did something wrong.
He's made some mistakes,
but he's helping us fix them.
Everyone makes mistakes.
I make mistakes all the time.
- And you try and fix them, right?
- Yeah.
That's what your brother's trying to do,
but he needs your help.
- Why don't we go talk to him?
- Okay.
Come on, let's go.
Mark? Mark?!
It's okay, Brady. It's okay.
It's not as bad as it looks.
They're taking me
to the hospital.
- I want to go with you, Mark.
- You need to stay with them.
Don't leave me alone,
Mark, please.
Listen to me, Brady. Listen.
You need to do whatever
this man tells you to do.
You'll be fine.
Who takes care of you, Brady?
- You do, Mark.
- That's right.
So you need to trust me when
I tell you you'll be fine.
He'll take care of you.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's make the call.
- Yes.
- It's Hauser.
I have the security protocols,
but there's a problem.
- What problem?
- My supervisor wants me to come in.
- I'll be there in 20 minutes.
- He wants me at the office now.
If I'm not there in ten minutes,
the protocols will default,
and I'll have to download
them all over again.
I need those protocols.
I can leave them
with my brother.
Brady?
Unless you want to wait for me
to get back from the office.
I don't have time.
Have your brother meet me in the
parking lot across the street.
He'll be there. Good-bye.
The parking lot.
Across the street. 20 minutes.
He needs to get to a hospital now.
Take him.
Mark! Mark!
Brady, it's all right.
It's all right. We're going to
take care of him, I promise.
Right now, I need you to
listen to me very carefully,
just like your brother
told you to. Okay?
Okay.
- Milo Pressman?
- Yeah.
Connell Johnson. I'm on loan
from District. Data forensics.
Yeah, I think we
crossed paths in Denver.
- That's right, we did.
- What can I do for you?
Well, I hear you and
Nadia Yassir are friends.
Yeah. Why do you ask?
Because I came across evidence
at the switching station
that proves Nadia's innocent.
- Explain.
- She wasn't streaming intel.
Her system was breached.
Where is this evidence?
- Ask Doyle.
- Doyle?
I hate to be a platoon rat,
but I don't know where else to go.
I gave him the evidence
at the crime scene,
and he still hasn't
logged it in.
Thank you.
Make sure Jack's team has a full
surveillance package with
infrared capability.
Why'd you do it,
you son of a bitch?
- Are you crazy?!
- Milo, hat's enough!
Tell him! Tell...
He's got evidence that Nadia's innocent!
- Is this true?
- Yeah.
And he buried it to
save his own ass.
He didn't bury it.
Milo. He didn't bury it.
It's a remote access module
that breached Nadia's computer.
He gave it to me
ten minutes ago.
Why didn't you tell
us about this?
Because I got it from
an unreliable source.
I wanted to make sure it was real
before I submitted it for evidence.
I ran a verification scan.
It's definitely real,
and Nadia is definitely innocent.
I'll review the evidence.
If it's true,
I'll release Nadia.
In the meantime,
go back to work!
Come with me, Morris.
Doyle...
I owe you an apology.
It's not your fault.
Still.
Milo, forget about it.
Johnson.
You have screwed with the wrong
guy for the last time, pal.
Uncuff her.
Excuse us, please.
We found evidence at
the switching station.
It proves your computer was
breached from an outside source.
You're cleared, Nadia.
I'm sorry this happened.
So am I.
Your first impulse will be to quit,
take legal action.
I don't blame you.
That's what I'd do.
But I'm asking you to stay.
This crisis is far from over.
We can't afford to
lose our best people.
We need you, Nadia.
I'll stay.
Milo's setting up
your workstation now.
I just sent over the assault vectors.
Nadia should be good to go.
Thank you.
We all thought she was guilty.
This is going to be awkward.
- Yeah.
- Especially for you.
Why especially for me?
Your feelings for Nadia
aren't exactly a big secret.
Thank you for
pointing that out.
Your station's all set.
Comm's up.
You'll have full security
access to the subnet.
Thanks.
Listen, Nadia, I just...
Look, Milo, I don't have time for
a heart-to-heart right now, okay?
I got a lot of catching up to do.
Excuse me.
I understand that. Nadia, wait.
Damn it! You're not going to
make this easy for me, are you?
You know what? Actually, I am.
Whatever you thought might happen
between us, you can just forget it.
That's not fair.
Milo, believe it or not, I don't
even blame you for suspecting me.
But you have to admit, this is not the
best place to start a relationship.
You're probably right.
But I still wanted
to say I'm sorry.
You said it.
I should get to work.
- Here.
- Thanks.
We haven't heard
from Dr. Welton,
and he's been giving
us regular updates.
Well, I'm sure if there
was something to report,
we would have heard from him.
Oh, gosh. I've never been
good at waiting for anything.
David had the patience of Job.
But not me.
Wayne is always
somewhere in between.
- We have a decision to make.
- What is it?
There's an increase in
intracranial swelling.
How serious is it?
It's not life-threatening yet,
but if it continues,
it could cause
permanent brain damage.
I suggest we
re-induce the coma.
No.
Sandra, you understand
the danger?
Yeah, but there's a
chance he'd be okay.
Yes, there's a chance.
Well, even if it's a small chance
for Wayne to stop Daniels,
then it's worth the risk.
I know Wayne would want
to see this through.
Dr. Welton?
You need to come quickly.
He's crashing. Get a code team in
here right away. Wait outside!
Code team to One!
Code team to One, stat!
Teams are in position.
You sure he can do this?
He just needs to get
Gredenko out of his car.
We don't have another option.
Just tell Charlie team
they've got one shot at this.
Damn it.
Brady, I need you to
wear one of these.
So we can talk to each other.
This way, you'll be able to hear me,
and I can hear you.
- I need to put it in your ear.
- Will, uh, it hurt?
No.
No, I promise.
See?
Now, I'm going to talk
you through this.
But we don't want Mr.
Gredenko to know that you can hear me.
So we have to pretend
that you can't.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Good.
You're going to give him this.
He's going to meet you in the
parking lot across the street.
I want you to stand on the sidewalk.
That's your position.
Okay.
We're set.
We should go now.
You don't need to be scared, Brady.
Everything's going to be fine.
I'm going to be able to
watch you the whole time,
and I'm going to be able to
hear everything that you say.
Now, I need you to
go to your position.
You remember the position
we talked about?
Yeah. I'm going to
go to my position.
Okay.
All teams, report in.
Alpha team, in position.
Bravo team, in position.
Charlie team, in position.
Charlie team,
you are responsible
for taking out Gredenko
with the tranquilizer dart.
Teams A and B,
I want you to acquire remaining targets.
Do whatever you have to,
to protect this kid.
Brady, it's Jack.
Can you hear me?
- I hear you.
- You're doing great.
- When can I see my brother?
- As soon as this is over, I promise.
Okay. Okay, good.
I have a visual on Gredenko's SUV.
Windows are tinted.
I can't see who's inside.
Brady? Do you see the car
that's coming towards you?
Yeah.
It's time to get ready.
I got a visual on Gredenko.
Charlie team, take your shot
as soon as you've got one.
Copy that.
- Do you have it?
- Yeah.
Give it to me.
I have a negative line of sight.
Hauser's in the way.
You look nervous, Brady.
Why are you so nervous?
Gredenko just gave the
order to shoot the kid
as soon as the
information's been verified.
Charlie team,
do you have your shot yet?
Negative. Hauser's
still in the way.
- Can you move position?
- Negative.
Brady. Don't forget to pretend
like you can't hear me.
You're doing great. I want you
to listen to me very carefully.
When I tell you, I want you to go
down to the ground and stay there.
Wait till I tell you.
Brady, get down on the ground.
Brady, get down on the ground!
All teams,
take out your targets.
All teams, there's a third
hostile inside the vehicle!
Brady. Brady, are you okay?
It's over. It's over.
You did great.
- I want to see my brother.
- Okay.
You can see your brother
just like I promised.
Get Gredenko back in the house.
Prep him. Contact CTU.
Advise Buchanan that we've
got Gredenko in custody
and we're prepping
him for interrogation.
Yes, sir.
Watch your head.
Brady, this man's going
to look after you.
He's going to take you
to see your brother.
- I want to see my brother.
- Yeah.
You did great. Thank you.
Okay.
We searched Gredenko's vehicle
and the surrounding area.
- There's no sign of the bombs.
- Is he conscious yet?
- Yes. You want help with him?
- No.
You know who I am?
I know all about you,
Agent Bauer.
Then you know what
I'm going to do to you
unless you tell me
where the bombs are.
And when I'm finished,
I'm going to put you on the fastest
plane we've got back to Russia.
I don't think President Suvarov's
going to be too happy to see you.
- Fayed has the bombs.
- Where is he?
I don't know.
But I can help you find him.
I'm listening.
I came here
to get security specs for the
Edgemont nuclear power plant.
- That's your next target.
- Yes.
Fayed's waiting for my call.
Make the call.
No.
First, my terms.
Amnesty from your government.
And a guarantee I won't
be returned to Russia.
What?
I'm offering you Fayed.
What's the problem?
I'm not martyr.
I'm soldier. And realist.
If I don't call him soon,
Fayed will get suspicious.
Admiral Smith,
is the Vickery ready to launch?
It's seconds from optimal launch
position, Mr. Vice President.
- Good.
- Mr. Vice President.
- Yes, Tom?
- Just spoke to Bill Buchanan at CTU.
They've taken Gredenko into custody.
Jack Bauer is questioning him now.
Does Bill think there's a chance
this could lead to something?
Well, he's confident that Bauer's
the man for the interrogation,
and he's hoping they get
the answers they need.
I hope his confidence
is justified.
Sir, the Vickery's in position.
They're standing by.
- Proceed with the strike.
- Yes, Mr. Vice President.
Mr. Vice President, if I may.
In light of the
developments at CTU,
do we not want to delay
this launch and just
see what Bauer gets
out of Gredenko?
I'm not going to
delay our response
based on what Gredenko
may or may not reveal.
But if Gredenko
gives up the bombs,
then surely that is
the desired result...
Then we can consider
this strike
as retaliation for American
lives already lost!
A reminder to the world there are
consequences to attacking our country.
Admiral Smith...
proceed with the launch.
Yes, Mr. Vice President.
Sir, the Vickery just received a
message over the COMPLAN subnet.
They've been ordered
to stand down.
What the hell are you talking about?
Who gave this order?
President Palmer, sir.
President Palmer?
Conference Room, Lisa Miller.
One moment.
It's for you, sir.
Yes.
Noah... it's Wayne.
Mr. President.
It is an incredible relief
to hear your voice.
To be frank, it's a surprise.
- I've called off the strike, Noah.
- We just received word.
Sir, this action
is a product of
careful deliberation between
myself and the Joint Chiefs.
Yeah, well, be that as it may,
the decision is mine
and mine alone.
I'm resuming my duties
as Commander in Chief.
Inform Admiral Smith
and the others,
there's to be no hostile action
without my direct authorization.
Is that understood?
Understood, Mr. President.
Good.
It's apparent to me that...
the President is still
suffering the effects from
the attack on his life.
He's not thinking clearly,
and in my judgment,
he's not capable of
discharging his duties.
I can't let him
remain in power.
Get me the Attorney General.
Synchro: Travis - Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com
www.tvsubtitles.net