We have a successful launch.
a general
in our central command--
General Mohmar Habib, who has
also been in contact with Fayed.
He's been helping orchestrate
the attacks on your country.
I really hope protecting this
man was worth pushing us
to the brink of World War III.
I've never found pharmaceutical
torture all that affective.
I have.
If this is supposed
to frighten me,
you're wasting your time.
I won't tell you a thing.
Watch out!
BUCHANAN:
We staged a fake rescue
of Fayed by CTU agents
posing as members
of a terrorist cell
with loyalties to Habib.
He wants us to help you
rendezvous with your men.
Where do you want us
to take you?
If you take your orders
from General Habib as I do,
how is it
I've never heard of you?
Fayed's gone!
Jamal's still alive.
Stay with him, call in a medic.
CTU, the bombs are secure.
Hello?
AUDREY:
Jack, are you there?
Can you hear me?
Audrey.
Help me, Jack.
Hello, Mr. Bauer.
Yes, Ms. Raines is alive.
If you wish her
to remain that way,
you will call me back
in ten minutes.
If you make any attempt
to find our location, she dies.
(dial tone)
Cheng.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and... FORD.
Every day, someone, somewhere
makes a bold move.
There's a car company
for people like that.
Agent Bauer, you really do
need to get to a hospital.
But I understand
the circumstances.
At least this will
help you with the pain.
Thank you.
Hey, Jack, so the
Marines, they're going
to secure the nukes
and prepare them
for transport.
They're calling
the shots now.
The military's taking over?
Yeah, according
to presidential order.
I guess DOD doesn't want
CTU in charge anymore.
So Buchanan, he wants you
to call him as soon as
the nukes are ready for
transport to a NEST facility.
Can you handle that for me?
Sure.
Jack?
What?
I just... I know you've
been through hell.
Not just today, but
the last couple of years, and...
I just wanted to thank you
for what you did today,
'cause it could have ended
a hell of a lot worse.
And it would have
if you weren't here.
I appreciate that.
Excuse me.
Agent Doyle, Highway
Patrol's finished locking
down all the roads,
and they're awaiting
your instructions.
(groans)
(phone rings)
Yes.
This is Bauer,
let me speak to Audrey.
You've already spoken to her.
I want to make sure
she's all right.
Her well-being is entirely
up to you, Mr. Bauer.
Everyone has given
up on you.
Everyone, except
for Ms. Raines.
Over the objections
of your government, her family,
her friends,
she came to Beijing,
just to find you.
Since you proved to be
a uncooperative prisoner,
we felt she would be an asset
we might be able
to exploit one day.
And that day is here.
I will hand myself over to you.
Tell me where.
A man who won't break
is of no use to us,
but the Russian suitcase
nukes you captured...
Why?
Your country has the technology
to build those weapons.
It's not the weapons themselves
we're interested in.
What we want is a component
from the triggering mechanism.
It contains a prototype
algorithm...
old enough to be free of any
modern decryption safeguards.
With it,
we'll have access to virtually
all Russian defense technology.
It's a simple exchange.
You give me the component,
I give you Audrey.
If you refuse, I kill her.
The Russians will know that we
supplied you with the algorithm.
You would be
starting World War III.
I suggest we leave that
to the diplomats to sort out.
Even if I wanted to, the bombs
are under military control.
I couldn't get
anywhere near them.
You'll find a way.
If I'm going to agree to this,
I want to speak to Audrey now.
Very well.
Speak to him.
Jack?
Audrey.
Are you all right?
Did they hurt you?
No.
Jack... I...
I'm sorry.
You have nothing
to be sorry for.
The only thing that's important
is that you're alive.
I know what
they're asking for.
I can handle it.
I promise you, I'm going
to get you out of there.
Just don't be frightened.
You have one hour
to call this number
when you're ready
to make the exchange.
An hour's not going
to give me enough time.
Cheng.
Cheng!
You know, you really should
work from Medical, sir.
Come on, at least they
can monitor you there.
I'm fine, Tom.
I... I don't think
that you are, sir.
And neither does Dr. Welton.
Putting myself under medical
supervision might give
the vice president
yet another pretext
to try and take a run at my job.
You don't need
to worry about that, sir.
What exactly do you have
on Vice President Daniels?
I have the truth, sir.
Now is the time that I need
to know what that is.
It is a tape recording
of Vice President Daniels
conspiring with Lisa Miller
to commit perjury
at your competency hearing.
I'd love to hear that
as soon as possible.
HAYES:
Mr. President, Tom.
I have good news.
CTU has recovered
the two remaining
suitcase nukes.
When?
Just a few minutes ago.
I just got off
the phone with Bill.
He's waiting to brief you
as soon as you're ready.
What about Fayed?
He and his men were killed
during the assault.
Then it's over.
Well, it certainly
seems so, sir.
Congratulations.
The American people should know.
And I want to tell them
that we're no longer at
risk of a nuclear attack.
I'll have the press corps
down here in 30 minutes.
No, no, Karen.
We're going to do this
from upstairs,
in the press room.
Should we wait for clearance
from Secret Service?
No, Tom, there's no need
for any of us
to be hiding underground
for a minute longer.
Inform Secret Service that
we'll be leaving the Bunker
and returning
to the Oval Office.
HAYES:
Yes, sir.
Morris is coordinating with the
Marines Technical Escort Unit
to transfer the bombs
to a NEST facility.
Now that they've taken custody,
I'd like you all
to submit your briefings
to the respective
department heads.
(phone ringing)
I'd like to share my pride in
the work that you've all done.
We were hit hard.
But not one of you gave up.
You've done excellent
work today.
O'Brian.
Hey, it's me.
Jack. You did it.
Chloe, listen to me.
I need your help.
Well, can't it wait?
We're just transferring the
bombs, and doing cleanup.
No, it can't.
What is it?
Chloe, Audrey's still alive.
No, she's not.
Yes, she is,
I just talked to her.
The Chinese faked
her car accident.
They've been holding
her a prisoner
since she was in Beijing
trying to find me.
Oh, my God.
We have to tell Mr. Buchanan.
He'll never go along with it.
Go along with what?
The Chinese want
to exchange Audrey
for an FB-sub-circuit board
from one of the nukes.
It'll give them
complete access to
Russian defense technology.
I want you to help me retrieve
one of those circuit boards.
Jack, we both know
that if we do this,
it will create an international
situation big time.
Chloe, I know.
I promise I will do
whatever I have to
to stop the Chinese from
getting that circuit board.
But right now I need you
to get me the schematics
for those bombs.
Those files aren't
on my system.
They were reclassified
when the DOD took possession
of the suitcase
nuke you disarmed.
Then you're going to have to
figure out a way to get them,
'cause without those schematics,
I won't know
what I'm looking for.
Yes, I understand, but I don't
know how I can do this.
Chloe, Audrey's life
is at stake. Think.
Wait.
Morris.
He had to file a report
with DOD
about the work he did
on the nukes.
It contained
a revised schematic.
It might still be
on his hard drive.
Can you access it?
Only directly
from his terminal.
Chloe, please, do it.
Where do you want me to send it?
To the cell phone that
I'm calling you from.
Use a secure line-- Alpha-539.
Hold on.
It's here.
The file's coming up.
I'm sending it
to your screen.
Stand by.
Copy that.
Come on.
Chloe, I don't
see anything.
It needs to load
before it sends.
There's still
30% to go.
Damn it.
What?
Morris is coming back
to his station.
Hurry.
There's nothing
I can do.
I need to log
out now. He's here.
No, Chloe, wait.
Jack...
I got it.
(phone beeps)
Yes?
OPERATOR (on phone):
Mr. President,
the vice president is here.
Send him in.
Noah...
Please sit.
Listen, I, uh...
I want to begin by expressing
my gratitude to you.
For a lesson well learned.
I'm not sure what
you mean by that,
Mr. President.
I still believe
attacking Abu Fayed's
country with a nuclear
weapon would have been
a serious mistake, Noah; I'm not
going lie to you about that.
But...
if you hadn't put that option
on the table in the first place,
I never would've gone
as far as I did.
And the bombs might
still be out there.
That being said...
I think we would both agree
that our relationship
has always been a marriage
of convenience.
A way to strengthen the ticket,
rather than a case
of us actually seeing eye to eye
on pretty much anything.
And now that
it's over, this crisis,
it's become clear to me,
Noah, that I just
don't think it's possible for us
to work together anymore.
Excuse me?
I'm asking for your resignation.
How dare you.
You don't have the right
to ask for my
resignation.
This isn't about
what the Constitution
says, Noah.
It's about what's best
for this country
in a time of crisis.
How in the world do
you figure that?
I can't lead effectively
with you undermining me
at every single opportunity
that you may get.
Now let's be honest
with each other.
That's exactly what you would
do if you stayed in place.
Mr. President...
I refuse.
Good night.
You don't want
to walk out that door.
Not like this.
Otherwise I may
have to make this
extremely unpleasant for you.
Now what are you talking about?
I'm talking about the
recording that Tom Lennox
has in his possession.
That's what I'm talking about.
Conspiracy to
commit perjury
is a serious offense.
Now I have to assume
you'd rather resign,
than spend the rest of
your life living with that
kind of humiliation.
So is resorting to blackmail
your idea
of effective leadership?
If there is anything I've
learned anything from you,
Noah, it would be
that sometimes it's
necessary to apply
a little brute force.
I don't need your
resignation immediately.
Let's give the country
a chance to take a breath
after what happened today.
Some time in
the next week
will be just fine,
Mr. Vice President.
NEST wants a flight path
cleared to Edwards
for 20 miles
in each direction.
Could you get back
to me with confirmation?
Thank you.
ETA on the helicopter
that will transport
the bombs is 15 minutes.
You should distribute protocols
to the NEST team.
I'm on that.
(keyboard clacking)
(computer beeps)
That's odd.
What?
I think someone's hacked
into my system.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Ever since
what happened to Nadia,
I installed a logging
program to track
any unauthorized access
to my hard drive.
You did?
It's telling me
that someone accessed
my files ten minutes ago...
and downloaded
the updated schematics
to those suitcase nukes.
I'm calling security.
Wait!
Don't call security.
(hangs up receiver)
I'm the one who hacked
into your system.
Why would you do that?
I'll explain it to you
in a little while.
Explain it to me now.
I did it for Jack.
Audrey Raines is still alive.
The Chinese are
holding her hostage.
What?
They're going to kill
her unless Jack delivers
an FB-sub-circuit board from
one of the bombs to them.
You've been to all
the same briefings.
The Russians have been
trying to keep that technology
out of Chinese hands for years.
I know.
Well, what are
the Russians going to say
when they find out we just
gave it to them?
It's not going to get that far.
How in the world
do you know
it's not going
to get that far?
Because Jack gave me his word.
I'm sorry, darling.
I can't leave it at that.
Yes, you can.
The bombs that
I reprogrammed for Fayed
could have killed tens
of thousands of people.
But that didn't happen.
I know what it felt like
to think that I could've
been responsible for each
and everyone of their deaths.
I can't be involved
with something
that could easily
end up starting a war.
It's not going to start a war
because it's not going
to get that far.
Besides, this has
nothing to do with you.
I did it.
Yes, it does.
Now that you've
told me, it does.
You have to tell Buchanan.
I can't.
Then you're forcing me to.
No.
I'm going to do it.
No! Morris!
I'm doing it.
I'll tell him.
Reinforcements aren't
necessary at this point.
The military
is guarding the bombs.
There's a CTU SWAT
team standing by.
They'll be en route soon.
All right, thank you.
What is it, Chloe?
Mr. Buchanan...
I'm sorry, there's something
that you need to know.
* *
You two, come with me.
Sir, this area's
off-limits.
I'm Agent Bauer.
I was the man that was
responsible for securing
these nukes. I'm under
a presidential order to
remove the FB-circuit board
from one of these bombs,
have it transferred back to
CTU for immediate analysis.
We don't have much time.
This building has been
compromised. Now open
the gate.
Sir, no one is allowed
in here.
Are you countermanding
a presidential order?
How dare you, Sergeant?!
Now you're wasting my time.
What's your name?
What's your name?!
I want your name, too.
Now!
That's not necessary.
Open the gate.
Open the gate!
I want both of you
to stand guard
while I remove
the circuit board. Come on!
One, two, three...
DOYLE:
Stand down, Jack!
I can't do that.
I won't say it again!
Drop it.
Agent Doyle, I am
following orders
that exceed your
security clearance!
He's a rogue agent.
Take him out!
I will shoot!
Put your weapon
down or I will
shoot you!
Take him!
Now!
(blow lands)
Secure him, he's under arrest.
Doyle, please.
Just listen to me.
DOYLE (over phone):
Bill, we've got Jack.
What did he say?
Not much. I had
to subdue him.
Let me talk to him.
Hold on.
Buchanan wants to talk to you.
Bill...
Jack, Chloe just told me
about Audrey and the Chinese.
I can't let you give
them the component.
I'm not going to.
I only need to have it long
enough for them to let her go.
I was never going to let
the Chinese keep it,
Bill, I swear to you.
Whatever you have planned,
Jack, I can't let you do it.
Bill, please...
Right now we're the only
chance she's got.
I understand what Audrey
means to you. I promise
I will do everything
in my power to get her back.
You didn't even
know she was alive.
Cheng is going to make it
impossible for us
to ever find her again.
We are her only hope
and you know it.
I don't know what
to tell you, Jack,
except let Doyle
bring you back here
and we'll work out a game plan.
Will you let me make
one more call?
I'm asking you
as a friend.
Who do you want
to talk to?
President Wayne Palmer.
I'll see if I can reach him.
Let me talk to Doyle.
Yeah.
He wants
to talk to you.
Doyle.
Keep Jack in custody while I
try to contact the president.
I'll route the call
through your cell.
Yes, sir. I understand.
Get him up.
(Bauer panting)
WOMAN (on TV):
White House sources
have confirmed
that terrorist leader
Abu Fayed is dead.
The president has reportedly
recovered from injuries
sustained from
the failed attempt on his life,
and he is expected
to make a statement shortly
regarding unconfirmed rumors...
(beeps)
Yes?
MAN:
Mr. President, Bill Buchanan
has Jack Bauer on the line.
Put him through, please.
(beeps)
Go ahead.
WOMAN:
Please hold for the President.
It's the president.
Excuse me.
Mr. President.
Yes, Jack.
Congratulations.
Is everything still all right?
Yes, sir. The bombs are secure.
But I'm calling
because I want you
to authorize a
field operation.
For what purpose?
To save
Audrey Raines.
What?
Mr. President,
she's still alive.
The Chinese have been holding
her for the past few months.
Now they're using her
as a bargaining chip.
In exchange for what?
For an FB-sub-circuit board
from one of the nukes.
They say they'll release Audrey
unharmed if I bring it to them.
It's my understanding, Jack,
that component holds the key
to Russian defense codes.
Yes, sir, I'm aware of that.
I'm sympathetic, I am,
and I promise you
that I will make available
to you the full resources
of this country
to get Audrey back,
but I hope you're not
expecting me to authorize
this exchange.
Not exactly.
Then what exactly?
Mr. President,
I need the Chinese to believe
that I am willing to go through
with this exchange.
I need to have
that component on me.
They're going
to need to see it.
As soon as I know
that Audrey is free,
I will destroy it.
And how can you
guarantee that?
I'm asking you to trust me,
Mr. President.
I give you my word that
that component will not end up
in Chinese hands.
But if it does, the Russians,
despite our peace accord,
may take action against us
for allowing it to happen.
Now, under most circumstances,
yes, your word would be
sufficient, but in this case,
Jack, I need to know details.
If I have to,
I will destroy
that circuit board
with a concealed
charge of C-4.
An explosion of C-4
would take out anything
within 30 feet of it.
You're going
to sacrifice yourself?
Yes, sir, if I have to.
Jack...
Mr. President, please.
Please, I am begging you.
Audrey Raines was willing
to give up her life
to save mine.
I cannot and will not do
anything less for her.
You're asking me to sign off
on a probable suicide mission.
With all due respect,
Mr. President, 16 hours ago,
your people were willing
to hand me over for dead,
and I did not hesitate.
Mr. President, you owe me.
And you're sure
this is the only way?
Yes.
All right, then.
I will not fail you,
Mr. President.
I'll tell Bill to give you
whatever you need.
Now I'm going
to need confirmation
that circuit board
has been destroyed
after Audrey has been released.
I'll have CTU embed
a tracking device in the board.
You'll have your confirmation.
Good luck, Jack.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Let me speak with Bill Buchanan.
Yes, sir. I understand.
Get over here.
What did he say?
Buchanan said the president
signed off on this,
and to give you
whatever help you need.
I'm going to need someone
to help me
with Audrey's extraction
during the exchange.
I want that to be you.
Fine.
Where are you going to be?
The name of the Chinese agent
that's holding Audrey
is Cheng Zhi.
He was responsible for
my interrogation and torture
for almost two years
in that Chinese prison.
As soon as I get
the signal from you
that Audrey is safe, two things
are going to happen.
I'm going to destroy
that circuit board,
and Cheng Zhi isn't going
to make it out of here alive.
So, in answer
to your question,
where am
I going to be?
Wherever I have to.
Let's go.
Are you going
to tell me what happened?
The president agreed
to Jack's plan.
The president's going
to allow Jack to hand over
a defense algorithm
to the Chinese?
No. Of course not.
Jack will destroy the component
as soon as he knows
Audrey's safe.
The Chinese will
never get it.
And how is he going
to manage that?
I don't know.
I guess President Palmer
trusts him.
Telling Buchanan
was the right thing to do.
You know it was.
It doesn't matter.
You should have trusted me.
Trusted you?
You're the one
that broke into my system.
That's because
I didn't think you'd back me up.
Obviously, I was right.
So you're going to hold this
over my head now, are you?
Yeah. For a long time.
For how long?
Could you give me an estimate?
I'll get back to you.
Nadia, Doyle's on line three.
They're going to lock you
on the tracker frequency.
This is Nadia.
It's me.
The tracker's on line.
The frequency marker
is Alpha-1793.
Signal's good.
You're on the grid.
Copy. Jack and I are
getting ready to move out.
(phone rings)
Yes?
I have the circuit board.
Where am I going?
Get on the 180 and head north.
Get off the first exit
after mile marker 49.
I will give you
further instructions
when you've exited.
I got it.
You have
a half an hour.
I don't think I
need to remind you
what would happen
if you are late.
I understand.
CTU has the signal.
They're monitoring
the device.
I'm set. Let's go.
Jack, you're taking
a hell of a risk.
If this goes sour,
it could stir a firestorm.
And for what?
If you were in my shoes,
you wouldn't do the same thing?
I don't mix relationships
with my job.
Whatever you had with this
woman, I hope it's worth it.
This isn't about what
I had with a woman.
Her name is
Audrey Raines.
She served this country
with honor. We owe her.
So get in the truck.
(knocking on door)
Come in.
You wanted to see me?
Close the door.
The president has just
asked me to resign.
What?
And I'm going to comply
with his request.
I wanted to
tell you personally before you
found out from someone else.
I don't understand.
Why are you going along
with this?
Why don't you just tell him
that you refuse?
He has a tape
of our conversation.
The one where we
conspire to commit perjury,
and he's threatening to use it
against me unless
I step down.
Oh, my God.
Tom Lennox
recorded it.
Bottom line is, I'm not
being given a choice here.
This is all my fault.
If I hadn't asked
you to lie about
Karen Hayes,
none of this
would be happening.
You were just trying
to protect me.
I could have turned you down,
but I didn't.
Don't blame yourself.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Aw, hell,
at least we'll have a lot more
time to
spend together.
The president said
to take a week,
but I want this letter
of resignation in his hands
by the time he finishes
his press conference.
I am through being
the loyal opposition.
Please, sit.
First, I want to say
that I'm grateful to report
that Abu Fayed, the man
responsible for these attacks,
has been killed,
and that all nuclear devices
have been recovered.
I want to take the time
to acknowledge the brave men
and women in our various
law enforcement agencies,
and let us not forget
our armed services.
All these people
have worked so hard
to bring this crisis to an end.
Their dedication, their
perseverance is without equal.
Despite the brutality
of these attacks,
we did not allow the violence
born of extremism
to push us to extremes.
And, as Americans, we can
and should take pride
and comfort in that fact.
Let me conclude
by asking for your prayers
tonight for all those
who grieve this day.
For all those whose lives
have been shattered.
Let us reach out and begin
the process of rebuilding.
Let us reach out
and begin the process
of national healing.
Thank you.
I'll take some
of your questions now.
Yes. Ian.
Mr. President, how certain
are you that the crisis
is, in fact, over, and that
there are no more of these
weapons on American soil?
Well, based on the intelligence
that I've seen,
I can say with full confidence,
Ian, that the worst has passed,
and that the individuals
responsible
for these attacks
have been apprehended,
or else killed.
Yes, Andrea.
Robin, sir.
Robin, yes. Robin.
I'm sorry, it's been a,
it's been a very long
day. Please, go ahead.
Mr. President,
there are several thousand
Muslim Americans
still being held
in detention facilities
across the country.
What's going to happen
to these people?
I've already directed
Homeland Security
to begin dismantling
these detention facilities.
Uh... all detainees
are to be released
once the immediate crisis
is passed.
Excuse me. Um, now
that the crisis
has passed, we will be, um...
we will be reviewing
the situation
regarding individuals
that we have in custody.
I'm sorry.
I'm, not, uh, I'm
not being very clear.
Uh, let me say again
regarding your question,
Andrea, that... Robin.
I'm sorry. Robin.
Let me say again regarding...
regarding your question
that the, uh...
the detention facilities
that, that, that we will, uh...
uh... that, uh...
We, we're going t... Ugh!
Oh, my God.
Get Medical right away!
LOWRY:
Code 4. Repeat, Code 4.
We need an emergency medical
team to the press room.
Get these people out of here.
HOLLISTER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
we need to clear this room.
All signs indicate the president
has suffered
a cerebral hemorrhage
brought on by injuries he
sustained earlier in the day.
Meaning he never should have
been brought out of the coma.
However detrimental
that decision was
to his health,
I'm confident
that in light of
his actions today,
he would continue
to support it.
I'm glad you're so confident,
Karen, since it was
your reckless action
that resulted in his stroke.
DR. WELTON:
Sir, it's unclear
if the stroke
was inevitable,
but in any event,
I'll take full
responsibility.
Excuse me.
Now is not the time
for recriminations,
self-imposed or otherwise.
Doctor, when will we know
the extent of the damage
and the prospects
for recovery?
After the MRI.
The president is being
prepped for transport
to Bethesda
as we speak.
Based on my
impressions,
the damage was severe.
I don't think we can
expect the president to regain
consciousness anytime soon.
So it is incontestable
Wayne Palmer won't
be able to continue his
duties as commander-in-chief.
There's no denying that this is
a great tragedy for the nation
and... for those of us who
know the president personally.
Just... take care of him,
Doctor.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Notify the Senate and the House
of the transfer of power
and have the sec def and the
chairman of the Joint Chiefs
authorize me under
the 25th Amendment.
Yes, sir.
Tom...
have the press secretary
issue a statement.
President Palmer's been...
incapacitated.
No need for alarm.
Executive authority's
been transferred to me.
Our...
hopes and prayers are with him.
All right, sir.
And I'll also need you
available to review everything
on the president's agenda.
All right, sir.
Actually, there's something
on the agenda
I think you'll want
immediate clarification on.
What's that?
Wayne Palmer just
issued a finding
allowing Jack Bauer to hand
classified Russian technology
over to the Chinese
in exchange
for the return of a
covertly held hostage.
Can you explain this?
Yes. That was
a personal request from Jack
Bauer to the president.
They have a
longstanding
relationship
and as Jack Bauer was
largely responsible
for recovering
the suitcase nukes today,
the president wanted to honor
his service to this country.
Karen, I asked you
to explain it, not excuse it.
Understood.
Bauer has guaranteed
that the technology
will not fall into the hands
of the Chinese.
It will only be used
to secure the hostage.
Incidentally, sir,
the hostage in question
is Audrey Raines,
daughter of James Heller.
Even Jack Bauer can't
guarantee that outcome.
Now, I am
happy to honor Agent Bauer's
service to this country,
but not at the risk of giving
classified technology
to the Chinese and...
potentially
damaging our
relationship
with Russia in the process.
You tell CTU
to stop Bauer-- immediately.
Sir.
The president expressly...
That's all for
now, Karen.
You, too, Tom.
Unbelievable.
Less than a minute
behind his desk
and he's already disregarding
the president's wishes.
Nevertheless, we both
share Daniel's unease
in handing
military secrets
over to the Chinese.
I know, Tom, but that
is not the point.
No, here's the point.
Daniels is now
the acting president,
whether we like it or not.
I'm off to the hospital.
I'll see you there.
(phone ringing)
Buchanan.
Hi, it's me.
How's president Palmer?
Not good.
The doctor says that he
has a cerebral hemorrhage
They don't know the
extent of the damage,
but obviously he's
not able to serve.
Daniels is going
to assume the office,
and the first wave of his hand,
he wants to stop
Jack's operation.
Jack has to return to CTU
as soon as possible
with the component.
Does the vice president
understand the circumstances
under which Wayne Palmer
agreed to this?
No. He's not that
kind of a man.
He doesn't operate
in shades of gray.
Does he understand Jack's not
gonna give up without a fight?
You just have to get
Jack back to CTU
as soon as
possible, okay?
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Listen up.
The White House has
ordered us to shut down
Jack's operation. How far away
are support teams?
Six miles.
Have them standing by,
ready to move in,
Contact CHP. Have them
set up roadblocks.
Chloe, I want you
to stand down
on this operation.
Why?
You've shown me
I can't trust you.
Morris, you cover comm.
Jack's not gonna
go along with this.
I know.
(phone rings)
Doyle.
Mike, it's Bill.
Can Jack hear you?
Say yes or no.
Yes.
There's been
a change in profile.
Noah Daniels is
acting President.
He wants the operation shut
down and Jack brought back
to CTU immediately.
Understood.
What's your
current location?
We're about two miles east
of the 180 interchange.
Okay, I need you to exit
at the 70, make
the first left.
We'll have roadblocks set up
with a backup team ready
to take Jack into custody
and recover the component.
All right, we'll do that.
You need to disarm Jack
as soon as quickly
and quietly as possible
before he finds out.
No problem.
(sighs)
CTU's got a report
from Cal Trans.
The 180's closed
due to high winds.
They're concerned about
possible fallout.
They want us to
take 70 instead.
Fine.
Don't you move.
Jack, what's the problem?
Earlier today,
I shot my old partner,
a friend of mine,
because he tried to stop me
from doing what I have to do.
Don't think for a second
I won't do that to you.
Slowly I want you
to pull over.
Now.
Take the keys
out of the ignition.
Put them on the center
console. And your phone.
Jack, you don't want
to do this.
Slowly get out
of the truck.
Back up towards
the fence.
Jack, listen to me.
Daniels is the acting president.
He's the one who
called this off.
Shut up and grab the fence!
This is gonna end badly, Jack.
You can't go against
the White House!
Jack!
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and... FORD.
Every day, someone, somewhere
makes a bold move.
www.tvsubtitles.net