This is Bauer.
Let me speak to Audrey.
Her well-being's entirely
up yo you, Mr. Bauer
What we want is a component
from the triggering mechanism
the FB sub circuit board
You give me the component
I give you Audrey
DOYLE:
Stand down, Jack!
I can't do that.
I won't say it again. Drop it!
Agent Doyle, I am following
orders that exceed
you're security clearance...
He's a rogue agent.
Take him out.
It's my understanding, Jack,
that component
holds the key to Russian
defense codes.
JACK:
I need the Chinese to believe
that I'm willing to go through
with this exchange.
I will destroy the circuit board
with a concealed charge of C-4.
You're going to sacrifice
yourself?
Yes, sir, if I have to.
You're asking me to sign off
on a probable suicide mission.
Mr. President...
you owe me.
JACK:
I want you to help me retrieve
one of those circuit boards.
CHLOE:
I'm sending it to your system.
The Russians have been trying
to keep that technology
out of Chinese hands for years.
I did it for Jack.
Well, what are the Russians
going to say
when they find out
we just gave it to them?
Well, it's not going
to get that far.
You have to tell Buchanan.
Chloe, I want you to stand down
on this operation.
You've shown me
I can't trust you.
First I want to say that
I'm grateful to report
that all nuclear devices
have been recovered.
Based on the intelligence
that I've seen,
I can say with full confidence
that-that-that
that we will, uh...
(groans)
Get medical right away!
Notify the Senate and the House
of the transfer of power
and the Sec Def and the Chairman
of the Joint Chiefs
authorize me under
the 25th Amendment.
Wayne Palmer just issued
a finding allowing Jack Bauer
to hand classified Russian
technology over to the Chinese
in exchange for the return
of a covertly held hostage.
Bauer has guaranteed
that the technology
will not fall into the hands
of the Chinese.
Even Jack Bauer can't
guarantee that outcome.
Tell CTU to stop Bauer.
CTU has the signal.
They're monitoring the device.
We're set. Let's go.
(phone ringing)
Doyle.
BUCHANAN:
Noah Daniels
is acting president.
He wants the operation shut down
and Jack brought back
to CTU immediately.
Understood.
Don't you move.
Jack...
Slowly I want you to pull over.
Now.
This is going
to end badly, Jack.
You can't go against
the White House.
Wait! Wait!
Stop! Stop!
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
Wait! Wait! Stop your car! Stop!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
What the hell?!
Are you crazy?!
I'm a federal agent in pursuit.
I need the vehicle.
Where's your badge?
(horns honking)
(tires screeching)
(phone ringing)
Pressman.
Milo, it's Doyle.
I need to speak with Buchanan.
Hold on.
Sir, Doyle's on line one.
Mike, it's Bill.
Do you have Jack in custody?
No, he got the drop on me
before I could get the
component-- I screwed up.
Where are you?
I acquired another
vehicle and I'm in pursuit.
Morris, do you have
Jack's position?
Yeah.
The tracker's still embedded
in the sub-board.
He's heading north on the 118.
Copy that.
Mike, Jack's going
to disengage that tracker
the first
chance he gets.
I'll get him
before he does.
All right, listen up.
Jack Bauer has gone rogue.
He has in possession
the FB sub-circuit board.
Mike Doyle is in pursuit.
He needs all
available resources
to stop Jack and
recover the component
before he gives it
to the Chinese.
Chloe.
I need you on task.
You said that...
I know what I said.
I need my best people
looking for Jack.
Can I trust you
to help me do that?
Yes, sir.
Good. Thank you.
MORRIS:
Oh, that's bloody marvelous.
What?
I just lost
Jack's signal.
How'd you do that?
I didn't do anything.
It just disappeared.
(electrical wires crackling)
CHLOE:
There must be something
in the transit ph.
You don't have to state
the obvious, Chloe.
I know there's something
interfering, I'm  trying
to figure out what it is.
CHLOE:
This doesn't have
to be personal.
Can we just figure it out?
It's not personal,
and I've figured it out.
This stretch of road
runs right along
the main voltage feed
for the Valley,
and Jack is using
the power lines as a shield
while he separates
the tracker from
the sub-board.
Can you keep an eye
on things? Can you?
I have to explain this
to Buchanan.
Hey, I thought
you got sidelined.
Buchanan wants me to help
find Jack.
Which is going to be harder now
that he's dumped the tracker.
Did you pull up Caltrans?
Yeah.
I just can't believe that Jack
would give up the circuit board
to the Chinese.
Jack would die
before he gives up that
component to the Chinese.
I agree with you.
The question is... would Jack
give up Audrey's life?
Exactly.
Look, I'll...
I'll check the satellites.
See if they've restored any
coverage in that area.
If you find anything,
send it to me, Doyle and LAPD.
How much farther?
We lost Jack
eight miles north
of your current location.
We think he used the power
lines as a shield
while he removed
the tracker.
You're headed in
the right direction.
See you if you can
pick up a trail.
I'll call you back
when I get closer.
Thank you, Morris.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a brief statement
and I will not be taking any
questions at this time.
The President is en route
to Bethesda Naval Hospital
and will arrive shortly.
The doctors have no idea
whether or not
President Palmer
will come out of his coma
in hours, days or weeks.
Vice President Daniels will be
addressing the country
at 9:00 a.m. Eastern time.
Thank you.
That's all, everyone.
Yes, sir.
Tom...
Stick around.
I want to talk to you.
All right, sir.
We need to clear the air,
you and I.
You still have
evidence
that could hurt me,
and I'd like to know what
your intentions are.
Truthfully, sir, I haven't
given it much thought.
Why don't you think
about it now.
All right, sir.
It concerns me that you engaged
in conspiracy and perjury
to achieve
political ends.
I don't think
that's behavior befitting
the acting president
of the United States.
Tom, the world has changed
in the last half hour.
Right now, this country,
above all, needs stability.
If I'm brought up on charges
in the first hours
of this presidency,
then America's left without
elected leadership.
If I might just complete
my thought, sir--
I made that tape both to back
you off your challenge
to President Palmer,
but also to protect me.
Now that was,
and remains,
my only reason.
What about forcing
my resignation?
That was Wayne Palmer's idea,
not mine.
So...
you're okay then
with me in this chair?
Sir, it's no secret
that policy-wise
you and I are in alignment.
I just simply hate
how we got here.
Now that we are here?
Yes, sir, you have my support.
(sighs)
In the event that we ever get
out of alignment...
I can't have you holding
this evidence
over my head.
It's understood, sir.
You have my word.
All right, Tom.
Glad to have you with me.
Now what do you suggest
we do with Karen Hayes?
Will she slow us down?
Of course she might,
but she is smart,
she brings balance.
Fine, then she stays.
Right. May I let her know, sir?
Sure.
Tom.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
(phone ringing)
Yes.
This is Bauer. I just passed
mile marker 49.
I have the sub-circuit
board with me.
Good. Go east on
the 118...
No, from this point forward
we do this my way.
Don't test me, Mr. Bauer.
Yes, I want
the component,
but Audrey Raines' life
means nothing to me.
Listen to me.
CTU is looking for me.
They want to stop
the exchange from happening.
I know their satellite coverage.
I need to pick the location.
All right.
Where?
There's an abandoned motel
called the Calderone
off of Highway 305.
Come through the
front door alone.
We'll make
the exchange there.
We both have a chance to get
what we want here, Mr. Bauer.
Don't attempt anything foolish.
We're leaving now,
Ms. Raines.
(speaking Chinese)
I spoke with Bill,
and he assures me
that CTU has deployed all its
resources to find Bauer.
I don't want to hear about
their assurances, Karen.
They let Bauer steal
the component,
so their assurances
mean nothing.
Well, if I may, sir.
I could authorize
ancillary agencies
to join the search.
That would increase
our chances
of finding Bauer.
Do it.
Is there anything else
you need from me?
I need from you?
Let me think.
(sighs)
I have the fate
of the Western world
and the lives of millions of
Americans hanging in the balance
and I can't...
stop thinking about you.
I'm not sure this is
appropriate behavior,
Mr. Acting President.
Well, there's the phone,
call to the media.
Tell them the acting
president's a dirty old man.
They already know.
I would like for you...
to spend what's left
of the night.
I'll go home and pick up
a change of clothes.
Good.
I'm at the Tampa exit
by the power lines.
It matches the last
coordinates Morris had
before the tracker
stopped working.
Mike, it's Bill.
The White House is telling me
if the Chinese get ahold
of this sub-circuit
board, we'll have
an international
incident on our hands.
I know the stakes, Bill.
Have you been able to figure
out where Jack's headed?
I'm working on it now.
It looks like he headed east.
What's up ahead?
Two state routes,
the 305 and the 98.
Do you have
satellite on both?
No. The radiation
from the fallout
made that area
hard to cover.
But the 98 has
Caltrans cameras--
I can check them.
No, don't bother.
Jack would know about
those-- he's on the 305.
And check the cell
towers in the area.
See if you can pick up a phone
call between Jack and Cheng.
And I think I saw Jack pick up
one of the terrorist's phones
at the warehouse-- that
might help narrow things down.
Chloe's got that grid
on her system-- get it from her.
Who's that?
Doyle. He thinks
Jack's on the 305.
How would he know that?
He figured it out.
Chloe, I need you to pull
the logs on grid 19-dash-12.
Get everything off that cell
tower for the last 15 minutes.
What am I looking for?
I think Jack's using
one of the terrorist's
phones that were tagged
at the warehouse.
Check all outgoing calls.
We'll get it.
Oh, um...
what is this?
Those are today's
decryption schemes
from the cell towers.
I'm sending you
some scrambled calls.
We're looking for a conversation
between Jack and Cheng.
Why didn't you speak to me first
before over-writing my screen?
I don't know,
that's just the way I did it.
Okay, okay. We're being
a little hostile, aren't we?
Fine.
I'm hostile,
but I just didn't get there--
you pushed me halfway.
Actually, you're right--
it's my fault, all my fault.
I didn't say
it's all your fault.
I said halfway, 50%,
point-five-- see,
you don't listen to me.
That's why I just sent it
to your screen.
Hey, guys.
What's going on?
My ex-wife
is suddenly showing signs
of irrational behavior.
Okay.
Do you know how
to defrag Huffman keys?
Yeah. Why?
Can you help me out with this?
Yeah.
Great. I'll just send
the files to your system.
That's a really good idea.
You should work with Milo--
you know, get cozy.
Would you please
stop acting like this?
I really hate it.
Why don't you
write down the way
you want me to act,
put it in a file, tab delimited,
the Milo loves it, and...
shove it.
Okay. I'll write it down--
the first item on the list
would be:
"Don't be such a jealous jerk."
Okay. Um, the day I'm jealous
is the day I kill myself.
Is there anything else?
How about: "Don't arm nuclear
bombs for terrorists"?
(exhales)
Sorry. I didn't mean that.
That's not how I feel.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not.
It just slipped out of my mouth.
Morris...
I'll call Mel
over at the FBI,
get them to share
resources with Bill.
(phone rings)
Good, and I'll... Oh.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Okay.
Well, tell him
I'll be right there.
That's strange.
Peter Hock
is in my office,
and he wants to talk to me.
Department of Justice?
What is that about?
I have no idea.
Be careful, Karen.
He's got a lot of
clout on the Hill.
I know. I'll call you.
Peter.
Early enough for you?
(laughs)
So, what's going on?
It sounded urgent.
You know that
I've been interrogating
Tom's chief of staff,
Reed Pollock, after his arrest.
That must be pleasant.
(chuckles)
Pollock's looking at a
probable death sentence
for his part in the
assassination attempt
on Wayne Palmer.
Mm-hmm.
Out of desperation, he's
offering up everything he knows,
hoping we'll show
some leniency.
And what does that
have to do with me?
Not just you, this involves
your husband as well.
Take a look.
Listen to me, Peter.
You and I both know
that there are
going to be endless hearings
looking into how Fayedmanaged
to acquire the nukes.
PETER:
And you know something
about that?
I can give you key information
that will help keep blame
away from this administration.
PETER:
I'm listening.
POLLOCK:
Well, I'm not saying anything
until I have some sort
of deal, in writing.
He's such a weasel.
We, uh, danced around
for 20 minutes, then he...
said this.
I'm telling you...
exactly what happened.
Bill Buchanan
had Fayed in custody,
and he let him go.
PETER:
And where's the proof?
POLLOCK:
Karen Hayes put it
in a blue file over at Homeland.
That's a cover-up.
And if you don't believe me,
I have recorded conversations
with Peter Iannone,
Kurt Hueig and Myra Mawk,
and they will all testify
that she sequestered the file
to protect her husband.
Do me a favor, Karen.
Save me some time.
Is it true or not?
The facts are true.
But there's no
cover-up here, Peter.
About two years ago,
we apprehended Fayed as part
of an FBI-CTU border sweep.
There wasn't enough
to hold him,
he was one of many,
and he was maybe
a mid-level player.
And that turned out
to be wrong.
Fayed wasn't part of a cell;
he wasn't funded.
This all happened
after he was released.
So why was it blue-coded?
Every year,
thousands of suspects
are arrested.
If there isn't enough evidence
to hold them, they're released
and blue-coded-- that's
just standard procedure.
The only way to guarantee
that no one becomes
a threat is to hold everyone
and deprive them
of their rights and freedom.
All right, Karen,
then if this was a no-fault,
why did this carry so much
weight with you 12 hours ago.
Why did you resign
rather than have this come out?
Come on, Peter,
we were under attack.
There was no way I was gonna
let this information touch
the president or my husband.
They needed to lead us
through this crisis unimpeded.
Well, here we are,
12 hours later,
Palmer's in a coma,
the country's in shock
after losing over 13,000
innocent lives, and all people
are going to be asking
is who let this happen?
Well, certainly not my husband.
He has devoted his life
to this country.
This isn't my call, Karen, but
I think you know how this works.
Someone's going to have
to go down.
And the farther
from the president
the better.
So what exactly are you saying?
It's going to be
either you or Bill.
Bill would be
my preference--
he's lower on the food chain.
But you'll do.
(phone rings)
Doyle.
NADIA:
We found Jack's call to Cheng.
What'd he say?
We haven't decrypted it yet,
but the triangulation
shows he's traveling north on
the 305 just like you thought.
Anything between me
and Santa Maria?
Uh, some small populated areas
in the county, unincorporated.
When does
the next one come up?
About nine miles
from where you are now.
All right, check it out,
and keep working
on that decryption.
I want to know what Cheng
and Jack said to each other.
Okay.
Are we converging
on Jack?
(phone rings)
Yeah. Doyle's...
Excuse me. Hi.
KAREN:
Hi. It's me.
Do you have a minute?
No. We're closing in on Jack.
What is it?
We have to talk about something.
Why don't you call me
when you have a few minutes.
Okay. Everything all right?
Just... do what you have to do
and call me when you can, okay?
All right.
Bye.
Yes?
Well, Doyle's headed
in the right direction.
He can't be that
far behind.
We may have a chance to stop
Jack before he reaches Cheng.
He's traveling north on the 305.
About there.
Hey, let me call you back.
Has CTU made any progress
in locating Bauer?
They're closing in, but they
don't have him in custody yet.
You were right about Hock, Tom.
I need to talk to you.
All right, shoot.
Remember earlier when
you threatened to use
that information about Fayed
to damage Bill and me?
Karen, yeah, mea culpa.
Wh-Why are we dredging
this up now?
No, no.
Tom, it's not me.
It's Reed Pollock.
He's looking for anything
to bargain his way out
of the death penalty.
Well, he can't.
Well, whether he can or he
can't, that ship has sailed.
Hock knows now that we released
Fayed from our custody
two years ago
in Seattle.
Okay, okay.
What does Hock want?
Distance from the presidency.
Ah, so in other words,
either you or Bill
has to take the blame.
Yeah. But it's more
than blame, Tom.
There's gonna be inquiries,
indictments, investigations--
lives will be ruined.
Not lives, careers.
Or rather, one career.
And it can't be yours.
Well, I can't do
that to Bill, Tom.
He's my husband.
Well, he can go on
being your husband,
but he sure can't
keep running CTU.
(sighs)
Well, if he goes,
then I'm gonna resign.
Haven't you already
resigned once today?
Karen, that's Bill's signature
on Fayed's release document.
Now, it's over for Bill.
It's not for you-- I mean,
you've got a job here.
Just do it.
(sighs)
Tom, how can I ask him
to step down?
You don't ask--
you simply remind him
that the man he personally
let out of jail
killed over 13,000 people
this morning.
Tom, he is not
responsible for that.
Karen, it doesn't matter.
He has been amazing today!
Look, look, look, the only way
for you to protect yourself
is to leave no doubt
in anybody's mind
where your true loyalty lies.
Now, they got Bill in
the crosshairs, okay?
You want to stand shoulder
to should with your husband,
that's your call.
(sighs)
(ringing)
This is Bill Buchanan.
If your matter is urgent,
please dial zero.
If this is not an urgent call,
please leave a message
at the beep.
(beep)
Bill, it's Jack.
I'm about to meet with Cheng
and exchange the FB
sub-circuit board for Audrey.
Hopefully,
by the time you hear this,
she'll be safe
and in your custody.
Bill, I know
I promised the president
that I would give him
confirmation
that the circuit board did
not fall into the wrong hands.
This message
is your confirmation.
The circuit board will be
incinerated in the explosion.
The meeting will take place
at the Calderone Motel
off of Highway 305.
Bill...
Please take care of Audrey.
And thank you.
You've been a good friend
All right, Marcy. I'll talk
to you in the morning.
Yeah.
You have a second?
What is it, Morris?
I'd like to request a transfer.
Why?
I need to get out of Comm.
You want to
elaborate on that?
Not really, no.
You and Chloe having problems?
You could say that, yes.
I really hate
to lose you in Comm.
Can we talk about
this in the morning?
Nothing's gonna change.
You don't
know that, Miles.
I do.
Look. Please.
Figure out where
you want to put me.
Anywhere is fine.
Just get me
out of Comm.
All right.
We'll work
something out
that, uh, that's good
for everyone involved.
Thank you.
(phone ringing)
Hi, honey.
Hey.
I have a minute.
Did you want
to talk about something?
Bill,
the DOJ investigator
found out about Seattle,
when you and Homeland
had Fayed in custody.
"Found out"?
It wasn't a secret.
We did everything by the book.
I can deal with DOJ.
Yeah, I know, but...
The problem is, they're
out for blood, Bill.
I can't let
this touch me.
Touch you? What are
you talking about?
Bill, I...
Why is this
suddenly an issue?
Are you concerned
I might implicate you?
No. No, but obviously there's
guilt by association here.
They're looking
for a scapegoat.
Yes. The pundits and
the press are looking
for anything to attack
the administration.
What are you saying?
I have to protect
the White House, Bill.
and in order to do that, I have
to distance myself from you.
How are you going to do that?
I'm your husband.
You asking me to resign?
No, Bill.
I have to fire you.
There's pressure on you, Karen.
Look, this is the only way
this can work.
And it has
to happen immediately.
or I'll be viewed as complicit
and my ability to stay on
as national security advisor
will be undermined.
Undermined?
We're talking about
the end of my career.
You don't think that
I've thought this through?
No, I don't.
You don't think
that I don't know
what this means to you?
No, I don't.
Bill...
Because the public
will make assumptions
that don't exist.
13,000 American lives lost.
I had the man in custody who was
responsible, and I released him.
It won't matter that I had
no evidence to hold him.
Look, you know how this works.
One of us has to take the fall,
and it can't be me.
I'm too close to the president.
I can't believe
I'm hearing this.
Who is pressuring you, Karen?
What are you not saying?
You have to trust me
on this, honey.
We will get through
this, I promise.
And... I love you, and that's
all that should matter here.
Is it?
Yes.
(phone ringing)
(hangs up)
Why is it taking so long
with Jack's phone call to Cheng?
It just is, Mike.
He used a double-length
key to slow us down.
We're going as fast as we can.
All right, I'm off the highway.
Mile Marker 19.
Checking surface streets.
(ringing)
Hello, Valley Cab Company.
May I help you?
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm a counter-terrorist agent.
This is an emergency.
I don't see any sign of Jack.
What's further north of here?
Nothing but national forest
for 32 miles.
He could be in
the Central Valley by now.
Wait. I might
have found something.
I'll get back to you.
Okay.
Nadia.
Has Doyle
found Jack yet?
Well, he might have a lead.
He's checking
it out now.
All right.
Come with me.
I'm stepping down
as director of CTU.
What?
What happened?
All I can say is
I have to step down.
No. Sir, that
doesn't make any sense.
Why would you quit--
now of all days?
I'm not quitting.
I was fired.
By who?
It doesn't matter.
I've contacted Division.
For now, you're acting director.
Mr. Buchanan.
We've been ordered
to escort you off the premises.
I know.
I'm briefing Ms. Yassir.
She's taking over
as head of CTU. We'll need
one more minute, please.
One minute.
Sir, we're in the middle
of 50 different things here.
Why would they do
this to you now?
I can't talk about it.
You need to accept it
and do the best you can.
No. I don't understand
why they would fire you.
You're the most ethical,
dedicated person
I've ever known.
There's no way you did
anything to justify this,
Damn it, Bill, what is going on?
It's just politics.
Division will be sending
over an interim director
in the next few hours.
In the meantime,
you can handle
anything that comes up.
What about the
extra redundancies
and everything else I've
had to go through today?
I'm not the right
choice to take over.
I've lifted all the restrictions
on your security clearance.
You shouldn't have any
trouble running CTU.
You are the right choice.
I don't know what to say.
Just stay on top
of the situation with Jack.
I will.
No one else
knows I'm leaving
You have to inform them
before it's posted
on the internal forums
I'll tell them.
What you said means a lot.
(phone ringing)
O'Brian.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah, got it.
Doyle just called in.
He's found Jack's truck.
Good, Morris.
What's happening
to Buchanan?
He's gone.
What do you
mean, he's gone?
I'm in charge.
Can I have everyone's
attention, please?
In a few minutes you're gonna be
getting a bulletin
on your systems.
Bill Buchanan has stepped down,
which means that
until Division
can send over a replacement,
he's named me acting director.
Nothing will change
operationally.
Your objective
remains the same--
Bring in Jack Bauer before
he can hand over the component
to the Chinese.
Thank you.
CTU, this is Doyle.
Do you copy?
Doyle, you're on com.
Go ahead.
Do you have anything
on satellite yet?
MILO:
Spotty.
Well, I found our truck.
Either Jack switched vehicles
or he parked it and he's nearby.
I'm gonna go look
at the buildings.
All right, there's some
infrastructure around
we can check
using thermal. Chloe?
I'm on it.
Hang on. We might
not need it.
What do you mean?
A limo just pulled off
the highway.
Redirect all nearby units
to my current location.
Okay.
Send Alpha and Delta teams
to that location.
Also send Air One, Two
and Three for air support.
All right.
Cheng just left the car.
Far enough.
Mr. Bauer.
Where's Audrey?
She's in the car.
Until I get the component...
Nothing's going
to happen
until I see Audrey.
I want to make sure
she's all right.
(speaks Chinese)
She's coming in now.
Audrey Raines is entering
the premises.
I think I'm gonna need
that backup.
You have the sub circuit board?
You'll get it as soon
as I know she's safe.
(speaks Chinese)
Take the gag
out of her mouth.
Wait!
I'll do it.
(speaks Chinese)
(whispering):
I'm so sorry.
CHENG:
You can continue
this reunion later.
How is this gonna work,
Mr. Bauer?
Audrey walks out
of her alone.
As soon as I see that she gets
down near the bridge
I'll know she's out of
the range of your sniper.
Then I'll give you
the component.
There's at least ten guns.
I need the field teams.
Let's do this.
I want you to walk
past the bridge a hundred yards,
on the right side of the road,
do you understand?
There's a gas station, and
a cab will be waiting for you.
He has instructions
to take you back to CTU.
You need to go.
Go.
All right, this is
going down now, Nadia.
Where are
the field teams?!
They should be there
any minute.
I need to do
something now.
They're releasing Audrey
which means Jack
is about to hand
over the component.
Mike, don't let that happen.
Give me the circuit board
or I'll kill her.
Oh, damn it!
(tires squealing)
Miss Raines,
stay where you are.
Stay down!
(men shouting,
gunfire continues)
(speaks Chinese)
CTU, this is Air One.
Do you copy?
Go ahead.
Cheng and his men have escaped.
They're in three black Hummers
heading north
towards the mountains.
Traveling off road.
Pursue and engage.
We've been hit!
We're going down!
I repeat, we're going down!
(engine sputtering)
* *
Agent Bauer, get down!
My weapon is down!
Get on the ground!
Who is your commanding officer?!
I am, Jack.
Stand him up.
Where's the sub-circuit board?
Cheng's got it.
I was set to blow the building
and destroy the component
until you engaged us
in a firefight.
Here's the detonator.
What's the problem?
We don't have Cheng, Jack.
What do you mean,
you don't have him?
The assault teams didn't have
time to get into place.
We had to make
a frontal assault.
He must have escaped
out the rear.
Nadia, did you get that?
Cheng escaped with
the sub-circuit board.
We got a chopper down.
We need those
other choppers ASAP.
I know. The chopper should be
there in five minutes.
Listen, before they went down,
they reported seeing Cheng
and his men
traveling in three
black Hummers
in the mountains
off road traveling north.
Copy that.
Now place Jack under arrest.
Understood.
Is he gone?
Yeah.
I gotta take you
into custody, Jack.
I had this handled.
Why the hell didn't you
listen to me?
Audrey, it's over.
It's all right.
You're safe.
Help me, Jack.
Please don't let them
do this to me.
Audrey...
Help me, Jack, don't
let them do...
Audrey!
It's me. I'm right here.
Do you even know who I am?
DOYLE:
Sit her down.
They've done something to her.
You got to help her, please.
We will. Let's go, Jack.
Please.
(indistinct muttering)
My God.
www.tvsubtitles.net