Abu Fayed,
a citizen of your country,
enters the United States,
detonates a nuclear bomb
killing thousands.
Next, Assad attempts
to assassinate the president.
AMBASSADOR:
You know fully well
that we have cooperated
with you since
the inception of this crisis.
I had an understanding
with your president.
And now you're going
to have one with me.
You help us find those nukes
before another goes off,
or I'm going to unleash
the full power of our military
on your country.
VASILI:
I'm terminating the American.
Do you confirm?
Yes.
(grunting)
MARKOV:
The American has shot Vasili.
He's in the basement.
Shut down the phone lines, DSL,
everything!
JACK:
Morris, it's Jack.
I know how
to find Gredenko.
He's in the...
(dial tone)
Morris?
Jack? Jack?
Jack Bauer's currently
being held captive
in the Russian consulate.
Doyle will help you
put a tactical profile together
for an assault on the consulate.
DOYLE:
Our primary objective
is to abduct Anatoly Markov,
the consul.
According to Jack, Markov knows
how to find Gredenko,
who controls the remaining
three suitcase nukes.
The Americans are coming in.
I thought you had that
under control.
Won't be long
before they have your position.
This drone is ready to launch.
Arm the bomb.
What's going on
at the Russian consulate?
Jack Bauer's still at large
and somewhere inside.
We have to go in.
Drop your weapon!
My name is Jack Bauer.
You need to contact
Bill Buchanan.
Tell him that
Fayed and Gredenko
are in the Shadow Valley.
Patch me in
with Buchanan.
(indistinct radio transmissions)
Medevac's on the way.
How you holding up?
I'm fine.
Doc?
He may have floating
rib fragments
which could cause
internal bleeding.
He needs
to be stabilized.
Agent Doyle,
I told you I'm fine.
I want to be involved
in this mission.
CTU has the ball, Jack.
Right now, this is out
of your hands.
We now believe Gredenko
is in possession
of at least five
RQ-2 Aerial Drones
(over speakerphone):
somewhere in Shadow Valley.
RQ-2s?
Unmanned stealth aircraft
which can be remotely piloted
from anywhere in the world.
And Gredenko's arming them
with the nuclear weapons
he provided to Fayed?
Yes, sir.
We're redirecting satellite
coverage over the Mojave Desert,
and the Air Force is scrambling
F-16s from Edwards.
But you have no idea how
close Fayed and Gredenko are
to launching
these drones?
No, sir, we don't.
(sighs):
All right, Bill.
You keep me updated.
Yes, sir.
GREDENKO:
Bring the trucks around.
We are moving out now.
What's wrong?
How many drones
have been armed?
Just this one.
GREDENKO:
Damn it.
We need to launch it now.
Get it ready.
Go, go.
Tell me what's wrong.
What's wrong?
The Americans
know our location.
How?
It was Markov, huh?
Markov told them.
All that matters is
that they know we are here.
We need to launch the drone
before they close in.
We have three bombs
and three targets.
We'll find a way to deliver
the other two bombs.
All this time we've tolerated
your condescension,
berating us for losing
the other bombs.
But now it's your fault.
Markov was your man.
Blame me all you want,
but if we stay here,
we'll be captured
or killed.
Refit the other bombs
into their casings
and load them on the truck.
Do it now!
Take them out!
We're accelerating our schedule.
Why?
I don't have time to explain.
I need you to launch
drone 0-7-0-9.
I haven't finished implementing
the evasion vectors.
They'll shoot it down
before it reaches its target.
Launch the drone.
You'll execute evasion tactics
once it's in the air.
Yes, sir.
(engine whooshing)
We need to leave now.
Come on, let's go.
We're repositioning
our satellites
as fast as we can, sir.
As soon as we make
visual contact,
we'll uplink a real-time feed
to your command.
(quietly):
Here.
(over phone):
Lives are at stake, Yassir.
Get me that intel.
Yes, sir.
You okay?
The truth? No, not really.
Hey.
We're going to get
through this, okay?
I hope so.
Is there
a problem, Chloe?
Yeah.
Are you going to tell us
what it is?
I was installing
security upgrades,
and I noticed you were using
Milo's clearance code.
Which, in case
you didn't know,
is a felony security breach.
No, it must be a mistake.
My system's been glitchy,
and I think I...
It's not a glitch, Milo.
Nadia's been working
with your user I.D.
So unless she stole it,
you gave it to her.
Milo was just trying
to help me do my work.
Nadia...
Homeland Security
sent down
an order restricting
my security access
because I was born
in the Middle East.
I've heard of that directive,
and I think it's wrong for us
to be racially profiling our
own agents, but it's still
a felony security breach
for you to be using Milo's code.
Chloe...
If you report this,
we can't help the situation
if we're fired and arrested.
If I wanted to report you,
I wouldn't be talking to you.
I'm telling you this so
that you'll be careful.
I mean, I noticed it.
Someone else is going
to notice it sooner or later.
BUCHANAN:
Nadia?
Yes, sir.
Morris has a satellite visual
on Shadow Valley.
It looks like the terrorists
have launched a single drone.
I'm conferencing
with General Walsh now.
I'll be right there, sir.
Coordinate with first-responders
in all target zones.
Put General Walsh through.
You're on with
Bill Buchanan, sir.
This is Walsh.
BUCHANAN:
General, we've made visual
contact with a single drone.
We're tracking it on satellite.
It's heading on a northwest
vector out of Shadow Valley.
Altitude is 3,300 feet
and climbing.
Velocity is 360 miles an hour.
I'm looking at the specs
on the RQ-2 now.
It's got a
low-profile design,
virtually impossible
to detect by radar.
We'll need to manually guide
our F-16s to intercept.
We're uplinking
a video feed to you now.
Have you determined
its intended target?
Yes. This is Nadia Yassir.
The closest target
is downtown Los Angeles.
That's a four-minute window.
Maximum airspeed of an RQ-2
is 400 miles per hour.
My F-16s should be able to
intercept it within two minutes.
MORRIS:
Um...
that may be a problem.
I can't find the drone.
The drone's gone.
How can it be gone?
It was passing between grids,
but when I switched
satellites...
Readjust based on
projected vectors.
I'm doing that now, General,
it's just not where
it's supposed to be.
Until you find it, I'll have my
F-16s stay in a holding pattern.
(beeping)
Yes?
I've accessed our connection
to CTU.
I've disabled
their tracking capability.
Then they cannot
detect the drone?
No. And I'll be able
to keep it hidden
from their satellites until
we've hit the target.
Good. I'll contact you again
once we are out of the area.
Sir, I was just talking
to Bill Buchanan at CTU.
They were tracking
one of the drones.
They've now lost
visual contact with it.
Lost visual contact?
Yeah, it's unclear
just how, sir.
They just simply
can't find it.
We have the most sophisticated
satellite network in the world.
How the hell did this happen?
CTU is still trying
to determine that, sir.
What about
the military?
Well, they've got three
squadrons looking for it,
but these drones
are invisible
to radar, so the pilots
are limited to making
visual ID at night
over hundreds of square miles.
Now, CTU has a ranked list
of potential
targets.
They're running civil
disaster scenarios...
Lisa?
Sir?
Advance the meeting
with the Joint Chiefs.
When do you want
it to happen?
Right away.
Wait, sir. Why...
Why are we assembling
the Joint Chiefs?
I warned
the ambassador, Tom.
You heard me tell him
that I'd hold his country
responsible
if another nuclear weapon
was detonated on our soil.
Sir, there's
absolutely no evidence
that his country
either sponsored these attacks
or is even in support of them.
His people need
to understand
that I'm not just
rattling my saber.
They need to see
with their own eyes
that I will answer this threat
with an in-kind
military response.
Wait.
"In kind," sir?
I want the Joint Chiefs
to draw up our own target list
for a nuclear strike.
--At its rated speed, the drone
should have reached Los Angeles,
so we can eliminate us
as a target.
In the next few minutes,
I can take Santa Barbara
and San Diego off the list.
How many targets does that leave
within the drone's range?
Counting cities with populations
over a million...
fifteen.
We have to narrow it down.
Assuming they want the maximum
civilian death toll,
how many likely targets
within the drone's range?
Areas with the highest
population density are
San Francisco, Las Vegas
and Phoenix.
Confirm that NEST teams and
First Responders have deployed
in those cities.
Morris, make sure the
Air Force prioritizes
their search
on that basis.
Yup.
(gasps)
Give me the projected
coordinates.
Bill.
Bill, did we pick up
Gredenko?
We're working on it.
Bill, what happened?
Gredenko escaped.
But not before
launching one
of the drones.
How close is the Air Force
to intercepting it?
F-16s were minutes away,
then the drone disappeared
from the satellite grid;
we're still looking for it.
Jack.
Get to medical.
There's nothing
you can do here.
Just keep me
informed, please.
I will.
Doyle, I want you
to run point
on the search for
Fayed and Gredenko.
Milo's monitoring from
the Situation Room.
I'll be right there.
I'll see you over at Medical.
Hey.
Could we have a moment, please?
They said you
were hurt.
I'm, I'm fine.
As soon as all
of this is over,
I'll come by and check
on you and Josh.
I always regretted things didn't
work out between us...
and...
I always believed
you did, too.
Maybe I was wrong.
No, you weren't.
Listen, Marilyn,
before I was taken prisoner
by the Chinese...
I, I was with someone.
She doesn't even know
I'm still alive, but...
I need to talk to her...
see what happens.
Are you talking
about Audrey Raines?
Yeah.
You don't know.
Do you?
(sighs)
Jack, I'm...
I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you this...
Audrey's dead.
I don't know all the details,
I just know what I read
in the paper
about her accident.
What accident? When?
It was a few months ago.
It was a car accident.
Somewhere in China.
China.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
(panting)
CHLOE:
There'll be separate
channels open
for all First Responders
in at-risk cities...
All First Responders
should coordi...
Why the hell didn't anybody
tell me about Audrey?
Mr. Buchanan didn't want to tell
you when you first got back,
because we all thought
Fayed was just going
to kill you.
But I probably should have.
I'm sorry.
She was in China looking for me?
She was the one
who figured out
the Chinese had taken you.
Apparently she spent
the past year
going through
back channels,
to try to get you out.
The rest of it's
classified by Division,
I don't know any more.
We were asked
to send the DNA records,
so that they could
get a positive ID
on the remains...
which I guess they did.
I want that file.
All right, Jack.
Now!
I have to dig it up
in archives.
Just do it.
The Secretary of Defense
and the Chairman
of the Joint Chiefs
will be attending
in person, the State
will be monitoring
via satellite.
And the rest of the
Cabinet will be provided
with video
transcripts.
Good.
You should also know that
Karen Hayes will be attending.
I thought I told you I wanted
her excluded from this.
She supported Wayne Palmer's
policy of appeasement.
She's going to be a problem.
Well, there was nothing
I could do.
She's still acting
National Security
Advisor.
But I've only given her
current circumstances.
Any objection to your plans will
not be able to gain traction.
(chuckles)
Oh, I've known Karen Hayes
for many years.
It's always been a mistake
to underestimate...
her.
Hello, Tom.
Somebody push
you down the stairs?
No, Karen, I tripped
over your ineptitude.
On that subject,
welcome back.
Look, Tom,
I don't want to play games.
I won't let you
blackmail me again.
So you do what you need to do,
I am here to represent
the President,
and I intend to stay.
All right, fair enough.
Karen.
No one is sorrier than I am
about what happened to Wayne.
Well, at least we have that
in common.
Please be seated.
As many of you
are already aware,
the terrorist who attacked us
this morning,
Abu Fayed, with the help
of Dmitri Gredenko,
has launched an aerial drone
that we believe is armed
with another nuclear bomb.
Efforts are ongoing
to locate this drone.
But should
those efforts fail,
we are looking at a second
nuclear attack on our country
in less than ten hours.
And I am determined
not to let this
attack happen
without a military response
on our part.
A military response
directed against
whom, Mr. Vice
President?
We were under the impression
that these terrorists were
essentially stateless.
Secretary Kanin, that is
the fiction they hide behind.
But...
everyone in this room knows
that elements within
Abu Fayed's country
train and fund terrorist
organizations like his.
It is time
to hold them
accountable.
The Ambassador
has just been informed
that if the nuclear weapon
on that drone detonates,
we will retaliate
with our own nuclear strike.
Now this will be
a warning shot, not
a full-scale attack.
The Joint Chiefs have been
instructed to identify
an unpopulated area
where there will be limited
civilian casualties.
Admiral.
The closest match
we have
to that scenario
is territory near
their northern border.
We believe this should result
in fewer than 2,000 deaths.
Long-term damage from
radioactive fallout, however,
could double that number,
depending on ground conditions.
I can accept that.
Mr. Vice President,
I'm sure you're aware
that our intelligence suggests
that their government
can't control
Fayed either.
They are doing the best
that they can.
And I'm saying they need to
figure out a way to do better.
Something tells me
that once this bomb hits,
they will.
If this bomb hits,
the opposite will hold true.
The moderates will be driven
from power,
the terrorists' position
will be strengthened there
and in the region,
and I don't hear anyone
talking about the Chinese
or Russian response to this.
We could start another
world war.
If I thought there was a high
likelihood of that,
I wouldn't be suggesting this.
Mr. Vice President,
the stakes are too high
for this decision to be based
on your personal
judgment.
It is my opinion
that this course of action would
be dangerous and reckless.
Consider your concern
registered, Karen.
But the debate is over.
America must start
to stand up
for herself.
The attacks on this
country must stop!
And as acting
Commander In Chief,
I believe this is the best way
to make that happen.
Admiral,
have a nuclear strike sub
standing by.
--Nadia?
I never got those SIM files
you were gonna send me.
Oh, yeah, your system
was overloaded.
So I gave them to Morris,
he's going to take care
of it for you.
Morris?
Yeah.
I mean, you really think
he can handle it?
Well, he seems
to be himself again.
Is he himself because he had
a drink and he smoothed out?
I don't think so.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Setting up a reverse
data stream on the drone's
satellite intel,
okay?
Morris seems better.
Is that a question?
Is he?
Yes.
Look, I need you
to do me a favor.
No.
I need you to check his breathe.
If he's better, great.
If he had a drink
and he's headed
for another crash
we need to know about that.
Fine.
Thanks, darling.
What was that for?
Just checking
your breath.
He's fine.
Thank you.
(typing)
Got to love this place.
HAYES:
Tom.
Yes, Karen, I hear you.
You can't possibly
be in favor
of Daniels' plan for
a nuclear strike.
You heard the Vice President.
It's a warning shot
into an unpopulated area.
It is a military offensive
on foreign soil.
And you and
I both know
it will be impossible
to contain.
Tom, you know this is
insane, I know you do.
I saw you in
that meeting.
I saw the doubt in your eyes.
Do not presume
to know what I am
thinking or feeling.
I serve at the discretion
of those above me.
You serve the interests
of the President.
And you know that
Wayne would not
sign off on this course
of action.
Wayne was wrong.
Every decision
he made today was wrong--
rejecting
my security initiatives,
using Assad as an appeal
to extremist groups.
And look what we've been led to!
You can't seriously
believe that.
You just cannot!
Doesn't matter what I believe.
As long as the President
is in a coma,
Daniels is the acting
Commander in Chief.
Now, if you want him
to abort that missile launch,
you had better pray
that CTU can find
and stop that drone.
We've got ground teams
on all roads leading out
of Shadow Valley looking
for Fayed and Gredenko,
but with SAT support dedicated
to finding the drone,
there's not much to go on.
MILO:
And CalTrans doesn't have
any cameras set up
in the outlying areas.
Mr. Buchanan, we figured out
how the drone
is able to stay hidden
from our satellites.
Whoever is piloting it
is able to anticipate
our repositioning directives,
flying through the gaps
in the images.
How can he do that?
CHLOE:
Our satellite data
is being relayed
to the drone pilot
through a workstation here.
We have a leak.
One of our own people?
Looks that way.
Can you isolate the workstation?
No. It's being masked
through a sub-circuit.
Morris is working on it now,
but there are
over 50 stations
in this building.
It could take an hour
to do a
signature trace.
We don't have an hour.
Run a trace match
on Nadia Yassir's
station.
Why Nadia?
Do it.
MILO: Wait, you
think just because
she's a Muslim,
that gives you the right...
I'm following
standard protocol.
Standard protocol?
She's already
been tagged
and given restricted clearance.
(scoffs)
And, yeah,
she is a Muslim.
That's enough to go on.
Everyone here
is thinking it,
even if they won't say it.
You're a racist.
BUCHANAN:
Milo,
I understand your distaste.
But we have to vet every
system in the building.
There's no reason
not to start with hers.
No, sir, there's every reason.
Nadia Yassir's 100 percent
loyal to this country.
She is not a terrorist.
Is this assessment based on
some private knowledge?
Or is it because you're
itching to sleep with her?
Son of a...
BUCHANAN:
All right!
That's enough!
Agent Doyle,
that was way out of line.
We don't have time for
your personal differences.
We have to find out
who's subverting our system.
It is Nadia.
The signature trace
matches her computer.
Shut down her workstation.
CHLOE:
I'm trying. The only way to cut
the data flow is to reboot
CTU's mainframe.
We'd be without system power
for more than 20 minutes.
Get security on the floor now.
Surrender
your station.
Excuse me?
Who are you streaming
our satellite data to?
What?!
Where is the pilot?
BUCHANAN:
Doyle, damn it,
that's enough!
Take her to holding.
Bill, don't let,
don't let him do this!
What are
you doing?!
Bill, I'm innocent!
I'm not a traitor!
Morris,
secure her station.
See if you can
run a back trace
on that leak.
Find out where
the feed is going.
Excuse me.
Victor.
What is the drone's
current position?
130 miles
southeast of target.
Have you locked in
the GPS coordinates?
Yes.
The bomb will detonate
over San Francisco
within 20 minutes.
--WELTON:
...you want the drip
to stay steady.
Add in some glucose
after about an hour.
If you see anything,
any movement,
twitch of the
eyelids, you get me.
Got it?
Dr. Welton,
I need to speak
with you.
I don't have much time,
Ms. Hayes.
What's the President's
condition?
It's worsened
in the last 15 minutes.
There was a buildup of
intracranial pressure.
We had to induce a coma
to relieve the swelling.
I see.
Good news is
we stopped it in time.
Doesn't seem to have been
any neural damage,
and his vitals are
surprisingly strong.
He's a fighter.
We have that much going for us.
Excuse me.
Doctor...
Yes.
Is there any way that you can
bring the President
back to consciousness?
I know this is an
unusual request,
but it's a matter of national
security that I speak with him.
I'm sorry.
It could pose
a serious risk to his life.
I couldn't possibly
authorize it.
Who could?
I'd need consent
from his family.
His sister is here.
But I would strongly
advise against it.
If the swelling
isn't contained,
the President could suffer
permanent brain damage.
I have to go, Ms. Hayes.
* *
This is insane.
Nadia can't be involved in this.
The signal was routed
through her station.
We can't ignore that fact.
Do you really believe that Nadia
is helping the terrorists?
I don't want to believe it,
but I really don't know.
Doyle's an ass.
He's doing his job.
If we want him to stop,
we have to prove she's innocent.
Hello. Think I
got something.
What is it?
I've set up
a feedback pulse.
Whoever Nadia's feeding
our data stream to
will read it as some
static in the line,
but we may be able
to ride the pulse
back to its source, find
the location of the drone pilot.
I've got it.
1530 Hillcrest.
Hillcrest, that's close.
Bloody close--
three blocks away.
Okay, tell Buchanan.
I'm asking you once
again, cooperate.
Help me put
an end to this.
(sighs)
(gasps)
I'm warning you.
I will do what's necessary
to get the answers I need.
Do you understand?
(gasping)
I understand everything.
I read your file.
I know what you did in Denver.
You enjoy hurting people.
You get off on it.
We're not here to talk about me.
We're here to talk about
what you know.
I don't know anything!
MILO:
Get away from
her, Doyle.
I said let her go.
What the hell
are you doing?
We got the drone
pilot's location
through Nadia's computer.
Where is it?
Three blocks from here.
1530 Hillcrest.
We're not through
with her, Milo.
(gasps)
Are you okay?
Milo?
You know I didn't have anything
to do with this.
Get out of here.
* *
Agent, what's going on?
We have a location
on the drone's pilot.
We're mobilizing now.
BUCHANAN:
As you know, whoever's
piloting the drone
is operating in close
proximity to CTU.
I'm instituting a level
one security lock-down.
All provisional safeguards are
in effect until further notice.
Let's go to work!
Marcy...
contact LAPD.
Have them coordinate
with tactical.
Seal off a perimeter.
Yes, sir.
Chloe...
have they confirmed
the address?
Yes, it's a relay station.
I've got the building
specs and layout.
I'm gonna need a PDA
and a phone.
I'll get them for you.
Thanks.
Jack, what are you doing?
I'm going with the team.
You're injured.
You should be in medical.
You should have told me
about Audrey, Bill.
We were asking you to give
your life, Jack.
I didn't think it
was right to tell you
about Audrey's accident.
It wasn't an accident.
She was murdered.
No one knows that for sure.
I do.
Bill, Audrey gave
her life trying to get me
out of a Chinese prison
because she thought
I was worth it.
I'm not going to let
her die for nothing now.
I'm going to finish this.
And when I do,
I'm gonna track down the people
responsible for her murder,
and I'm going to take
care of them, too.
Please, you have to
let me finish this.
All right.
I'll tell Doyle
you're running point.
--The drone is approaching
the city.
I'm beginning descent now.
How long until the bomb
detonates?
At its current speed,
the drone will reach
the target perimeter
within three minutes.
It will detonate automatically
when it reaches
the perimeter line.
I'll bring it in
at an altitude of 500 feet
to achieve maximum damage.
Don't worry, tovarish,
everything is set.
It will happen exactly
as you planned.
Concentrate on
the task at hand.
Then call me when it's done.
Yes, sir.
Bill, it's Jack.
We're in position.
The gate was open,
there's a utility truck
parked behind the building.
Our back-trace shows
the intrusion
into our system is
coming from a room
in the northwest corner
of the switching station.
Jack, I'm looking at an updated
schematic now. Your most direct
route is through the rear
entrance, to the left.
Okay. Did you get that?
Yeah.
(grunts)
Do you want me
on point?
I got it.
Let's go.
Whatever you say.
(clattering)
What was that?
Go check.
(gunshot, groaning)
Let's get a medic.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Do you copy?
We copy.
Jack, what's your status?
The drone pilot is down.
I'm at his controls now.
The target is
San Francisco.
I repeat, the target
is San Francisco.
Alert local law enforcement
and First Responders
in the area, and
open a channel
with the Regional Control
Center up there.
Got it.
These controls are
for navigation only.
There is no way
to deactivate the
bomb remotely.
CTU, we're linking you in now.
You should have it.
It's coming through.
Jack, is there any way
for you to determine
what triggering
mechanism they're using?
It looks like they wired
a GPS module into the bomb.
It'll detonate as
soon as it crosses
its designated
perimeter.
I'm trying
to steer it away now.
Don't turn the drone
too sharply,
or it'll stall,
and you'll lose control.
Copy that.
On its current course,
the drone will cross
the perimeter
and detonate
in 30 seconds.
Jack, you're getting
a stabilizer warning.
I see it.
20 seconds.
Ten seconds.
Okay, it's turning.
The drone did not
cross the perimeter.
I'm fighting a stall.
I'm losing control
of the drone.
I need to find a
place to land it now.
All right, according
to the specs,
it's gonna need 500 feet
of runway to land.
Okay, closest to the drone's
current position,
there's a long stretch
of residential road
straight ahead of you.
That's a negative. Find me
an area that's unpopulated.
Hold on.
If you can get
the drone farther east,
there's an industrial
park along the Bay.
I'm uploading
the coordinates now.
Have Regional Command deploy
units to the area immediately.
Regional Command...
Come on.
(engine whooshing)
The drone is down.
(clanking)
MORRIS: Mr. Buchanan,
none of the First
Responders in San Francisco
are reporting a detonation.
The bomb did not
go off on impact.
Jack, did you copy that?
Yeah.
Can we get a visual
from anyone at the site?
I'm showing a fire
and rescue unit already
arriving at the scene.
What's the status on the pilot?
He's alive, barely.
Do whatever you have to
to get him conscious.
(sirens blaring)
(indistinct radio transmission)
(beeping)
Get the Geiger counter.
(beeping continues)
(static crackling)
(crackling continues,
then ceases)
Move out! There's radioactive
material in this area!
Pull back
and wait for HAZMAT.
Move it!
Sir,
I have Bill Buchanan
on line one.
Bill, what do you have?
Mr. Vice President,
the drone was intercepted
before the nuclear bomb
was able to detonate.
Oh, thank God.
Congratulations, sir.
We were able to take control
of the aircraft,
crash-landing it
in an industrial park
at the edge of the city.
But in the process,
the bomb's nuclear
core was compromised,
and radioactive
material was released.
So what we're essentially
dealing with is a dirty bomb.
Sir, this was not
a dispersal device.
It was a radiological spill.
It was an attack
on our nation.
Bill, are there casualties?
Local Responders
got there before HAZMAT.
They were almost
certainly exposed
to fatal doses of
radiation, but so far,
it appears that
radioactive material
was not widely dispersed.
Casualties should
be minimal.
At least we've got that to be
grateful for. Thanks, Bill.
Proceed with the warning strike
as planned.
Sir, the primary
attack was averted.
CTU was successful.
There will be civilian
deaths, as well as untold
environmental damage.
I hardly consider
that a success.
The damage will be minimal
compared to what
we just avoided.
Sir, I think we should
consider ourselves fortunate.
Tom?
Sir?
Mr. Vice President,
we were led to believe
that this warning shot
would be fired
only in response
to the detonation
of a nuclear device.
That is a technicality, Tom.
I gave fair warning
to the Prime Minister,
and I intend to carry it out.
Secretary Kanin?
How long will
it take to move
the submarine
into position?
Once you've given the order...
within the hour.
The order is given.
Launch the missile...
...as soon as they're in range.
www.tvsubtitles.net