-=The Last Fantasy=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:Allen
-=www.eastgame.net=-
24ep06
MAN:
Going down! No!
WAYNE:
How many people died in this?
No less than 12,000.
Four more tactical nuclear
weapons were stolen along
with the one that went off.
CTU was trying to determine
where Fayed was
at the time.
The worst case scenario
is that he
is still alive
and in possession of the
remaining nuclear weapons.
My engineer died
in the blast.
The device used
to reprogram the trigger
was destroyed as well.
I have four more bombs
whose triggers need
to be made operational.
We need someone who could
replicate what that device did,
with modern equipment.
McCarthy will find
someone for us.
Tell the man these bombs
will go off today.
Walid overheard
some conversations
about the bombs.
If there is an active
shell inside
that detention facility,
we need Walid to find out more.
He's wiring you.
It's a two-way radio.
Now you're going
to tell me
what we found in your
wallet, you understand me?
(grunts)
You're going to say
that I asked about this man.
Got to make them believe
you're working for them.
What if they find out
he's wearing a wire?
The guards inside know
what's going on.
They'll keep an eye
on him.
I sent Fayed to negotiate
with an ex-Soviet general
about the cache of tactical
nuclear weapons.
What was the name
of the general?
Dmitri Gredenko.
Assad just gave us the name
of a Russian general
Fayed contacted a year ago
about the nukes.
Gredenko did business
with BXJ Technologies,
specifically with your father.
My father?
I haven't spoken to him
for over nine years.
Well, we'll send someone over
to talk to him.
I should do this.
He'll talk to me, if I go alone.
You will never guess
who just called here.
Who?
Your brother Jack.
What's he want?
He's looking for the old man.
Damn it, we should have killed
Jack when we had the chance,
instead of handing him over
to the Chinese.
Look at the bright side:
you got out--
you're here--
so just relax a little bit.
Gray, people in
this country are dying.
And I need some information.
Are you going to
give it to me
or do I have to start
hurting you?
I told you I don't
know where Dad is.
What do you want from me?
The truth!
That is the truth.
I swear to you on
my family's life.
Not good enough.
(sudden shout)
WAYNE:
Although the crisis we face
today is a grave and dire one,
we will rise above it.
We have been challenged
as never before.
This time, against this enemy,
armed with these weapons,
we must rely
on the strength and faith
of every single American.
And that faith is unshakable.
We must rise above our fears,
above our bigotries
and stand our ground.
Our goal is the defeat of
the enemy and the preservation
of our values.
We've achieved that goal
in the past.
And so we shall again.
Thank you.
I wish he had not
said that.
Sir?
Made a promise
he can't keep.
The American people have got
to get used to the fact
these security measures
are a way of life,
they're not some
temporary Band-Aid.
Now you're making policy
unilaterally, Tom.
The president was
absolutely clear
about your proposals.
I'm sorry,
what is this about, Karen?
"National Guard
supplanting police
"in major cities,
expanding detentions
based on soft intel."
You authorized these
without presidential consent.
Now how many times do you think
we are going
to be going over this?
I am taking preparatory steps
to allow the president
to act swiftly,
should he decide to act at all.
Nobody is authorizing anything.
That's what you said
about the detention facilities,
and yet those
"preparatory measures"
turned into an illegal
paramilitary operation.
Well, however you may choose
to characterize it,
The president agreed
to all of these actions...
That's because
you've distorted the facts.
What is it, Tom?
Is it that you think I'm some
bleeding heart liberal
preaching civil liberties--
is that it?
I'll tell you what I think.
The Constitution is
a wonderful thing, Karen,
but back in the days
of the Founding Fathers,
the weapon at hand was
a single-shot musket.
It took a half a minute
to load and fire.
Fayed just killed 12,000 people
in less time without
even taking aim.
I love the Constitution,
but I won't be ducking behind it
when the next nuke goes off.
I'm a realist, too, Tom, and
I am willing to do what it takes
to protect this country...
No, you are not!
But I am looking a little
further down the road.
These warrantless arrests and
detention centers
will cause
irreparable damage
to this country.
Hey, you know something?
Why don't you just hop a shuttle
over to Justice Department...
You are using this crisis...
You don't belong
in National Security.
...to advance a very
dangerous agenda,
Tom, and take advantage
of Presidential power.
You know something?
I'm done in here.
And I will
not let you do it.
And if you think
that you are going
to wear me down, you are
sadly mistaken.
Actually,
you're wearing me down.
No, that's right,
you won't make
the same mistake again, because
you're going to give the file
to Sharon, she's going
to handle it from there.
No, get it done.
I need Karen Hayes
to go away.
I'm putting the last
ties on that...
I need this now.
I need the president to
sign off on my proposals.
She has gone from being an
irritant to an obstacle.
And she will be gone
soon, sir, I promise.
I'm just waiting
to hear back
from a few more people,
then you can approach her.
This work you're doing for me,
it doesn't go unnoticed.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Buchanan.
Yes.
Are you aware
of the internal
security mandate that's
just been issued?
I haven't looked
at the hourlies yet.
What's going on?
Anyone identified
with a Middle Eastern
background is required
to put a redundancy layer
on all their log-ins.
I see.
Look, normally, I'm not
sensitive to this kind of thing,
you know that,
but this is not the time to be
racially profiling people
who have grade-four
security clearance.
I agree, I'm not going
to argue with you.
Good-- so you give
me an exemption?
I'll take this issue
to the attorney general,
but it's not going
to happen right away.
Well, how am I supposed to work
with one hand tied
behind my back?
Listen, you
and I both
knew when I hired you that
a Muslim working counter-terror
in the United States
was going to have to
put up with some unfair
measures-- this is
one of them.
I know.
But today, of all days...
Especially today.
I need you to stay focused
on the big picture.
When this is behind us,
I will take this issue
to the attorney general,
I promise you.
Have we heard from Jack yet?
Not since he went
to go see his brother.
Want me to try and reach him?
No. He'll call us
when he has something.
(muffled grunt,
rapid gasping)
(explosive cough,
wheezing)
You lie to me again,
the bag goes back on.
Do you understand me?
(raspy coughing)
Start talking, Gray!
(gasping):
Dad...
Dad didn't want anyone to know
where he went.
He didn't even leave a number,
in case of an emergency?
No, you can't reach him, Jack.
(catching breath):
After the bomb was...
detonated,
he told me he was
cutting himself off.
(crying quietly)
I don't believe you.
(sobs loudly)
I think he told you
where he was going.
No, no! It's the truth!
Fine...
No, no!
I don't know! I don't know!
All right, all right,
all right, all right!
(growling gasps)
He went to see a...
a guy who works for us.
His name's
Darren McCarthy.
Why?
It was my fault.
I made a mess.
Dad's trying
to clean it up.
What do you mean?
You were right.
It's about the nukes.
(sighs, gasps)
The connection you
found between Dad
and Gredenko had to do
with a... a contract
that was awarded to us.
Through the company?
Yeah, it all went
through BXJ.
What did an ex-Russian general
have to do
with the contract?
It was his job... to release
the old nukes into the U.S.
for decommissioning.
BXJ was hired to dismantle
some of the smaller bombs
and to recycle their cores
into energy production--
we do it all the time.
What happened?
(heavy sigh)
I hired McCarthy to
oversee the job,
but I didn't check him
out carefully enough.
So, basically, he came in
with the lowest bid
and you just hired him!
I-I... M-My head was into
other things at the time.
I-I-I... H-He came in
with good references.
I saw no reason to get
all anal about it.
So the nukes that these
terrorists are in possession of,
including the one that was just
detonated in Valencia,
were supplied by McCarthy
and stolen from you.
Yes, in a nutshell,
that's it.
Sam told me Dad left
yesterday...
which means that you and he
knew about this
before today,
and you didn't report it.
We didn't report it
because we thought
we could take care of it
more efficiently.
Damn it, Gray!
Do you know how many people
have died
because you're trying
to cover your ass?!
We had no idea that this
was going to happen.
And besides,
what Dad and I are doing
to stop this is
more effective
than what you and your
people are gonna do.
What, exactly,
are you doing?
Dad put together a security team
and he went out
to look for McCarthy.
Where?
He was staking out
McCarthy's office.
He checked in about an hour ago.
Where is this office?
He's in Simi.
We're going.
I'm not leaving
my family, Jack.
Not today.
Oh, yes, you are.
Get up!
Graem, where are
you going?
Jack and I have to go
find Dad.
What do you mean,
find him?
He's not reachable right
now; we have to go out
and pick him up-- I want you
to stay here, all right?
You stay with Josh,
don't either of you
go outside the house.
I'll be back
as soon as I can.
What's the address?
McCarthy's office
is off the 23.
5137 Olson Avenue.
Who are you calling?
(phone ringing)
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Let me speak to Bill.
He's being briefed
on Fayed.
Have you picked up
any threads?
Not yet.
I've got one-- I want you
to send two field units
to 5137 Olson Avenue,
in Simi Valley.
It should be off
the 23.
I want them to wait
for me there.
Get Bill to call me back
as soon as he's out of
the briefing.
Okay, I will.
So that's it, Jack, huh?
You're just gonna
sell out Dad and me.
--We've been monitoring
ground movement
ever since
the bomb went off.
We locked down streets,
we're doing vehicle
searches--
so far, nothing.
No sign of Fayed.
MORRIS:
Which means he could still
hunkered down within
the perimeter-- what are
we doing about that?
We've got NEST teams
in the area now.
They're going
street by street.
That'll take hours.
Yeah, Morris,
it's all going to take time.
If we could do it quicker,
we would.
We can use the direction
of the fallout to our advantage.
If Fayed is still
in the perimeter,
he'll be moving
in the opposite direction.
And he'll have to be
monitoring the fallout.
Which means he's got technology
in the "on" position.
Let's use radio
frequency satellite,
see what we can come up with.
Good.
Get on it.
Mr. Buchanan,
Jack just called in.
He's following some kind
of lead in Simi Valley.
He wants you to call
him right away.
Anything else?
Nothing.
He asked me to send
two teams to meet him.
Any leads on finding
Gredenko?
Not yet.
CIA is trying
to track him
down in Moscow.
Okay, thank you.
If you give CTU McCarthy's name,
they will eventually
come after the family.
That is not
necessarily true.
CTU is interested in
finding these bombs,
not networking
a series of indictments.
Oh, will you not be
so simple-minded for once
in your life!
CTU,
like every other federal
organization, is made up
of human beings
with ambition.
When the dust settles,
they will start
digging deeper,
you can count on it.
Well, unfortunately for you,
Gray, right now
you're going
to have to trust me.
Trust you? After what you
did to me at the house,
all I trust in is your
sadistic tendencies.
(cell phone ringing)
This is Bauer.
What'd you find out?
Bill, I want you
to run a locater check
on a Darren McCarthy.
Who is he?
He was an independent
munitions contractor.
He worked for
BXJ Technologies.
How does McCarthy
figure into all this?
My father's company
hired him
to decommission
the nukes.
I believe he brokered
them to Fayed.
So except for McCarthy,
your father's company
had nothing to
do with Fayed?
I don't know BXJ's
involvement yet.
All right, we're on it.
Where are you?
I'm heading to McCarthy's
office in Simi Valley.
I don't think he's there,
but I might be able to get
something off his computer.
We have teams standing by.
Let me know.
Copy that.
(phone snaps shut)
You know, if you're doing
this to come after me,
eventually Dad will
get caught in the middle.
Or maybe you want that,
maybe you want
Dad to go to prison, too.
Boy, Jack...
it's good to see your loyalty's
still with your family.
If I were you,
I wouldn't talk about loyalty.
McCARTHY:
I know it's not easy, that's why
they're willing to pay
$7 million cash.
What about Taylor Paskal,
why can't he do it?
MAN (on phone):
He's a theoretical physicist.
He doesn't have enough
practical background
to reprogram a nuclear trigger.
Who does?
I'm still looking.
Fayed needs
someone now;
get me a name, damn it!
(slams phone down)
Where are we going now?
What do you care
where we're going?
Darren, I don't feel
safe in this city.
I was here when you
mentioned that earlier.
Okay... It seems to me
like whatever this is
you're trying to do
is a long shot.
You're just going
to waste all this time
and it's going to be
harder to get away.
(tires screeching)
Get out.
What?!
Your negativity is not
what I need right now.
I need less stress, not more.
(gasping)
(wry laugh)
How sure a thing...
is this $7 million?
Now that's the
type of question
that I love
hearing from you.
(cell phone ringing)
Yeah.
Have you found an engineer?
Not yet.
Why not?
(sighs):
Give me a break, Fayed.
This is not some easy
one-stop shopping.
You said within
the hour.
I know what I said.
It's just taking longer.
I told you I'd find someone
and I will.
(closes phone)
SAMUELS:
That's the last of the group.
So what do you do with them now?
Patch the images over to CTU.
They can cross them
with international watch lists.
Didn't you already
vet these people?
CTU has more resources.
They can go deeper,
find the connection to Fayed.
Samuels just sent us
images of the men
Walid is undercover with.
MORRIS:
Excellent.
Send them to my system,
when Nadia
gets me the manifest;
I'll cross them against
all of our watch lists.
Wait... Nadia didn't get you
the manifests yet?
No.
Why not?
I haven't a clue, mate.
Hey, you were supposed
to send the manifest
from the detention
facility over to comm.
Why don't we have it yet?
I'm backed up.
Well, why are you backed up?
Milo, I'm doing
the best that I can here.
You got a problem with it,
take it somewhere else.
Hey...
I'm just trying
to understand what
the problem is.
The detention facility's
one of the only
live leads we have.
Go ask Buchanan.
Okay.
We've got a support team
in place, if Jack needs
more backup,
he'll let you know.
Yeah.
What is it, Milo?
Nadia.
She's falling
behind on her tasks.
What's going
on with her?
Nothing.
Petition her workload
and hand some of it off
to another analyst.
I've only got her
working on one process.
She's doing some things
for me directly, Milo.
Just do it, please.
Mr. Buchanan,
with all due respect,
is there something
going on here you don't
want me to know about?
Yes, there is, Milo.
Either give Nadia enough
time to finish the work,
or give the work
to somebody else.
Sir, I'm the technical leader
on the floor.
If you want me to do my job
effectively, I need to
know what's happening.
Because Nadia's of
Middle Eastern descent,
she's been flagged
by Homeland Security.
That's ridiculous.
She's... lived in this country
since she was two years old.
She's... a registered
Republican, for crying out loud.
You're wasting your
breath, Milo--
there's nothing I can do
about this right now.
Let it go, will you please?
No, sir, I don't see how
we can just "let it go."
Aren't we trying
to find four
suitcase nukes that might
still be in this city?
Milo...
I need everyone on the floor
working at full speed.
I understand that, Milo.
Now get back to work.
Yes, sir.
(phone ringing)
Yeah, hi.
Have you heard
about this latest mandate
from Homeland Security?
No, why. What is it?
They're racially
profiling our own agents.
What?!
It just came down
from the White House.
The problem is one of my best
people is hamstrung.
She has to work twice
as hard to get through these
security measures.
They're not security
measures, Bill.
They're the paranoid delusions
of Tom Lennox.
Is there anything you can do?
I can talk to the president.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(hangs up phone)
He went off to Valencia
over an hour ago.
How many were killed?
We don't know yet.
(over speaker): They say
there are four more visitors.
WALID:
Four more visitors.
What does that mean?
I'm not sure.
But you think it
may have something
to do with what happened
in Valencia?
How did you get the information?
Why are you asking
so many questions?
Whatever happens
out there
affects us in here.
We need to share
everything we know.
Heydar has been in contact.
How?
He smuggled in a cell phone.
How did you do that?
Cell phone? How did he get
a cell phone in there?
These facilities
were put up quickly.
The security's
still pretty porous.
Then we need
to get this man's phone
and find out
who he's talking to.
If Walid can get the phone,
I can trace any call
that's been
made from it.
If I can get a live
conversation, that's worth
more than a list
of phone numbers.
Fine. Then, after that,
get Walid out of there.
No. They're talking to him now.
That's a big get.
We have to keep
listening in
on whatever they say.
This is Agent Samuels.
I'm going to need
to get into a cell tower--
grid location:
15 comma
twenty-seven.
It's done.
All these people
will come forward
if we need
them to testify?
Yes. I put the screws
to every one of them myself.
They're all yours.
Good.
Oh, Karen...
I need to talk to you.
Just a minute.
Now would be better.
Have this signed,
and then send it out.
This, uh, this just simply
isn't working for me.
I can't have you
stand in my way
anymore.
What?
I need the president's
undivided attention,
and you, frankly,
are dividing it.
Well, I'm not going
to stop doing my job, Tom,
just because it irritates you.
I thought
I made that
perfectly clear.
Yeah. I'd like you to tend
your resignation, Karen.
(scoffs)
My resignation?
What are you smoking?
No, no, no. I'm here
to blow away all of the smoke.
I want to talk about your
husband's
incompetence,
and your covering it up.
I don't like this
conversation.
What are you talking about?
14 months ago,
we had Abu Fayed in CTU custody
in Seattle,
and Bill Buchanan
signed off on
his release.
I don't believe this.
The case that
you're referring to,
if I remember correctly,
involved over 20 detainees.
Not prisoners, Tom.
Detainees.
And, at the time,
there was not enough evidence
to hold them.
It's just a little grayer
than that, now, isn't it?
If what you're saying
is true, how come
that incident wound up
blue-coded at Homeland
in a dead-end file?
I got Peter Iannone here,
Kurt Hueig, Myra Mawk...
They were all
in the pipeline--
all ready to testify
that you sequestered that file
to protect your husband.
I did nothing illegal
or incorrect!
Every single one
of those detainees
were cleared of any
conspiracy charges.
Nevertheless,
one of these detainees
detonated a nuclear bomb
in Los Angeles.
You think your husband
could survive that story?
Or you, for that matter?
Do you want to get in the ring
with me, Tom?
You've got skeletons
in your closet,
and I will not
hesitate to pull them out.
We've all got
our skeletons, Karen.
It's proof
we don't all have.
I've got mine.
How long before
you get yours?
You're a son of a bitch.
I never claimed otherwise.
But I am not out to hurt
you or your husband
personally.
I just need room to work.
Your resignation
within the hour.
--Can we go a little slower?
There's no rush.
Morris, I'm going
as fast as I can.
Why don't you just go back
to your station?
I'll send it over as soon
as I'm ready.
No, I'm curious as to why
it's taking you five minutes
to do something
that should take
ten seconds.
Because I borrowed
two of her processors
to run a batch job.
She's running on 20%.
Oh, yeah? Then why didn't
somebody tell me this?
I just did.
Fine. But don't
keep any secrets
from me, darling.
We're on the same side.
Why'd you lie for me?
I talked to Buchanan.
Yeah, it's pretty frustrating.
I'm sure.
What are you doing?
I'm logging you in
under my user I.D.
That's illegal.
And you didn't do it, I did.
Thank you.
Yeah, you should...
be fine.
(quiet conversation)
Excuse me, Mr. President,
I need to speak with you.
Karen, I'm a little
squeezed for time right now.
Can we talk later?
No, sir, we can't.
Okay.
Thank you.
Mr. President, I am tendering
my resignation,
effective immediately.
What's going on, Karen?
It's a personal
matter, sir.
Is there something wrong
with you or Bill?
No, we're fine.
It's... I cannot elaborate.
I've noticed that you and Tom
have been locking horns
these past few weeks.
Is that what
this is about?
Sir, I would rather not say.
Damn it, Karen,
that is unacceptable.
Mr. President...
I need you!
I need different
points of view.
Now I understand it's difficult
to sit in a room with someone
who opposes you
constantly,
but that is part
of your job.
And I have never seen
anyone handle it
better than you.
Now I am sorry, Karen, but I
cannot accept your resignation.
Not now, not today.
No disrespect, sir,
but you're going to have to.
Mr. President,
I'm here to tell you
that the past few weeks
have been
some of the must difficult weeks
that I have ever seen
a president face.
And I am truly honored
to serve under you
here in Washington.
And I appreciate that you value
my advice,
but, sir, the truth is, you have
been your own best counselor.
You know what
to do, sir.
And I have no doubt,
absolutely no doubt...
that you will continue
to rise to this challenge.
Is there anything I can do
to change your mind?
No, sir, there is not.
I would appreciate it,
however, if you would reassign
me to L.A. CTU.
I feel I will serve best there.
I'll approve you for
military transport west.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. President.
I'm sorry.
So am I.
Oh.
Excuse me, Karen,
I'm so sorry.
Oh, actually, Karen,
I'm glad I caught you.
I've got a State Department
white paper
I was hoping you
could look over
and then take
to the president.
No, you'll have
to give it to Tom.
Well, I thought
you handled that.
Give it to Tom.
Excuse me.
(phone ringing)
Yes.
Karen Hayes is out.
--The last one is a black Kia,
California license plate
Niner, Yankee, Sierra,
Uniform, 1-0-8.
That one's not registered
to McCarthy either.
Okay, I want you
to cross-reference the names
with registered owners,
see if any of them correlate.
What do you want
me to do with the
backup teams?
Where are they?
They're holding
a two-block radius.
Send one of them over
to the parking lot here,
tell the other
to stand by.
I'll get back to you.
Where's McCarthy's office?
What floor?
Second floor.
Let's go.
--You all right?
Yes, I'm fine. Thank you.
--All right, I've got the phone.
Good. I'm going to give you
a number to dial
then CTU will be able
to access the phone's records.
After dialing the number,
hit the star button twice.
The number is 310-597-3781.
Again, the number:
310-597-3781.
Once we get everything
off the SIM,
I'll let you know,
you can put the phone back.
All right, but hurry.
It won't be long before
he discovers it's missing.
He got the phone.
There's nothing else he can do.
Well, let's just
see what we get.
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Agent Samuels.
We've got the phone.
I'm piping a byte stream
to you now.
Work up every number you get.
All right, it's coming through.
What's it look like?
This data's encoded.
It looks like there's over
120 numbers or so.
I can't tell if they're
recently dialed or stored.
I'll untangle it
and get back to you
in a few minutes.
But you got
everything, right?
Yeah.
Walid did a great job
of getting that phone.
Then please let him go
before he gets hurt.
I'm going to tell you
one last time, Ms. Palmer--
these men know something
about the bombs
that we don't.
Walid has earned
their trust.
That's a situation
that we've lucked into.
And we will
not terminate it
as long as he can continue
to harvest information.
All right, Walid,
you can put the phone back.
Okay.
(phone rings)
Yeah, Chloe.
I don't think these guys
you're tracking are connected
to anyone.
What are you talking about?
They knew about
the other four bombs.
They found out
from a web page.
What?
The cell phone had
a browser on it.
The cache had a web page.
It wasn't public,
but they could've
connected in.
Was the Web site
password protected?
No. These pages
come and go.
But a lot of people
know about them.
These guys aren't terrorists--
they're just spectators.
Why didn't they report
the Web site?
Because you have them locked up
for having
terrorist links!
Why would they
give you information
that, in your eyes, would
incriminate them even further.
All right, thanks, Chloe.
I'm getting Walid
the hell out of there.
This is Agent Samuels.
Notify the guards.
We are taking
Walid Al-Rezani out.
I was at home with my
wife and my children,
and they barged right in
and the grabbed me.
No search warrant,
nothing.
And they say this country
is about freedom.
This is not freedom.
My phone.
It's gone.
What do you mean it's gone?
I just had it over there.
You... You took it.
No, I did not take your phone.
Yes, he did.
I was walking back here.
He fell in front of me.
Search him.
No, get away from me.
Open the gate.
Can't do that, ma'am.
I need to get in
there right now.
What are you doing?
You spied on us?
You're worse than they are!
You son of a bitch!
Heydar, no!
(shouting)
Let us in.
(clamoring)
Walid, Walid.
Oh, my God.
I'm okay.
Oh, no, no, you're not.
You're hurt.
I need a medical team
on site now.
I've got a civilian down.
--CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, we're here.
The parking lot's almost empty.
Yeah, the building's been
evacuated because of the bomb.
Does Jack want us in there?
No, hold your positions.
Keep an eye on all the
exits and entrances;
wait for my call.
All right. Standing by.
Which one's his office?
Last door on the right.
Let's go.
Take a seat.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for anything
in McCarthy's system
that connects him
to BXJ or the nukes.
What's that?
That's McCarthy's employment
contract with BXJ.
Whoa, whoa! What happened there?
Some kind of electronic
shredding trail.
Look at the time code.
Ten minutes after
the bomb went off,
McCarthy started
shredding files.
(door bangs)
(whispers):
Get up... now.
Come on, Jack!
Don't make a noise.
(light tap)
(louder tap)
Don't you move.
(grunts)
Stop.
You know him?
Yeah.
He's my son.
I'm surprised to see you
here, Jack.
We all feared
the worst.
Give me my gun back.
What are you doing here, Jack?
I'm working with CTU.
We're looking
for Darren McCarthy.
McCarthy's not here.
I know what you're trying
to cover up, Dad.
Gray already told me.
Did he? And where is he?
McCarthy's office.
There's nothing there, Jack,
believe me.
Get Graem in here.
Wait.
You'll need these.
I didn't trust him not to run.
I'm doing everything I can
to find McCarthy.
What in the hell
are you thinking,
trying to do this
on your own?
I only learned about it
yesterday.
When Graem told me
about the diverted weapons...
The second you knew
the bombs were missing,
why didn't you call
the authorities?
He told me that the bombs
couldn't be detonated;
the triggers were deactivated.
He was wrong.
Evidently!
Look, Jack,
I'm just trying
to keep my son
out of prison.
Dad, where is McCarthy?
I don't know.
When I do, we can
pick him up together.
That's not what he wants, Dad.
He wants us both in prison.
What I want
is to find the nukes.
If you're held accountable
for what you've done,
that's the bed you've made.
You hear that, Dad?
You hear that family love?
We'd be better off
if he was still rotting away
in a Chinese jail.
Who are you calling?
CTU.
Jack, look, work with me.
I'll tell you
what I know,
but for now,
keep Graem out of it.
We're talking about
prison, Jack.
He's your brother.
Graem knew what
he was doing was wrong.
He was responsible
for those nukes.
He should have been
more careful.
And the second he knew
they were stolen,
he should have reported it!
Oh, you always do what
you should, right, Jack?
How about when Dad needed you
and you disappeared?
Come on, Jack, give us a chance
to clean this up.
Dad, there are four more bombs
out there.
I cannot-- I will not--
be responsible
for thousands and thousands
of lives just
to try and protect
this family.
Wrong! Protecting family is
everything, and I think
your dead wife
would agree.
You son of a bitch!
Jack!
All right,
let's do it your way.
No, Dad!
No, no, no,
he's right.
Call CTU.
I don't think so.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Put the gun away.
You work for me.
No, Dad, he doesn't.
This is insane.
You don't think
I'd let you run loose
without keeping an eye
on you, do you?
Tell them to put the guns away.
Shut up, Dad.
Well, I'm glad we can
all finally put our cards
on the table.
Family. (scoffs)
Let's go.
Yeah, talk to me.
Yeah, so?
You think you can get him?
And he hasn't left town?
Okay, text me everything
you've got on him.
They're
looking for you
at your place.
What makes you think
they can't find you here?
A: Because I'm not that stupid,
and B: Because we're not going
to be here long enough
for anyone to know.
I really hope you know
what you're doing, Darren.
Always.
And when I'm done
with this deal,
I may just buy you
a small country.
As long as it's not
Palm Springs.
Everything's been handled.
We're clear to go.
Good. Let's move.
Good God.
What have you done?
Jack forced my hand.
Call me when it's over.
-=TLF SUB TEAM=-
http://tlfsub.eastgame.net
www.tvsubtitles.net