www.ydy.com
proudly presents
sync:xjeff0
www.ydy.com
24 Season 6 EP 7
Previously on 24
I need karen hayes to go away.
I understand,sir.
I need the president to sign off on my proposals.
She's gone from being an irritant to an obstacle.
I want to talk about your husband's incompetence,
and your covering it up.
I did nothing illegal or incorrect.
Your resignation within the hour.
Mr.President,I am tendering my resignation.
Is there anything I can do to change your mind?
No,sir,there is not.
Walid has earned their trust.
These men know something  about
the bombs that we don'T.
I don't think these guys you're tracking
are connected to anyone.
They're not terrorists.
I'm getting walid the hell out of there.
You spied on us?
You're worse than they are!
Son of a bitch!
a nuclear bomb just went off,like,
25  miles from here.
When I'm done with this deal,
I may just buy you a small country.
Have you found an engineer?
I told you I'd find someone and I will.
It's just taking longer.
start talking,gray!
I made a mess.
Dad's trying to clean it up.
What happened?
I hired mccarthy to oversee the job,but...
so the nukes that these terrorist
are in possession of,
including the one that was just
detonated in valencia,
was supplied by mccarthy and stolen from you.
Yes.
I'm heading to mccarthy's office in simi valley.
We have teams standing by.
Let me know.
Stop.
He's my son.
What are you doing here,jack?
Jack: I know what you're trying to cover up,dad.
Gray already told me.
Mccarthy's not here.
Hey,what are you doing?
Put the gun down!
You work for me.
No,dad,he doesn'T.
You don't think I'd let you run loose without
keeping an eye on you,do you?
This is insane.
********
I am at the edge of the safe zone.
Behind me is the nuclear blast.
Emergency medical teams are being
overwhelmed by the number of injured.
In what president palmer has confirmed was
a tactical nuclear weapon detonated
just a little over two hours ago
in this valencia neighborhood
north of los angeles,
more than 12,000 people are
estimated to have perished in the blast.
Lapd is spread thin,but on an encouraging note,
we've heard that they are receiving a flood...
I just heard about karen's resignation.
I'm sorry for the loss.
Are you really sorry,tom?
Because your words seemed somewhat hollow to me.
It's no secret karen and i butted
heads the last few weeks.
Nevertheless,I respected her as an adversary.
She never gave me a concrete
reason why she resigned,
but there was something...
something she wasn't telling me.
This may have something to do with it.
This is a draft of the executive order
I presented this morning.
Karen found out I was going to resubmit
it to you for your authorization.
And so she quit?
That makes absolutely no sense to me,tom.
She's never been afraid of a fight.
maybe she finally realized her
arguments are invalid and that
this is the only possible response
to the danger we're facing.
You want to tell me why I would sign off on
something that I rejected six hours ago?
Because,sir,six hours ago,
we didn't know fayed had nukes.
Even so,tom,you're talking
about suspending habeas corpus,
extending the length and broadening
the criteria for those detention centers.
Those actions will constitute a
brazen abuse of executive power.
Those actions will degrade fayed's network,
limiting his ability to make use of
these remaining nuclear weapons.
Sir,fayed's sole intention here is the
destruction of our country,
its infrastructure,social order,
entire way of life,and he's got the will
and means to make good on that threat.
Tom,have you stopped to think about the fact I
would be forcing the people who elected me
to give up the rights and freedoms that
define the essence of this country?
Sir,if one more nuke goes off,
it would have been fayed who's
redefined our country.
Pass this out to the cabinet.
We'll convene in 30 minutes.
You're doing the right thing,mr.President.
Reed.
Call the cabinet in for an emergency session.
Tell general white we're ramping up.
Does that mean the president
is signing off on this?
He wouldn't convene the cabinet unless he was.
Good work,reed.
Well,I'm just doing what needs to be done,sir.
Getting rid of karen is distinctly unpleasant,
but she left us no choicE.
hayes.
Girl,I'm sorry I'm late with the briefing.
Tell the president we're still tracking
fayed through mccarthy.
Bill,I've just had to resign.
Resign?What are you talking about?
Can't get into it right now,
but I've asked to be reassigned to
cut as an on-site liaison.
Karen,you can't leave the
president today, of all days.
Bill,do you think that I would do
this if I had any other choice?
Lennox has something to do with this,doesn't he?
I cannot talk about this right now.
I will see you in a few hours.Okay?
Karen?
mr.Buchanan.
What is it,chloe?
I've been trying to reach jack on his cell phone;
he's not answering.
Try his backup teams.
I tried; they're not answering either.
Maybe he had them all go dark.
He wouldn't do that without telling us first.
Send in the support units,see
if they can get a visual.
All right.
And keep trying jack.
******
So after we're done,where do
you want us to meet you?
I'll be here another hour dumping hard drives.
We'll meet you back at the house,then.
Just make sure it goes exactly according to plan.
Don't worry.
It's my job to worry.
it was all for you,jack.
Everything I worked for,everything I built--
it was all for you.
After you left,I tried to convince myself that
graem was capable of heading the family...
protecting the company
I guess,
on some level,I always knew the truth about him.
I just wasn't willing to admit it to myself.
I don't know what you want me to say.
I want you to understand that
after you left,graem was all I had.
I pushed you away,didn't I?
I'm really sorry.
get out.
Come on.
Don't do this,sir.
Whatever graem's paying you,I'll double it.
Just keep it moving.
Get down on your knees,both of you.
No.
You son of a bitch.
At least have the guts to look me in the eye.
I needed to question him.
They were gonna kill us,jack.
Search his pockets for the keys.
Damn it!
*****
Bill,it's jack.
Jack,we haven't been able to reach you.
Are you all right?
Yeah,I'm fine,but all the members of
the backup team have been killed.
Have you found mccarthy?
Not yet,but I know how to get to hiM.
How?
My brother.
You said your brother wasn't involved
when mccarthy brokered the nukes.
He lied to mE.
He didn't tell us everything.
Based on what?
He just tried to have me and my father killed.
Bill,I need you to set up a perimeter
around his house.
I'll send a field team right away.
Have them do an immediate recon,
confirm that he's there.
I want burke standing by with
an interrogation kit.
Jack.
What?
As it stands now,mccarthy is
our only lead to fayed.
We need to find fayed before he arms the nukes.
I'll get back to you as soon as I make
contact with the field team.
We need to go.
rita.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm hungry.
There's a candy machine in the lobby.
Don't worry.We'll be leaving soon.
You said that an our ago.
Sit down,rita.
Yes?
Good news.
I found someone to program the
trigger codes for your bombs.
Who?
I've just you sent his profile,
employment record,education,
the whole curriculum vitae.
You should have it on your screen.
I'm looking at it now.
He seems qualified.
Oh,he'll get the job done,
but he won't work willingly.
He'll need to be coerced.
Okay,when will you have him?
Within the hour.
Call me when you do.
mr.Buchanan,
you need to listen to this.
What?
Nsa intercepted a stream of chatter--
part of it's an audio recording.
They've identified one of the voices
as belonging to fayed.
Let's hear it.
Good news.
I found someone to program
the trigger codes on your bombs.
Who?
I've just sent you his profile,
employment record,education,
the whole curriculum vitae.
It should be on your screen.
I'm looking at it now.
He seems qualified.
he'll get the job done,
but he won't work willingly.
He'll need to be coerced.
Okay,when will you have him?
Within the hour.
Call me when you do.
Second voice matches the sample
we pulled off mccarthy's voice-mail.
They lost numair in the explosion,
so mccarthy found someone else to arm the nukes.
Send the file to audio forensics.
Have them scan for any background
artifacts that could give us a location.
Yes,sir.
I had morris working on something,too.
We also found an image file
inside the data stream.
Nsa thinks it might be a photo of the engineer.
Is this it?
Yeah,it got all corrupted during the intercept.
I'm writing a salvage utility.
I should have a new code in a second.
Getting an image of the engineer may be our
only way of stopping those nukes.
Give me an estimate.
Well,that's hard to say.
Could be ten minutes,it could be an hour.
********
Who's the agent in charge?
My name is jack bauer.
Mr.Bauer,I'm hal turner.
I'll be on point.
Are your men in position?
Yes,sir.
We've sealed off a one-block radius,
and our recon has confirmed
your brother's inside--
his wife and son are in there as well.
I want you to inform your team
to use nonlethal force.
We need to take my brother alive.
Understood.
Let me go in with you.
No.
You wait here.
I need to question graem alone.
What are you gonna do to him?
Whatever it takes to find out what he knows.
I'm not stupid,graem--
I know something is wrong.
Everything's fine,marilyn.
You're a lousy liar.
You always have been.
You know,if you insist on being here,
why don't you make some coffee?
Why don't you make your own coffee!
Will you two stop fighting?
That's all you guys ever do is fight.
I'm sorry,honey.
We're just all a little tense today.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Nothing.Why don't,
why don't we leave your father alone.
He needs to work.
put the weapon down!
Drop the gun!
What the hell is this,jack?!
Put it down!
Do it.
Get on the floor!
Take it easy,jack!
I want you take him into the next room,
have burke prep him for questioning.
I want every hard drive,
every memory stick in this house
uploaded and sent over to ctu.
Pick him up.
Go.Go.
What are you doing to my dad?
Josh,I'll explain as soon as I can,
but right now I need to speak to your mother.
Please,just take a seat.
Please,son,come on.
Let's go.
Let go of me!
stop looking at me like this has
something to do with us,
because it doesn'T.
Graem just tried to have me and our father killed.
Why?
Why would he try and kill you?
They nuclear bomb that was
detonated earlier today--
the terrorists acquired it
from the family's company!
Gray's been trying to cover it up.
I'm sorry,marilyn.
I understand how difficult this
must be for you to believe.
It's not.
I may not know the details of what he's done,
but I know what he's capable of.
There are four more other bombs out there.
We need to get them back--
is there anything that you can tell me?
Like what?
Did gray talk about a man named mccarthy?
No.
Are you sure?
He hasn't confided in me in years.
He probably never did.
Marilyn,thousands of lives are at stake.
Please,just think.
I wish I knew something,I really wish I did,
but I don't know anything.
And josh doesn't know anything,either,
and he doesn't need to know.
I'll do everything I can to protect him.
No!
I've seen what happens when
you try and protect people.
I just want to get my son,
and I want to get out of here!
Marilyn...
sir,we found two computers,
both linked to one network.
He was trying to erase files--
we're sending what's left over to ctu.
Okay,good.
My sister-in-law and my nephew
don't need to stay here.
Have them transported back to ctu.
They can be debriefed there.
Yes,sir.
Mrs.Bauer.
We're taking you and your son back to ctu.
Josh?
Grandpa.
You okay?
Not really.
Wait in the car,baby.
Jack told me what graem did,
what he was involved with.
Is it true?
It's complicated.
But it's true.
You make sure he keeps josh out of this.
I panicked,jack.
That's all there is to it.
You panicked?
That's your excuse?
You panicked?!
You tried to kill me and our father.
I was backed into a corner.
I was just protecting my ass.
You knew about a tactical nuclear
weapon on american soil.
You are responsible for the death of
thousands and thousands of people.
You think I really wanted
that bomb to go off,jack?
I think you knew more about
mccarthy than you told me.
How do i find him?
I don't have a clue.
How do i find him?!
I just told you I don't know.
There are four more bombs out there.
This isn't a joke,gray.
Tell me now,how do I find mccarthy?
I told you everything I know,jack.
respiration and temperature patterns indicate
deception,especially his last reply.
Set up the interrogation package.
You don't want to make me do this,gray.
We grew up together,jack.
In all those years,I could never make you
do anything you didn't want to do.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
Over here.
It's morris's brother.
Timothy?
He's on his way to horizon regional hospital.
On-site paramedics confirmed he
has severe radiation exposure.
It says he's in critical condition.
I'll tell him.
Wait,chloe.
I think we should hold off.
Why?
Morris is the best hope we have
for restoring that file.
If we drop this on him now,
he might completely shut down.
It's his brother-- we can't keep it a secret.
I understand.
This might sound insensitive,but for a second,
put aside your personal feelings for
morris and consider what's at stake.
We need him to finish
writing that salvage utility.
I know morris; he can handle it.
I hope so.
Morris?
Yes,darling?
I have some bad news.
It's about timothy--
he's been taken to the hospital.
I'm sorry.
Well,this can't be right--
it says he was pulled...
from his car by rescue workers
just north of valencia.
Operator.
Yes,could you connect me with horizon
regional hospital,please?
-******* -What was he doing in valencia?
I'm sorry,sir,all circuits are busy.
Yes,I realize that the lines are busy--
this is ctu,los angeles,calling--
I need an emergency breakthrough.
- I cannot help you at this time,sir.
- I know...
Sorry.
I-I have to go out there.
Morris,hey,
I know it's hard,okay?
But we are in the middle of a crisis.
We need to find the engineer before fayed does.
You can't just leave.
You can't expect me to sit there when my
little brother is dying in the hospital.
I'm sorry,milo.
Morris...
listen.
12,000 people are dead.
If fayed finds an engineer,
it'll be many,many more.
Four bombs is about a million people.
Think about this.
You can finish writing the program--
you can do it.
Yes,I can-- but you started already.
It will take me half an hour to
figure out what you've done.
You need to stay here and do your job.
Please.
Okay.
Thanks.
Buchanan.
Bill,it's jack.
Did chloe pull anything off the hard drives?
No,she came up empty.
But 15 minutes ago,the nsa picked up a
conversation between mccarthy and fayed.
*******Mccarthy's found another engineer
to arm the four remaining nukes.
He's delivering the engineer within the hour.
The nukes could be operational within 45 minutes?
That's right.
I'll get back to you.
Ctu just confirmed that mccarthy is
looking for an engineer for fayed.
They're gonna arm the nukes.
Then you're wasting time talking to me,jack.
You're holding something back.
That machine doesn't lie.
Then it must be broken because
I've told you everything I know.
That's hyocine-pentothal.
It's a neuro-inflamatory,designed to induce pain.
All you have to do to stop me from
using it is tell me how to find mccarthy.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Two cc'S.
come on,come on.
I can take this to seven cc'S.
You will experience pain I can't even describe.
At eight cc's,I run the risk of
inducing a heart attack.
Gray...
make no mistake about it,
I will go there if I have to.
Please,just tell me what I need to know.
Please.
I don't want to hurt you.
You sure about that,jack?
Please,gray,just tell me what I need to know.
How do I find mccarthy?!
Do it.
Two cc'S.
breathe.
Just breathe.
Please...
just tell me what I need to know.
How do I find mccarthy?!
Damn you.
Four cc'S.
That's eight cc's total,jack.
His vitals are spiking across the line.
Four cc's!
Jack,don'T.
The machine knows you're lying!
I know you're lying!
Tell me the truth!
it has nothing to do with mccarthy.
it has to do with palmer.
David palmer?
Yes.
I gave the order for his assassination.
And agent tony almeida...
and agent michelle dessler--
your co-workers--
they're all dead because of me.
I arranged everything.
I set the timetable,
I paid off the killers,
I even lured you out of hiding to take the fall.
Today wasn't the first time
I tried to have you killed,jack.
Why?
Because I love my country!
And in the real world,
sometimes that means you have
to do things,terrible things...
even unforgivable things,
for the sake of your country.
But you know all about that,don't you,brother?
We're the same.
I mean,look at me.
We're the same!
We are not the same!
You want me to kill you?!
Do it!
I'm gonna do it my way!
Four more cc'S.
I can't do that.
Pick up the syringe!
Do it!
Now!
Son of a bitch!
-******** -Get me somebody in here now.
You want to die?
Drop your weapon!
Drop it!
You're gonna die.
Shut down the iv.
Shut it down.
I'm here,baby.
I'm ashamed.
What do you mean you're ashamed?
For spying on those men.
I thought I was doing the right thing.
I was wrong.
You did the only thing that you could do...
okay,and that was the right thing.
you're the bravest,most principled
man I've ever known.
you get some rest,okay?
hello?
Sandra?
It's wayne.
I just heard what happened to walid.
I am so sorry.
Is he going to be all right?
Yeah,I think so.
What they told me is confusing.
They said walid was working undercover
to expose some plot.
There was no plot.
The men weren't part of any conspiracy.
They were just bystanders.
They tell me these men had information
about the nuclear weapons.
One of the men pulled it from the internet
and showed it to his friends.
Sandra,they should've reported that.
They were afraid they were going to get into
more trouble than they're already in.
Most of these men were pulled from their jobs and
their homes on trumped-up immigration charges.
And now they're facing deportation.
Wayne,you are detaining without due process
the people whose help you need the most.
How do you expect for them to help
if they don't have any legal protection?
Wayne...
I'm scared.
I know.
Everything's gonna be all right.
What's the status?
Program's finished.
I just ran it,but this is all we got.
I still don't have a clear image.
what are you doing?
I'm downloading an unlicensed
application from a hacker's site.
It might kick-start things.
Or it could corrupt the file.
I know these guys.
They write really good code when
they're not serving time.
Unbelievable.
That's what graem was holding back?
Not only was he responsible for
david palmer's assassination,
but he directed the entire conspiracy.
He was trying to protect the company.
That's what he's trying to do now.
Incredible.
I wish it got us closer to
the nukes,but it doesn'T.
He doesn't know where mccarthy is.
Were you able to pick up anything on nsa chatter?
We think it may contain an
image of mccarthy's engineer.
How long till you know for sure?
Can't say.The file's badly corrupted.
Morris is working on it now.
As soon as my brother's ready for transport,
I want him sent back to ctu
for further debriefing.
I've redirected a chopper to jackson
middle school,
four miles west of your position.
Thanks,bill.
Dad,graem made his own choices after
you let him start running the company.
You can't make yourself responsible for that.
That's not fair.
I'll tell you what isn't fair.
You deserved a better family,jack.
Not this.
Not us.
I can just imagine what you must be feeling.
All that time we lost...
what I wouldn't give to have some of it back.
Me,too.
Agent bauer.
Yeah.
Your brother's been stabilized.
He'll be ready to move in ten minutes.
Thank you.
Dad,i want you to go back to ctu.
Okay.
I need a few minutes.
Of coursE.
They're sending a chopper for me.
I have to go.
there.
What?
The plug-in's working.
How long's it going to take?
It's restoring.
You'll have a photo of the
engineer in two minutes.
Just don't touch anything.
Now I have got to go and find out
what's happening with my brother.
Save it,milo.
Thanks for trying to help.
I'm leaving.
Watch my station,okay?
Be careful.
Call me when you find anything out about timothy.
I will.
Congratulations,tom.
It's an excellent plan.
Well,thank you very much,mr.Vice president.
It's about time someone in this administration
stood up to these people.
To be honest,
I didn't think this president had
the stomach for the cure.
I think we're about ready for kickoff here,sir.
I'm going to put you on speakerphone.
Is the vice president with us?
I'm on the plane,sir.
I'm assuming everyone here has
read executive order 1066?
Tom first proposed his plan to me very
early this morning,and I rejected it.
Sacrificing the rights and freedoms guaranteed
by the constitution seemed like,
like too steep a price,
even for the promise of securitY.
But then fayed murdered 12,000
innocent americans with a nuclear weapon.
I felt compelled to revisit my earlier position.
After careful reconsideration,
I remain convinced that my initial
response was in fact the right one.
That implementing this plan--
would be a terrible mistake.
I cannot and I will not endorse these actions.
Some of you actually seem to feel
that the constitution is somehow
valid only during times of peace,
but not during wartime.
That is not what the founders intended.
With your indulgence,sir,
george washington's enemies wore bright
red coats and marched in a straight line.
The founders could have never
conceived of a stateless enemy,
hiding among us,that targets not our soldiers,
but our civilization.
Your plan would only hinder the efforts
of law enforcement to stop fayed.
How does my plan hinder law enforcement,sir?
By marginalizing and thereby radicalizing the
very people whose help they need to enlist.
The american muslim community is our best
line of defense against these terrorists.
But we americans need to demonstrate that
we are governed by the rule of law and never,
never by the politics of fear.
Mr.President.
Yes,noah?
Before you make any unilateral decisions,
maybe you should hear some
other people's thoughts.
I'm sorry,noah.
The discussion on this matter...
is over.
This better work.
Jack's on his way back to ctu.
I want holding "a" and "b" prepped
for interrogation
and put together a clearance package
for him,no restrictions.
Yes,sir.
We have it yet?
It's gonna be a few more seconds.
As soon as we I.D.The engineer,
I want it posted on the interagency subnet.
We need all eyes possible on this.
Yes,sir.
Oh,my god!
It's morris!
It's his cv,personal history,everything.
Where is he?
On his way to horizon regional hospital.
We got to call that.
His brother was hurt in the blast.
He just left.
Security.
This is bill bhanan.
Has morris o'brian left the parking lot?
He just drove out,sir.
Damn it!
Milo,contact lapd.
Put an apb out on his car.
Chloe,see if you can raise him on his cell phone.
Bauer.
Jack,we just id'ed the engineer.
It's morris o'brian.
Morris?
Yes.
The file we intercepted was morris's photo and cv.
Mccarthy was sending it to fayed.
There is no doubt morris is the engineer.
Fine.Put him under a protective watch.
We can'T.
He's gone.
He got a call claiming his brother
was in the hospital.
He just left.
We're trying to raise him on his cell.
Morris,hold on.
He's on line one.
We got him,jack.
Patch me through.
Morris,it's bill buchanan.
We're on the line with jack bauer.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to the hospital.
You need to come back to ctu immediately.
I can't do that.
Morris,this is jack.
Listen to me.
There is nothing wrong with your brother.
It's a setup.
The engineer mccarthy's looking for,it's you.
Me?
It was your photo mccarthy was sending to fayed.
Morris,you need to turn the car around now.
Okay,okay.
Morris!
Get out of the car or the next one's in your head!
What the bloody hell do you want?
Don't talk,move!
Come on.Let's go.
Jack,they got him!
It sounds like they're transferring
him to another vehicle.
Chloe,bring up a satellite feed
five-mile radius of ctu.
Hurry.
Drive.
yes?
We're on our way.
How soon can you be here?
15 minutes.
We'll be waiting.
With my money.
You'll get paid as soon as I have what I want.
Let me be clear.
I'm just delivering him.
You'll have to make him cooperate.
He'll cooperate.
Agent burke,
I'd like to speak to my son.
All right.
Five minutes.
Thanks.
How am I doing?
You're doing great.
Everyone thinks jack is so tough.
Maybe he is...
but so am I.
It's nice to know that I can take
anything he can dish out.
You told him about palmer.
I had to give him something to
make him think I cracked,
but I kept you out of it.
It's gonna get a lot worse.
He's not finished.
He knows you didn't tell him everything.
And I won'T.You know I won't,dad.
They're going to take you to ctu.
They'll do things there that'll make
this seem like a cakewalk.
Well,like i said,
I can take it.
I'd like to believe that.
The problem is,I have to be sure.
Well,you can be.
I'll hold my mud,dad.
Everything's going exactly according to plan.
Jack bought the ruse.
Oh,I know.
I'm sure we convinced him that you were
going to have me killed as well.
Yeah,
that makes me the bad guy and you the good guy.
I take the rap,do some time,you skate free.
Get me out when you can.
Meanwhile,the company lives on.
Dad,stick to the plan.
That's what you've always said,right?
Make a plan.
Stick to it.
Sometimes you have to make adjustments.
I would never betray you,dad.
I love you.
I love you,too,graem.
You've been a good boy.
Done everything I asked.
Only this time,I asked too much.
Sorry.
Dad...
my son's had a seizure!
Get in here now!
Hurry up!
What happened?
Is he going to make it?
I don't know. Please,give us the
room so we can work.
Get ctu medical now!
My god,
if you people killed my son,I swear...
you're gonna regret it for the rest of your life.
24 Season 6 EP 7
-=end=-
sync:xjeff0
www.ydy.com
proudly presents
www.tvsubtitles.net