Well, hello, Hank.
So good of you to come up.
Well,
I'm not gonna miss
the America's Kidz
got singing finale.
Last time I was this excited
was this morning.
I saw a cat wearing
the same sweater as its person.
[Laughs]
Jack, you remember
my granddaughter.
Oh, hi, Mr. Donaghy.
Kaylie.
There's Jenna Marone.
So, Jack, how's your wife?
Still kidnapped?
How's the yearbook going?
I heard you made editor...
Of the photo captions.
[Giggles]
Hey, Pop-Pop, wait up.
[Mocking]
I'm so excited
for the finale.
Not that it matters,
even if Brock doesn't win,
he is going to get
a record contract.
So, it definitely
doesn't matter.
This isn't the last
we will be seeing of Brock.
Well, whoever wins, it's
a great night for the industry.
Kidz is a hit the whole family
can watch together,
not your usual sitcom crap
full of gratuitous vulgarity
and pratfalls.
Wah! Oh!
Oh, my penis!
Jenna,
this is a big night.
And I've got
something big planned.
Tonight during
the finalists' duet,
I'm gonna cry.
Now, of course, none of these
little condom accidents
could actually make me cry,
so I'm gonna rub this
under my eyes
to help me fake it.
It's an old acting trick
I learned
from Glenn Beck's
prostitute.
Well,
mark my words, Jenna,
tonight is going to
be the greatest.
Disaster
in the history of television.
The young contestants apparently
inebriated on live TV.
♪ Oh, Shushanna...
I gotta throw up.
[Vomits]
What happened?
Why haven't you been
returning my calls?
Because my phone
melted last night, Lemon.
Come here, Jack.
Mm...
That was my angriest hug, 'cause
that's how I feel right now.
Instead of heading
back to Philadelphia,
I'm going down
to deal with the FCC.
The Federal
Clown Commission.
I hope that comes off
as respectful.
My father was a clown,
and I know how hard
those men work.
I'm going to
get to the bottom
of what happened
last night, sir.
I've already detained Brock
and Ava under the patriot act.
People have forgotten
about that thing,
but any white male
can arrest any other person.
[Knocks]
Hello, peers.
Sure has been
a busy morning
down in
the Standards department.
Because of last night's
cluster-whoops,
Darren was fired.
Then he threatened
to come back with a gun.
Then I got a promotion,
and the desk
closest to the door.
Here are my new
business cards.
Late night programming?
So you're covering TGS now?
And a wonderful
new show from D.L. Hughley
that's already
been canceled!
I feel like
Oscar the grouch today,
and not just
'cause I woke up
in a garbage can
this morning,
startling someone
named Gordon.
What's wrong, Tracy?
I can't eat
for 24 hours
'cause I have
a colonoscopy tomorrow.
I'm starving!
You know, fasting
can actually clear your mind.
In college, I once
went on a hunger strike
- to protest apartheid...
- Oh.
You're the one who solved that?
Thank you so much.
1997 Heather Locklear,
what are you doing here?
What? Jenna!
Save it, Liz.
Yes, I was disappointed that
I didn't get to do my fake cry,
but I do have a plan B.
The whole point of the cry
was to humanize me,
to change
public perception,
but what else
humanizes a monster?
Motherhood.
Oh, God. Don't adopt.
That child
is better off in Somalia.
It could be a pirate,
or a warlord's concubine.
This is better
than adopting.
Remember my little moneymaking
scheme back in Chicago?
Cashing your dead aunt's
social security checks?
Oh, no,
I'm still doing that.
I'm talking about
when I donated my eggs.
So, a couple of months ago,
I called
the calumet city egg donation
center and house of blues
to see if there were
any little Jennas out there
who wanted to meet me.
Hang on, are you saying
you have a kid?
No, I don't.
Oh.
I have six kids.
Jerome, share the bronzer,
you slut.
[Scoffs]
Dear God.
[Exciting jazz music]
♪
30 ROCK
S06 Ep 11 - Standards and Practices
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
I'm a very
powerful man, Brock.
Little league tryouts
are coming soon.
How would you like
to wind up on a team with...
None of your friends?
It was her idea!
She made me do it!
Brock just
sold you out, Ava.
[Snaps]
What are you
doing to Molly?
She already had to
live through world war ii.
Brock said it was
all your idea.
No, it was her idea.
She's just so cool.
Like a human silly band!
Who?
Who's a human silly band?
I'm tall enough now
that there isn't
a roller coaster in the world
I can't go on.
- Wow.
- So...
You guys drink beer.
Or are you babies?
[Opens can]
Jack versus Kaylie,
round two,
colon...
No subtitle necessary.
[Door opens]
Mommy announcement.
I hope we're all waxed,
because you're coming with me
to my interview tonight
for Barbara Walters'
10 most overexposed people.
Oh! Barbara Walters!
[Excited chattering]
Okay, so, let me just quickly
identify everyone's good sides.
Left, left, right,
right, left...
Oh, Judy. That's not really
on message.
Look, I didn't
call the donation center
to be on TV, Jenna.
I wanted to go get a cup
of coffee and get to know you.
If you want
to get to know me,
read my 2006 interview
in AmTrak magazine.
If you want to be my daughter,
put on this wig and smile.
Oh, there you are, liierz.
[Gurgles]
Boy, I am still not comfortable
calling you by your first name.
Then again,
you've never been comfortable
calling me by my
full Christian name.
Kenneth.
Oh, no, "Kenneth" is short
for andromakennethamblesorton.
- So, what's up?
- Oh.
Wait, what is this?
"Additional restrictions
to broadcast standards"?
Yes.
People are pretty upset
about last night.
How can we do "Fart doctor"
without the word "fart"?
I'm surprised
they allow you to say "doctor."
It's so close to "gynecologist"
which is disgusting.
Have you seen this memo
from Standards?
Kenneth is being a real...
dingbat,
which is now the harshest word
we are allowed to say.
Oh, you can blame that
on Kaylie Hooper.
She's the one
who ruined the Kidz finale.
Really? What a... dingbat.
Why didn't
I see this coming?
I knew this company
was making me lose my edge.
That's why I hired a Cato
to attack me at random.
Like inspector clouseau.
Cato?
Don't attack me
tonight, okay?
I know I told you that
when I say, "don't attack me,"
that's when I most
need you to attack me,
but I'm serious.
Cato?
Aah!
Excellent, Cato,
excellent!
Did Kaylie really think
I wouldn't figure this out?
No, she knew I would.
So, she's going to
be ready for me.
Good.
I like a fair fight.
Okay, she is
just a teenage girl.
Lemon, you know very well
that a Nemesis can be anyone...
Or anything.
[Sighs]
Autocorrect.
I was trying to say
"pen organizer."
Oh, God!
You're a winter!
I don't know
what that means.
Why are there only six chairs
out there? There's seven of us.
Oh, no. One of us will
have to sit out the interview.
I'm just gonna choose at random
who it's gonna be.
Eenie-meenie-miney-moe,
out goes ♪ y-o-u
- I'm sorry, Judy.
- Bye, Judy.
All: [Condescending good-byes]
Could've just gotten
another chair.
[Knocks on door]
Who is it?
Sweetie, it's Pop-Pop.
I came back from D.C. early,
and I lost my darn key.
[Chuckles]
What a world.
Surprise.
[Deniro impression]
I'm very good at voices, Kaylie.
I'm very good.
I know what you did.
And you had to assume
I'd break Brock and Ava,
so, you're ready for this,
but here's what
you weren't counting on...
This has nothing
to do with you!
I just had to get
Pop-Pop out of town
because I am
in so much trouble!
Henry and his friends had to go
to the King of Prussia mall
last Thursday night
'cause it was a half day,
and I couldn't go
'cause I had piano,
and my friend Vickie,
well,
she said she got grounded
'cause she went
to some highlighter party
with Dylan
while his parents
were out of town.
Whoa, okay, hang on.
Calm down.
And then fat Vickie
saw her there,
so I called her,
and Henry answered her phone
because he had
Vickie's phone!
Wait, which Vickie?
Fat Vickie?
Vickie P.
Are you even listening to me?
- Okay.
- God!
Vickie used to be
my best friend.
I had her youface password,
so I logged onto her account,
and posted
all these photos
with "I am a slut"
written on her forehead,
and then school found out,
so now my life is over!
Please!
What does this have to do
with sabotaging me?
This has nothing
to do with you!
I messed up the show
to make sure
Pop-Pop wouldn't come back
to Philadelphia with me,
'cause Dr. Melvoin is trying
to kick me out of school,
and if Pop-Pop comes
to the teacher conference,
well, then,
he'll let them expel me,
and I'll have to go to some
school in the middle of nowhere,
and then I might as well
be dead!
Wait, where are
your parents?
Who knows?
My mom is in Indonesia
visiting her charity
where poor children
make shoes.
Isn't that
just a sweat shop?
I know!
And then my dad put
a Porsche engine in a model T
and drove it to Mardi Gras!
I know what it's like
not to have your parents around.
I once took
a log with googly eyes
to a father-son picnic.
But, uh,
who's going to take you
to this parent-teacher
conference?
I don't know.
I have nobody!
I wanna die!
[Screams]
Do you have a second,
Kenneth?
No, there's only one of me.
What? What are you asking?
Look, we have
a show tonight.
You can't just take away
all these words
we've been using
for the past six years.
Oh, that reminds me.
You can't say "using" on TV.
It implies drug use.
We're saying
whatever we want.
No, you can't.
That's an order.
I stole that speech
from an episode JAG,
but it applies here.
Are you kidding me?
Last week you were a page,
now you're telling me
how to run my show?
Well, I am arguing
back at you.
I have enough crap to deal
with around here, Kenneth...
I'm interrupting you
'cause I'm good at arguing!
I don't need you
to make my life worse.
I am responding,
I am matching your tone,
and making my own point.
You know what, Kenneth?
Fine. You win.
But as we saw
the other night on Kidz,
anything can happen
on live TV.
- Right, Tracy?
- What?
I'm just saying, Tray,
you're very unpredictable.
And we'll write
clean sketches,
but you might
just do your stand-up act.
- Who knows?
- Okay.
I'm still fasting
because I misread my calendar.
Tomorrow
is my colonoscopy.
Today was my meeting
with Colin o'Scopy.
Therefore, I have no idea
what you're saying,
talking Turkey leg.
Were you
a difficult teenager?
Well, I was voted
head of the PTA, so no.
I'm accustomed to dealing
with difficult people, Lemon,
but teenage girls, ugh...
Are a puzzle.
Oh, yes, how was your meeting
with your Nemesis?
I volunteered
to accompany Kaylie
to a parent-teacher conference
at her school.
- What? Why?
- It's complicated.
The point is, and I never
thought I'd say this,
I actually feel badly
for Kaylie.
On the other hand,
I know full well
that this is
an opportunity to destroy her.
I could get her expelled,
sent off to some
second-rate boarding school,
then on to that last bastion
of the incompetent rich,
USC.
I don't know, Jack,
you should stay out of this.
No, I could
help this girl.
Or destroy this monster.
If I could just tell whether
she's vicious or vulnerable.
That's the problem.
She's a teenage girl.
She's vicious
and vulnerable.
She might be
completely lying,
like when I was 15
and told everyone at my school
that I'd already
gotten my period,
or she could be
in real trouble,
like when I was 17,
and finally got my period
at a very loosely supervised
petting zoo.
Once again, Lemon,
I leave your office
more confused
than when I entered,
but having glimpsed yet another
tile in the rich mosaic
that is your
menstrual history.
So bravo wants to do
a reality show about us,
and I thought
the opening credits
could be all of us
in a giant dog bed,
and you guys are suckling
on prosthetic dog teats
that I'm wearing.
Actually,
we had a different idea.
Now that Judy's gone,
it's kind of obvious
someone is the odd person out.
It's Jerome, right?
I didn't want
to say anything
'cause I was trying
to be a good mother,
but you're cheesy,
and everyone hates you.
No, Jenna, you.
You're so much older
than the rest of us,
so we're thinking
the show is more like
The girls next door,
and you're that old boat captain
that shows up sometimes.
That's Hugh Hefner,
Jessica.
Yeah, we have no idea
who that is,
so you're kind of
just proving our point.
I see.
Very well.
Looking for this?
Well played.
Oh...
[Sighs]
[Crying]
Dude, what's up?
I'm just having
a bad day, sir.
All right, bro-bro,
let's just be cool,
and sit down and pee in silence,
like dudes do.
It's just...
I started a new job,
and it's stressful enough
just having my own wastebasket
that I have to fill every day
without Liz Lemon
yelling at me,
and I just wish
I had never been born!
[Heaves]
'Cause if I can't even
get my friend Liz...
At least I thought
she was my friend...
To respect me,
how will I ever run a network
and boss around
those Jewish executives
that were trained
from birth to argue?
So, I should just
give Liz what she wants,
and quit.
[Sobbing]
Bro...
You should just smack
that Liz in the mouth.
Sorry I babbled
so much.
Thanks for listening.
I'm Kenneth, by the way.
Me too. I'm Kenneth.
Kenneth... uh...
Toilethole.
I'm so sorry Dr. Melvoin.
You know, I already apologized
to Vickie, and to fat Vickie.
Fat Vickie's parents
were very upset
that she was dragged
into this mess.
I know.
I know what I did was stupid,
and I've really learned
my lesson.
Look, if I could
go back in time,
I'd just...
I'd skip clarinet,
and I'd go to the spring
football with my friends,
and none of this
ever would've happened.
Or you simply could have
not posted those pictures.
On hot Vickie's
youface page, miss Hooper.
Uh, hold on, Melvoin.
You told me
it was the piano,
and that everyone went
to the King of Prussia mall.
Well...
I don't remember.
And I'm just
so emotional right now.
[Sniffs]
Ha!
I'm sorry, how are you
related to miss Hooper?
I'm her Nemesis.
You bastard.
Don't do this, Donaghy.
I think that this school
has done everything it can
for Kaylie,
but the only fitting
punishment...
Is expulsion.
It's days like this
that remind me
why I got into teaching
in the first place.
Kenneth,
we need to talk.
I don't know,
'cause someone
who actually cares
about my feelings
told me to smack you
in the mouth.
No, don't listen
to Kenneth Toilethole.
- You know him?
- Yeah. He's great.
We should all go
get dinner sometime.
Kenneth,
you can do this job,
and I do respect you.
Then wash my feet
with your hair.
No! But I did completely
rewrite the show.
We're not even using
the word "dingbat," Mr. Parcell.
A Parcell man
has never been called "mister"
outside of
an execution chamber.
Oh, boy.
[Crying]
The blonde ones,
they turned on me.
They threw me away like
I was some kind of Judy.
Oh, God.
Is this how Judy felt?
Judy was nice and sweet
and wanted to get
a coffee enema or something,
and I treated her
like garbage.
Well, then why don't you
apologize to her?
She's right behind you.
Oh.
Judy,
you're so beautiful now!
Oh.
I just came to say good-bye
before I head home.
I wish we had spent
more time together,
but I guess I'll see you
on TV.
No.
Of all my children,
you're the only one
that proves
there's any good in me.
Forget TV.
Let's go get
that coffee now.
No. You know
you can't do that.
One minute to air.
One minute.
I have to stop Jenna
from leaving. You just...
No problem.
I'll cover.
Day two of my fast,
and you were right.
My mind is clear,
and I'm sharp as a tack.
Great, Tray, thanks.
My brain is working
overtime.
I finally understand the ending
of The sixth sense.
Those names are the people
who worked on the movie.
Oh, yeah, and I just got
what you were trying
to tell me yesterday.
You want me to do
my filthy stand-up act
instead of reading
the cue cards.
No.
Jack! Help!
I was right about Kaylie,
and I crushed her.
That's great.
I need...
The whole time,
she was playing me,
but in the end, she made
the biggest mistake.
She could not have been worse
in that meeting
than if she had
wanted me to...
Son of a dingbat!
Tracy's gonna do
his stand-up act on the show!
What are we gonna do?
I'm gonna live bleep him.
Normally, I'd have to get
permission from Irene first,
but there isn't time.
You know why I love
Dominican women?
'Cause they love to [Bleep]
those big [Bleep] [Bleep]
'Cause they eat all our
[Bleep] aloud.
I'd like to introduce [Bleep]
housed in a [Bleep]
[Bleep], booooy!
You just ate a [Bleep]
with extra [Bleep]?
Well, you called
the right [Bleep].
That's our show
for tonight!
See you next week!
[Cheers and applause]
- That was amazing!
- It sure was.
Kenneth,
I'm Gaylord Felcher.
The head of Standards?
I have never seen
bleeping like that,
so guess what?
I'm [Bleep] promoting you,
you little [Bleep]-face.
All right, Felcher, you don't
have to talk like that.
Well, who's gonna stop me?
Who among you has the power
to censor the censor?
What a surprise.
Whatever are you doing here,
Kaylie Hooper?
Enjoying my total lack
of adult supervision.
I just had fruit roll-ups
for dinner...
At a strip club.
[Sighs]
Do you wanted to get expelled
from school, didn't you?
Look who figured it out.
It only took you,
oh, I don't know,
a million hours.
You didn't lie to me
about getting sent to school
in the "Middle of nowhere."
What I realized too late is,
you were talking
about Beekman Academy,
right here in Manhattan,
in the neighborhood
North of ware street,
otherwise known as,
uh, "noware."
Now I'll be able to be close
to my boyfriend Henry.
Like hot Vickie could
ever steal him from me.
He's going to NYU.
To study acting.
[Snickers]
If Pop-Pop had gone
to that meeting,
he would have just
written a check
and made it all go away.
You needed somebody
to throw you under the bus.
You needed a patsy.
I, uh, couldn't
help but notice
that lacrosse ball
in your backpack.
Too bad I'm on the board of
the Central Park conservancy,
so beekman won't have a field
to play on next year.
Well, good, 'cause I planted
that lacrosse ball there
to get back at a girl I hate
who plays lacrosse.
Her name is Jack... ie.
Jackie... officecouch.
Damn you, Donaghy!
Cato? Seriously,
not tonight.
I mean it this time.
- Aah!
- [Groans]
Son of a dingbat!
Sorry.
That phone call took forever.
Where's Kenneth Toilethole?
You just missed him.
Again.
[Groans]
He had to go
to the bathroom.
You know what?
I'll go get him.
No, don't!
Every time one of you leaves,
the other one comes back.
You know,
I'm starting to suspect
that I have bad luck.
Dude, bro, where's Liz?
You didn't see her?
She just left.
Oh, I gotta go feed the meter.
Ohh!
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net