Why did I just received this viewer essays
on the subject
"why I love TGS?"
Please tell me it's not--
- the annual TGS viewer
walk-on contest.
It's great promotion, Lemon.
We found that if someone
is actually on NBC,
they're 4% more likely
to watch it.
- Really?
We're doing this again?
After what happened last year?
- Gassy Patsy,
you can't eat--
- [robotic voice]
Keep the white house white.
[Audience boos]
- You know who enters
these walk-on contests?
Weirdos.
- Read the essays, Lemon.
It's not going to kill you.
- Oh, really? 'Cause this one
is typed on the inside
of a bloody halter top.
- Just pick one.
And while you're at it,
which one of these ties
do you prefer?
- I thought you said
a man should never wear pastel
unless he's a black guy
on Easter.
- Usually, but I'm going
on the today show
to talk about Avery,
and I need to tone down
my natural aura
of strength
and sexual dominance.
Which wasn't going to happen
with the tie
I was going to wear.
- [Gasps] Oh, my.
[Stammers]
So, uh, what is the news
with Avery?
- Uh, there isn't any,
and that's the problem.
The U.N. is useless,
the state department
is full of democrats,
and as it turns out,
amnesty international
is nothing but a company
that makes and sells candles.
- That explains all the vigils.
That is a good scam.
- It's been a year,
and the media have moved on.
- Media is a plural noun.
Put this tie on.
- I have to find a way
to get Avery's story
back on the front page.
Fortunately, I run a network
with a news division,
and I will do whatever it takes
to keep Avery's plight
in the public eye.
Even...
Go and see Matt lauer's band.
It's blues rock, Lemon.
It's called...
"Rhythm and news".
- Lemon, no.
[Exciting jazz music]
Synced by yescool
www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
- Sir, I've been thinking.
I know I'm a big shot now
with my suits
and a desk lamp that I control,
but I just want you to know
I will always be a page
at heart.
Even if I did just receive
a fancy award at my new job.
- On behalf of
the mother[Bleep]
Standards department,
I, Gaylord Felcher, present you
with the "employee
of the [Bleep] week" award.
Let's give it up for this
[Bleep] [Bleep] [Bleep] [Bleep]
[Bleep] Bag of [Bleep].
- So what can I get for you?
- And Hazel's on it, Tracy.
Kenneth, can I speak with you?
- Can you?
You just did.
- What's your problem?
- Oh, my, well...
My parents were
technically brothers--
- look, I'm trying to do
my job here.
Tracy's my responsibility now.
I take care of him.
- Oh, well, I'm sorry,
Ms. what's-her-name,
but I'll always be there
for Mr. Jordan.
He has a special place
in my heart.
Just like Nana Parcell,
my heartworm.
- Ugh!
- Hey, Jack.
What are you still doing here?
Your segment was bumped.
- What?
Why? You guys doing
another hard-hitting expose
on how to plan a staycation
with your cyber bully?
- No, it's real news for once.
There was a mine collapse
in China.
Turns out,
to keep labor costs down,
all the miners there
are babies.
They pay 'em in yogurt.
- God.
Remember when we used to be the
world leader in baby cuteness?
I can't compete with that.
- Also, adult dogs can't fit
in the baby mines,
so they're lowering down puppies
to bring in supplies.
- [Sighs]
- Hey, thanks for coming
to see my band last night.
- Yes, I didn't expect you
to play for four hours.
- Hey, dummies, I need you guys
to write a sketch
with a non-speaking part for
whoever wins this dumb contest.
And do not write another
sketch about Krang
from teenage mutant
ninja turtles.
No one knows who Krang is.
It would be a waste of time to
talk about Krang on television.
No more Krang!
- Liz?
- Krang!
What the hell, Hazel?
- Can I ask your advice,
woman to woman?
- Are you sure?
'Cause I took one of those
"which gossip girl are you?"
Quizzes,
and it said I was
the dad's guitar.
- [Scoffs] Please.
You are so amazing.
This place
is such a boys' club,
but you boss them around
like an Amazon warrior queen.
And look at your body.
Your rack is like, "pow!"
- Hazel, what is the question?
- It's Kenneth.
He's not a page anymore,
but he keeps trying
to do my job for me.
And when I confronted him
about it,
he was so condescending.
He laughed at me, and then
he undressed me with his eyes.
And then he had his way
with me.
With his eyes.
- Ugh. The male gaze.
- Yeah.
They're all a bunch of gays.
- No, Kenneth is sweet,
but he's still a man.
And in our society,
men get praised
for just taking
whatever they want.
But what do people call women
who are tough and ambitious?
- Leslie or Courtney?
- What? No.
A bitch.
Well, you may be at the bottom
of the totem pole now,
but you're in the game.
So play it like a man and don't
let anyone try to stop you.
Just like the karate kid--
Hilary Swank "Karate Kid IV".
- I want you to be my mentor.
- Julie-San,
fighting not good.
But if must fight, win.
Kesuke Miyagi, Karate Kid IV.
I accept!
- You listen to me, Blitzer.
Either CNN gets back
on the Avery Jessup story,
or I'll tell everyone your
real name, Steel Hammerhands.
[Click] Hello?
Steel?
Mr. Hammerhands?
- Jack.
I have an important
actor request.
- This is not really
a good time, Jenna.
- I want you to hire a giant
to stand in the background
of every scene I'm in
to make me look daintier.
It works.
It's why Lamar Odom married
that giant Kardashian girl.
- I run a TV network,
and I still can't get my wife's
story on the air.
The world may have forgotten
about Avery, but I haven't.
Sometimes at night,
I sit here in the dark,
drinking scotch,
staring at that doorway,
hoping against hope
that she'll walk
as if nothing ever happened.
"I'm home, Jack.
And I brought back a bunch
of oriental sex powders."
- I know how you can get
Avery back on television.
Her story has everything!
Blondeness, kidnapping,
a villain with an accent.
It's the perfect TV movie.
I should know.
I played Italian party whore
in the Amanda Knox story.
- A TV movie--Jenna, I don't
want to trivialize this ordeal.
- But those movies get results.
Every kidnapped woman
I've ever played
has been released.
- Well, it would allow me
to control the story.
- Well, you better hurry, Jack.
Oxygen is already working
on a movie
about the baby miners.
- Then we'll have
to slow them down.
Gabriel...
Send a bunch of pies
to the Oxygen network.
- Excuse me,
Ms. what's-her-name.
What's that?
- Not that it's any
of your business,
but Tracy's jaw is tired
from pretending to be pac-man.
So I'm making it easier
for him to eat.
- No! No!
He can't eat that junk.
He just got his cholesterol
down to triple digits.
- Get off my ass, Parcell.
I'm doing my job.
You think you can push me around
just because you have a penis?
- I definitely have a penis.
- You think I'm some
delicate little girl
who'll do whatever you say?
Well, I'm not delicate.
I've been in tons
of car wrecks.
- Hazel, I just peed this.
Could you take care
of it for me?
- Sir!
I am resuming responsibility
for your care.
You are in dire need
of a getting-your-act-together
montage.
♪ Down so low,
don't know what up is ♪
♪ When--
- I'm sorry, Tracy.
You wanna be bossed around
by this trailer park Hitler?
Or do you wanna do whatever you
want with a sexy, fun bitch
who just bought you a pinata?
- Awesome!
- [Inaudible]
Miss Lemon, do you
have a moment
or are you busy regretting
your life choices,
for example, missing your window
for having children?
- Get to the point, Kenneth.
- It's Hazel.
I'm trying to help her,
but she's gone crazy.
- Uh-huh.
You can't handle the fact
that a woman is doing
your old job.
What a world.
I bet even Hillary Clinton
has to put up with this crap
from whoever was
secretary of state before her.
- You mean Condoleezza--
- Shut up.
Look, I believe in Hazel.
I happen to be her mentor.
So to quote Mr. Miyagi,
"leave girl alone or you deal
with me, surf shop owner."
- Hey, sweetie.
How was your day?
- Not even half over, Hazel.
Ugh! I still have to read
all these essays.
Okay.
- Look at you.
You're a whirlwind--
in charge in the board room...
And the bedroom.
- Sure.
- You're a modern,
DTF type woman
whose whole vibe says,
"yeah! Dig sex and I'm not
gonna apologize for it."
- Okay, here's a little
bedroom tip.
Put a bag of popcorn
in the microwave beforehand.
That way, when you're done,
you have a treat.
- I wish I had your
emotional intelligence.
My boyfriend Razmig and I
have hit a little rough patch.
- Okay.
Lay it on me.
- Well, I went home
this afternoon to get some,
and I found Razmig banging the
fattest chick I've ever seen.
And you know,
I used to weigh 800 pounds.
- Stop right there.
You didn't hit a rough patch.
He cheated on you.
You have to dump him
immediately.
- What?
How can you say that?
- Hazel,
I'm trying to help you.
- By asking me to break up
with the man I love?
Helping me would be teaching me
how to spice things up.
Like by greeting him
at the front door
wearing nothing
but false teeth.
I'm very disappointed
in your mentorship, Liz.
If this were two years ago,
I would sit on you
till you died.
- No wigs.
I said no wigs.
You're not a lead, Gabe.
At best, you're a featured extra
with no lines.
Do you understand?
- Hey, Gabe.
- Lemon, would you be interested
in writing the screenplay
for the greatest love story
ever told?
- You mean Lois Lane's love
affair with journalism?
I said it.
- Avery and me.
I'm producing
a television movie
to get her back
in the headlines.
For obvious reasons,
I'm fast-tracking the project.
The script is due on Monday.
- Monday?
Hmm. I guess I won't be able
to go to the gym this weekend.
- I know it's short notice,
but I would consider it
a personal favor
after six years of listening
to you complain
about how there are
so few women on death row.
- Is a coincidence,
or is the system sexist?
Oh! Speaking
of our amazing dynamic,
I have taken on a mentee
of my own, Jack--
a page named Hazel.
- You're a mentor?
But that makes me
a grand-mentor.
And I'm still so young.
- Don't worry.
I already messed it up.
I told her to break up
with her awful boyfriend
and she got really mad at me.
- Often, the best way
for a mentee to learn
is for you to let her fail.
- Wait, does that mean
you've done that to me?
When?
- Um--
- I think the crowd
at the Apollo
might welcome a change of pace.
- You're right.
You should do it.
Sometimes, they have
to learn the hard way.
If Hazel rejects your advice,
let her.
She'll get there on her own
just like you did
after the crowd at the Apollo
chased you into the river.
- Okay, I understand the irony
of what I'm about to say,
but I reject that advice.
Don't worry, I'll bring you back
a t-shirt from successtown.
Ow! My groin!
- Mr. Jordan!
- K-dog.
You were wrong.
They do still make crossbows.
- You let him buy a crossbow?
And a motorcycle?
- No, Kenneth, I let him buy
a motorcycle ramp
and no motorcycle!
Can I help you?
Tracy's very tired.
He didn't sleep last night.
- Why not?
If he doesn't get at least
14 hours a night,
he starts to go crazy.
- We on a show within a show!
My real name is Tracy Morgan!
- Well, Tracy wanted
to go clubbing.
And I don't know
if you know this, Kenneth,
but night clubs
are open at night.
- You didn't let him drink,
did you?
Mr. Jordan can't mix alcohol
with his medication.
- I'm not an idiot, Kenneth.
I took him off his medication.
- You what?
Why are you doing this?
- Because Liz told me to.
Having access to Tracy
is an opportunity,
and I'm taking advantage of it.
Did you see page six today?
Those are my toes
he's sucking on.
And he did not want to.
[Gasping] Ah, mm.
- Jack!
What the hell is this?
- Where did you get that?
- Donna from casting and I
are friends.
Well, not so much friends
as I own a magnet
that can scramble her pacemaker.
- Jenna,
you are not playing Avery.
- Why not?
This movie was my idea!
- I appreciate that.
You can play
a Korean party whore.
I just don't think you can
capture Avery's essence.
- That's ridiculous.
I posed bottomless in essence.
- Jenna, Avery is worldly.
Traveled.
She went to Yale.
- Oh, I see.
You think I'm stupid,
just because my college
got tipped
over by those Miami heat fans.
- I didn't say stupid.
Jenna, there are many kinds
of intelligence.
Practical, emotional,
and there's actual intelligence,
which is
what I'm talking about.
- I want this part, Jack.
It's a guaranteed
Emmy nomination.
- I'm sorry.
I've made up my mind.
- Very well.
But let me ask you this, Jack.
Would a dumb person be able
to think of something amazing
to say as she leaves?
- Liz, we have a show
in four hours.
Have you still not picked
a contest winner?
- Ugh! Fine,
I'll just pick one at random.
It's Joren van der Sloot.
- We can't fly someone
from Peru now.
There's no time.
- Oh, Hazel, we need to talk.
- I'm busy, Liz.
Tracy wants me to page for him
in Las Vegas this weekend.
Is this dress appropriate
for watching pornography
with Penn Jillette?
- Okay, normally we don't
encourage Tracy to go to Vegas,
because of his gambling
addiction and his fear of magic.
But maybe a weekend away
from Razmig is a good thing.
- No.
Razmig's coming with me.
- [Armenian accent] What?
Who is this, Hah-zel?
I no permit you talk
other woman.
- Okay, I'm putting
my foot down.
This guy is no good for you
and I order you, as your mentor,
to dump him.
- You don't know what you're
talking about, Liz.
Razmig is amazing.
He makes me laugh.
- Oh, where is toilet pail?
Razmig must make mud.
- [Chuckling] Razmig!
- Hazel, no.
I'm not letting you--
- [Jack's voice echoing]
Let her fail, Liz.
Let her get there on her own.
- You know what, fine.
You're right, I'm wrong.
Go, be with Razmig.
- Thank you, Liz.
It takes a big woman
to admit she's wrong.
- You are a big woman.
You have pictures?
Fat nudes?
- [Knocking]
I need your help, Ms. Maroney.
- Absolutely.
Oh, I thought
you were someone famous.
You sound a lot
like Reese Witherspoon.
What do you want?
- I'm afraid if Mr. Jordan
goes to Las Vegas this weekend,
he's gonna die.
- I'm not hearing my name,
Kenneth.
- So I thought you--
- oh, thank God.
That took forever.
- I thought you could teach me
how to get around Hazel.
If I could just get one minute
alone with Mr. Jordan--
- you can convince him
he's wrong. Yes!
But how do you get
his attention?
All the world's a stage,
Kenneth.
Just play the part.
- Play the part?
+
- Ms. Lemon.
If it's not too late,
I would like the essay contest
to win a role
on TGS with Tracy Jordan.
- No, Kenneth, you can't enter.
The contest isn't open
to NBC employees.
- I know, ma'am-maw.
Which is why I just quit my job
at standards and practices.
- I may [Bleep] hate you
right now,
you little [Bleep], but
[Bleep] damn it I respect you.
- Kenneth,
you know this is just
to be a non-speaking extra,
right?
- I know.
But have you ever loved
something so much
that you would sacrifice
anything for it?
- Nope.
But you know what,
this is perfect.
Because then I don't have
to pick some crazy person,
and I know you won't do anything
weird on the air.
- I'm Kenneth!
- Get to wardrobe,
contest winner!
This is gonna be a great show.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's Charles from the U.N.
We found your wife
and I dropped her off
at the office.
She should be there
right about now.
- Jack, it's me.
I'm home.
- No, you're not my wife.
- How could you say that,
darling?
I'm Avery jesbert.
- Jenna?
- No, don't turn on the light.
Surprised?
- Let's set aside
how idiotic that plan was,
and imagine a world
where it actually worked.
- I appreciate your feedback.
- If I had believed you
for one second,
I would've been devastated,
heartbroken!
- You wanna talk
about devastation?
How do you think I felt when you
told me I couldn't play Avery?
- You are a monster.
What you have done here today,
it's--it's...
The second cruelest thing
that anyone has ever done to me.
Do you know what
the cruelest is?
- When I went to the bathroom
on the hood of your car
before I thought of this plan?
- Avery had me committed
to a mental hospital
so she and her college roommate
could use my yankee tickets
on opening day.
- That's a nice story, Jack,
but I don't hear my name in it.
- You--
- Finally.
- You may not have
Avery's grace and acumen,
but you do have the one thing
that makes her so special--
her ruthless pursuit
of self-interest.
It's the heart of capitalism.
And the beautiful black heart
of my wife.
Jenna, you have Avery's essence.
Congratulations.
The part is yours.
- Oh! You won't regret this.
We're gonna get her home, Jack.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have a female condom
to take out.
Unless...
Going once...
- Four, three--
[audience cheering]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
a message from the president
of the United States.
- Goo-goo, ga-ga,
my fellow ah-meh-ri-cans.
- Okay, he's never been worse.
Is Kenneth supposed to enter?
- I love you, sir.
- Ken, where have you been?
- Damn it.
- I've been here all along.
I never left.
And I never will.
- Go to commercial.
- They told us
we can't do that any more.
- What?
- I quit my job
to be here, Mr. Jordan.
It was the only way
I could get around Hazel.
- You quit your job for me?
- I'm not just gonna sit by
and watch you destroy yourself.
'Cause I would do anything
for love,
but I won't do that.
- The girl in that video was hot
in an early '90s kind of way.
- Now... Take your medicine.
- This has been a message
from the president
of the United States.
- Tough night?
Come on, Lemon.
The show was all right.
What about the sketch
with the guy who was worried
about his sexual performance?
- That was a real commercial for
an erectile dysfunction drug.
- Well, I laughed.
So, uh, how did things
shake out with Hazel?
- Not great.
My way, which is still
the right way, didn't work.
So just to see,
I did your thing.
- Good.
You let her fail.
That's how the banking industry
learned its lesson.
And now they're doing amazing,
and everyone's honest.
- Mm. Your thing
didn't work either.
- Are you sure?
Mentoring is not
an exact science.
- Why aren't there
more female serial killers?
What does that say
about our society--
- Liz!
- Oh, here she is.
She's here.
- Liz, I was watching the show
fall apart
while Razmig gave me
a prison tattoo of his face,
and I heard your voice.
I finally heard
everything you said to me.
"Hazel,
you're a beautiful flower.
"Let yourself bloom.
"What are you doing
this weekend, Hazel?
Are there still bath houses?
Let's go to one!"
- I never said any of that,
but--
- you were right all along.
You knew I was making
the wrong choices.
But you let me fail.
With Razmig, with Tracy.
- Yes, I was definitely
on top of that Tracy thing.
- You were teaching me
the whole time,
and all the while lighting
a fire with that hot ass.
- I'm... Jack.
I'm your grand-mentor.
Liz?
She's beautiful.
This next lady is from White Haven,
Pennsylvania
Okay! Please welcome
to the stage Leminem!
Ooh!
[Scattered applause, booing]
- ♪ Ahhh, do the sprinkler,
♪ Do the sprinkler, do the sprinkler,
do the sprinkler.
♪ Here we go, here we go.
♪ White Haven, PA.
♪ Apollo theatre. Come together...
♪ Have you ever thought
about the women of the world
♪ Teen moms, grandmoms,
even little girls.
Go White Haven.
Synced by yescool
www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net