- Lemon...
What do you think?
"kidnapped by danger,
colon,
"the avery jessup story,
comma,
"brought to you with limited
commercial interruptions
"by pride bladder control pads.
Pride: Make every
room a bathroom."
- Really, is that the title?
'cause as the writer,
I was thinking
Of naming it
dancing with ophelia--
- Don't overthink this.
It's a classic love story.
Boy meets girl.
Girl gets kidnapped
by asian dictator.
Boy makes movie
to get girl back.
Girl's so grateful she does
birthday things to boy.
Boy falls asleep.
- You're forgetting boy
meets girl's mother.
They are creepily attracted
to each other.
- What does that have
to do with avery and me?
Just stick to the story,
lemon.
Tell it exactly how
it happened.
If you get this right,
gay men will be dressing up
Like avery for Halloween
for the next 20 years.
- Okay.
Oh, speaking of Halloween,
are you dressing up this year?
- Lemon, it's March.
- 'cause I'm gonna
be mitt rom-mummy.
I call it.
You can't steal it.
- Why wouldn't you
be mitt-zombie?
- Because I'm an idiot!
Oh, come on, liz.
Think for, like, one second
before you buy all that gauze.
[exciting jazz music]
♪
- I didn't want to write a song
for the film.
I wanted to focus on
making the film--
- What film?
The avery tv movie?
- But my manager, gary greasy,
Harangued me to write a song
for the film...
- Oh, no, in her mind, she's
already accepting an award
For whatever this is.
- I need to thank
my co-writers, gary greasy
And jesus, a homeless man
I stole the melody from.
We also filmed a video
for the song for the film.
Thank you.
♪ kidnapped, my heart
has been stolen ♪
♪ I am kidnapped and
I wonder for how long ♪
♪ my darling gone so far
♪ but not forever more
♪ I am kidnapped
- [chuckles]
that's awesome.
I didn't even realize your song
was the original.
- What are you talking about?
- Weird al.
- ♪ knapsack,
the zipper is broken ♪
♪ on my knapsack
and I lost my bakugan ♪
♪ trapper keeper, snickers bar,
my thermos hit the floor ♪
♪ broken knapsack
- What is that?
- Weird al yankovic
parodied your song.
Like, michael jackson's eat it
or adelesomeone likes food.
- [sighs]
- it's a huge honor.
Like, when people wanna see
your boobs at mardi gras.
- It's nothing like that.
I'm calling my lawyer.
Weird al corrupted
something beautiful
That was written to
distract gary greasy
While he came down from meth.
- Hey, kenneth, nice tux.
- My father wore this
to his high school prom.
The theme was enchantment
under the jim crow laws.
- So, what's up?
- Well, as you know,
I recently had a minor setback
In my goal to become
president of television,
But I'm ready to start over
again at the bottom.
- Well, we're not
really hiring now.
- I'll do anything.
Except work in
the sound department.
Those guys are--
[dubbed over]
beautiful geniuses
--Holes.
- Look, I'm sorry, kenneth.
It's just the budget's
really tight.
- Okay.
But if anything comes up,
Put a message in a bottle
and throw it in the river.
That's where I go every day
to fish for shoes.
Say, old janitor,
Do you know if they're hiring
in maintenance?
- Oh, we're always looking for
the next generation of janitors.
Throw your resume away
on the fourth floor
And we'll be in touch.
[all chatter]
- okay, everyone.
Welcome to the table read for
Kidnapped by danger:
The avery jessup story.
Brought to you with limited
commercial interruptions
By pride pad.
Pride: The world is
your toilet.
[all cheer]
Written by elizabeth
"diablo" lemon.
We open on
a midtown restaurant.
Jack donaghy, 50s,
big irish head,
Sips drinks with avery, 30s.
- Avery, do you believe
in love at first sight?
- I believe in two things.
Fast money and fast curves.
- We smash cut to
a night of passion
In a completely dark room.
Bathing suit areas
get a workout.
Interior, hotel room,
one month later.
Jack sits on the bed
in a tuxedo.
His cell phone rings.
- Jack, where are you?
- We reveal jack's high school
sweetheart, nancy donovan,
In bed next to him.
[ridiculous boston accent]
- jack, who's calling ya
At such a wicked late hour?
Ya mother?
- Jack looks around
the wedding reception.
Across the way, his friend liz--
think courteney cox--
Dances with a handsome pilot--
Think a young fred grandy.
Jack turns to nancy.
- I love you, nancy.
I want to marry you.
- Stop it, jack.
Avery's here
and she's knocked up.
- Jack looks shocked.
- You gotta do the right thing.
I'll miss you, jack.
Go red sox.
- My character seems so passive.
I mean, what if I were like,
"I need to sleep with you both,
one more time to decide."
I don't know,
I'm not a writer, but...
Do that.
- Yeah--
- Liz, am I going
too big on the accent?
- No, that's how people from
boston sound to me.
- Great.
- Lemon.
My office now.
- Hey.
You have amazing skin.
- I'm married to a woman.
- I got four inches of steel
that might change your mind.
- Sid, how long will it take to
get a cease and desist order
Against weird al yankovic?
Oh, that's too bad.
Did they also take away
your handgun license?
- Don't do it, j-mo.
You don't want to
mess with weird al.
- Oh, please.
I'm not afraid of
anyone in show business.
I turned down intercourse
with harvey weinstein
On no less than three
occasions...Out of five.
- I'm telling you,
just let him do it.
Eminem backed down.
Lady gaga backed down.
- Tracy, I'm supposed to perform
my song on fallon tonight.
I can't do that now.
It's ruined.
I'll have to write a new song.
- Don't you understand?
He's gonna parody you again.
That's what he does.
That's all he does.
You can't stop him.
- Unless, I write a song
that can't be parodied.
- Impossible.
What do you think phil collins
Was trying to do
with sussudio?
- Which weird al famously
parodied soup soupy-o.
I'm not saying it'll be easy,
but if anyone in the world
Is talented enough
to pull it off...
- I'll make coffee.
You also make coffee.
After the coffee contest,
we'll start working.
- Yeah.
- Really, lemon?
You had to include nancy donovan
in your screenplay?
- You told me to write it
exactly how it happened.
- That's not how it happened.
You took the facts
and you twisted them
Like chubby checker took
the traditional standing dance
And made a mockery
of it with "the twist".
This is a love story, lemon.
You clearly have no idea
how to write romance.
- Hey, you wouldn't say
that if you read
My    mythbusters fan fiction.
It is sexy.
And you're welcome for not
twisting any more facts.
Like the fact that nancy got
divorced for you
With no idea that you'd already
gotten another woman pregnant.
And when avery abandoned you
for her career,
You told her to go.
- Jack, we need to talk.
- Now there's this hot slut.
[clears throat]
hi, I'm liz.
I work for jack.
- Diana jessup.
And I'm glad to see
the endgame of feminism
Is women dressing like
dennis the menace    at work.
- Diana, I wasn't expecting you.
- It has come to my attention
that a television movie
Is being made about my daughter.
- I knew you would not approve.
- Because it's crass, jack.
Like personalized wedding vows
or standing up in a pool.
And to hear about it
the way I did.
My housekeeper
started screaming.
- I should have called, but I
thought it would be awkward.
I--I mean I thought
you would disapprove.
Not that there's anything
awkward between us.
- Of course there's no other
reason it would be awkward.
And I didn't dream
that I was a sex slave
To a squid-like alien
with your head.
Jack, if this
tv movie will help,
Then I won't stand
in the way of it.
But I am gonna stay
here and make sure
The jessup name is not soiled.
- Of course, I'd love
to have you.
Uh, I mean, as a guest,
not, uh, under a waterfall.
- I'm gonna go freshen up.
The train was disgusting.
I flew here, but I saw
a train from the window.
- What are you doing? Leave.
- No. This is weird and I am not
letting it get any weirder.
All my life, I have been
the third wheel
That prevents people
from having sex.
- Well, movie's over lizzie.
Why don't you head on up to bed?
- Are you kidding?
It's your anniversary.
We're celebrating!
Let's get these
scabs off my knee.
- In college, they called me
"the blocker".
- I don't need a chaperone.
- I'm sorry, but you're stressed
and you're lonely
And that woman
has flawless skin,
Like an organic chicken.
I haven't had lunch.
- Oh, you're still here.
- That's what they all say.
+
♪♪
But I don't think there
are any small jobs,
Only small people,
Like children, or a giant
who's very far away from you.
All I want is an opportunity,
sir, to once again work
For the greatest company
that has ever existed
Since the creation of
earth 800 years ago.
[as the nbc jingle]
♪ I love this
- This is everything that jenna
will be wearing in the movie,
But of course, jenna
isn't as slender-hipped
As avery or, uh, you.
- Jessup women have terrible
osteoporosis in later years.
- You must crumble
like greek statues.
- You guys like factoids?
Check this out.
One in four americans
has an std.
Chlamydia, herpes, garden
variety genital swelling--
- That's quite enough, lemon.
- Rectal fissures.
- Lemon, a word.
Actor time-out.
Just wanted everyone to know
that I'll be method acting;
Staying in character
at all times.
It's a technique
that was invented
By constantin stanislavski
When he was four years old
And wanted to act
like a pirate.
- Uh, this is
lance drake mandrell.
He'll be playing me
in the movie.
- I'll be...Becoming you.
- Easy, chief.
Lance, this is diana jessup,
avery's mother.
- Diana, are you
a time-traveler?
Because I don't know
how my mother-in-law
Could be younger than my wife.
- [flattered gasp]
- Was that supposed to be me
saying that?
Because I would never
use that much math
In complimenting a woman.
Their brains can't handle it.
- [giggles]
it's evolution.
- That's exactly the kind
Of stuff I need to know.
Hey, quick question, jack.
Our underwear, is it regular
black bikini cut?
Or is it silk boxers
with tweety bird on them?
Because I have both.
- I think you and I should
Have a meeting with wardrobe.
- The resemblance is quite
striking, don't you think?
The fighter pilot wrists, the
hair like a mature otter's pelt,
Shoulders you could
ride bareback.
- I'm sure you don't
wanna hear this,
But every woman here would love
to slip it to your son-in-law.
- Slip what?
- Whatever.
Drill him against a wall.
The point is,
that would be wrong,
Because we all work for jack.
But boy, I'll tell you that
lance drake mandrell
Seems like
the next best thing.
Wouldn't mind giving him
the old skin flute.
- Interesting.
- Okay, how about this?
♪ don't say good-bye--
- are you kidding me?
Don't eat that pie, don't eat
my fries, don't wear that tie,
Don't smell that guy.
We got to be better than this.
- All right.
♪ these lonely eyes--
- I'm sorry, did you
just say baloney thighs?
Because that's the name of
the boat weird al's gonna buy
With the money
he makes off you...Dumb bitch!
I'm sorry.
I just care too much.
- We might as well just write
a song about pizza,
Because at the end of the day,
that's what it's gonna be.
Oh, my god.
If we did that,
he'd be powerless.
There's nothing you can
change pizza to.
- Because it's already weird.
- Exactly.
Weird al's about to get
a taste of his own medicine.
- I'm jack donaghy.
I am jack donaghy.
[wretches]
Oh, god.
This ice tea is so strong.
[knock on door]
- lance.
I mean, jack.
- What do you need, diana?
I'm very busy right now.
I've got to get to the bottom of
this business case.
- I wonder if you might
say something negative
About obama for me.
- "hope"?
More like "nope".
- And what is your opinion
on hybrid cars?
- Prius is the latin word
for impotence.
[sexually flustered]
rose wine?
- Pairs well with
failed suicide.
- Oh!
- Oh, you know, hey, this has
been great practice,
But I'm late for
a tooth-whitening appointment
And they just freak out
if you don't
Give them 24 hours--
- no, no, no, no.
Stay in character.
- There hasn't been a good
Non-boat painting
in 5,000 years.
- [moans]
- Sometimes to prevent monkey
business, we must create it.
The blocker.
- What do you want, lemon?
I've gotta get to the bottom of
this business case.
- Ugh, do you really
have to be here, lance?
I'm trying to find a quiet place
to finish this rewrite.
- How is that rewrite coming?
Maybe jack should go to the gym.
You know, the actor playing him
can do four boy pull-ups.
- Actually, jack,
the rewrite is not going great
Because I'm the only person
willing to admit
How messed up this situation is.
- Sounds like you
need some advice.
Ronald reagan use to say--
- Stop right there, lance.
Only nancy used
reagan's first name.
And only during bath time.
- You've got a long way to go
before you're jack donaghy,
But, my god, you do
have amazing eyes.
- Thank you.
- Oh, hello jack.
Both: Hello, diana.
- You can deal with liz, jack.
I was on my way out anyway.
- Wait, where are you two going?
- Out for a drink.
- Stop acting like me.
- How is taking your
mother-in-law
Out on a date
acting like you?
- Uh, it's not, obviously.
Uh, you two go and
have a good time.
- We will.
It's impossible not
to have a great time
At planet hollywood.
- [wretches]
- Ice tea.
- [gags]
- Jack, there's a reason I can't
write this the way you want it.
I don't care if it's nancy
or diana or your insistence
That the jack character have
an awesome catch-phrase.
- An idea that's off
the charts, kemosabe.
- You're living
in a dream world.
- Apparently because I thought
you were a writer.
- Hey, I'm trying to help you.
Who do you think got diana
and lance together?
- The blocker?
- But of course that doesn't
bother you, right?
Because there's nothing
going on
Between you and diana,
And your relationship
with avery was perfect,
And the only problem
is that I can't write.
- That pretty much sums it up.
You're fired, lemon.
I'll write this thing myself.
- Fine, but you are in denial about your life.
That's not a way out.
+
- Hey, guys, it's me.
Oh, my sandwich
from the other day.
I hate to waste food,
but I'll probably get
Free executive sandwiches
like this forever.
Nothing can stop me now.
[squeals]
It's okay.
I'm doing great.
Everything's gonna work out.
- Hang on, kid!
We pool our tips.
[musical lead-in]
- Now, here to sing
her original song
From the upcoming
nbc television event
Kidnapped by dangethe very
talented jenna maroney.
- ♪ I eat pizza,
I eat cheese ♪
♪ I eat lots of broccolis
♪ I eat ice cream
way too fast ♪
♪ burritos always
give me gas ♪
♪ fart so loud,
fart so loud ♪
♪ yum-yums make me
- Kingslayer!
- I've never been kissed
like that, jack.
- It's because we're
so in love, avery.
That's why we're perfect,
avery.
- Make love to me...Now.
This is garbage.
- [sighs]
- Oh, mr. Subhas,
your wife is on the phone.
She's making dinner
and she wants to know
If you found any
prosciutto today.
- Why are you dressed
like a janitor?
- It's my new job.
- But you just got promoted.
- Well, I've had
a few setbacks,
But only a quitter quits, sir.
So, here I am.
Starting back up
the ladder to my dreams.
My career dreams.
Not the dream where those two
tennis sisters chase me.
- You really are
an extraordinary
Young man, kenneth.
No matter what happens, you
always keep your chin up.
- Medically,
it's a neck ridge.
- I mean, look at you.
You're not just back
where you started,
You're doing worse.
And even if other
people say to you,
"your life is a mess.
Stop looking at your
mother-in-law.
I can't write your movie,"
You stay positive.
You always believe that
everything is going to work out.
How do you do it?
- Well, I'll tell you
my secret, sir.
[whispering]
I lie to myself.
Every morning,
when I wake up, I say,
"everything's gonna be okay."
But I'm lying.
And I don't know
how much longer I can do it.
[piercing inhalation]
Have a swell night, sir.
- Let me guess,
you're all watching
My triumph fallon
last night?
- No, you gotta see this.
- ♪ daddy's fightin' overseas
♪ lord, keep him safe
for mommy, please ♪
♪ can't make up for
time that's passed ♪
♪ but now he's coming
home at last ♪
♪ heart so proud
♪ daddy make my heart
so proud ♪
- Yankovic!
He reversed the parody.
He normal al'd us.
I feel so--
- Honored?
- I've gotta go call
my dad and thank him.
You know he was stationed
at pearl harbor?
During the korean war?
- Well, congratulations, lemon.
You were right.
I've been lying to myself.
Maybe my whole marriage
to avery was a lie.
- Whoa, no, that's not
what I was saying.
Everyone lies to themselves.
I mean, I refuse to buy
larger underwear,
And it looks like when you tie
a string around a roast.
Okay, so we agree.
Things are complicated.
But that doesn't mean you can't
figure it all out.
You just have to get
avery home first.
- How?
Lemon...
We can't make this movie.
- Yes, we can.
We just have to do what you've
been doing all along.
Lie...To everybody.
[dramatic music]
- I'll never let you capture
my wife from here,
On the top of
the empire state building!
[groans]
- Korean freeze ray!
- Jack!
- Nothing can keep us apart!
Our love is off
the charts, kemosabe.
- ♪ I am kidnapped
- Cut! All right.
[bell ringing]
It's a wrap.
All right, now let's hurry up
and edit this thing.
It's on in two days.
- Seriously, man.
Call me. I wanna board with
you at big bear, all right?
- Lance, I wanna thank you
for you professionalism
On this project.
- Thanks, jack.
If it weren't for this gig,
I never would have
hooked up with diana.
I'm not one to tell tales
out of school,
But she's a real
hotshot at boinking.
She boinks like a dog.
I'm not a writer.
She made me boink
her this morning
And at first, I was like,
"please--
- I get it, lance.
Uh, thank you.
- Wow, it's just
good to be, uh,
Lance drake mandrell again.
Get back to doing
the things I love,
Like getting high and
going to the planetarium.
- So, thank you, jack.
Hopefully, the next time
we see each other,
Avery will be home.
- It'll all work out, jack.
- Thanks, lemon.
And, uh, thank
the blocker for me.
- Hey, when this movie airs,
Can my name be the first credit
that comes up at the end?
- This is
a group process, lemon.
Don't be an egomaniac.
Synced By YesCool
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net