I finished my Kabletown self evaluation!
Nailed it.
"My greatest weakness
is humility.
I'm probably the most humble
person in the whole world."
I wrote that.
These self-evaluations
are a charade.
People cannot be impartial
about themselves.
You should read what some
of your coworkers wrote.
What three words
best describe me?
The. Complete. Package.
My greatest weakness...
Is chocolate.
Surprisingly the only person
who was honest was Jenna.
"Strengths: None.
"I am the worst person
I know.
"When I used to live with Liz,
I would videotape her sleeping
and sell it to
Japanese businessmen"?
No wonder that tour group kept
calling me "sleep whore-San."
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't read that.
I filled it out last night
after mixing alcohol
with prescription... exhaustion.
I need to redo it.
I can't believe I have
to read all of these.
This is the biggest
waste of time
since NBC's diversity
writing program.
That was a good idea, but all
of our actors are so white.
Slap it to me, Daddy-O.
Popo popped dookie
down by the vacants.
[Exciting jazz music]
♪ ♪
30 ROCK
S06 Ep16 - Nothing left to lose
sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
[phone vibrates]
This is Jenna.
What are you wearing?
[British accent]
Jenna, love,
it's English director
Christopher Nolan.
Mr. Nolan,
I saw you across the room
at the Dark Knight premiere.
I was shooting blow darts at Maggie
Gyllenhal from a heating vent.
Yes. How would you like
to be in my next movie?
I quit this show!
To hell with you all!
Go to hell!
I just need you to do a
quick camera test for me.
I do not understand
Christopher Nolan's methods.
He's directing a live-action
Smurfs sequel,
so I went to Times Square,
did cartwheels like he asked...
Oh, boy.
We got the whole
thing on tape.
This was a prank?
This isn't body paint.
It's a spray they use
to kill geese at airports.
What happened, J-Mo?
Did you pass out in
a goose costume at LaGuardia?
[All laugh]
Ugh, what is
that smell, Tracy?
It's the new fragrance
I designed.
It's called "Desire,"
but with a "Z"
instead of the second "E."
What is that supposed
to smell like?
All my favorite things.
The Knicks, a mop from
a strip club, a carefree hobo,
a crate with a new giraffe
in it, and broccoli.
It smells disgusting.
Yeah, I wouldn't know.
I lost my sense
of smell years ago.
But when one sense goes away,
the others make up for it.
I have an incredible
sense of touch.
I feel an old Jack-o-lantern
from last Halloween.
Are you serious?
You can't smell?
Why haven't you
been to a doctor?
Who has the time,
with work, family and hobbies
and listing excuses?
[Inhales deeply]
Oh, my.
It smells like grandma's house
at Christmas.
That's when we found her
dead on the toilet.
Pete, I spent
the morning going over
these Kabletown
self-evaluations.
Your evaluation gave me pause.
Are you sure?
Those look like hands to me.
Here's the problem.
In answer to the question,
"where do you see yourself
in five years?"
You wrote,
"right where I am."
That's an unacceptable answer.
I mean, what if
the Wright brothers had said,
"let's just keep
making bicycles,"
or Alexander windowblinds
had said,
"no, I don't want
to partially see outside"?
Yeah, no, I get
what you're saying,
but I'm Pete Hornberger.
The last time I tried to put
myself out there,
the girl turned out
to be a cop.
Do you understand how this
attitude reflects on me?
I am also required
to complete
one of these inane
self-evaluations.
It's a farce.
What?
Like Frasier?
But that's fun...
But I can't say
I'm succeeding as a manager
if you're failing
as an employee.
You have no ambition,
Pete.
No, no,
you don't understand.
For me, that five years
thing is very ambitious.
Look at my life, Jack.
My father was a congressman.
I was valedictorian
at St. Andrew's,
an olympic archer,
fourth guitarist in Loverboy...
As a teenager.
It's almost unbelievable.
If it weren't all true,
I'd say it doesn't
even make sense.
But now look at me.
The last two decades
have been a freefall.
If I could stay in the same
place for the next five years,
that would be
a huge accomplishment.
Do you know who you remind me of?
George W. Bush,
during his "let's do coke and
buy the Texas rangers" phase.
But he made a decision
to be the best president ever
and then he was.
You've lost your mojo, Pete.
And I'm going
to get it back for you.
Well, something is definitely
obstructing your sinus cavity.
Now we have two options.
I can either drill a hole in the back
of your head,
and push it out
with your brain...
Okay, that sounds good.
Or I could just pull it out
through your nostril.
We'll do the second one.
Thank you.
You know, they don't tell you
this until after you've paid
for medical school,
but being a doctor
is exactly like
the game "Operation."
And there we go.
My buck Rogers decoder ring!
How long has
that been in there?
Those things
are from the '70s.
Yeah, you know what else
is from the '70s?
Women staying quiet.
I totally remember this.
When I was nine, I found it
on the floor of the "G" train.
I knew if my Foster mom saw it,
she would make me sell it
at a pawn shop
to get our family a cheerio.
Okay, sometimes
I think the stories
of your childhood poverty
are exaggerated, but continue.
So I hid the ring
up my nose.
I must have forgot about it.
You may feel some
burning and tingling,
but you should regain normal
sensation in just a few hours.
Oh, I'm sorry, I was talking
to my lover on my Bluetooth.
Uh, one moment, suki.
Anyway, Tracy,
you should start
regaining sensation
in less than an hour.
But a newly regained sense
can be a very powerful thing.
Even overwhelming.
So if you do have
an extreme reaction,
please try to get it on video
for my nephew's funny website.
Uh, Liz, are you getting
enough vitamin "C"?
[Chuckles]
May I suggest messily eating
an orange while I photograph it?
[Knocks on door]
Kenneth, what do you
know about revenge?
Well, the Bible
says it's wrong,
but it's the surprise hit
of the season on ABC,
so I don't know.
Anyway, I know how busy
you are,
so I got you some more
tattoo concealer.
Thank you.
I just ran out.
I was so young
when I got this.
Who even remembers 2007?
Wait, how did you know
I was out of concealer?
From your trash,
Mrs. Maroney.
The garbage man knows all.
In this big trash bag,
I see everyone's mistakes,
their embarrassing secrets,
their dreams they don't
dare share with anyone.
Oh!
Like this.
Interesting.
Kenneth, you don't
happen to have
the other writers' trash
in there, do you?
No.
I can't handle
that much volume.
[Chuckles]
I'm kidding.
They call me "the natural."
I'm so good,
the other janitors
just sit in the basement
all day
getting drunk and laughing about
this idiot they know.
Oh, no.
Kenneth, this concealer
is the wrong color.
Oh, no.
I'll be right back.
Keep an eye on my trash cart?
Oh, I'll keep an eye on it.
[Cackles]
[Chuckles]
Look at us,
laughing together,
like a couple of Jews watching
The Daily Show.
This is the gym of
the New York racquet club, Pete.
Theodore Roosevelt
was a member here.
In fact,
many of the animal heads
mounted downstairs
were shot by T.R.
Including the one that looked
like a terrified Asian man?
It was a different time,
Pete.
Today, the most powerful
men in New York
still come here to exercise.
And nothing is a better workout
for body and soul than boxing.
It's the first sport
man ever invented.
Except of course,
uh, hide and seek.
Shh.
Uh, yeah.
Boxing is primal, Pete.
It's exactly what you need.
So come on,
don't just stand there.
Throw a punch,
feel like a man.
A man who, years ago,
was on top of the world,
who saw Paula and dragged her
back to his cave.
Actually she took
me that first night.
Hit something.
Put your frustration
into your fists
and hit something!
Hornberger!
Get up, Pete.
Get up and fight.
For God's sake, Hornberger,
the dummy is winning!
Why are you kissing it?
I'm submitting
to its strength.
It's the Alpha.
Good morning, fresh coffee.
[Inhales]
Good morning, clean floor.
Funny, Kenneth.
You don't have any smell
at all.
Don't worry about it.
♪ Perfume and roses
and strong halitosis ♪
♪ powders and flowers
and spicy clam chowders ♪
♪ I can smell,
I can smell, I can smell ♪
♪ I can smell ♪
♪ I can... ♪
Daddy?
- Nice save.
- Oh, no.
Vengeance announcement.
Look what I found
in the trash.
An email confirmation
in Frank's name for one ticket
to see Taylor Swift
at Nassau Coliseum.
[All laugh]
She writes the songs
herself.
When she can't cry any more,
she writes!
What are you
laughing at, Toofer?
You're the man who took
professional boudoir photographs
and then tried to mail them
to Parade magazine columnist
Marilyn Vos Savant.
[All laugh]
I happen to think
that smart is sexy.
Our foreplay would
be puzzle-solving.
Uh oh, Lutz's turn.
What is this gonna be?
Oh, no. I don't
have anything for you.
You don't matter.
But if you two dirtbags
ever mess with me again,
I'll take this
to the next level.
You don't do 22 episodes
of "Celebrity outhouse"
with Lorena Bobbitt without
learning a few things.
You're at rehearsal
before me?
Of course I am, Liz-dad.
I'm your good boy.
[Sniffs]
I memorized all my lines,
so can I go
get dressed
for the photo shoot now,
so you don't
have to wait for me?
Sure, little buddy.
You know,
smell is the sense
most closely associated
with memory.
I know, Dotcom, that's why
whenever I smell that jacket,
I remember being bored.
The only person
you're insulting
with that attitude
is yourself.
Obviously something
about the way I smell
reminds Tracy of his dad.
Well, his father did
work for a soup factory
and you are constantly eating.
It's not a food thing,
grizz.
I think it's my hair pomade.
Midnight symphony?
My grandfather used that.
Midnight symphony.
You are the conductor of your
own proud African orchestra.
Midnight symphony.
- You use midnight symphony?
- It works, Dotcom.
It was discontinued a few years
ago, but I bought seven cases
of it on eBay
from a guy named Reggie.
You're still here.
You didn't go
to the store for milk
and heroin and
then never come back.
That was his excuse?
You stayed because
you love me.
Right, daddy-Liz?
I do love you... champ.
- But I could love you more.
- Well, you just wait.
Watch this.
Be careful, Liz.
Be very careful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Dotcom.
Pete.
Confidence is a spectrum.
On one end,
the ultra-confident end,
you have people like
Jack Donaghy, Vladimir Putin,
Orville Redenbacher.
Corn is not
the only thing he popped,
if you know what I mean.
Then...
You have the other
end of the spectrum.
Yeah, I get it.
Men with no confidence.
No, men who have
nothing left to lose.
Great men like Richard Nixon,
the 1980 olympic hockey team,
my good friend John Rambo.
This is you.
And I shouldn't have
been trying to get you
all the way to the tiger,
because all you needed
was a little push
to get you to
nothing left to lose.
This is how you get
your mojo back, Pete.
No, I am there, Jack.
My job is killing me,
my family resents me,
the other day I was mugged
by what I'm pretty sure
was two five-year-olds
in a trench coat.
I already have nothing
left to lose.
No, you have
one more thing.
[Gasps]
No. Not the ring.
You're clinging to something
that's gone, Pete,
and it's not coming back.
Allow yourself to be reborn.
Your life is tied
to the fate of the ring.
It must be destroyed.
Are you quoting
Lord of the rings?
No, I'm quoting myself
talking to Bruce Willis.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't tweedle-Dee
and tweedle-black.
We need to talk
about what you did.
Well, you know
what they say, boys.
If you can't stand the heat,
get off of Mickey Rourke's
sex grill.
No, this isn't about us.
It's Lutz.
- I didn't do anything to Lutz.
- That's the problem.
He has a thing about
being left out of stuff.
The man has
self-esteem issues.
I don't know why.
Well, he is estranged
from his son
Kellan Lutz from Twilight.
I'm sorry, are you asking me
to apologize to him?
Look, yeah,
we mess with people,
but there's a line
we don't cross.
For example, after you went
through our trash,
we went through yours.
And we found this.
My self-evaluation!
I want to be famous to make
people love me
because I hate myself.
The Jenna I talk to
at night in the mirror
thinks I should kill myself.
Also, I caused that
Italian cruise ship to crash.
We could do a lot
of damage with this.
But we're not going to.
Whatever.
Hey.
How's my boy?
Working hard?
So hard, papa Lemon.
You're not gonna wanna run away
and start a new family in Ohio
and have a daughter
you also name Tracy.
Not if you're good.
I've been thinking of some
new characters for the show.
[Jimmy Fallon's voice]
This is my Jimmy Fallen
impression.
Awesome, awesome, I love it!
It's my favorite!
Wow, Tracy,
that's great.
Tracy, what's all this stuff?
Just some stuff I needed
from home, like my bed.
It's a California Kong,
which is two
California kings tied together
with gorilla leather.
- Wait, you're living here?
- I have to.
Turns out Angie's cooking
smells very ethnic,
and I definitely can't
be around my family.
I didn't expect this, but
teenage boys don't smell good.
Wait, you can't
be around your kids?
What about baby Virginia?
Do you know what she does
in her underwear?
Something I once did
at the oscars
that caused Daryl Hannah
to throw up on me.
Tracy, you can't just
abandon your family.
I've got all the family I need
right here, L.L.
Now back to work.
"Open on: Philadelphia, 1776.
John Adams and
Mitt Romney enter."
Commentary!
[Chuckles]
So stupid, Lutz.
Disgusting.
Why don't you learn your lesson
and stop trying?
That girl at Starbucks smiles
at everybody, Lutz.
Everybody!
She doesn't want
you to kiss her.
No wonder people don't include
you in things.
No wonder Kellan never wants
to see you again.
You're worthless.
[Elevator bell rings]
Kenneth, be honest.
Am I the worst person
you know?
Ms. Maroney, judging
is for God and his angels.
So, yes, you are.
Where's the writers' trash?
Oh, I've already
taken it down
to the sub-basement
compacter room.
The writers had me clean out
their refrigerator today,
so the trash smelled like, to
use a technical janitorial term,
total ass.
Kellan, why?
Okay, I know
the answer to this,
but I just need to hear it.
If I have to choose
between work productivity
and what's best
for one of my employees,
I choose work, right?
Great. Thank you.
Something about my shoes.
- Good meeting.
- Uh, which employee?
Gah, what does it matter?
It's Tracy and he has never been
more productive.
[Mumbling]
But he abandoned his family
and his baby daughter
to do it.
Lemon, I invented
business mumbling.
[Mumbling] You white garbage
bag full of pudding.
What?
Look, when you're
a supervisor, your job
is to squeeze everything you can
out of your employees,
but there's a line
and you've crossed it.
Since when do you
care about any line
other than the bottom line?
Sorkinesque Repartee.
Because I'm doing it too.
I'm taking advantage of Pete
like you're
taking advantage of Tracy.
I said I'd fill out
my self-evaluation
after I'd fixed Pete.
A task I knew deep down
- could never be accomplished.
- Yeah, he's a mess.
But Pete's just an excuse.
The fact is I can't
fill this out
because there's a question
I don't know how to answer.
"Where do you see
yourself in five years?"
For the first time in my career,
I don't know.
I could wind up anywhere.
Running this company,
making couches,
serving as mayor of New York.
Or I could be 6 feet under...
In the subterranean paradise
we built to escape the poor.
Yeah, I get it.
As a writer,
that uncertainty is the fate
that always I am
to face being.
Well, I'm not used to it.
But that's not Pete's problem,
it's mine.
You go talk to Tracy
and I have to stop Pete
from shaving his head.
Oh, God.
So, Lutz.
You thought I left you off
the hook the other day?
Well, you wish.
I spent the whole night
going through the garbage
trying to find the perfect thing
to humiliate you.
Yeah, we know.
We took photos of you
and sold them
to a garbage fetish website.
[Female speaking german]
This was all a prank?
I knew the mirror thing
would get her.
Ooh, I'm so sad.
I never talk to my son,
Kellan.
It's all made up, Jenna.
Kellan Lutz isn't my son.
He's my grandnephew
and we're very close.
Unbelievable.
I was actually doing something
nice for Lutz and...
Oh, my God.
I was doing something nice.
You took advantage
of my niceness.
Why are you smiling?
You spent the night
in our garbage.
We win!
No, I win.
On my self-evaluation, I said
I'm the worst person I know.
But it's not true!
Thanks to you guys,
I'm the fourth worst.
♪ Jenna's amazing
like a star in the sky ♪
♪ Jenna's amazing like
a star in the sky ♪
Pete, I apologize.
I never should have
told you how to live your life
like some sort of American
Barack Obama.
Commentary.
The truth of the matter is
this whole thing
wasn't even about you.
It was about me.
Really? 'Cause it seems
like it was about me, Jack.
Do you know what
was under my hair?
A birthmark.
Good God.
It looks like a swastika
made out of penises.
I know what it looks like!
Since you've been "helping" me,
my life has gotten worse.
I broke my nose, a gay rabbi
chased me through midtown,
and last night, Paula wouldn't
touch me looking like this.
Do you know what it's like
to try to have sex
wearing a child's
little orphan Annie wig?
- No.
- You know what?
You've done enough.
Get the hell out of my office.
Congratulations, I knew
I'd make a man out of you.
Get out!
There's the confidence.
Please, just leave.
Pete, you're welcome.
[Laughs]
[Knock at door]
You wanted to see me, smell?
Sit down, champ.
[Grunts]
Oh, why are you so heavy?
'Cause so much of me
has died.
Okay.
Tracy, I'm so proud of you.
You have grown into
such a wonderful person
for these last 24 hours.
But when you're a father
or even a father smell,
sometimes you have
to make sacrifices
to do what's right
for your family.
I just wanna make you
proud of me, L. L.-Dad-Liz-dad.
I know.
But there's only one thing you
need to do to make me proud.
Pop dookie down
by the vacants?
Boy, if I had a dollar
for every time I've been asked
to reverse
one of my procedures,
my bitch ex-wife
would be a millionaire.
May she rest in peace.
- All right.
- Wait, Dr. Spaceman.
There's so much
I haven't smelled yet.
A magnolia tree in spring,
the towels at
a miss Hawaiian tropic contest,
the sweat
of a terrified Webster
as you load him
into a Cannon.
Tracy, you have to do this.
Now, full disclosure,
I lost your ring
at a Bodeans concert,
so I'm gonna shove this
hilarious pencil-topper
up there.
Get a haircut, or I'm gonna
shove you up a black guy's nose.
Very well.
You leave me no choice then.
Goodbye, helpful Tracy.
Goodbye... daddy-head.
Goodbye only evidence
tying me
to my ex-wife's disappearance.
[Whimpers]
Aah!
Five years from now?
Well, I'd like
to still be working for NBC,
or whatever NBC
is in five years.
A T-shirt company probably?
My greatest strength is that
I'm a good listener.
Watch.
In five years,
I hope I don't have to do
this hat thing any more.
In five years,
I'll probably be dead
and no one will even notice,
and yes,
this is my second attempt
at writing my self evaluation.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net