Liz,
there's something
wrong with Pete.
Oh, my God, is he dead?
I... I don't know what happened.
Kenneth, I need a light bulb
replaced in my dressing room.
Easy as pie, Ms. Maroney.
What could go wrong?
Why would I even say that?
Hey, whatever
happened to TiVo?
Remember, you used
to fast-forward,
it'd make that sound?
Boop-boop, boop-boop.
Yeah. Yeah, then it'd
be all like, bung-bung.
- Boop-boop, boop-boop.
- Bung-bung, bung-bung.
Boop-boop, boop-boop.
What's this?
It's Terry, the gender-neutral
doll I had when I was a kid.
And he/she has his/her
baseball glove and baby.
And both sets of genitals!
That was hard to track down.
Today, almost all of them
are in police evidence lockers.
So, happy three-month
anniversary,
and happy two-week anniversary
of you going to the bathroom
when I'm here.
You shouldn't
be buying me gifts.
You should be saving
for your business.
Oh, I think
remembering our anniversary
is going to get
me some business.
Aww, yeah!
There's a whole other hand
where that came from, big boy.
Not my best.
Hey, listen, why don't
you go in late today, okay?
I'll make pancakes
with M&Ms in them.
Fine, I'll stay!
Gyah.
All right.
Do you want a smiley face?
German flag, please.
Jordan's comments have
angered gay-rights groups
and are likely
annoying his co-workers
who thought they'd linger
over breakfast this morning,
perhaps with a new lover.
Wow, that is some detailed
reporting, curry.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
When I say "NBC,"
you say...
Over it!
- NBC!
- Over it!
Word.
Ugh, look at that
old bag from TGS.
Okay,
I am a human being, sir.
Oh, you mean my tote bag.
Yes, I need a new one.
Look, I'm sorry about Tracy.
He really is a good person.
Do you think I'm
pulling this hat off?
No.
- From the top!
- Over it!
Oh, my God, there you are.
We're losing sponsors, Liz.
Did you know that snuggles
the fabric softener bear
is gay?
He's dating the charmin cub.
I thought they were babies.
Unbelievable.
Tracy, do you know how many of
your hard-working and dedicated
co-workers are gay?
Him. Him.
Her when she's drunk.
I genuinely don't know.
That one's a puzzler.
And why did you have
to offend the gay community?
It is the most organized
of all the communities.
They make the Japanese
look like the greeks.
How is what I said offensive,
and that's not?
Because no one
heard me say it.
Look, I need to know what
we're apologizing for, Tray.
What did you say?
Being gay is stupid.
If you want to see a penis,
take off your pants.
If I got turned into a gay,
I'd sit around all day
and look at my own junk.
Oh, my God.
First of all, if you
"got turned into a gay"?
Do you think the people of
Raleigh, North Carolina
turned Clay Aiken gay?
Why not?
The Bronx turned me dyslexic.
Look, you're a public figure,
and believe it or not,
the dumb things you say
may influence or hurt people.
You need to apologize.
I already called Glad,
Liz Lemon.
Thank you for calling Glad,
stronger trash bags
with less plastic.
This is Diane.
How may I help you?
Hey Diane,
it's Tracy Jordan.
Sorry about what I said.
- Well, okeydokey.
That's the wrong
"glad," Tracy.
Whatever. I'm tired of
apologizing all the time
for just being myself.
Remember when I offended
stubborn people?
That took forever
to sort out.
Well, Tracy,
I know you don't want me
writing an apology for you.
That's terrific, thank you.
Aww.
Lemon.
I'm on top of the Tracy thing.
I just spoke to him...
Actually, I want to talk
to you about something else.
Because of my unfortunate
situation with Avery,
I'm alone.
And I know, of course,
that you're not seeing anyone,
therefore I've decided
that you and I
should become
friends with benefits.
No, thank you, please.
Aha! The only reason
you would reject that offer
is if you had
a secret boyfriend.
Right,
that's the only reason.
I saw you, Lemon.
At the movies, last night,
with your mouth on a man.
Why would you
keep this from me
after all
of our time together?
This is hurtful, Elizabeth.
What's his name?
I don't want to tell you.
Why?
Is it a stupid name,
like "Dakota" or "Barack"?
His name is "Chris,"
and I'm sorry,
but for my own reasons...
And "Chris" is spelled?
No "h" and two "s"s.
That! Right there, that's
why I didn't want to tell you,
because I knew you
wouldn't approve of him.
Why? What does
he do for a living?
Criss is trying to...
You can stop right there.
He's an entrepreneur.
He's currently meeting with
investors in the
hopes of starting an
organic gourmet
hot dog truck.
Lemon, I have said
"good God" to you before,
but I don't think
I've ever meant it until now.
Good God!
Where does this person live?
- Don't worry about it.
- How bad can it be?
Jersey city?
His parents' apartment?
It's not a walk-up, is it?
He's actually been living
with me for the past month.
Ah.
No, I am not engaging,
I am not inviting input, Jack,
because Criss is different.
How is he different?
Well, that's just
a stupid question.
I mean,
I'm more relaxed around him.
My jaw stopped popping.
Listen.
And for once I'm not
overthinking everything,
which is why
I don't want you in my head.
Ah, but I'm already
in your head, Lemon.
The fact that you felt
you had to keep "Chris,"
and I'm saying his name
with an "h" and only one "s",
the fact that you
kept him from me simply proves
that it doesn't matter
whether I meet him or not.
You already know
what I would say,
and you know I'm right.
I'm ignoring you.
You're not here.
- Who's not here, Liz?
- I don't know, Liz.
- I love you.
- Oh, I love you too.
So I might as well
meet him and get it over with.
I'll probably love him.
After all,
we're both Princeton men.
Princeton?
No, Criss went to... no!
I am on to you. I am not
going to talk about him.
You can't keep me out.
Oh, Ms. Maroney.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
- Jenny McCarthy died?
But who could have been
slowly poisoning her?
Was she poisoned?
I have no way of knowing,
because I'm
just hearing about it.
No, ma'am,
I spoke to maintenance
about replacing the
light bulbs in your room,
but Mr. Subhas is refusing
to do any work for TGS
until Mr. Jordan issues
an apology for his remarks.
He also said
that he thinks, quote,
"sexuality is a continuum,"
and he is but
a voyager on a vast
ocean of pleasure.
- This is unacceptable,
Kenneth.
Do you understand
how important
proper lighting
is to an actress?
Especially now that I'm
officially a "B-list" celebrity,
thanks to
America's kids got singing.
Oh, congratulations,
Ms. Maroney.
I just found out this morning,
Teri Polo and Ving Rhames
called me at home.
So what if a tour came by
and some Fanny pack fatty
took a picture of me in my
poorly-lit dressing room?
And then they put the
picture on the Internet?
That can't happen.
I need my special,
pink-gel fluorescents,
and I need them now.
But only maintenance
is allowed in the supply room.
Kenneth, do this for me,
someone I hope
you consider a friend,
and who in return
thinks of you
as sort of
an albino slave-monkey.
Aw, you think of me?
Mm-hmm.
But I don't have a key.
You think we need a key?
I guess someone's never been
locked in a dog crate
and thrown overboard for
displeasing the sheikh.
A statement from TGS head
writer Elizabeth Lemon, adding...
I gotta get a real headshot.
In other news,
after lots of high financial...
And now, I am
headed home for a "nooner,"
which is what I call
having pancakes for lunch.
Liz Lemon, did you just
call me an idiot on this TV?
Yeah, but...
And what exactly
is that supposed to mean?
It means you're someone
who should know better,
but you constantly
do stupid things.
How dare you! I am nonplussed,
and that is the correct usage.
You have offended
and humiliated me.
Well, maybe now you
know how gay people felt
when you suggested
that they sit around all day
and look at their own junk.
Wait.
Why don't they do that?
Okay, you're right, L.L.
I do get how they felt.
Insulted, marginalized,
and outraged.
Which is why I'm going to do
exactly what they did
and organize
a protest of this network.
A protest? By whom?
By idiots!
What an idiot.
All right, I'm out.
I've been dealing
with Tracy all morning,
and clearly this
is only going to get worse.
Time to go into
Hornberger crisis mode.
Is that when you cry
on the floor in your office?
Nope, I do that
when I see myself
in the mirror on my birthday.
Crisis mode is when I down
a couple of sleeping pills
with scotch, pass out
in my secret napping place,
and hope I dream about
that latina security guard.
The one you always
kiss on the mouth.
That's normal in Guatemala.
Oh.
Picking a lock
is like riding a bike.
They're both skills you need
to escape the Atlanta Falcons'
equipment room.
Hurry, Ms. Maroney.
If Mr. Subhas
finds us in here,
I don't even know
what he'll say,
because I can't understand him.
There!
My pink fluorescents.
They're the same lights poultry
farms use to keep the birds
from pecking each
other to death.
Are you as turned on
as I am right now?
Oh,
we have to clean this up.
"Fluorescent lights
contain Mercury."
That's poisonous.
I'm well aware
of that, Kenneth.
I faked Mercury poisoning
to get out of my contract
- - The musical.
"If broken, remove all people
and pets from the room"?
Why? Are there fumes?
Are we breathing
Mercury fumes right now?
Kenneth. I'm going to tell you
what I told Phil Spector.
"It's gonna be okay, baby.
"We just have
to get some trash bags
"and get back here
before anyone's the wiser.
Then we can keep
recording my album."
Oh, come on, Subhas.
Got to keep daddy's
special sleepy-place clean.
Hey, so check this out.
I think I saw Billy Dee Williams
in riverside park this morning
when I was meeting dogs.
Now that seems like a good use
of time for a busy entrepreneur.
Hello, Lemon.
Chew with your mouth closed.
So, question about
Lando Calrissian...
Is that an Armenian name?
Is he a space Armenian?
I don't know.
The Kardashians are Armenian,
they're into black guys,
so there's something to it...
I like how his voice goes up
at the ends of sentences.
That's very masculine.
Oh, my. Is that a tan line
on Criss' thumb?
Did Criss used
to wear a thumb ring?
Oh, better hold on
to this one.
He's getting
a free muffin soon.
Wow, I've never seen a
sunglass hut credit card before.
Oh, a ukulele with an
Obama sticker on it.
Hmm.
this guy might suck
That was a gift
from Criss' kickball team.
Well,
I think I've seen enough.
Which totally supports your
theory that the phillie phanatic
is biologically a female.
Oh, yeah,
if you watch those games,
that thing definitely
has a menstrual cycle.
- Right?
- You gonna put on pants today?
Eh.
I'm in your head.
We're here, we're proud,
I came up with this rhyme!
You brought this on yourself,
Liz Lemon.
The so-called idiot community
will not be silenced.
For God's sake, Tracy.
We are legion.
We are America.
Frat guys, DJs,
loud-mouthed old bitches,
investment bankers,
the tramp-stamped,
parrot-heads,
anti-vaccination crusaders,
and people who won't
shut up about scuba diving.
It's a whole
other world down there.
And our celebrity
spokesperson,
actress Denise Richards.
That's right.
I'm an idiot. Surprised?
Well, I am.
For all "intensive purposes."
Our community
is mobilized now, L.L.
And we're not leaving
until we're heard.
You can't ignore us,
Liz Lemon.
We will be out here every day,
misremembering movie quotes.
Because as Braveheart said,
"you can take our freedom,
unless you take our lives."
Say you approve
of Criss, Jack.
Am I in your head, Lemon?
Yes, but don't be so proud.
I also have a lot
of imaginary arguments
with the couples
on house hunters.
Why can't people
look past paint color?
Lemon, obviously
I can't approve of someone
I've never met.
Yeah, well, I'm not
letting you meet Criss,
because you
won't approve of him.
Well, then I guess
this is a catch-22.
Although I don't know for sure,
because I refuse to read
literature that questions
the morality of war.
Look, clearly
I hurt your feelings.
You're upset that
I didn't tell you about Criss.
No, no, no, I'm quite
over your subterfuge,
although I do expect
a note of apology.
And don't try to make it funny.
Just apologize.
But I feel like
people expect comedy...
They don't.
It's exhausting.
However, you're right that I am
having an emotional reaction.
It's very frustrating
to watch someone I care about
do something she clearly
knows is bad for her,
like that week you wore
those blue contact lenses.
I looked like Adriana Lima.
And you don't know
that Criss is bad for me,
and you never will.
So you better get
on board the Criss train.
Criss-a, Criss,
Criss, Criss-a,
Criss-a, Criss-a,
Criss train!
Do you have any water?
You know what, Lemon?
Fine. You are
technically an adult.
You can do
whatever you want.
Really? So I won?
With the train thing?
I won't ask any
questions about Criss again.
You promise?
Promise.
With two "s"s.
I would, however, like
to ask you why Tracy is outside
cursing this network
on a megaphone.
It's a good one, Jack.
Tracy has organized a protest
of NBC by his fellow idiots.
He what? No, no, no, no, no.
We need idiots.
You certainly need idiots.
Who do you think
is watching your show?
Funky taste-makers?
Black nerds,
jet blue passengers
who fall asleep with the TV on,
pets whose owners have died,
and, uh, idiots.
You need to fix this.
I don't know
what to say to those people.
You wrote "remember
to DVR Kendra" on your hand.
I think you can handle it.
Ah, no, damn it.
Now I gotta
pray for a marathon.
Jiminy Cricket, copyright
Walt Disney company, 1940!
Mr. Hornberger? Sir?
Pete!
It's Jenna!
The woman you're in love with!
What's wrong with him?
Is this because
of the Mercury?
What does the box say?
"For a complete catalog
of our lighting products,
visit our website."
We need a computer.
Poor Mr. Hornberger.
He came in here to do
something for the show,
something important,
and now look what we've done.
What you've done.
You broke the lights.
We have to get help.
Are you out of your mind?
We need to call security,
and an ambulance.
Think, you fool.
Imagine what the Internet
would do with this.
"Maroney found in closet with
unconscious married man
and inbred virgin."
Again? No way.
I have too much to lose now.
I am this close to becoming
the spokeswoman for
the vaginal mesh industry.
Vaginal mesh.
Nice try, prolapse.
Now, if you want to take the
fall for this, be my guest.
But I can't be
connected to it in any way.
Take what fall?
Oh, please.
You said it yourself
how many rules we've broken.
"B" and "E", theft and
destruction of company property.
And who knows
what we've done to Pete.
If anyone
connects you to this...
I'll get fired.
They'd kick me out of
the page program faster than
a fella can come up
with folksy similes.
No one can know
this was our fault.
But we have to help
Mr. Hornberger.
What do we do?
I don't know.
But I know someone who does.
Talk to me.
I'm on my way.
Any idea what bus
I take to get there?
'Cause I'm in Chinatown,
baby.
Hi, this is
Tracy's cell phone.
Dot com,
hold the steering wheel.
I've got to leave
my outgoing message.
What did I just hit?
Was that a person?
Is that paint or blood?
Dot com,
this did not happen.
We take this to our graves!
Tracy, uh, this is Liz.
Please call my office.
My extension,
as you have pointed out,
spells "anus" with an "I".
- Hey, what's up?
- What time you coming home?
Because I'm...
taking you out to dinner
What?
I called sunglass hut and got
my credit limit raised to $80,
plus, they told me I only needed
5,000 more shades points
to get free lens wipes,
and I haven't even gotten
to the good news yet.
That's all awesome.
What happened?
I got an investor
for the truck.
I went over my whole business
plan, guy gave me ten grand.
Oh, my God.
Okay,
if you got it in cash,
we can spread the money out
on the bed
and kiss on top of it.
But nothing more.
And I have a cold sore.
Damn it.
No, it's a check.
But look at it.
It's beautiful.
It's him.
Not cool.
Who's that man
behind the curtain
His kiss
will make you certain
of the one name
you'll be blurtin'
during love-making
Kelsey, Kelsey
one touch
and you're not caring
how much you paid repairing
that China hutch that you
kicked down the stairs
during love-making
thanks to Kelsey,
his name is Kelsey
his friends
call him Kelsey
or sometimes just "Kels"
his name is Kelsey,
he's very wealthy
he doesn't have
to be doing this
Kelsey
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net