♪
Tracy, Jenna.
We all know what happened
when you hosted
the St. Patrick's day parade
three years ago.
[Celtic music]
Wake up,
mother-[Bleep].
And when you hosted
two years ago.
Die, demon!
Why didn't you
ever call me back?
Unfortunately,
unless Harry's law
really took off this week
and no one told me,
you two are the biggest stars
at the network.
But this year,
everything you say
will be scripted
and on prompter.
Do not deviate
from the script.
Jack, Tracy and I
are total pros.
On television,
and when it comes to
the assisted suicide debate.
Secret handshake,
my baloney.
Hazel,
I won't be here tomorrow,
so... I wanted
to give you this.
It's the tail I had
until I was 16.
Well, don't worry
about the parade.
I'll take care
of Tracy and Jenna
like they're
my own children.
Which is a bad example,
because I left my kids
at a sears in 2004.
Oh, I told you about
Mr. Jordan's allergies, right?
Yes, Kenneth.
He's only allergic
to allergy medication.
But he loves it.
And Ms. Mulroney's...
Kenneth, let go.
This is my rodeo now.
Well, not literally,
of course.
The U.S. Rodeo Association
does not lift lifetime bans.
So are you gonna work
through St. Patrick's day?
Don't you want to celebrate
Ireland's great accomplishments,
like Michael Lohan
and vomiting into a bagpipe?
Wow, Lemon,
so I take it
you will not be
wearing green tomorrow.
I will be wearing
head-to-toe orange,
in honor of protestant
William of Orange,
inventor of the Orange,
according to Yahoo answers.
You in Orange?
You'll look
like a creamsicle
with an old tooth
stuck in it.
Well,
you'll never see me,
'cause I don't leave my house
on St. Patrick's day.
Criss and I are going
to ride out hurricane shamrock
holed up in my apartment,
laughing at excerpts
from Angela's ashes.
You know, some people might
find your attitude offensive.
Oh, what are they
going to do about it,
write a meandering play
about how amazing the Irish are
at not overcoming adversity?
Well, I'm sorry
we can't all belong
to ethnic groups
as beloved as the Germans.
Please,
without Germans,
you wouldn't have any
of the Indiana Jonesmovies.
Lemon, your secret love
of the Irish is well-documented.
After all,
I am your mentor,
you dated Dennis Duffy,
and in the '90s,
you gave money to the IRA.
I thought it was contributing
to a retirement account.
You know, I think
someone needs to learn
a St. Patrick's day lesson.
[Speaking gaelic]
What is that?
A curse?
Take it back,
you witch!
[Exciting jazz music]
♪
30 ROCK
S06 Ep 12 - St. Patrick's Day
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
On Radio: This American life,
Saturday, March 17th,
St. Patrick's day.
You know, everybody complains
about the weather,
but today on the program,
we meet somebody who actually...
[Glass breaking]
Hey, what are you doing?
Get out of my studio!
[People cheering]
Happy St. Patrick's day!
Let go of me!
Didn't you hear
my show on bullying?
Hey, Criss,
watch this.
[Celtic music playing]
Megan!
Look at them spin around.
They're so confused.
- Awesome.
- It's too many Megans, right?
I love you.
Uh huh.
I just ordered thai food.
How much do you love me now?
[Knock at door]
Man, they're fast.
You know what, I can't wait
till the asians take over.
Thank God for delivery,
keeping us inside
and safe from
all the Irish nonsense.
Hey, dummy.
The curse.
What's up?
I'm Dennis,
- a former lover of Liz's.
- Oh.
I tried to steal beer
from a Duane reade,
and some black guy
cold-cocked me.
Ooh, like a security guard?
I don't know, pal.
I don't see people
that way.
[Groans]
No, no.
No.
Hey, before we go on,
- do you want to pray together?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Michael Jackson's ghost...
- Oh, Great Kabbalah monster...
NBC is showing the promo
I worked on for the parade!
I'm famous.
And now back to
NBC's live coverage
of the 2012
St. Patrick's day parade,
with hosts Jenna Maroney
and Tracy Jordan.
Oh, my God!
They said my name first.
But I'm more famous
than you.
Oh, this is probably
some Hollywood prank,
like on the set
ocean's 12,
when I put that snake
in George Clooney's bed.
I was not in the movie.
Or maybe now that
Kidz is a giant hit,
I'm the one
America wants to see.
You better not be
talking about
my dear friend,
America Ferrera.
Get your stuff
out of here,
'cause I get
the bigger dressing room now.
I'll replace your lizard
with a gay guy
in a giant champagne bottle.
Siri, kill Jenna!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what's going on?
I get second billing
to this small-boobied grandma?
No, you guys are friends,
remember? "My baloney"?
The only baloney Tracy has
is the baloney he's full of.
[Crying]
Why would you say that?
You can't take that back.
[Sobbing]
Siri: I killed Jenna elfman.
Is that right?
Did you show them
the promo?
Hazel, we don't let them
watch NBC.
Jenna thinks
that Christina Aguilera
lost her voice
during childbirth,
and Tracy doesn't
need to know
that he just became
number two around here.
That kind of mistake
can ruin everything.
I don't like
the way you're talking to me.
Why don't we drive to Sears?
I'll buy you a toy.
Excuse me.
May I help you?
What? We don't use your
bathroom when you're not here.
I'm Lutz.
Frank, first of all,
what are you doing here
on a Saturday?
None of the writers can
go out on St. Patrick's day
because we all have faces people
naturally just want to punch.
So we're all
hiding out here,
playing
Colonizers of Malaar.
It's a strategy board game
from the makers Goblet quest
and virginity keep.
In Malaar,
you build a kingdom
and battle
for world domination.
Right now, I'm just
the Lord of the Karthian plains,
but that means
I control all the wheat!
Huh.
It's actually interesting.
You have
a monopoly on wheat.
But what happens if you
overproduce, flood the markets?
Prices drop,
your economy collapses.
You've got
to diversify, Frank.
It's basic capitalism.
What other resources
do you have?
Uh, unicorns?
Can you breed
and sell them?
There's got to be
a market for unicorns.
If I've learned anything from
reading Liddy's princess books,
unicorn hair
has magical properties.
You've got to know
your product, Frank.
That's awesome.
Ah, it's nothing.
That kind of thinking
is what I do for a living.
At least, I used to.
You just have
to replace "Malaar"
with "Fairfield, Connecticut,"
and "unicorn" with...
"Project: Unicorn,"
a death Ray.
Hot dog truck, huh?
I went entrepreneur, too.
I got this new business
where I burn your old DVDs
onto laserdisc.
Whoa, Dennis,
I don't think you should
be drinking with a head injury.
[Laughing]
That's a good Liz impression,
Criss.
She's a bummer.
Well, 911
is still busy.
What could be causing so many
medical emergencies today?
Oh, right,
an Irish religious festival.
Irish pride!
Go, Celtics!
Celtics suck.
Go, Knicks!
As soon as I get through,
I'm getting you an ambulance,
and you are
out of here, Dennis.
No, no, no, no, no.
I can't get into an ambulance.
I don't have health insurance
because of Obama.
Look, Liz, I don't think
he needs to go to the hospital
for a concussion.
I was a volunteer EMT.
At burning man, and we agreed
never to talk about that.
At sunset,
the CACTI start to resemble
people looking for hugs.
It gets ugly, Liz.
You know, there's some things
I miss about being with you,
like having somewhere
to hook my SEGA up to,
but this constant judgment...
Criss deserves better.
Criss, may I speak to you
alone for a minute?
No. Anything you need
to say to him,
you can say
in front of me.
Me and Criss...
- We're bang brothers.
- Ugh.
♪
God, live TV's such a rush.
It's like sex,
but your husband isn't looking
at a picture of a bridge.
Peter, can you
explain this to me?
Well, obviously
I'm host number one.
We all saw the promo.
Hazel, the script had
Tracy and Jenna's names in it.
Did you change that?
Duh!
After you PMS-ed
about their names yesterday,
I thought numbers
would make everyone happy.
We're on in five,
four, three...
Both: Welcome to the 2012
St. Patrick's day parade on NBC.
They're both reading
host number one.
Would a third host help?
I am S.A.G. eligible,
but I will only do nude stuff
if there's a mirror behind me.
Forget the parade, Hazel!
For six years,
we've been tricking them
into thinking
they're friends,
and you've undone
all that in a day.
Both: I understand you have
some interesting trivia
about this year's parade.
No way,
that's amazing!
No.
I've moved on.
Both: I couldn't agree more.
I'm playing
two timber
and one brick
to build a bridge
and establish
a trading post in Midgar.
[Dice clatter]
That failed...
And the Orcs
raped everybody.
Okay, and I am offering Frank
500 gold coins
for the neutral land
between the Elf kingdoms.
- I'll double it.
- The price is now 3000.
- I'll mortgage Theowyn castle.
- I'll take out a loan.
Don't you see
what you're doing?
You're creating
a real estate bubble,
and the only person
who'll benefit is sue,
who'll buy up
all the neutral land
for cents on the dollar.
Thanks a lot, Klootzak.
I don't come to where you work
and slap the...
It's basic macroeconomics,
people.
None of you is fit
to be king of Malaar.
And you would presume to wield
the scepter of Thalbain?
Yes.
Yes, I would.
Why are you
being nice to him?
What, you want me
to be jealous?
I'm not that guy.
I'm this guy.
No, you need
to know something.
Dennis Duffy is
like the Terminator
with cheaper sunglasses.
He just keeps
coming back,
because his potato brain thinks
he still has a chance with me.
Hey, Liz, you'll be back.
If I ever see you again,
I'll kill you.
You'll be back.
- Never again!
- You'll be back, Liz Lemon.
You'll be back.
I'm not kicking Dennis out
of here in his condition.
Guy with a concussion
on St. Patrick's day
is like a horse
with a broken leg.
Exactly.
We should shoot him.
Don't you see
what he's doing?
He's already driving
a wedge between us.
Criss, get in here.
There's a lez movie on showtime.
Um...
[Dramatic music]
♪
[Indistinct chanting]
[Dice rattling]
Ugh, three again?
And your yak...
Has smallpox.
Rockefeller, no!
[Cell phone ringing]
What?
Dennis is here.
Take back your curse.
This isn't funny anymore.
Oh, really?
You're cursed?
Try ruling over
the desert wastelands of Kroth
with no spell cards.
Are you playing Colonizers
of Lamar with the writers?
Malaar, and this game
is just dumb luck.
I dug all these trenches
to irrigate the desert...
But no one's playing
his rain ca...
[Yelps]
I'm trapped
in a barren wasteland,
and no matter what I do,
I can't get out.
Wait.
[Hangs up phone]
Oh, my God,
it's happening again.
The desert of Kroth
is Kabletown.
I've got
to get some fresh air.
So fine,
two can play at this game.
I'm putting
an old German curse on you.
[Speaking German]
[Door opens]
- Hey, Dennis had a great idea.
- No.
I should take the hot dog
truck out after the parade,
and sell empty buns
to drunk people.
Oh, my God, Criss,
he's just trying to get me alone
so he can start a gas leak
or claim squatter's rights
or hit me over the head,
and when I wake up,
we're on our honeymoon.
At seaworld.
Are you sure
this is Dennis's obsession?
'Cause you're the one who can't
seem to stop talking about him.
Are you kidding?
I know Dennis Duffy's brain.
I saw some of it
when he jumped on the ice
during an islanders game.
His next move
will be
mentioning some fake girlfriend
to try to make me jealous...
But I'm going to turn it
against him.
And once again, the puppet
will become the puppet master.
What does that mean,
"once again"?
That's not a thing.
This ends right now.
Dude, you missed
the end of the lez movie.
Their daughter,
she goes off to college,
and Mark Ruffalo,
he's just gonna do
his own thing
with the restaurant.
Look, is there anyone
you want us to call
to let them know
you're okay?
I left a message
for Megan earlier,
but it's hard for her
to answer her phone,
'cause her boobs
are so big.
I'm sorry,
and who's Megan?
She's my lady, Liz.
I'm seeing someone.
She's a card girl
at kangaroo boxing matches,
so she's got a body,
and she's loaded.
Her grandfather
invented the stop sign.
Wait, are you saying
you're over me?
Elizabeth,
don't do this.
[Fake crying]
Because I am not over you.
I never will be!
I love you, Dennis.
I love you so much...
Whoa, what the hell, Liz?
No, Criss,
I'm just proving my point.
I don't care
what you're doing.
So it turns out
you can't say "I love you,"
- just not to me.
- Wait, what?
It's not like you haven't
had the chance to say it.
- Love you.
- You're the best.
- Scooby-doo.
- I love you.
- I just ordered thai food.
And I thought you were
just emotionally infantile.
I am!
Me baby.
Yeah.
I'm gonna take the truck out.
Oh, no, it's happening.
The wedge!
[Groaning]
Liz, we need to talk.
Open the bag of wine.
And we're back
with our live coverage
of the St. Patrick's day
parade.
I'm Al Roker, taking over for
Jenna Maroney and Tracy Jordan.
He should have said
my name first.
Roker should be
on my side.
Why, because you both have
had huge weight fluctuations?
[Sobbing loudly]
[Phone ringing]
[Shouting]
What?
Okay, that's not how you're
supposed to answer the phone.
Just thought I'd check in.
Everything's fine.
Pete says
I'm doing great.
I'm not about
to screw this up, Kenneth,
'cause I'd get kicked out
of show business,
and then
how would I be famous?
By starting a fire
and then rescuing everyone
from it?
And then I'm a hero
and then I'm Playboy?
Hazel, are Mr. Jordan
and Ms. Maroney fighting?
Well, you're not a page
anymore, Kenneth.
That information
is classified.
[Solemn music playing]
♪
You look troubled, son.
Would you like
to talk about it?
I'm stuck, father.
Stuck in a company
that won't innovate or change.
I feel helpless.
Impotent.
Whoa, buy me a drink first.
[Laughs]
Sorry, we've been instructed
to keep it light.
Ah.
Now there's a man
who overcame some difficulties.
I'm sure you know
the story of St. Patrick,
driving the snakes
out of Ireland.
I'm going to have to stop you
right there, father,
'cause I know for a fact
that there were
never any snakes in Ireland,
and St. Patrick didn't drive
anything out of anywhere.
Knock, knock.
First of all, he was born
in fourth century Ireland.
He might as well have been
born in a grave.
His only worldly possession
was no snakes.
But he turned that...
Huh... into sainthood,
a holiday,
this magnificent cathedral.
He was just some guy
starving in the wilderness...
Exactly like me.
But he found a way
to change his luck,
to take nothing
and turn it into...
[Awed whisper]
By the scepter of Thalbain.
Out!
Now!
[Sighs]
Look, Liz, there's something
I've got to tell you.
- Not interested.
- Megan isn't my girlfriend.
I know,
and I am not letting you...
She's my wife.
We just got back
from Seaworld yesterday,
and I know this is
hard for you to hear...
Oh, yeah, it's so hard for me
to hear about your "wife."
I'm so jealous.
Dennis, baby!
I would have
got here sooner,
but I passed out
laughing on 69th Street.
That's hilarious, Megs.
What's up, sugar?
- Hi, how are you?
- How are you doing?
Wait a minute,
Megan is real?
I thought you were
lying to get us back together.
That's why I said
I loved you.
I was trying
to call your bluff.
Wow, you know,
that's really messed up, Liz.
Okay, wait,
you said you love him?
[Laughs]
Okay.
You got two minutes
to fill a sock with quarters,
and then we go outside.
Oh, my God, stop it,
no more of this Irish nonsense.
Dennis, you came in here,
possibly as part of a curse,
and ruined everything!
What? I did nothing.
Hey, if anyone's full
of Irish nonsense, it's you.
- Excuse me?
- Think about it.
You're the one
that got all emotional
and made a fool of herself
at a party.
This wasn't a party.
Tell me about it.
It sucked.
Look, you're stubborn,
you hold grudges,
you're emotionally repressed.
She's been living
with this great guy,
and hasn't said
"I love you" yet.
Really?
Not even on a Ferris wheel?
- Ugh.
- Let's face it, Liz.
You're the most
Irish person here.
Happy St. Patrick's day,
dummy.
Wait, it's St. Patrick's day?
St. Patrick's day, baby.
[Shrieks happily]
[Sighs]
The first car is here
for whichever one of you
wants to leave first.
[Groans]
Why do I keep
doing this stuff?
Is 70 not a good IQ?
Well, the bigger star
gets the first car.
But the sign says
it's for host number two.
I'm scared, J-mohr.
And not just 'cause
today's the day
that guy that tried
to kill me gets out of jail.
I'm scared 'cause...
What if I'm not
the biggest star anymore?
Tracy,
I know how you feel.
I've felt that way
for the past five years.
And now that I've gotten
everything I wanted,
all I can think about is
how quickly it can all go away.
Tell me about it.
A year ago, I won an Oscar.
Now look at me.
I had to beg to take over
for Andy Rooney.
And it did not go well.
When I was a kid,
you could get
a prostitute for $5.
You know what?
I'll read host number two.
No.
We'll read it together.
Aww.
Know this, Hazel.
I will always be here...
For them and for you.
Nothing can ever make me...
[Over megaphone]
Move your car.
[Siren wailing]
[Indistinct chatter]
I'd like to spend
my remaining gold...
To purchase a fire spell.
And against whom will you
be casting this spell?
Against myself.
I am setting fire
to my own desert.
- You're insane!
- Am I?
I'm going to turn
my desert into glass,
and glass is a commodity
that you all need,
for your elfin
oracle mirrors,
for your crystal palace,
for the colorful
glass beads
that you keep buying
for some reason.
I'm going to wear them
to the pirates' ball.
You need my glass.
And I'll take your gold...
And eventually,
the throne of 1,000 kings.
You see, it doesn't matter
if I'm on the wind-blown
dunes of Kroth
or in the fluorescent-lit
boardrooms
of 30 Rockefeller Plaza.
[Echoing]
I will create something
from nothing.
Today Malaar...
Tomorrow Kabletown.
[Coins jangling]
Your highness, you may take
your right as king.
I am a virgin...
with white guys.
All right,
mustard only.
There you go.
Enjoy your bun.
Sorry, sorry.
These are
the only green things I own.
More importantly,
I have never been with someone
for longer than nine months.
You and I have been
together for six,
so I assume something
will go wrong soon.
You'll tell me
you believe in ghosts,
or I'll reveal
that I am terrible
at expressing my feelings.
But it's not
because I don't have them.
It's just because...
I'm used
to being let down.
Wait, is now the time
on St. Patrick's day when
we talk about our feelings?
I don't understand
your art, Kevin.
[Spluttering]
But this isn't fair
to you, Criss.
This is the happiest
I've been in a long time,
and I'm sorry that I can't
just be a normal person
and tell you stuff.
Like, nice stuff.
Like...
Greeting card stuff.
Oh, you're right there,
buddy.
Come on, homestretch.
Come on.
[Groaning]
Okay.
I love you.
I know.
[Gasps]
You solo-ed me.
[Crowd shouting]
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Both: Thanks, host number one.
Let's take a look at
what's happening live
in Rockefeller Plaza.
I love you.
Oh, I got this!
That is a person named
Liz Lemon
who just told some dude
she loves him.
Well, I have known her for a long time
and she never said that before.
Is sure as rewarding as a TV viewer when someone you're interested in shows growth.
Also, TV viewers
liked when in a show is a song.
♪Oh Danny boy, the pipes,
the pipes are calling♪
♪From glen to glen, and
down the mountain side♪
Don't you dare fade out on me.
www.tvsubtitles.net