♪ Cleanup, cleanup ♪
♪ do your own housework,
you little crackers ♪
- what?
- My kindergarten teacher
was a former black panther.
Oh.
Hey, I'm gonna fix that
loose baseboard upstairs.
Wow, look at you,
all sweaty with your tool belt
and your '90s haircut.
You look like
you're in a gay porno.
Oh, yeah?
You're one to talk, buddy.
I'm Brent.
I'm the new guy on the crew.
I'm Rod.
I'm the boss.
And what I say goes.
I've never been
with a man before.
Looks like
I'm the boss now... Rod.
- Oh! What are we doing?
- I don't know.
Whatever! Let's wrestle!
It doesn't matter.
Liz, what is "adoption stuff"?
- Are you adopting a kid?
- No. Don't worry.
That's from a long time ago.
It's not happening.
You have a baby name book,
and you circled Adolf?
Actually, I borrowed that book
from my mother,
so be glad I'm not a boy.
Okay, well,
why'd you give up on it?
I have to work late tonight.
What am I gonna do with Joshua?
I thought I could do this
by myself.
You know what?
Murphy brown lied to us.
She had Eldin.
Can you hold that, please?
You closed the door on her?
The point, Criss,
is I didn't want
to be that woman.
I didn't want to do it alone.
But let's face it.
Murphy Brown had
the whole fyi gang
in her corner...
Jim Dial, Frank Fontana, Corky,
even Miles, in his own way.
Yeah, but you're not alone now,
and if a kid is something
that you still want,
and you're in your 40s,
then...
We should...
we should have a...
we should have
a serious conversation
right now.
Oh, my God, relax.
This is my life, and I love it.
I've got my job,
and I've got you,
and I keep getting
my neighborallure magazine.
If there's anything that needs
fixing in my life,
it's a certain loose baseboard.
Okay, well, I'm gonna fix it.
And do not send Brent up there.
I won't.
Dude, I'm back
from the hardware store.
Sync and corrections by Sp8ky for
www.Addic7ed.Com
this country's taken
some hits lately.
But when we get hit
and are down,
we don't stay down.
We get up, and we hit back
with our fists
or our nunchakus.
And then, when we're done
hitting and we're tired,
'cause nunchaku-ing
can wear a guy out,
we sit down on a couch,
an American couch...
A Kouchtown couch.
Damn.
Lemon, do you know
you are sitting
on 5,000 new jobs?
And not jobs that came
from some government bailout.
They came
from a rich white guy.
We have been creating and
solving this country's pRoblems
for 200 years.
Where's our history month?
It is a nice couch.
Good lumbar support.
Absorbent fabric for nap drool.
That's just the prototype.
As we speak,
our fellow countrymen
are rolling the new
Kabletown couches
off the assembly line,
earning an honest day's pay
so they can go to the store
and buy milk for their families,
which costs...
I don't know, $90 a gallon?
I'm meeting
with the vendors tomorrow,
Raymour and his
conjoined twin, Flanigan.
Ashley of Ashley furniture
will be there,
and he is a genitally
androgynous pinhead.
Hmm.
It's a colorful industry
with a lot of fun characters.
Well, good luck fixing America.
I hope success
isn't far, far away.
What aboutstar wars
do you want to say, lemon?
Let's just get to it.
I did some spring cleaning
this morning,
and I found this
baby princess Leia costume
that I bought years ago,
and I thought
it might fit Liddy.
Oh, thank you, lemon.
It might be a bit small
by Halloween.
Halloween?
A girl can wear this anywhere.
School, church,
alone on the playground,
a child therapist's office.
Also, I thought you might want
this Nixon biography that my dad
gave me for my birthday.
It had just come out,
so as a joke,
my dad signed it as Nixon.
Yes, a joke.
Nixon's been dead
almost 20 years,
not in cryogenic hibernation,
resting up for 2016.
I'm getting rid of all my junk
so Criss can redo the upstairs.
Wow, you two
are really nesting.
Yeah, all that's missing
is the joint
answering machine message.
I'm thinking Sonny and...
Cher.
Lemon, I know
how this will be received,
but before it's too late,
let me set you up with someone.
Oh, my God.
Come on, Jack.
My colleague is newly single.
His name is Kevin.
I'm gonna stop you at Kevin.
Has anyone ever known
a good person named Kevin?
Kevin garnett
helped me move once.
I'm good, thanks.
Kevin costner cooked me dinner
after a bad breakup.
Kevin Sorbo intRoduced me
to his podiatrist.
This is an outrage.
I didn't get to work
an hour late
just to be the first one here.
I'm sorry, tray.
I don't know where Jenna is.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I was busy burning down
the panda express
that I had fallen in love with.
Oh, my God, Jenna.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Liz.
I'm just having
a celebrity breakdown.
It's the new sex tape.
Something I wish I'd known
before I released my sex tape
with the six flags guy.
- So this is just for attention?
- Exactly.
Anyone who's anyone
has had a breakdown.
"Da-mi", "de-mi",
Heather, Lindsay,
Britney, Muammar...
so sad.
A life cut short.
He gave the best diamonds.
Okay, good.
I thought maybe you were
really losing it,
because, you know,
Paul's with someone else and...
oh, no.
This is for Paul.
You see,
when you have a breakdown,
all your old lovers
come out of the woodwork.
Justin and K-fed,
Bruce and Ashton,
Samantha Ronson
and Herbie the Lovebug.
This is how I get Paul back.
Wow, that is idiotic.
But as long as it
doesn't affect work...
what's that, celestia?
All right.
I'll do it.
Mr. Donaghy, hi.
I'm Stewart der.
I'm the chief engineer
here at Kouchtown.
Do you know the history
of this building, Stewart?
During world war ii,
the Bazooka Joe corporation
used a softer version
of their gum
to make armor-piercing
bullets... Here.
Years later,
the government took it over.
They turned it
into a training facility
for single mothers
to teach illegal immigrants
how to fill out
unemployment forms.
But then we took it back.
Ah, good morning,
fellow patriots.
Keep voting republican.
We've got your back.
Now let me have a look
at this marvel
of American industry.
Good God!
This doesn't look
like the prototype.
Looks more like the prototype
than most things in this world.
How could this happen?
The one in my office
was perfect.
Oh, we didn't make
the prototype.
We bought it at west elm.
Besides you,
whom do I fire for this?
I don't know. You?
I mean, you're the one
who insisted on hiring
American engineers.
All they teach us now is
how to build rollercoasters
and survivor challenges.
This is what we've been
making for the past month?
We have 10,000 of these?
I wouldn't know.
I'm not a math guy, really.
This is only a setback.
I just have to create a market
for terrible couches.
Besides, what did
Theodore "Bazooka" Joe do
when his eccentric
millionaire father
left him nothing
but a tiny pink rock quarry?
He baked those rocks
and sold them to children.
As gum.
Tracy, I need your input.
I cannot give it to you.
I'm a married man.
But more importantly,
I find you very unattractive.
No, I need your advice.
I'm having
a celebrity breakdown.
I've been there, j-mo.
What's the matter?
Partying too hard
with Christian slater?
Furious about Nafta?
Y2k panic?
My heyday was the '90s.
No, Tracy, I'm faking it
to get Paul to come back
and take care of me.
Fake breakdown.
Interesting.
I thought next I'd go nuts
on thetodayshow,
really blow it out.
Jenna!
Did Hamlet start the play
by stabbing people?
No.
He started by being boring
and ruining my anniversary,
'cause Angie wanted
to take advantage
of "all the great theatre
in New York".
Okay, I get it.
You have to build
to the big breakdown,
like in
a c+c music factory song.
My heyday was also the '90s.
So what have you done so far?
Well, I've acted crazy at work.
And I think this blind item
in the post
is about me.
"What teenage a-lister..."
get serious!
We have work to do.
Hey, want to watch Mythbusters?
Mm. Can we have sex after?
'Cause those guys always put
fuel in my tank.
Who is
cigarfan@nbcuni.Com?
"Avail 4 javamanana per Jack.
Deets 2 follow. Kev"
who is kev?
Oh, my God.
He gave him my email?
Who gave who your email?
Okay, I know you're not
gonna be threatened
or jealous about this.
'Cause I got it going on?
Jack is trying to set me up
with some d-bag
he works with.
"Sent from one of
my four iPads"?
This guy sounds amazing.
Obviously, I'm not going.
Let me just write him back
in his language.
"Broseph.
Sor-sor on the haps..."
no, you know what?
You should go.
What, are you kidding?
No, if you don't go,
you're not gonna be able
to tell Jack
how wrong he is.
If you do go just have coffee
with this guy,
maybe Jack will shut up,
and I'll finally get
the acceptance
that, you know,
every 39-year-old man craves
from his girlfriend's boss.
I do like telling Jack
when he's wrong.
And maybe Kevin
will insist on paying,
and I can get a jazz cd
and a ham sandwich.
"Dudely, let's make coffee
our bitch."
When did we get so soft?
You know what this country
used to sit on?
Logs.
Girders.
Poles.
Being comfortable?
That's not what America's
all about.
Kouchtown.
Sit down or get out of the way.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Help, I can't move.
Tell me, can you even look
at the television?
I can see the floor.
I can see the veins
behind my eyes.
Oh! I can see pain!
Come.
My whole body is asleep.
Oh!
That's a bad couch, Jack.
It is unfortunate.
The design forces the sitter
into what Israeli
military interrogators call
a stress position.
Oh.
It cuts off circulation
to the legs
while simultaneously
spreading out the ribcage,
making it difficult to breathe
while the body begs
for oxygenated blood.
It comes in espresso,
dandelion,
putty, and,
as you see here, lagoon.
So you're gonna just try
to sell discomfort?
I don't have a choice.
If I blow this,
Hank hooper will never give me
another shot.
I'll spend the rest of my career
behind this desk
trying to lure alf
back to television.
Okay, Jack.
Well, I'm gonna go meet
your buddy Kevin now.
Yes, he mentioned
you were getting together.
And you certainly are
dressed to impress.
You look like
a substitute teacher
who just got
her one-year a.A. Chip.
Well, I'm just doing this
as a formality, Jack.
Lemon, I know
you don't trust me,
but keep an open mind.
I'll do my best,
but I watched, like,
thrMythbusters last night,
so I'm pretty exhausted,
if you know what I mean.
Our next guest has had
a troubling 24 hours
that has the tabloids talking
and her friends... Concerned.
Let's take a look.
Thank you.
Dhanalakshmi,
I'm happy for you,
and I'm gonna let you finish,
but I just gotta say,
Gurubarath Kurrupuswami spelled
one of the toughest words
of all time!
That's yesterday afternoon.
Here you are
earlier this morning
being asked to leave
dick Cavett's birthday party.
That's unfortunate.
Then a kleptomania relapse
ending in orgasm and arrest.
Wow, Jenna Maroney
has gone crazy.
She sure has,
said the second guy.
Jenna, I know a lot of people
are asking,
are you okay?
Matthew, I'd really prefer
to just talk
about my upcoming project.
Me running through that window.
Aah!
Right this way, folks.
Mr. Donaghy will be with you
in just a moment.
I'm so sorry.
Where I'm from,
Uncle Sam's mouth is sewn up,
and then he's set on fire,
so I don't know how he talks.
Greetings, gentlemen
and female eunuchs
of the furniture industry.
I give you a new couch
for a new era,
designed and manufactured in...
America.
It's a simple couch.
Oh, good God, my leg!
I can hack it.
Pain is in the mind.
Oh, sweet heaven.
It's like I'm full
of lightning.
Jack, it's Ethan Allen.
Are you all right?
What do you want to know?
I'll tell you anything
to make it stop.
You want secrets?
I'll give you secrets.
This couch...
Is a failure.
I hate golf.
One time in college,
I smoked a clove cigarette.
I keep buying candles as gifts
and keeping them for myself.
My natural hair color
is bright red.
Agh!
Amateur hour.
Ugh!
Agh.
Good luck finding
someone stupid enough
to buy those couches, Donaghy.
Everybody loCate your buddy,
and let's make our way
to the subway.
I'm sorry, sir.
If I could buy your couches,
I would.
You know,
that's exactly what you'll do.
Okay.
And will you accept dancing
as money?
Kenneth.
Drag me to my office.
Agh!
I issued a statement
on your behalf using Twitter.
A media-savvy crackhead,
I know.
I said that you were being
treated for exhaustion
and that you wanted
to thank your fans
for all their support,
and also, you saw Tracy Jordan
do 11 pushups.
I just hope this works.
Well, some of your
former loved ones
are already here.
David Blaine.
I can see that you're
on a skateboard, David.
This is why we broke up, Jenna.
I know we only spent
one night together.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
That never happened.
Sure it did.
I ate a pizza slice
off your back.
At one point,
your veneers fell off,
and you had
these little baby fangs.
Thank you, Frank.
It feels like only yesterday
you were in my gym class,
Jenna.
Now, you weren't the only
student I dated,
but you were the only one
who shot my wife.
Jmo, these are
from Mickey Rourke.
No! Tracy, put them down!
I don't know.
Maybe 'cause I'm
a season ticket holder?
Hi, you must be kevi...
no. No, let me fin...
let me finish.
- Are you...
- He's my dad.
It's "take your daughter
to work" day,
which I object to
on feminist grounds.
It's patronizing.
Like girls don't know
what jobs are.
I'm Liz, by the way.
I'm Catherine,
but everyone calls me Cat.
Although I'm trying to get
people at school
to call me scout,
like in to kill a mockingbird.
I love that book.
I had my first crush
on a shop teacher
who looked
just like Boo Radley.
Yeah, scout's not getting
much traction, though.
Well, it's hard
to force a nickname.
I tried to get
my high school tennis team
to call me ace,
but they wanted to call me
shorts accident.
So we settled on supervirgin.
Okay, so I might not get scout,
but I can negotiate up
from puked in thermos.
Well, then,
let me ask you this.
Would Jeremy lin be willing
to videotape a message
for my buddy's bachelor party?
Ugh.
Sorry. She's with me.
It's "take your daughter
to work" day,
and Kabletown's really
into all this family shiz.
So what have you learned today?
That people who talk
the most in meetings
often know the least.
She sat in two meetings
with me.
I crushed it.
So what's your deal?
You ski?
I don't. You know, if I'm
gonna fall down a hill and die,
I want to do it for free.
Brian. What is up, slick?
Do you think
I could pull off a haircut
like scout had in the movie?
I've been there, Cat,
and you should know
that people are gonna assume
that you're...
I'm a lesbian?
I know.
I just needed to hear it.
So, what do you want to
be when you grow up?
Either the wicked queen
inDisney on ice
or the third woman president.
Well played.
I am giving you gum for that.
Where is he?
Where is "kev"?
It's game go.
What are you doing?
What...
game go is not a phrase.
I don't know.
I just got really wound up
at the thought
of you getting checked out
by some creep.
And he's in trouble, too,
'cause I watched
some boxercise videos
on demand
before coming down here.
Hi. I'm Criss.
This is Cat.
This is Kevin's daughter.
She's awesome, unlike Kevin,
who is wearing a rope bracelet.
And I did not give it to him.
People assume I gave it to him,
but I'm like, "you're not
pinning that on me."
I can't believe
you really came down here
to try to fight my date.
That hasn't happened to me
since senior prom,
when Rob Sussman tried
to fight Richard Sallatto
because they had secretly
broken up with each other
the night before.
Why are you so out of breath?
'Cause I ran
all the way down here.
Why didn't you just take
the subway?
'Cause that's not romantic.
Watch a movie, Liz.
I wish my boyfriend
did stuff like this,
but I feel the passion is gone
since he left for college.
I'm totally messing with you.
Guys, I'm 11.
Oh, thank God.
That is not funny, young lady.
It's a little funny.
I'm sorry, j-mo.
I called the front desk,
but there's
no one else down there.
Paul didn't come.
I guess I faked this
stupid breakdown for nothing.
Jenna, I've been thinking.
Why? You're famous.
I know, but I don't think
you were faking anything here.
Maroney, you jumped
through a window.
You made out
with paz de LA huerta
at a children's museum.
You tried to dine at balthazar
without a reservation!
And you did all that to get
some guy's attention.
That's crazy.
That's a breakdown.
I think I've made
the biggest mistake of my life.
I've never made a mistake,
so I don't totally understand,
but I'm here for you, J.
Of all the crazy things I did,
you know what the craziest was?
Letting Paul go.
I was scared to be happy.
Now I never will be.
I'll take this regret
to my grave.
You mean our grave.
Where we'll lie
on top of each other
in one coffin,
pelvis to face, for eternity.
You were here the whole time,
taking care of me.
I was afraid too, Jenna.
I had to be sure
that you wanted
the same thing that I did.
And now I know.
You sick bitch.
Tracy, if you'll excuse us.
No, Paul.
If it wasn't for Tracy,
we wouldn't be here right now.
He can stay.
No, I'm cool.
I'm gonna leave.
- Lemon, how did your date go?
- It was amazing,
but not in the way
that you would expect.
Cat's a great kid, isn't she?
You really thought
I'd set you up with Kevin?
I've been trying to fire him
ever since he invited me out
on a Halloween party bus.
But his daughter's terrific.
So you set me up
on a play date?
I thought Kat
would remind you why
you purchased
the princess Leia costume
in the first place.
Don't give it away just yet.
That's very nice of you, Jack,
but you need to learn
that some women
choose to be childless
and are content with that.
This is not a choice.
Oh, you are being so
trans-vaginal right now.
The past few days
have only confirmed my fear
that we're running out
of good Americans,
so honestly, your country needs
a few more Liz lemons.
Oh. Okay.
So this has nothing
to do with Criss?
I don't care how you do it.
I don't care
if you join the big sisters
and torture inner-city girls
about punctuation.
Any amount of lemon
is better than the crap
we're turning out lately.
Exsqueeze me, Mr. D.
Couches are ready to ship.
In trucks.
Ship in trucks.
What?
Wait, you sold them?
To whom?
I just had to find a buyer
who has too much money
and loves to waste it.
So every defective sofa
that Kouchtown makes
will be purchased
by your beloved
tax-and-spend government.
What are they going
to do with them?
Sink them and make a reef
to protect gay turtles?
I don't know, lemon,
and I don't care.
Mr. wang,
we know you were spying
for north Korean intelligence.
Give me something
I can take back to Langley.
Then we'll get you
out of the couch
and send you home
with a CIA gift bag.
I totally blew off
that week of Korean we did.
Let's get the translator.
- I think maybe I still...
- I don't think you should...
- want to be a mom.
- Give up on having a kid.
Okay.
We're on the same page.
I think we've talked
about it enough.
Maybe we just put a pin in that
and have some fun.
I'll open a puzzle.
I'll make a stew.
Life is happening.
When did gum get so soft,
you sons of bitches?
You know what this country
used to chew?
Tree bark.
Glass.
Shotgun shells.
The broken swords
of our vanquished enemies.
That's why I buy
Bazooka Joe gum.
It's like chewing a Mountain
that someone shot
a freeze ray into.
What's wrong
with this country? Huh?
When did we lose our way?
Detroit?
Life is hard.
Shouldn't everything else
be harder?
Bazooka Joe gum!
Sync and corrections by sp8ky for
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net