Previously on 24:
I´ll be right back.
Renee!
(Jack grunts)
Oh, God...
(gasping breath)
You said you had video file
implicating people inside
the Russian government who were
responsible for Renee's murder.
I want that file.
Tell me where that file is,
now!
It's in a safety deposit box!
Where?
DANA:
First Unity Savings.
I had nothing to do
with Renee's death, Jack.
No.
You never give up, do you?
(beep)
(loud pop)
LOGAN:
Bauer may have Walsh,
but he can't have
the evidence yet.
We've still got a chance
to stop him.
I'm not the only one
who can prove
that elements
in your government
conspired to undermine
the peace process.
So you expect me to
kill Bauer for you?
You have the covert assets
here to do the job.
Maybe I do.
But I don't have the
resources to find him.
CTU does.
And the man in charge
of the search now
reports to me.
We got him.
Once they have Bauer, I'll find
out where they're holding him.
You'll have to take him out
while he's in custody.
Freeze!
Police!
Do not move.
(cop grunting)
(woman screaming, gunshots)
Jack...
tell me what I can do.
Nothing.
(gunshot)
(over radio):
Mund, this is Captain Walleki.
I'm on scene. You got
that guy from the bank yet?
Just bringing him
up, Captain.
Right.
It's Cole Ortiz.
He says he's with CTU.
WALLEKI: You were with
this woman at the bank.
Do you care to tell
me who she is?
Her name is Dana Walsh.
Shot twice
at close range-
lot of powder residue
around one of the entries,
like an execution.
WALLEKI:
Thank you, Mund.
Get him to CTU,
now.
DANA: The hit on
Hassan is all arranged.
Bazhaev and his people are
taking care of everything.
Well, I'm pleased
to hear it,
but you could have just as
easily called to tell me that.
DANA: I wanted to know if you've
spoken to your superiors...
told them that I'm out
after this goes down.
I told them
what you wanted.
He feels the same as me:
we have too much invested in you
to let you walk away.
You should be focused on getting
the E.M.P. device into CTU,
not on your boyfriend, Ortiz.
DANA: He's my fiancé, and I
told you to leave him out of this.
I warned you to stay away
from him, but you didn't listen.
And now you think
you have feelings for him?
You think you love him,
going to marry him?
Yes.
I am.
And if you
have a problem
wrapping your brain
around that fact,
maybe I should talk
to your boss in Moscow.
You talk to no one but me.
We're done here.
Don't contact me again
until Hassan is dead.
(phone rings)
Yeah?
Hey, it's me.
I sent you
a DAT video file.
Okay. I got it.
It's uploading right now.
Okay, I need you to get me an
I.D. of the man in the video.
Also, I'm coming in hot,
so whatever you have to do
to protect your systems from
getting flagged, do it now.
What about the woman?
You need an I.D. on her?
She's dead.
I'll see you
in a few minutes.
All right.
Jack Bauer's last known location
was First Unity Savings Bank
on Lexington,
where police responded
to a 911 call,
apparently from Dana Walsh.
She's dead now.
Bauer killed her.
Cole Ortiz,
who is known to be
aiding and abetting Bauer
is being brought here
for questioning.
Now, I need everybody
not committed
to the U.N. security task
to devote their full attention
to finding him.
I want all cameras routed
through facial recognition
and all phone calls monitored.
You don't have the bandwidth,
you steal it from other tasks.
If you think you have a lead,
you bring it to me immediately.
Any questions?
Why did they go to the bank?
Dana said she
had evidence
of Russian involvement
in Hassan's murder.
Maybe that's where
she was stashing it.
There's no evidence;
the president dismissed this.
Well, she went to the bank
with Jack to get something.
Yeah, what she got
was an explosive device
that made possible her escape.
It was her plan
all along.
Look, Jack Bauer
can't accept the fact
that Dana Walsh was
an enemy agent
working solely
with the I.R.K. opposition
to Hassan's government.
His... grief over Renee Walker's
murder is causing him
to create this fantasy
about a Russian conspiracy.
The simple truth is,
he's lost it,
and he's a danger to himself
and the community.
So let's stop second-guessing
the operation,
and find him.
(slaps table)
Something is
seriously wrong here.
Pillar's ignoring
the key questions,
and the questions that he
is answering, no one's asking.
What are you getting at?
I think Jack's right:
this is a cover-up,
and Pillar's involved.
That evidence was
at the bank, and Jack
has it.
You don't know that.
It's all
speculation.
It may be just like Pillar says.
Until I know otherwise,
I got my orders.
(scoffs)
I'm clear.
Well, you
weren't kidding.
You said you were
coming in hot.
All the police scanners
are talking about you.
They said you shot
and killed some woman.
Construction site
on the East Side.
Was that the same woman
in the video
you sent me?
Yeah. Did you I.D. the man?
No. I'm not going to, either...
till you tell me what the hell
is going on, Jack.
You saw the video.
Dana Walsh is a
Russian operative.
She facilitated
the assassination
of President Hassan
and the dirty bomb attack
that would have wiped out
the entire Upper West Side
if we hadn't
stopped it.
I don't want to know
about what happened today,
and I don't care;
I want to know
why you're out there on your own
and why everybody's after you.
Because the president tried to lock me down.
Why?
Because I know she's
trying to cover up
the Russian's involvement
in today's attack.
Then why didn't you disappear?
Because I can't!
Listen, I want
to help you, Jack.
I really do.
I need you to be
straight with me.
Tell me exactly
what's going on.
The Russians took
something from me.
Her name was Renee Walker.
They killed her
inside my apartment.
And I need to make them pay.
All right.
Actually, I did I.D. the guy.
(typing)
There he is: Pavel Tokarev.
Primary operative,
Russian intelligence.
Where is he?
I don't know exactly.
He's in the USA.
Came in a month ago
on a diplomatic visa.
(scoffs) Diplomat.
I tried to access
the Russian database
in the embassy.
He didn't show up
in the consulate.
He could be
anywhere, Jack.
To keep everything quiet,
they'd have to be
a small unit, right?
Yeah.
I think I've got an idea.
Get me a secure line.
Meredith. I didn't expect
you'd still be here.
Oh, fact check called:
there are a few items
left on the
Hassan piece.
Abby can follow up
on it for you.
I know. I just... I need
to make sure it's right.
I know what he meant to you.
It shows in this
piece you wrote.
What a great man he was.
You've done him justice.
I hope so.
Miss Reed, there's
a call for you
on 3.
Thank you.
Let me know if
there's anything you need.
Thanks, Gary.
(sighs)
(sets mug down)
This is Meredith Reed.
Miss Reed.
Who is this?
My name is Jack Bauer.
Please don't say anything;
just listen.
The people that you think
are responsible
for killing President Hassan
were not working alone.
They were being
funded and managed
by people working inside
the Russian government.
How do you know this?
I have proof of this:
a video file that was made
by a Russian agent
working out of CTU.
She made it
for her own protection.
It explains everything that
happened in the last 24 hours.
Have you contacted the
authorities about any of this?
I can't.
I'm being set up, just
like you were yesterday.
I need to get
this evidence to you.
There's a coffee stand
on the third floor
of Turner's Department Store.
Do you think you get there
in the next 20 minutes?
(panting):
Miss Reed...
yesterday I helped
clear your name.
Right now I need you
to help clear mine.
Please.
(sighs)
Of course I'll help you.
I- I want to know the truth
as much as you do.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
Where's Bauer?
I don't know.
You're in some trouble here,
Cole.
I assume you're aware of that.
Luckily for you,
I'm in a position
to make all that go away.
I reviewed your record.
You've had a exemplary career
up to now.
You're Pillar.
That's right.
Jason Pillar.
I've been asked by the president
to oversee the effort
to retrieve Jack Bauer.
Madam President?
Yes.
So you're a part
of the cover-up?
Oh, I see here
you served in Fallujah.
I- I spent two tours
in command of a marine unit
in Baquba myself.
We're both soldiers.
So you understand, when
the commander-in-chief deems
a course of action necessary
to the national good,
it's not our place
to question it.
The truth is:
we're on the same side.
We both want what's best
for our country.
Bauer doesn't care about that.
He didn't give a damn
about what happened to you,
just as long
as it served his needs.
He used you.
So let's start over.
Do you know where Jack Bauer is?
Probably somewhere
with the evidence you guys
keep saying
doesn't exist.
You really don't want
to be playing with me.
(headset beeps)
What?
Good news:
we may have a line on Bauer.
We intercepted a call.
Last chance.
You don't take it,
there's nothing
anyone can do
for you.
Take him to holding.
Arlo got a cell phone
intercept report
off of NSA's Echelon.
Keywords: Hassan, Russian
government, Jack Bauer.
Did Arlo hear any of the conversation? No, not yet
- all he's got
so far are
the data handles,
but he's processing
the voice matrix now.
Are we sure
it's Bauer?
No, not yet, but the
other side of the call
was a phone registered
to Meredith Reed.
She's the reporter
CTU arrested last night
before the first attempt
on Hassan's life.
Rumor has it she was
also his mistress.
If Bauer was going
to reach out
to someone with
the evidence,
she would be an
excellent choice.
Arlo, stop
what you're doing.
Tag and lock
the intercept download
and send it directly
to Eden's system.
She'll take it from there.
That's not necessary, sir.
I said I want Eden to handle it.
Thanks, Arlo.
JACK: There's a video
file that was made
by a Russian agent
working out of CTU.
She made it
for her own protection.
It explains everything that
happened in the last 24 hours.
REED: Have you contacted the
authorities about any of this?
JACK: I can't. I'm being set
up just like you were yesterday.
I need to get
this evidence to you.
There's a coffee stand
on the third floor
of Turner's Department Store.
Do you think you can get there
in the next 20 minutes?
Jack Bauer.
PILLAR (over phone):
Yes, sir.
We confirmed
the voiceprint.
So...
take it to the press-
that's his next move.
It appears to be.
Reed's connection
to Hassan means
she'd be
highly motivated
to help him.
And he hasn't shown
her anything yet?
No, sir.
Which still means
that we, we don't know what
the evidence actually is.
Well, it will be
in our hands soon enough.
This is a major
opportunity
to make everything
go away, sir:
Bauer and the evidence.
I've already dispatched
the Russian ops team
to the location.
They'll be in position
well before the meet.
NOVAKOVICH:
You need to deal
with local law
enforcement,
make sure Pavel
has room to move.
PILLAR: Yes, we're deploying
NYPD away from the site,
but we'll still
need your guys
in and out as
quickly as possible.
Understood.
Jason, this is, this is
a major break you've got,
a major break.
Thank you, sir.
We'll shut this down.
I want to stay on top of
this personally, Mikhail.
So will you let me
have Pavel's number?
Can you make this room
less public?
You wanted me for something?
Yeah, the call
you intercepted-
the one
that Pillar hijacked-
do you think
it was from Jack?
I can't be sure.
The program hit on keywords
Hassan, nuclear, Bauer,
but all three have been
in the news
in the last
few hours.
But the call was
to Meredith Reed's cell phone.
She's a journalist with
an interest in the Hassan story.
Plenty of people
could be calling her.
Doesn't have to be Jack.
Okay, then explain this.
Cell intercept report
comes in here.
Two minutes later
Pillar downloads
the entire conversation
into a segregated server
surrounded
by firewalls
like I've never seen.
Then what does he do?
Call one, call two,
call three.
Who'd he call?
I don't know.
They're outside of CTU and
they're all completely masked.
So the question is this:
if the call was nothing,
then why are they
still hiding it?
If the call was Jack, then
why haven't they dispatched
CTU SWAT team?
Why haven't they alerted NYPD?
Arlo,
they're in on the cover-up.
Look at them.
Why?
Why would they want to do that?
Because he knows
too much.
He's gotten a hold
of Dana's evidence,
which proves
the Russian involvement
in Hassan's assassination.
They can't let him
go public with that.
That's why I have
to find him,
and I need your help.
Okay.
How do you
want to do it?
I'm gonna talk to Cole.
He just spent the past two hours
with Jack and Dana.
He must have some idea
of what Jack's up to.
Pillar's got Cole
continuously monitored.
You can't get in there
without being seen.
We'll create a loop and graft it
into the security feed.
That's the
other problem:
they added an extra layer
of oversight to our system.
Second I try to move
beyond my security clearance,
I get an on-screen warning.
They're watching
everything we're doing.
Okay, fine.
We'll use this,
create a mobile hot spot.
That way we can work off
our own net without Pillar
breathing down
our necks.
Got it.
(beeps)
Setting up
alternate network
now.
We're up.
Okay, I'm restricting
access
to you and me.
How long will it take
you to make the loop?
I can only give
you 90 seconds.
Anything more than that,
somebody will notice.
Okay, text me
when you're set up.
âª âª
Fredericks,
McDermott was injured
in the E.M.P. blast,
so I need you
to collect
the night shift
time cards
and take them
to my office.
Okay.
Like now?
Yes, ma'am.
We put a loop
in the security feed.
I've only got
90 seconds,
so I'm gonna get
straight to the point.
I need to find Jack
or else they're gonna kill him.
Who's gonna kill him?
Pillar and whoever
is working with him.
You need to tell me
where he is.
I got no idea.
You were at the bank with him;
he must have said something.
Hey, what Jack says
and what he does
are two very
different things.
He's trying
to expose the cover-up.
He doesn't give a damn
about any cover-up.
He's taking out anyone who was
anywhere near Renee's death,
starting with Dana.
She gave him the evidence
and he killed her anyway.
She took the gun out
of the safety deposit box.
She was probably
shooting at him.
He shot her point-blank.
He executed her,
just like she said he would.
There e no
good guys here.
Jack, Pillar...
they end up killing each other,
maybe it's
the best thing.
No, Jack's my friend.
If I can find him,
I can talk him down.
These people are just
going to kill him.
I need you to be
on my side.
(scoffs)
Everybody wants me
on their side.
Who am I
fighting for?
If we can get to him,
we can expose the cover-up.
You just stay here
and feel sorry for yourself.
I'm gonna go find him.
Wait.
Look, it's not much, but Jack's
got to be working with someone.
Who?
I don't know; I never saw him,
but Jack showed up
with state-of-the-art
weapons and comms,
so he's got to have
a contact in the city.
You want to find Jack,
you find his supplier.
Thanks.
(exhales)
(dialing)
Arlo.
You got out in time.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. Listen,
I know what Jack's doing.
Pull up his files, get me the
list of his known associates
in the tri-state area, anyone
he's worked with in the past.
Okay.
In the next half hour,
the man who has widely
been acknowledged
as the vital "third partner"
in the peace process-
Russian President
Yuri Suvarov-
will touch down at JFK.
He'll be ferried
into Manhattan by helicopter
and then to the U.N.
(no audio)
(phone vibrates)
Yes.
Pavel, update, please.
My team is in position.
Any sign of Bauer?
Not yet.
I need to know.
What about the woman?
The woman?
The journalist, her disposition.
Ms. Reed is aiding and abetting
a terrorist.
She's a serious threat
to both our countries.
Do what you have to.
(phone beeps)
I see from Ethan's notes
that we still have not
completely resolved the issue
of site access
for the
inspection teams.
I believe it was resolved.
President Hassan agreed
the inspectors would have right
of passage over
our entire country.
But he exempted schools.
Only primary schools.
Omar didn't think
ten-year-old children would be
building nuclear missiles.
Of course.
I remember now.
I- I do apologize.
Are you all right,
Madam President?
It's been a long day.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Madam President.
If you'll excuse me
for a few minutes,
there's someone I need to see.
Of course.
Where is he?
He's in
the conference room, ma'am.
Thank you for seeing me,
Madam President.
I have good news.
We've located Bauer.
He-He has the evidence, but...
Charles, you assured me
that that
wouldn't happen.
Please, let me finish.
We know exactly
where Bauer will be
and when, and-and
we have an operation underway
to reacquire him
even as we speak.
Believe me, this is good news.
(inhales and exhales loudly)
Let me know as soon
as it's resolved.
I need to get back
to the negotiations.
Just... There's just
one thing, Madam President.
Uh, we are three hours away
from the signing of the treaty.
Isn't it time
for my role in the process
to be officially recognized?
I was thinking
some kind of, uh, announcement
to the media, perhaps
by your press secretary,
or maybe even by you yourself,
Madam President.
It was, you'll recall,
our agreement
that I would have a public face
on this historic day.
I believe I've earned it.
I will talk to my
press secretary.
She will make the announcement
in time for the
1:00 o'clock news.
Thank you very much,
Madam President.
We have contact.
Target heading
to the third floor escalator.
Acknowledged.
I see her now.
We have eyes on Reed.
Reed is confirmed.
Units 2 and 3,
Reed is approaching you.
Confirm contact.
Reed confirmed.
Approaching the meeting place.
Any sign
of Bauer?
Where is he?
He should be here.
No sign.
Pavel, do you see Bauer?
Not yet.
Unit 1,
report.
We have no visual of Bauer.
WOMAN: Jason,
where are you going?
There he is.
He's heading up towards...
Damn it, I lost him.
All units,
Bauer is on the third floor.
Do you see him?
I do not have him.
What?
He's there. We see him.
Get your eyes open, damn it!
I have not seen him.
EDEN:
Got him.
PILLAR: Bauer is approaching
the target from the southwest.
He's got a brown
leather jacket and jeans.
EDEN:
There he is.
PILLAR:
Pavel,
he's in view.
He's closing in on the café.
You should have a clean line
on him.
Pavel, if you have
a shot, take it.
I've got him.
Put it down.
Everything's all clear
up at the top, Jack.
Got her. Come with me.
Do exactly what I say. Okay.
All units, target is
in the open. Take him out.
I repeat: take him out.
You stay down here. You
don't move. Oh, okay.
Don't move!
All right.
(people screaming)
(gunfire)
(Meredith gasps)
(screaming continues)
JACK:
Move!
Okay.
What the hell just happened?
He knew it was a trap.
Don't let them out
of your sight.
We lost him.
Just keep looking!
REED: Those people you shot
- who were they?
Russian operatives.
You have any problems?
No.
Let's go.
(sighs)
Jason. Tell me.
I'm afraid I have bad news, sir.
All of Pavel's team is dead,
and Bauer has Pavel.
He was ahead of us
from the get-go, sir.
He must have anticipated
that we'd use Echelon,
and he put out a series
of keywords, knowing
the listening stations
would pick them up.
He played us, sir.
He knew we'd use off-book
resources to deal with him.
He used that journalist
to draw them out.
Now, sir, I hardly need
to tell you that the situation
is grave.
Pavel knows everything.
He ran Walsh;
he set up the Russian ops.
If Bauer gets Pavel to talk...
But at the moment, sir,
you still have
complete deniability.
President Taylor made
all the decisions.
I think the time has come
for you to distance yourself
from this mess.
It's regrettable,
sir, deeply so,
but I believe it's
what's best for you.
You...
20 minutes from now,
the president's press secretary
is going to make
an announcement.
She will say
I have become part
of the president's team,
and-and I have been
indispensable
in bringing this peace process
to a successful close.
Sir, may I say that
that is a bad idea?
You need to distance yourself.
What? You keep using
that phrase.
What-What does distance myself
mean?
Do I just slink away?
This isn't your fault, sir.
There were circumstances
we couldn't have anticipated.
Namely Bauer.
Well, then, we find Bauer,
and we neutralize him.
We're public now,
Jason.
We're committed.
And I have worked...
We...
We have worked too hard
just to throw this all away.
Do you understand?
Yes, of course, sir,
but Pavel...
No.
Pavel is a good soldier.
He won't talk,
whatever Bauer
does to him.
I, uh...
I put you at CTU, Jason,
for a reason.
They have huge resources.
You have intelligence
and tenacity.
You use those
capabilities.
Find Bauer.
Yes, sir.
I'll head down
to the scene myself.
Good.
Keep me posted.
He wants to move forward.
Does he understand
what actually happened?
Yes, but he says
we still have options.
(sighs)
I need to know
you're with me on this.
(sighs)
Yes. Yes, I'm with you.
Good. I'm heading out.
I'll clean up the scene, remove
all trace of the Russians,
and get on Bauer's trail.
I'll take CTU
SWAT with me.
Tell NYPD to put a two-block
perimeter around the store.
No one goes in or out
without my say-so.
What reason do I give them?
National security.
Anyone gives you a hard time,
invoke the White House.
(sighs)
Any luck with
Jack's associates?
No. Even discounting
dead people,
and people
from foreign countries,
it's still going to take hours.
I think I can narrow it down.
I just picked up a 911 call
from Turner's in Midtown.
There was a oot-out,
people killed.
I managed to get into
the store's security system.
Oh, my God.
That's Jack.
They're trying to kill him.
Yeah, that part
of the plan
didn't go so well.
I tagged the footage
15 minutes before
to 15 minutes
after the shooting.
If we run facial recognition
on the camera feeds...
We can match it to the database
of Jack's associates,
maybe find out who
he's working with.
Thanks, Arlo.
No problem.
Copy the camera footage
to my screen.
I'll send you half
the personnel files.
We're clear. Let's go.
Let's go.
Where are
we going?
Over here.
Empty your pockets
right now here.
(Jack mumbles)
We'll be safe here
for a while.
(sighs)
(zippering)
RICKER: Jack? We
don't have much time.
(panting)
Take off your coat.
Now!
Those people
you killed...
you were ready for them,
weren't you?
You knew they
were coming.
Yeah.
So you...
you knew they'd be listening
to our phone call.
Isn't that right?
You used me to draw them out,
right?
That's right.
I could have been killed
back there!
You weren't.
Now, pick it up.
I said
pick it up!
REED: What about the evidence
you said you'd tell me?
Was that a lie, too?
No.
The evidence is
on this memory card.
When you see it,
you'll know it's real.
Take it.
My partner's gonna take you
somewhere to show it to you.
I'm sorry things had
to play out like this.
I didn't see another choice.
REED:
What are you gonna do?
Put your hands
behind your back. Now!
Don't do this, please. You
don't want to do this. Take her
to the storeroom.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Please, you cannot do this.
The evidence
I gave you
doesn't tell me
how Walsh was involved.
He will.
Come on.
No.
He's a human being!
You cannot do this
this way!
Sit over there.
Springfield, M1A rifle.
.308 round.
You know, about four hours ago,
I had a friend of mine-
very good friend-
named Renee Walker was killed
by a rifle just like that.
Go to hell.
(grunts)
(chuckles wryly)
You first.
DANA (on video): The hit
on Hassan is all arranged.
Bazhaev and his people
are taking care of everything.
You talko no one but me.
We're done here.
Don't contact me again
until Hassan
is dead.
To be honest with you,
Renee Walker was more
than just my friend.
But you already know
that, don't you?
Because you saw us
in the bedroom of my apartment.
Now, you're either not very good
at what you do...
or you wanted her to suffer.
Because with that rifle
from that range,
it was an easy kill shot.
But instead,
you shot her...
(quiet grunt)
right there...
two inches
below her heart,
so she would
bleed out slowly.
I watched her
gasping for air...
as the blood
slowly filled her lungs.
She died in agony,
which is exactly what
I'm gonna make you do
unless you tell me
what I want to know.
(grunting in pain)
(yells)
(gasping in pain)
(Pavel yelling in pain)
(yelling)
Start talking to me!
You want to know
I killed your girlfriend?
I killed her.
I kill your bitch!
I did it!
(Jack yells, blows striking)
Please... please,
you've got to stop him. Please.
He needs answers,
and he's gonna get 'em.
I can use this.
There's enough here.
I don't need any more.
Tell him I don't need
any more. Please.
You're not going anywhere.
(blows landing in distance)
(Jack grunting)
(yells)
(panting)
(indistinct radio transmission)
MAN:
Let's go.
Move aside. Move. Move.
Please step back
from the bodies.
This is now
a CTU crime scene.
I need all weapons
and documents you found
on these people.
This is all we got, sir.
None of them
had I.D.s on them.
This is the man
we're looking for.
His name is
Jack Bauer.
Now, you need to spread out
and check every floor
and every exit.
He has a hostage with him,
so he won't have gotten far.
Bauer's armed
and extremely dangerous,
so if you don't want
to end up like these people,
shoot on sight.
Let's go.
Hey.
So, why don't we
start this again.
I already know that
you killed Renee Walker.
What I want to know...
is the name...
(grunts)
of the Russian pig
inside your government
(grunts)
...that gave the order.
Give me a name, and
I'll end this quickly.
I give you my word.
You think you know about pain?
You don't know
anything yet.
(screaming)
Give me the name of the person
inside your government
who wanted Renee Walker dead!
Give me the name!
(screaming)
Who gave the order?!
Who inside your government
wanted Renee Walker dead?
All you got to do
is give me the name!
(low grunting)
(flame whooshing)
You are so stupid.
Renee Walker wasn't
a threat to you.
Her work was finished.
She was done. We were out.
All you had to do
is leave us alone.
Now, why couldn't you
just leave us alone?
(screaming)
I want the name
of the person
who gave the order
to pull the trigger!
Who gave the order?!
Now!
Did it on my own!
You're lying. You're nothing.
You didn't have the authority.
I want the name!
Give me the name!
My name is Pavel Tokarev.
(clicks on flame)
(screaming)
(flame stops)
(panting)
This isn't working.
Damn it!
Where's the SIM card
for your phone?
Where's the SIM card?!
Where'd you drop it?
You dumb bastard,
you swallowed it.
You swallowed it.
This is for my friend.
(gasps)
(grunts)
âª âª
What do you got?
Fine. There's another
service hallway.
Check all the service
hallways over there.
Make sure they're
locked down.
You guys, I want you to go up
there, stay on the third floor.
Do it now.
(panting)
PILLAR: You've reached the mobile
number of President Charles Logan.
We can't take
your call right now,
but if you leave a message,
we'll get back to you
as soon as we can.
Transcript by .com
Sync by addic7ed.b3
www.tvsubtitles.net