There's an irk splinter cell
trying to smuggle weapons-Grade
Uranium into the city.
Just read the threat assessment.
Look, i need you to shut down
all bridge and tunnel traffic
Into the city.
where'd he go?
There's only one way
for them to get in.
Across the east river.
That's right.
Ctu was just hit by an emp.
All of our systems are down.
It's a real mess.
Where's jack?
I think he might be
in some kind of trouble.
We need to find him.
You need to get ctu
back on line as soon as you can.
Once you acquire
jack's position,
You can direct me to him.
I have a faster way
to get us back on line.
They won't listen.
then you need
To make them listen, chloe.
Do what you have to do.
Frank haynam, senior engineer
at the new york field office.
I hope that you're here to help,
because we can damn well use it.
You going in through
the clr processor?
That's right. We're gonna
create a brand-New subnet.
That'll take forever.
I think
i can create a workaround.
Why not tap directly
into the trunk line?
What i'm suggesting
will be a lot faster.
I'm here to clean up your mess.
You need to leave.
You get out.
Get out!
We got power to comm.
Load the rods into the zodiac.
It'll be short work
Once we get the rods
across the river.
a vehicle is coming.
wait until the suv's in range,
Then take them out.
Get down! Now!
I've got two men
leaving the doc in a boat.
They're carrying a box
the right size and shape
For the rods, jack.
Jack, i got through to ctu.
They just got back on line.
Nypd's sending choppers.
We still got a real good shot
of finding them.
oh, god.
I know you're involved
with that robbery, miss walsh.
What?
You are out of your mind.
I'm not leaving here
until i know the truth.
Ctu is back on line.
I know.
Their helicopter's
searching the river.
They're getting close.
We're going to need your help
getting clear.
I will get you
out of there.
Stand by. I'll call you
in a few minutes.
You have grade iii
level bruising.
Are you sure you don't
want any painkillers?
They're wrapped tight.
They'll be fine.
I can't know
if the ribs
Are broken without an x-Ray.
You should see a doctor.
Any more stress could cause
the lung to collapse.
Trust me,
they're not broken. Thanks.
Renee: are you sure
you're okay?
Fine.
Where are we at
with the fuel rods?
We found the zodiac
partly submerged
In the river
near 11th street, empty.
The rods are
in manhattan, jack.
It's not over yet.
Ctu doesn't think we're more
than a few minutes behind.
Who's running the ground op? Cole?
Yeah.
Okay, i want you
to contact chloe.
Get her to download archival
photos from 11th and the river.
Have her date 'em
back 15 minutes.
Fire it up. I want you ready
to go as soon as
We've got a target.
Sir, just spoke to a witness
who said he saw four men
Unloading the contents of a
metal crate into a yellow cab.
He didn't get a plate.
Chloe, can we roll back
satellite?
We can now. Nsa
just rerouted them.
I'm logging onto
their server now.
This is from
one minute ago.
I'm rolling back in
30 second increments.
This is from six
minutes ago.
Find them
in real time, chloe.
Arlo, alert nypd. Dana?
Right here, sir.
Contact hazmat
And nest teams,
get them mobilized.
Right on that.
Almost there, sir.
okay, i'm live.
Suspects are proceeding
west on 14th street.
Cole did you get that?
Yes, sir.
On the move.
they've located you
on satellite.
How far away are they?
Not very. Hold on.
Arlo: nypd confirms
they have units on the way.
Hastings: how far out?
Ten blocks
Coming from the north.
Head to the south.
Turn left.
Suspect just turned
south on seventh.
Got it.
I hear sirens.
Hurry up.
Just a second.
I'm inserting
the machine code now.
Just get ready.
Satellite will be disabled
for 30 seconds.
On my mark.
Go.
What happened?
The trunk line just went out.
Get it back!
Cole, we just lost picture.
Last known location--
Seventh and waverly.
Copy that.
Where are you now?
On the hudson,
heading uptown again.
You'll run into ninth avenue.
You'll be able to blend
into cab traffic there.
Back up.
Cab's gone.
Find it!
Scanning.
Arlo, help me
widen the grid.
You take west of seventh,
i'll take east.
Widening it now.
anything?
Not yet.
You, chloe?
No. We were out for 30 seconds.
They could be anywhere.
Cole, we're back up,
but we lost them.
I'll have nypd cordon off
the area.
You have them check
Every garage, warehouse,
loading dock.
They must have pulled in
somewhere.
Yes, sir.
Get me the president.
Are we clear?
Yes.
Good. We're moving
the weapon into place
As soon as it
is assembled.
I need you to send me nypd
patrol patterns and checkpoints.
As soon as it's safe.
That's not good enough.
I need them now.
My instructions
were to help you,
Not jeopardize my cover.
I will call you back
when i can.
Madam president,
i'm afraid i have bad news.
Despite our best efforts,
The terrorists have gotten
the nuclear rods into manhattan.
How good
is your intelligence?
Are you sure?
We are, sir.
In fact we had a visual
on the suspects
Until a few moments ago.
What happened?
We lost them.
We're launching a
multiagency search
In the area we
think they're in.
That you think they're in?
Will you be able
to find them, or not?
We're doing everything
in our power, mr. Kanin,
But right now i don't
have an answer for you.
Madam president, i'm sorry
to have to tell you this...
I can no longer guarantee
the safety of manhattan.
How the hell
could this happen?!
Ctu had one priority: to make
sure this didn't happen!
It's unacceptable!
Mr. Hastings, i want you
to consider the entire resources
Of the government
at your disposal.
Whatever help you need,
we must find those rods.
I understand, madam president.
We also need to
prepare for the worst.
I want all branches of
local law enforcement ready
To respond to an imminent
radiological attack.
Yes, ma'am.
Ethan, set up a situation room
And assemble
the national security team.
Has president hassan
Been evacuated from the un yet?
He will be shortly,
but as of right now,
He's still at the un.
Get me jack bauer.
Yeah, but how long
was the satellite was down?
What, 30 seconds?
Yeah. I know what
you're thinking, jack.
Odd we lost the feed just as we
were closing in on the target.
Who was running point at ctu?
Chloe o'brian.
You know her from before, right?
yes.
And you trust her?
With my life.
Mr. Bauer, i have
president taylor for you.
Cole, i've got to call you back.
I got the white house
on the line.
Hello?
Jack, it's president taylor.
I'm calling to ask you a favor.
Anything, ma'am.
President hassan and his family
are being evacuated
From the un and brought here,
and i would like
For you to supervise
that operation.
With all due respect,
madam president,
I think i'd be much more helpful
staying in place
Here with
ctu. Besides,
Secret service
is more than capable.
Well, that may be true,
but i'd feel a lot better
Knowing you were on the job.
Jack, in light
of the threat to new york,
President hassan's role
In securing a lasting peace
is more crucial than ever.
I need him safe.
I understand, ma'am.
I'll leave
for the un immediately.
Thank you, jack.
I'll see you when you get here.
Yes, ma'am.
She wants me
to supervise hassan's evac
To mcguire air force base.
All right, let's go.
Renee.
Renee, i need to do this
on my own.
We're not going
through this again.
I'm coming with you,
end of discussion.
Do you have the rods?
In the trunk.
Where is ali?
He didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
Tarin will take his place
as driver.
How long before
the device is functional?
All we have to do
is load in the fuel rods.
Tarin.
Get ready to leave.
I want to place the bomb
As soon after i talk
to the president as possible.
agent o'connor.
Jack bauer.
I know who you are, sir.
I've been briefed
by command at mcguire.
Ms. Walker.
Agent o'connor.
We're cleared
for a subterranean evacuation.
The feeling is
that president hassan
Will be safer
underground in the event
Of a radiological attack.
Agreed.
How many agents?
There are seven secret service,
Including myself, two of
hassan's internal security,
And now you and ms. Walker.
What's the time frame?
Ten minutes.
There's a service tunnel
that runs parallel
To the path lines
leading into new jersey.
We're just waiting
on the vehicles now.
I'd like to see the exact route.
Of course.
I have the maps
and evac protocols
In the conference room,
But president hassan is asking
to see you first.
He's in the council chamber.
Fine. You two get started.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
Sir.
Mr. Bauer.
President taylor
wanted me to supervise
The evacuation
of you and your family
To mcguire air force base.
So i'm told.
And i'm glad for it.
How long will it take for you
And your family to be ready?
We're ready now.
My wife and daughter
are in the residence
Awaiting your instructions.
Give us ten minutes
And then we'll evacuate you
and your family
Through a service tunnel
under the building
And straight on to new jersey.
And here i thought i would be
leaving the united nations today
At the head of a peace march
down fifth avenue.
My president still thinks
that might happen, sir.
I hope she's right, mr. Bauer.
Me, too, mr. President.
Give us ten minutes.
We need to talk about
a response, madam president.
I've prepared three
Retaliatory
strike scenarios
Against targets inside the irk.
do i need to remind you,
General brucker,
the islamic republic
Is an ally?
You don't.
But what good is an ally
If its citizens can
Attack us
on their own?
Madam president,
A call's come into
the white house switchboard
From a man claiming to be in
possession of the nuclear rods.
He wants
to talk to you.
Do we believe
he's who he says he is?
Confidence is high, ma'am.
He's offered details
Of recent events that no civilian
could know, plus he's
On an anonymous icc
channel that's scrambled
And impossible to trace.
Put him on speaker.
This is president taylor.
Good morning,
madam president.
This is going to be
a short conversation.
Who are you
and what do you want?
You know i have
the fuel rods.
You know i got them
into manhattan.
What i want now
is to convince you
That i have no desire to
harm innocent americans.
And yet you're
threatening them with a bomb.
Actually, a radiological
dispersal device,
Madam president,
capable of contaminating
40 square blocks under
a dense radiation cloud.
Any attack
on the united states
Will prompt a retaliation
against your country.
I would expect
nothing less.
But you should
listen to me.
What i'm asking
for is simple.
Turn over
president hassan.
What?
He's a traitor to his people
and must stand trial
For his crimes.
That will never happen.
You have exactly one hour
to change your mind.
Mr. Woods knows
how to contact me.
Madam president...
The clock starts now.
40 squares blocks--
How many people is that?
Between a 100,000 and 150,000.
Rob, inform
Ctu of the threat,
but the ransom demand
Stays in this room.
Tim, call up
the new york guard
To support first
responders,
And have the military
police execute
An evacuation plan.
Yes, ma'am.
Madam president?
What is it, rob?
Well, i'm just going to say it.
We should consider
the alternative.
What alternative?
We have an out here.
I think we should take it.
You mean, give in
He demand to turn over
President hassan?
No one man
Is worth the lives
of tens of thousands.
And you know what? I bet
He would agree.
Madam president,
are we really having
This conversation?
Doesn't it
Deserve a conversation?
Not unless you're intent
on destroying
Our moral authority.
This country's unique place
among nations, maybe forever.
As opposed to what?
The irradiation
Of all those people?
Real businesses,
real homes
Uninhabitable
for a hundred years or more?
Madam president,
I agree.
Giving up hassan is wrong,
But a 40-Block wasteland
at the heart of new york city
Is unthinkable.
This country would
never be the same.
The country would Crucify us
if word ever got out
That this could
have been avoided.
Now we're talking politics,
for god's sake?
We're talking about the primary
role of government--
Any government-- Which is
To protect its citizens.
It could also escalate,
Madam president.
They attack us,
We attack them back.
The entire region could be
drawn into the conflict
And destabilized.
Excuse me, general,
But weren't you the one
just advocating
For a retaliatory strike?
Well, in the military,
We like to talk about facts
on the ground.
Well, they have changed,
madam president.
Now, we have
a viable option.
Viable?
Is that the sense
in the room then?
That surrendering
President hassan
is somehow viable?
In the first place,
The people who are offering us
this deal cannot be trusted.
How do we know they won't
detonate the bomb anyway?
Secondly, president hassan
Is a guest of this country.
He is my partner in peace.
And i will not sell him out
To the very terrorists
that we are determined
To defeat.
And finally,
Caving to any terrorist demand
Weakens this nation
immeasurably.
Now, we have 60 minutes
To find these
bastards.
And i believe we will.
But if we don't,
and the worst happens,
We will deal with it.
We will pick ourselves up off
the floor and deal with it.
Why? Because that's what
we do.
Americans don't stay down.
We rise up together
in times of crisis.
We carry on.
Is that clear?
Start the calls, tim.
Yes, ma'am.
Chloe, i need
an updated list
Of road closures
and checkpoints.
I thought arlo was
interfacing with nypd.
He is, but national guard
units are on their way,
So are teams
from fbi new jersey.
I want to know where the holes
are, so i can plug them.
I'll forward it
to your screen now.
Thank you.
yes?
It's me.
Do you have the roadblock
information?
I'll have it for you
in five minutes.
Did you speak
to president taylor?
I did.
Her response
was as i anticipated.
But as the time pressure builds,
she'll change her mind
And give up hassan.
I'm certain of it.
What if she doesn't?
Then we'll strike
a hard blow against the city.
Either way,
the peace process dies.
It's ready.
I don't have time to deal
with these anymore.
Mr. Weiss?
Can i have a word?
Certainly.
I thought
secretary kanin's
Point was a good one.
If we simply turn
hassan over,
We risk damaging the good
name of the united states.
What are you suggesting?
Uh, a third way.
A covert action
in which we
Deliver hassan
to the terrorists,
But make it look like
they took him hostage.
Two birds, mr. Weiss.
We spare new york
And we preserve our reputation
In the eyes
of the world.
I admit, i'm intrigued.
But...?
It'll never fly.
You heard the president.
She won't go for it.
Not in a million years.
No, of course, she won't.
The question is,
Will you?
I'm asking
For your cooperation, mr. Weiss.
For the good of the country.
Well, even if i agreed to help,
it's too late.
Hassan's already
on his way here.
No, it's not. A wet ops
team was mobilized
In the event of a strike
against the irk.
If you get me hassan's exact
route, i can redirect them
To intercept
his security detail.
I don't have access
to that information.
It's being handled through
The secretary
of state's office.
Then we just have to get it
from mr. Kanin.
It's sedition, general brucker.
Are you familiar with the fourth
nuremberg principle?
If the orders
of the president
Are illegal,
it is our
Moral obligation
to disobey them.
And you think they are? Illegal?
The president
is letting her idealism
Get in the way
of her responsibilities
As commander in chief.
It's hardly the same thing.
You don't think so?
With the fate of
an american city in the balance?
"The primary role
of government is to protect
Its citizens."
Your words, mr. Weiss.
It's time to decide
whether or not you meant them.
The white house just received
credible intelligence
That the terrorists
we've been tracking
Plan to detonate
a radiological device
In new york city
in less than 50 minutes.
all of us in this building
have friends
And family who live in the city.
We know we are
Bound by law not to warn them.
But we also know it is still
in our power to protect them.
We are their
last line of defense.
That is our job.
That is what we will do
With every second
of every minute we have left.
Starting now.
Go back through
all your leads.
Appeal to your sources
one more time.
Find that bomb.
I just heard from our source
inside ctu.
Based on the roadblocks,
amsterdam is closed off,
But there's a potential
target area just to your left.
You'll be avoiding
nypd checkpoints
To the south and west.
All right.
Turning.
Can you park
in that block?
Yes.
Good. The fallout radius
will include a good part
Of the upper west side.
I'll wait for your call.
How many men
on the detail?
Eleven. Hassan's own security,
secret service,
And two former agents--
Jack bauer and renee walker.
Why is bauer involved?
The president trusts him.
And believe me, he's not
someone to be taken lightly.
Oh, he's up against
an elite team
Who will have the advantage
of surprise.
Bauer and his people
don't stand a chance.
The loss of life is regrettable,
mr. Weiss.
No one feels this more keenly
Than a soldier
who's led men into battle.
But right now,
we don't have a choice.
ethan.
What's going on?
Oh, i'm sorry.
I thought you were
with the president.
I was.
What are you doing in here?
Oh, i asked mr. Weiss
To pull up the latest
white house readiness protocols.
He couldn't log on
from his computer,
So we were trying from yours.
I was also reviewing
president hassan's itinerary
To see if we could facilitate
a military escort.
Hmm.
Open the door.
I'm afraid
i can't do that, mr. Kanin.
Then get out of my way.
Rob?
Ethan, listen, i...
No, you listen to me.
I think i have a
pretty good idea
What's going on here.
Sit down, mr. Kanin.
There are some things
you need to know.
There sure as hell are.
But i'll stay where i am,
If you don't mind.
Ethan, do what he says.
Sit down, please.
this is bauer. Go ahead.
I said, go ahead.
Give me your phone.
General...
Get your hands
off of me!
wait!
This is beyond madness.
The two of you will spend the
rest of your lives in prison.
Maybe, mr. Kanin.
But my guess is that one day,
The country
will thank us for it.
Rob... i'm begging you.
Don't do this.
Don't betray your president.
ethan? Ethan?
All right.
Ethan!
My god! Ethan!
Okay.
Oh!
Ethan, here, here, here.
Call 911.
We call for help,
the first thing
He does is get word
to the president.
But he's having a heart attack!
We can't just do nothing!
We didn't do nothing;
you gave him his medication.
Well, it's not working.
Look, i realize
that you two are close.
But this is not
an emotional decision,
This is a tactical one.
We wait to acquire hassan
Before calling an ambulance,
understand?
What if he doesn't
make it that long?
We have to pray that he does.
All right?
All right.
Come on.
We pick up the service tunnel
under third avenue.
From there, the trip
to mcguire by convoy
Is less than 30 minutes.
Thank you, ms. Walker.
Secretary kanin,
this is jack bauer.
I can see on my phone
that you just tried to call me.
Please call me back
as soon as you can.
Thank you.
This is bauer. Patch me through
to mcguire air force base.
How far are you from an access
point into the tunnels?
Uh, based on
what i'm looking at,
Less than two miles.
Well, the security detail's
already on the move.
Can you get there in time?
Yeah, if we haul ass.
And the ambush
happens where?
At the vehicle, sir.
Remember, the objective
is president hassan.
Do what you have to do
to take him alive.
Yes, sir.
Good luck.
Thank you. Have him call me back
as soon as possible.
renee.
Yeah?
Secretary kanin
tried to call me.
Now he's not
answering his phone.
The operator at
mcguire air force base
Can't find him either.
Something's not right.
Keep your eyes open.
Hold up.
We set?
Yeah, the vehicles
To transport the
hassans are 200 meters
Up the tunnel.
There is a section
Of construction we
couldn't get by.
unit one, this is mcguire.
Your route to gate 4
has been secured.
Did you walk it?
Yes, sir. All clear.
Get the family.
This way.
Our suvs are a short hike
up the tunnel.
Stay together as we
move towards them.
This is bauer.
Patch me through
to secretary kanin.
here they come.
Man 2:
is hassan with them?
Yes.
Masks on.
Take your positions.
Wait until the targets
are in the kill zone.
Remember, we need
to take hassan alive.
secretary kanin?
Just a minute.
Yes, what is it?
Excuse me, sir, but jack bauer's
calling for secretary kanin.
Well, the secretary
is busy with me right now.
I understand
that, sir,
But mr. Bauer's persisting.
He says it's very important.
He's holding on line one.
All right, thank you.
I'll take care of it.
Jack, hi. It's rob weiss.
sir, we're in
a service tunnel under...
I'm sorry,
you're breaking up, jack.
Can't hear you.
I said, we're in
a service tunnel under the un.
We're evacuating president
hassan and his family.
Is everything all right?
You tell me.
Secretary kanin tried
to get ahold of me
About ten minutes ago
on his private cell.
I've been trying him ever
since; he won't pick up.
Well, the secretary's tied up
With the joint chiefs
right now, jack.
Do you know what he wanted
to talk to me about?
Honestly couldn't say.
I could've been anything.
I don't think so.
He knows we're conducting
a sensitive evac.
He called me during it.
There's got to be
some kind of a connection.
Well, i'll make sure
he gets the message.
Mr. Weiss,
I don't think you understand.
I need to talk
to secretary kanin now.
That's not possible.
What do you mean,
it's not possible?
We're dealing
with an imminent
Terrorist attack
on our soil!
Just do your job
and let us do ours!
all due respect, sir,
i am doing my j...
Hello? Hello?
Son of a bitch
just hung up on me.
He's under a lot of
stress; they all are.
I don't give a...
agent o'connor, stop.
Start walking
them back now.
Something's not right.
We're gonna head back
to the un, reassess there.
Let's go.
President hassan,
i'm very sorry,
But you're too exposed
down here.
Whatever you think
is right, mr. Bauer.
They're turning around.
How far are they?
About a hundred yards.
Okay, take out
as many as you can.
Renee!
I need you to get
president hassan
And his family to the side
tunnel and back to the un!
What about you?!
I'll be right behind you!
President hassan,
You need to go.
Now. Now!
Okay, go.
Go, go.
Go! Go!
Your orders are to
stay with president hassan.
You need to go.
I know what
i have to do, sir.
Good luck.
Thank you, sir.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Now!
See if you can get wide
and outflank them.
I'm going to try to draw them
into a crossfire.
Shoot only on my command.
Engage.
Mr. President, we
need to keep moving.
Your people are being
slaughtered, mr. Bauer.
We need to help them.
They're buying us
the time we need.
Don't let it
be in vain.
We need to go now!
Give me a weapon. No.
I've been a soldier,
mr. Bauer.
I can handle a gun.
I'll fight with you.
Mr. President, my job
is to protect you.
You need to do what
i say. Now, go!
We to keep moving.
Come on.
come on. We got to go.
Renee, we're not
going to make it.
Take cover.
Go! Go!
I'm going to head up the middle.
As soon as i set these off,
i want you to start firing.
Doesn't matter if
you hit anything.
Just make some noise.
Mr. President?
You take care
of your family.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Mathis! Donner! Go!
Move! Move!
Move! Move! Move!
I'm going to take
the high ground.
In about five seconds,
start giving me cover fire.
Okay?
Take the weapon off.
Take the weapon off now!
Now!
Who are you?
You're making
a huge mistake.
You're american.
Why did you attack us?
Because a dirty bomb will
be detonated in new york
Unless we deliver hassan
to the terrorists.
What are you
talking about?
A ransom demand has been made.
Him for the bomb
by 06:15 hours.
Jack, that's less
than 20 minutes.
Does the president
know about this?
She's refusing to deal
with the terrorists.
This is
general brucker's operation.
Get up. Get up!
What are you doing?
I'm going to get you
up to the street level,
Where i can make
a phone call.
There's no time for that.
This is on you now.
You have to deliver
hassan to the terrorists.
I don't take orders
from anybody
But the president of the
united states. Now, move.
keep moving.
Yes?
Why haven't i heard from you?
Because i don't know anything.
What does that mean?
Are the americans
handing over hassan, or not?
The only information we have
Is that he's being transported
to mcguire air force base.
We lost communication
with his security detail
About 20 minutes ago.
So president taylor
doesn't intend to give him up.
Samir... think for a minute.
You use that bomb,
you lose your leverage.
The president leaves me
no choice.
The blood will be on her hands.
Samir!
tarin?
Yes?
The president
has not responded.
Start the countdown.
You need to stay with the bomb.
Make sure no one interferes
with it.
Tarin, did you hear me?
Yes, i heard you.
Your name will never
be forgotten, my friend.
Your family will be
honored above all others.
www.tvsubtitles.net