Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Sync: Brownie
Previously on 24.
This is Meredith Reed.
Ms. Reed, the people that you
think are responsible
for killing President Hassan
were not working alone.
They were being funded
and managed by people working
inside the Russian government.
How do you know this?
I'm being set up, just like you
were yesterday.
I need to get this evidence
to you.
Arlo got a cell phone intercept
report off NSA's Echelon.
Keywords: "Jack Bauer."
PILLAR:
We confirmed the voiceprint.
Reed's connection
to Hassan means
she'd be highly motivated
to help him.
Take it to the press.
That's his next move.
This is a major opportunity
to make everything
go away, sir:
Bauer and the evidence.
I need to find Jack...
or else they're gonna kill him.
If we can get to him,
we can expose the cover-up.
Jack's gotta be working
with someone. Who?
I don't know. I never saw 'em,
but Jack showed up with
state-of-the-art
weapons and comms.
Pavel, do you see Bauer?
If you have a shot, take it.
I've got him.
Put it down.
Everything's all clear
up on top, Jack.
Come with me.
Do exactly what I say.
(shouting and screaming)
Move!
PILLAR:
He knew it was a trap.
The evidence is on
this memory card.
Take it.
As soon as you see it,
you'll know it's real.
DANA: The hit on Hassan
is all arranged.
Bazhaev and his people are
taking care of everything.
I already know
that you killed Renee Walker.
What I want to know is the
name of the Russian pig
inside your government
that gave the order.
Where's the SIM card
for your phone?
You dumb bastard,
you swallowed it.
This is
for my friend.
(grunts, crunching)
MAN: You've reached the mobile
number of President Charles Logan.
ANGELA: As a principal
player in this
unprecedented and historic
peace initiative,
Secretary of State Kanin's
untimely decision
to withdrew for health reasons
was a difficult one.
However, the president wishes it
to be known
that in Secretary Kanin's
absence and per his own
recommendation, she has sought
and gained the counsel
of former President
Charles Logan.
Now, the president
is acutely aware that this
decision bears some controversy.
But President Logan's experience
with foreign policy
and his skills in negotiation
have already proven
to be a great asset
in these final hours before the
signing of the peace agreement
with the Islamic Republic.
Once Mrs. Hassan...
Excuse me,
Mr. President.
...and the IRK delegation...
Your car to the heliport
is ready and waiting downstairs.
Has, uh, President Suvarov's
plane arrived yet?
It should be
touching down at JFK
within the next 20
to 30 minutes,
and then he'll be choppered in
to the 93rd Street
Heliport.
Thank you, Ellen.
Tell them
I'll be down in a moment.
Yes, sir.
ANGELA (on TV):
Once Mrs. Hassan
and the IRK delegation
have hashed out a few remaining
points of protocol
with President Taylor...
(phone ringing)
...the signing will commence
as scheduled.
Tell me
you have a lead on Bauer.
PILLAR:
I'm sorry, sir.
We tracked him
to an adjacent building,
but Bauer managed
to get out of the cordon,
along with the reporter
Meredith Reed.
Also, he's killed Pavel.
I've taken
jurisdictional control
over the scene from NYPD.
We should be able to keep
this contained, but it...
it's not gonna matter
if Bauer's already
passed along the evidence
he got from Dana Walsh
to the press.
The story's going to come out.
No, not necessarily.
We still might be able
to manage this.
Look, sir,
I- I know you've told me
that you're committed
to seeing this through,
but you can still extricate
yourself from this mess.
There's no evidence
of your involvement yet.
You can still delay
the press announcement.
It's too late
for that, Jason.
The White House
Press Secretary just announced
my role in the
peace process.
There is no turning back.
And there's something else
you should know.
Bauer didn't just kill Pavel.
He butchered him.
He beat him savagely,
and then he eviscerated him.
I don't think
Bauer's just looking
to expose the Russians'
involvement
in the plot against Hassan.
This guy's out for blood.
Then you better find him
and stop him, hadn't you?
Yes, sir.
Keep me posted.
I'm not going any further
till you tell me
what happened back there.
You killedhat man, dn't you?
Ms. Reed, your
life is in danger.
You want to get through
this thing alive,
you're gonna do
exactly what I say.
Do you understand?
Jack, I can't get a locate
on the number you called
from this phone.
It's restricted.
I'm gonna have
to route a back trace.
Can you do it here?
No. I need the equipment
at my place.
Get back to me as soon
as you got a location.
All right.
Let's go.
Who is it
you're looking for?
Someone who can give me the
names of everyone se involved.
And what are you gonna do
when you finthem?
It doesn't concern you.
How can I trust you
if you don't tell me
what you're doing?
Because I'm not the person
who's trying tkill y.
The video file
that I gavyou
is the onlproof of
the Russians' mplicity
President Hassan's
assaination.
But the conspicy doesn
end with the Russians.
There are people within
our own government
that are trying cer this
up, including President Taylor.
Why would the president
want this covered up?
Because she's trying to keep the
peace accord alive with the IRK.
And she knows if
Dalia Hassan finds out
that the Russians had a hand
in the death of her husband,
she'll never
sign the agreement.
What do you want from me?
I need you to break the
story in casI don't make it.
I think Presidt Hassan
deserves that, don't you?
Leme see
your cell phone.
Okay.
Wait.
at are you doing? I...
They've seen
you with me.
The authorities are
going to start monitoring
your usual forms
of communicaon.
You can't go home, you
can't go back to your office.
Is there anyone that you
work with that you trust?
Uh, my edito Gary Klausner.
You need to try and
get him the evidence.
I can get you as
far as a pay phone.
After that,
you're on your own.
I'm glad we were able
to come to terms.
So am I.
Thank you, Madam President,
for your pience with me.
I am still new to this.
You are a natural
leader, Dalia,
and you have a superb
advisor in Minister Jamot.
I appreciate the endorsement,
Madam President.
Pardon me...
for interrupting.
We were just finishing up.
Dalia Hassan.
Charles Logan.
I'm honored to finally
meet you, Mrs. Hassan.
I was a great admirer
of your husband.
I'm so sorry for you loss.
Thank you.
President Taylor tells me
you were instrumental
in convincing the
Russian delegates to stay
at the negotiating table.
I'm honored to play
even a sll part
in such an historic event.
Madam President, may I
have a few moments with you?
I'll see you
at the signing.
You still haven't found out
how Logan convinced
thRussians to stay?
I've investigated it,
but I learned nothing
from the delegates.
I can have our intelligence
service look into it.
No. Thank you, Jamot.
I trust President Taylor.
We have to assume
that if she involved Logan,
it was for a good reason.
The operation to capture
Jack Bauer was unsuccessful.
He got away,
along with the evidence
that he took from Dana Walsh.
You said you had the
situation under control.
Clearly,
I was overly optimistic.
And in my optimism,
I neglected to tell you
that Bauer made contact
wi a journalist.
Meredith Reed.
My God...
You need to call her
publisher right away.
Deny any foreknowledge of
whatever evidence she has,
and demand that they
do not run the sto.
You're suggesting
muzzling the press?
Have you forgotten
that freedom of the press is
Constitutionally
protected?
You are the president,
for God's sake.
Invoke national security.
You tell them this
story will start a war.
Innocent lives
will be lost.
New lies to cover the old ones.
The time has passed for hand
wringing, Madam President.
If you don't use the
power of your office
to shut this story down,
your peace agreement
won't be the only casualty.
You don't need me to
tell you the damage
that your criminal
prosecution will do
to this country.
This country survived
your presidency.
But it won't survive yours.
Me- I inherited
my presidency.
I was never
nearly as popular as you are.
And most of my alleged
misdeeds never made the press.
But if you were
to bare your sins
to the people who put
you in office...?
You are a beacon
of righteousness,
not only for Americans, but
for the rest of the world.
You are the president
who had her own
daughter arrested
rather than see
justice go unserved.
You're a poison.
I never should have
let you to do this.
With due respect,
Madam President,
I- I gave
recommendations,
I made whatever arrangements
needed to be made.
But every decision
was yours.
Let's not pretend
otherwise.
I've-I've studied you
for a number of years, Allison.
I pride myself on being
a good judge of character.
You're a smart woman.
You've always known
what needed to be done
and were willing to do it.
Which is why I know
you will call
Meredith Reed's publisher
and make sure he
kills the story.
I would suggest
you do it now.
You, uh...
You have a signing
ceremony to prepare for.
And I need to go meet
President Suvarov.
Chloe,
you need to see this.
What is it?
I just
tapped into a live feed
from Pillar's team.
This guy was found strung up
and sliced open
in an abandoned building
across from the department
store. He's got Russian papers
on him, but I can't make 'em
out; the rez is too low.
Looks like someone left
a sniper rifle at the scene.
What's the caliber?
Bring it up.
They tagged it
as a.308 Springfield.
That's the gun
that killed Renee.
That's got to
be the shooter.
Jack did this,
and you still think
you're gonna be able
to talk him down?
I gotta try.
Pillar and his people
are just gonna kill him,
and I can't
let that happen.
(beep)
Got a match from the department
store security feed- 82%.
That's the guy
helping Jack?
Yeah, James Ricker-
Ex-Green Beret, Special Ops.
He served with Jack in the Gulf
before Jack was
enlisted by CTU.
Just one problem.
He's dead.
It says he was killed in
a chemical plant explosion
in Basra seven years ago.
Yeah, well, then he must have
a twin who was there
when Jack reversed the ambush.
You better go
back to your station.
Pillar's watchdog
is getting suspicious.
Arlo,
cross-reference
Ricker's photo
with State DMV database.
He must be living
under an alias in the city.
We find Ricker, we find Jack.
Okay.
(phone ringing)
JACK:
Yeah?
You get the location?
RICKER:
You didn't tell me that was
Logan's phone that I was
tracing, Jack. Does it matter?
Yeah, it kind of does.
I think you
know it, too,
or else you would've been
straight with me.
Listen, taking out a bunch
of Russian spooks is one thing,
moving on an ex-president,
that's quite another.
That's a seriously line
you're crossing there, pal.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Are you gonna give me
the location or not?
Logan's in a vehicle.
He's moving west
from the U.N.
I'm syncing up with the
Secret Service deployment grid.
I'll upload his route
to your tablet.
Hold on.
Okay, I've got it.
Listen, Jack, I sure hope
you know what you're doing,
because this path you're on,
there ain't no
coming back from it.
I wasn't planning
on coming back.
Look, you're right,
you've already done
more than I had a
rit to ask for.
I want you to start erasing
all your connections to me.
Jim...
thanks for everything.
Good-bye.
Oh. Thank you.
Are you sure that's all you
need? Should I call the doctor?
It's just a headache.
I'm fine. Thank you.
You wanted to see me,
Madame President? Yes, Tim.
Please sit down.
You remember the reporter
CTU arrested last night?
Yes, uh, Meredith Reed.
It has been brought
to my attention
that she intends to publish
an unfounded story
regarding Omar Hassan's murder.
What is she
gonna be writing?
I need you to contact the FBI,
have them search
the Sunday Magazine offices,
locate Reed,
and seize whatever evidence
she purports to have.
Um, I-I... I don't understand.
Her allegations are false,
but the allegations alone
could derail the peace process.
Well, even so, Madam President,
you have to be aware,
they'll accuse you
of censoring the press.
Tim, I did not ask
for your counsel.
I know exactly what
I'm ordering you to do,
so please just do it.
Yes, ma'am.
(grunts)
Hey, drop-off
and receiving?
Uh, yeah, straight ahead.
Right there.
Thanks.
Just make sure Duggan knows
he's covering the Logan profile.
Tell him we'll work out
the byline later.
(phone rings)
Editor's desk.
This is Klausner.
REED:
Gary, it's me.
Look, a-are you alone?
Can you speak freely?
Yeah.
Yeah, wh-what's going on?
I don't have a lot of time;
I have a lead on a story.
I'm listening. I have a
digital video recording
indicating that the IRK
terrorists who killed Hassan
were being funded and run
by Russian operatives.
(scoffs)
Uh, y-you sure it's legit?
Where did you get it?
From Jack Bauer.
Bauer?!
The man's a fugitive.
Look, Gary, it's really
not safe for me to talk.
I'll explain more
when I see you.
Can you meet me?
Sure, of course.
All right, that diner
with the coffee you hate.
I can be there
in, uh, 15 minutes.
Okay. And, Gary,
don't tell anyone.
All right?
I got it.
Meredith... be safe.
Yeah. You, too.
There's no need to panic.
NOVAKOVICH: Do you know
what he did to Pavel?
He was beaten savagely,
gutted like a pig.
His men shot dead.
I'm... I'm sorry to hear that,
but we both knew that, uh...
Bauer would be
a difficult problem to solve.
You know what he's doing,
don't you?
He's eliminating
everyone involved,
working his way up-
how long before he gets to me?
That's not
going to happen.
How can you be so sure
Because you
told me yourself
your man would
never talk,
and if that's
true, then...
nobody outside
of your inner circle
can point
the finger at you.
I promise you...
Bauer's never
going to know.
And on the upside,
his recent activities
have given us
a bit of an advantage.
What advantage?
CTU orders concerning him
have been upgraded
to "shoot on sight."
First you have to find him.
They're going to find him;
don't worry.
He can't... he can't stay
under the radar forever.
I'll keep you posted.
(tires screeching)
(horns honking)
(gunfire) DRIVER:
Come in! Come in!
We're under assault!
We are trapped
in the 4th Street
underpass.
DRIV: Unit LEZ-1,
requesting immediate backup.
Both entrances are blocked.
We are boxed in.
Oh, that's... that's Jack Bauer.
That's got to be.
Did you hear what I said?!
That's Jack Bauer!
DRIVER: I repeat: we
need immediate assistance.
Don't just sit there!
He's coming for me!
Sir, stay in the vehicle.
We're armored and
the glass is bulletproof.
(gunfire)
LOGAN:
Close the door!
DRIVER: We are being
attacked by automatic gunfire.
The assailant is masked.
It may be
Jack Bauer.
Close the door! Secure the
vehicle! Close the door!
(grunts)
Kill him!
(Logan gasps)
(gas hissing)
(coughing)
(continues coughing)
(coughing, hacking)
(gagging)
JACK: Mr. President, get up,
or I will kill you right here.
Move!
(gunshot)
I just got your flash.
What'd you find out
about Ricker?
You were right.
DMV records show Ricker
living in Suffolk County
under the name Simon Strocker.
I tried to confirm,
found out he moved from there
18 months ago,
but he left
a forwarding address
with the postal service-
it's right here in SoHo.
Hey, Devon,
what's going on?
Pillar's people are requesting
backup for the team
in the field.
Why?
You didn't hear?
Jack Bauer just kidnapped
Charles Logan.
How the hell
did he pull that off?
Charles Logan?
I need to hear what's going on
in that room. Follow me.
How far out are you?
We're approaching
the tunnel now.
How the hell did
Secret Service let this happen?
Bauer hit the town car
with tear gas.
The agents were too
incapacitated to pursue.
PD's got the
tunnel locked down.
I'm working on getting
you schematics.
Hurry up.
(tires squealing)
CTU! Make a hole!
(man coughing)
Where did Bauer take
President Logan?
I don't know.
(coughing continues)
You must have
seen something.
(coughing)
me on- tell me
you saw something.
Sorry, sir.
Nothing?
No one saw
anything.
Eden, they went through
an underground service gate.
I need those schematics.
Sending them to you now.
Go.
All right, Kirsch,
take the corridor.
Brown, you're down there.
Ames, you're with me.
Remember, unless it poses
an immediate threat
to President Logan,
you shoot Bauer on sight,
and you shoot to kill.
Let's go.
(Logan panting)
Through here.
(grunts)
Look at me.
I said look at me!
(whimpers)
You're going to tell me
everything I want to know.
Jack, you're making a mistake.
Don't you even try and pretend
you're not a part of this.
I found the man
who killed Renee Walker:
the Russian operative
Pavel Tokarev.
I got his cell phone.
The last call he
got was from you.
I know how it looks.
You got to let me
explain. Explain what?
That you sent for him
to kill me?
You sent him to
kill me, right?
Yes! Damn it, yes!
Why did you take out a hit
on Renee Walker?
I had nothing
to do with that.
I was brought in
after that happened.
Who brought you in?
President Taylor
needed my help
to bring the Russians
back to the table.
I- I called my
sources in Moscow.
They told me that people
in their government
were behind Hassan's
assassination.
I- I told the Russian delegation
I had evidence of that fact
and the names of
everybody involved.
It was just to keep
them at the conference.
What evidence?
What evidence?!
It doesn't exist.
I was playing poker.
It was a bluff. It worked.
It kept Taylor's peace agreement
on the table, but you...
You were determined
to screw things up.
And to... Oh! Oh!
Ow! Easy. Jack!
Jack! Jack! I admit.
I admit,
I was part of the cover-up,
but I'm not part
of the Russian conspiracy.
I had nothing to do with
the terrorist attack
or your friend's death.
I- I... I'm... I'm not
the bad guy here.
Okay, but you know who is.
You know the name of the person
inside the Russian government
who's giving the orders.
I want that name.
Jack...
Give me the name!
Jack... You got five
seconds before I put a bullet
through your head. No! No!
You don't have to do that.
Five...
I'll tell you.
four... three...
Mikhail Novakovich.
He's the head of the
Russian delegation.
He's been trying
to kill the peace treaty
from the start.
(panting)
You're lying.
No! No! No! I'm not lying
to you! No! No! No! No!
You got my call
from Pavel's phone.
You check the
previous calls.
There's a dozen more
from Novakovich.
I'm telling you.
He's the one you want.
(door thuds open)
Shut up!
(muffled groan)
Say another word,
and I'll drop you
right here.
(Logan gasping anxiously)
Get on your knees.
Oh, no. Please.
Don't shoot me, Jack.
If I was gonna kill you,
you'd already be dead.
(choking)
(gags)
PILLAR: Bauer was
just here- find him!
Mr. President?
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Eden, I need a med unit
at the 49th junction.
On its way.
Is it Bauer?
PILLAR:
No. It's the president.
He's unconscious.
Bauer escaped. I'm gonna need
you to redirect the pursuit.
I'll stay with the president.
Understood.
They still might
catch up to him.
They haven't yet.
Do you have Ricker's file?
Yeah, including
his current address.
I'm sending it
to you now.
How are you planning
to handle this?
We can't send any tactical units
to pick this guy up
without Pillar finding out
about it.
I'm not using
any of them.
Then who are you
going to get?
All of our agents are fully
deployed in the field.
There's nobody to send.
There's one.
(sighs)
Ms. O'Brian?
Ms. O'Brian?!
I just saw the
flash from division.
They approved
your request
to release Agent Ortiz
into your custody?
Yeah, I'm in a hurry, so...
What do you think
you're doing?
He's a non-cooperative witness
who is facing federal charges.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm still in charge
of UN Security,
and you've taken away
all my resources.
And not that
it's any of your business,
but Agent Ortiz designed
the entire UN operation.
The signing is in less
than two hours.
His assistance
in the field is vital.
I'm going to have to
clear this with Pillar.
Do what you want, but to me,
you have bigger problems,
like not finding Jack Bauer.
(sighs)
Are you Meredith?
Yes.
There's a Gary Klausner
on the phone for you.
It's up
by the cashier.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Where are you?
Meredith, the FBI is here.
Showed up before I could leave.
They're looking for you,
questioning everyone,
including me.
You didn't tell them anything,
did you?
Of course not.
But they've got
an executive order
from the president.
They say you're in possession
of materials that pose
a national security risk.
It's a cover-up, Gary.
The White House is trying
to suppress the story.
You can't let them.
Look, until we clear this up,
you have to protect
that evidence.
I told them I haven't had
any contact with you,
but for all I know,
they're tracing this call.
You better get the hell out
of there.
And go where?
Mr. Klausner.
We said no communication
outside of our presence.
I- I I'm canceling
an appointment.
Gary, they're going
to bury the truth.
Not if I can help it.
I'll-try to put a call in
to Ed Sampson
at the Justice Department, but
until then, lay low.
Now go.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I have to go to
the U.N., and
division has given you
a temporary furlough
into my custody.
Since you had earlier
command of UN security,
I'm gonna need your help
coordinating protocols
and deployment for
the signing ceremony.
And Pillar's okay with this?
I'm still provisional
Director of Operations.
I don't need his consent.
So, are you coming,
or would you rather
wait here for your
federal prosecution?
(scoffs)
Let's go.
I'll take him from here.
You want to tell me
what's really going on?
Yeah.
You were right
about Jack.
He is working
with somebody.
It's James Ricker,
ex-CIA Op.
We found him living
at a place on Mercer Street
under the alias
Simon Strocker.
Maybe he's still
with the company.
No. I checked with Langley.
He was listed as deceased.
More than likely, he's gone
into business for himself,
dealing arms or intel.
In any case,
he's not going to be happy
we tracked him down.
Wait a second.
Why are you telling me this?
I need you to talk to him.
Get him to tell us
where Jack is.
Are you good with that, or
have you still not taken sides?
I want to expose this cover-up
as much as you. I'm in.
Good. Log sheets
will show you
accompanying me to the UN.
I've secured you a separate
vehicle waiting at the gate.
Is there any more
intel on Jack?
Has he resurfaced again?
Yeah, you could say that.
Sir, I just
received word.
President Suvarov's plane has
touched down at Kennedy Airport.
Tell Ivan to bring
the car around.
I want to be at the UN
when the president arrives.
(phone ringing)
Where's Novakovich?
I'm not going to
ask you again. 11th.
11th floor, suite 1170.
How do I get up there?
Secure elevator
inside of garage.
Where's your keycard?
I don't have one.
(grunting)
Where is your keycard?
I don't have one, I swear.
His personal guards have them
at elevator.
How many?
Two.
And upstairs?
One outside the suite,
two inside.
Another by elevator.
Where else?
Where else?!
That's all.
That's all I know.
(grunting)
(bell chimes)
(blade slashing)
(bell dings)
(groans quietly)
Do you really need an arsenal?
Better to have
it than to not.
Besides, Ricker's
a trained killer.
He's gone to a
lot of trouble
to stay off the grid.
Fair enough.
I also have to consider
the possibility
that Jack's with him.
Listen, Chloe,
I can't be worried
about Jack anymore,
not after what you told
me he did to Logan.
Obviously, Logan's
part of the conspiracy.
He terrorized a tunnel
full of commuters
with automatic
weapon fire.
He shot Seet Service agents.
He shot to wound.
He's careless, and he
only cares about revenge.
Does that sound like
the man you know?
Like the man
you're trying to save?
This is about exposing
the Russians' cover-up.
It's not about Jack.
Are you sure about that?
Because if
Jack's there,
and he makes any move
other than complete surrender...
...I'm putting him down.
You still want me to go?
I don't really have a choice.
Whatever happens,
call me at the U.N.
You got it.
(engine starts)
You'll approach
the rostrum
immediately prior to the signing
ceremony, and take a seat here
in position three,
next to your mother.
I'm honored.
But is that appropriate?
I may be her daughter,
but I don't have any
official role in government.
(knocking on door)
Excuse me.
Ms. Hassan, there's a call
on your father's secure line-
a woman demanding to speak
with your mother.
She's in a meeting.
That's what I said,
but this woman
is quite insistent.
Who is she?
She won't say.
We're done,
Ms. Hassan.
I'll see you in
the staging area.
Thank you.
Line two.
Hello. Who is this?
Ah. Is this Kayla?
Who are you?
Sorry, um...
my name is Meredith Reed.
I need to speak to your mother.
I know who you are.
What do you think
you're doing calling here?
I- I know I'm the
last person that
either of you wants
to talk to right now...
You're right.
I'm hanging up now.
No, please, please, your mother
needs to hear what I have to say
before she signs the agreement
with President Taylor.
What is it that is so important?
I- I'm sorry, I need to speak
to your mother directly.
Haven't you caused
my mother enough pain?
Leave us alone!
It's about the people who
really murdered your father.
What are you talking about?
We know who was responsible.
What you don't know is,
those people were working
under the orders
of Russian agents.
What?!
Hello?
When your mother gets back
from her meetings,
have her call me
at this number- can
you take this down?
(panting)
Go ahead.
It's 212-555-0121.
I'll explain everything
to her then.
Wait...!
Meredith Reed?
FBI. Get your hands where
we can see 'em. Wait,
wait, what-what is this?
What is this?
Wait. Wait.
You have no right
to take that.
I- I haven't done
anything wrong.
What is this?
You're under arrest.
I
- I've done nothing wrong. Let's go.
I've done nothing wrong!
(knocking on door)
Yes?
Mr. Woods, ma'am.
I've just received word
from the FBI.
Reed is in custody,
and they've secured
a data card they found on her.
(sighs)
No one sees what's on it but me.
Understood.
MAN:
Sir, we'll take it from here.
No, you won't
- I'm riding with him to the hospital.
(clears throat)
Give him some space.
(weakly):
Nova... Novakov...
Nova...
Novakovich.
Warn...
Bauer knows.
Warn Novakovich
Bauer's coming after him.
PARAMEDIC: Sir, we gotta
get going. Not yet. Just do
what you can for him here.
Understood.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
Yes?
Mr. Novakovich?
Hello? Hello?
It's Berkov.
We've been attacked.
It was Bauer.
Where's Novakovich?
He's dead.
Everyone is dead.
Berkov, did Novakovich
say anything to Bauer?
I need an ambulance.
Just answer my question.
What did Novakovich
say to Bauer?
Nothing. Bauer
just came in shooting.
But he was bleeding.
I think he was wounded
by one of the guards.
All right, sit tight;
an ambulance is on the way.
Go.
(quietly):
Novakovich is dead.
Bauer killed him,
killed all of his men...
(continues
indistinctly)
(phone ringing)
Yes?
LOGAN (clears throat):
Yuri.
Charles Logan.
I was under the impression
you were going to be
at the heliport for my arrival.
Yes, well...
(raspy chuckle)
...I ran into some trouble.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
It appears that
Mikhail Novakovich
was just murdered
by Jack Bauer.
What?! Yeah, and,
uh, Bauer learned
that, uh, Novakovich
was responsible
for ordering and...
coordinating Omar Hassan's
assassination, as well as
the rest of Samir's activities.
Where would he get that idea?
From me.
The lunatic was
gonna kill me, Yuri.
What can I say?
Think of it as, uh,
sacrificing
a rook for a king.
Then Bauer has no idea
that Novakovich was operating
under my orders?
None.
Uh, according to a witness,
Mikhail didn't have a chance to
give you up, even he wanted to.
As far as, uh,
Bauer is concerned...
the trail ended
with Novakovich.
And he's being hunted
by every law enforcement
agency in the city.
And I've-I've heard
that, uh... (chuckles)
he's been wounded.
unded- there is nothing more
dangerous than a wounded animal.
Look, if you're
so worried about Bauer,
you never should
have given the order
to kill Renee Walker.
That's what stirred up
the hornet's nest.
If I had known that
yowere going to find out
about our activities
and use that information
to blackmail me
into signing
Taylor's peace agreement,
I wouldn't have bothered
with the woman.
Water under the bridge, Yuri.
I needed an opportunity
to put myself back in the game.
I'm sorry that it has
come at your expense.
You wouldn't begrudge
an old friend
his second chance in the sun.
LOGAN (over radio):
All right, then, I will, uh,
I will meet you
at the United Nations...
(clears throat)
as soon as I can.
(Jack groans, pants)
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net