Our security police have completed their initial sweep
of the capital city.
65 known members of the opposition have been arrested
and are being questioned.
Have you learned anything?
Were any of them working with my brother?
It's too early to tell.
Kayla, your father is a great man,
but Farhad's betrayal has changed him.
What can we do?
The president says
you may be involved with his brother.
He's ordered me to detain you.
I'll talk to him.
President Hassan's crackdown
isn't just a response to the attempt on his life.
There are unsecured nuclear materials in play.
CTU is running an undercover operation
to retrieve them as we speak.
I've got something.
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
A local vice group just impounded $120,000.
I help you do this and you never call me again.
That's beautiful, man. Absolutely beautiful.
It's a cop.
You're going to have to slip past him.
- I'm at the warehouse...
- Nick!
Kevin, stop him!
I hear there are materials for sale.
Talk straight.
What materials?
Nuclear rods.
Nobody deals in nuclear rods, nobody.
We have a problem.
Vladimir Laitanan knows about the fuel rods.
Come on, Vladimir, push them harder.
Somebody knows something.
No one knows, there's no one left to call.
Look, it's over!
What is wrong with you?!
Renee.
Stop, stop.
- They're Russian.
- What are you doing?
I need to let them take me.
When CTU gets here, you tell them to start tracking me from the air.
These people are gonna lead us to everything we're looking for.
I'm unarmed, don't shoot.
We can do business.
Where's Jack?
The Russians took him.
He said that you'd be monitoring him from the air.
We haven't seen anything.
Where is he?
Yeah?
Where the hell are you?
Hey, Jenny girl!
You said you would call me as soon as the two of you got clear.
I'm sorry, sweetheart, I forgot.
We-we got-- hold on-- we got caught up
celebrating our score.
Celebrating?
You put a police officer in the hospital.
Hey, that wasn't me, that was Nick.
A- And look, why do, why do you got to focus on the negative?
We're flush 120 grand.
Why don't you just come down here,
have a drink, celebrate with us?
We're at a club in Jersey City called Starlight.
We'll work out your cut.
What cut?
I don't want anything from you, Kevin.
We're done.
I want you to put my key
in my mailbox and get the hell out of my life
like you promised.
Yeah, that-that's not going to happen.
What does that mean?
This is a sweet operation that we got going here, you know?
You getting the access codes and-and us pulling the jobs.
W- W-Wait...
We had a deal, Kevin.
You promised me I do this one thing for you
and then you leave me alone.
I- I know and I, and I, and I meant that, all right,
but things change, okay, an-an-and...
We can get rich off of this, Jenny.
You can't do this to me, Kevin.
Jenny, please...
Look, bitch,
you're in this up to your neck.
You want your boss and want your boyfriend finding out
you're not who you say you are?
You're gonna be our golden goose, okay?
- Hello?
- Dana.
What are you doing?
We got a situation; you need to be on the floor.
Dana...
I heard you, I will be right there.
Who was that on the phone just now?
That's none of your business.
Actually, it is.
When you start sneaking away
to make phone calls or leave the office,
making me cover for you,
it becomes my business.
Now, who was that?
Kevin?
How the hell would you...?
Are you spying on me?
Look, you want to step out on your fiancé,
it's fine with me.
God knows I've got no love for the guy.
You have no idea what you are talking about.
I am not cheating on Cole.
Okay, whatever you want to call it,
you'd better start telling your boyfriend what's going on
or I will.
Now, come on.
Our undercover operation just went south.
What's happened?
Jack Bauer was grabbed
by an unknown group of armed Russians.
We think they're the ones in control of the nuclear rods.
Are we tracking them?
We can't.
They took Bauer through an underground access
behind the building.
Without aerial support, the best
my people could do was track them
to a drainage junction near Avenue Y and Ocean.
They must have had a vehicle standing by.
Jack's cell phone was trashed at the scene.
Well, there has to be something at the site
to help us ID the vehicle.
Tire treads, transmission fluid, oil residue?
No, there's nothing, sir, the trail's gone cold.
Well, what about Walker?
Did she get a good look at these people?
I don't know, sir.
Frankly, she's pretty messed up right now.
Blaming herself for Jack's circumstances.
Well, she should.
She crippled this operation when she murdered her contact.
Without Vladimir Laitanan, we have no lead to finding Bauer
or the nuclear materials.
You get her back to CTU for debriefing.
I want to know what the hell happened.
Yes, sir.
You might want to consider
running a psych eval on her when we arrive.
Count on it.
You were supposed to be coordinating with NSA,
monitoring chatter.
I know, something came up, I had to take care of it.
What was so important?
It's my fault, Mr. Hastings.
I asked Dana to recover a datalog
I accidentally deleted from archives.
I didn't have clearance.
I'm uplinking to NSA servers now.
All right.
Just get on it.
Roll back any chatter within the last 20 minutes.
Right now that's all we've got.
Let me know if something turns up.
I need to brief President Taylor.
Thank you.
You can thank me by putting aside
whatever it is that's bothering you
and helping me find Jack.
He's my friend and he's in trouble.
Take him down the hall.
Where is Vladimir?
Dead.
So are his men.
The German said they tried to rip him off.
Did he also say how he knows about the fuel rods?
Who are you?
Ernst Meier.
I've been looking for you to make you an offer.
You know who I am?
No.
All I know is that there's a very powerful man
in the Russian syndicate who's been trafficking
weapons-grade uranium,
specifically U-235 fuel rods.
After the nasty business with Laitanan,
these men brought me here,
so I'm just assuming you're that man.
Where did you get this information?
I represent a consortium of private interests.
They intercepted communiques within the Islamic republic.
From whom?
Farhad Hassan...
or someone in his camp.
In either case, you're doing business with the wrong people.
And who are these people-- the ones you work for?
I'm sure you can understand I'm not at liberty to say.
Aah!
You should be less concerned about who I work for
and more concerned about the deal
that they're willing to offer you.
I'm not interested in your offer.
$250 million,
half of which is ready to be wired to you immediately.
The other half you will receive
upon final acquisition of the fuel rods.
You pose a very difficult problem for me.
You show up out of nowhere,
knowing far too much of my business,
yet I've never heard of you.
You've never heard of me because I'm good at what I do.
What I'm concerned about... is that you're a cop.
I just killed three people back at that garage.
Vladimir Laitanan-- I stabbed in the eye.
You really think I'm a cop?
As a child, I saw KGB throw an entire family
off the roof of a building,
two of them small children.
I know what cops are capable of.
So I ask you again:
Who do you work for?
I'm sorry, I can't tell you that.
Dimitri, work on him until he's ready to tell us everything.
No, we can make a deal.
We can still make a deal!
No! No!
No!
You have buried your brother's body?
It's Oleg's necklace.
You gave it to him at his confirmation.
You keep it.
To remind you of him.
I'm glad you're back.
We may have a problem.
What is it?
There is a man down the hall who claims to be an arms broker.
He knows about the nuclear rods.
How could he?
He says there was a leak from Farhad's people, but I wonder.
Until I know for certain who and what this man is,
I've stopped the transport of the rods.
They've been redirected to our weigh station
off the Wantagh Parkway.
I'm sure Farhad can't be happy about that.
I haven't told him yet.
Perhaps we should tell him together.
How long do you plan to hold him off?
That depends.
On what?
On how long it takes Dimitri to break this guy.
Okay, Mr. Policeman.
I'm not a cop.
I swear to you.
Please, don't do this.
Tell me what you know.
We are exhausting all efforts
to ascertain who took Bauer and where,
but until any progress is made, we just have to hope
that Jack can find some way
of salvaging the operation on his end.
What even makes you think he's still alive?
Only the fact that he wasn't killed
at the point of abduction.
Mr. Hastings, I need a realistic assessment.
What are the odds of finding and securing
these nuclear weapons within the next few hours?
I can't answer that, ma'am,
but the longer we're out of touch
with Bauer, the less likely our chances.
All right, Mr. Hastings.
Continue to coordinate with my office.
I want updates every 30 minutes.
Yes, ma'am.
I just spoke to General Wasim.
He's very worried.
Your brother's crackdowns back home are intensifying.
Everyone is being arrested.
Our window of opportunity is closing.
And why didn't the general call me himself?
Perhaps he's losing confidence
in your ability to complete our mission.
This is my mission.
My plan!
Of course.
But we're running out of time.
If your brother dismantles our opposition forces,
we will no longer be able
to reconstitute our nuclear program.
He won't succeed.
At this rate, he will.
How much longer must we wait
for the delivery of the uranium?
Not long.
The rods should be arriving to you within the hour.
Have your men ready.
I'll call you back.
Yes? What is it?
There is a man downstairs who's shown up
to outbid you for the fuel rods.
Is this some feeble attempt to renegotiate terms?
Not at all. This man, Meier,
claims someone in your organization
tipped him off to our deal.
That's not possible. He's lying.
At any rate, in light of his sudden appearance,
I'm halting delivery of the rods for the time being.
What? You can't do that.
It's already done.
I cannot take the risk that we may be exposed.
The longer you delay, the more time
my brother has to crush his enemies.
If he manages to purge everyone in the military
who opposes him, the uranium is worthless to me.
That's your concern.
Mine is to make certain this Meier is not a policeman.
One of my men is interrogating him now.
That could take hours, even days.
Not days.
I can promise you that.
You promised to assassinate my brother, too.
Your failure to eliminate him
has put me under enormous pressure, and now,
because of your people's inability to maintain secrecy,
you break our agreed timetable to suit your needs.
Don't speak to my father that way.
We've honored every agreement we made with you,
and shed a lot of blood for it.
My father's allowed you to stay here
and hide from the Feds at great personal risk to our family.
Tell him to put the gun down.
No.
We're not taking any more of your demands.
Throw him out of here.
Let his own people shelter him if he thinks we're such fools.
I'll drive him there myself if that's what it takes.
It would seem you have used up our hospitality here.
Perhaps it's best you join your men
at the rendezvous point to wait for delivery.
And when will that be?
When I think it's safe.
Not a moment before.
Make sure he gets where he's going.
Still got men back at the scene in case we missed something.
In the meantime, I'll work out
the aerial sweep protocols with Arlo.
What are you doing to find Jack?
Everything we can, Ms. Walker. Come with me.
Have you checked all the... the traffic cams, subway routes?
You have all this technology working for you--
comm surveillance, satellite tracking.
We're using everything at our disposal.
Then how come you haven't found him yet?
Why don't you have any leads?
The best lead we had is dead.
I know about your suicide attempt.
You should have been honest with me.
O'Brian will take your statement.
I want to know every detail about every event
leading up to the death of Vladimir Laitanan.
When she's done, take her to medical.
I've ordered a full psych evaluation.
Yes, sir.
Uh, you can write your statement here.
Hastings blames me for what happened to Jack.
And he's right.
No, he's not.
He shouldn't have said that.
The only reason that Jack was even
part of this operation was because of me.
So whatever they're doing to him right now,
it's because of me.
I have to find him, Chloe.
Renee, I know how you must feel.
Just... just take one thing at a time.
We have to deal with what you did.
So write your statement.
I'll check back with you.
Cole.
Hey.
Do you have some time? I need to talk to you.
Can it wait? I need to review these protocols
before Arlo distributes them.
I've got it covered.
Go talk to your girlfriend.
What's up?
You all right?
No, I'm not.
I have a big problem.
And it's the reason why I've been acting kind of weird
the past few days.
Okay.
Listen, if you're calling off the engagement,
you couldn't have picked a worse day.
No.
No, I would never do that.
Good.
So what's bothering you?
There are things about my past
that I haven't told you.
I'm listening.
Hey.
I'm sure I haven't told you
everything about my past either.
I don't care what happened before I met you.
All that matters is now
and what we have to look forward to.
I think that's all that matters, too.
So what are you so worried about?
I don't want to lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Excuse me.
Agent Ortiz, Mr. Hastings needs to see you in his office.
Uh, tell him I'll be there as soon as I can.
- No. Go.
- Hastings can wait.
So can this.
Talking to you has helped.
I think I know what I need to do now.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Maybe later you tell me what this is all about.
Who do you work for?
Who else knows about the fuel rods?
Everybody has a limit.
Don't worry,
I'll find yours.
You're working with the police.
Admit it!
Tell me and the pain will stop.
Who else knows?
I told you... I'm not a cop.
Please.
I'm just a businessman.
Who do you work for?
I'm an independent contractor.
I couldn't even tell you if I wanted.
Please.
We'll see.
Wake up.
I said, wake up.
I told you I didn't want to be disturbed.
Your daughter is still demanding to see you, Mr. President.
She refuses to leave.
Very well. Send her in.
Kayla, my love,
I'm in the middle of a crisis, so unless it's an emergency...
It is an emergency.
We need to talk about you having Tarin arrested.
Tarin has been taken to the embassy
to help clarify a few questions,
strictly routine.
I know you believe he's been working against you.
What I don't understand is why.
He refused to follow my orders.
You asked him to arrest the family
of one of your delegates.
A man you considered a friend.
Kayla, this is a matter of state; it doesn't concern you.
It doesn't make sense.
Tarin was in the car with you--
if the assassination attempt was successful,
he would've been killed, too.
The world is full of men willing to die for their cause.
I know you consider Tarin a friend.
And your loyalty is commendable.
But trust me, I have my reasons.
We are more than friends.
We're in love,
and have been for almost a year.
You've been carrying on with this man
behind my back?
You say that to me,
after driving mother away with your infidelity.
Please, Father.
Don't let Uncle Farhad's betrayal
turn you against everyone who cares about you.
I can't think of a better way
to completely infiltrate my life and influence my judgment
than getting close to my daughter.
It's not like that.
You're not to see that man again, ever.
Father...
I'm done with this conversation.
I need to get back to my work.
What's happening to you?
Come on.
Damn it!
I am holding the rods until Meier comes clean
about how he knew of the transfer.
If what Meier said is true about the leak in Farhad's team,
it will be dangerous for us.
So we must unload the rods, finish this.
Let them be someone else's problem...
And we erase any evidence.
Once Dimitri is finished, and I'm satisfied
the German is telling the truth,
I'm going to want to hand off the rods
to Farhad tonight.
Keep your men out of sight along the perimeter.
Mikhail and his men will stay with the cargo.
Check to see if the rest of the street lost power.
Just us.
It's Meier.
Cover the exits.
Check the fuse box.
Come on.
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe. It's Jack.
Jack, everyone's been looking for you.
Where are you?
I need you to trace this call
and send a Tac team immediately.
- Jack?
- Chloe, just trace the call.
Jack!
We're sure NYPD's got the perimeter locked down?
The restaurant and everything in a block radius is secure.
Our response team will be there soon.
Where's Dana?
She logged out of the building about 15 minutes ago.
Something about fixing a faulty relay
at our 17th Street station.
Why didn't she just have IP maintenance take care of it?
Good question.
She had to manually reboot the firmware herself.
That's what she said anyway.
Where are we with this man Bazhaev?
It's coming through right now.
I've cross-accessed interagency servers,
also Interpol and FSB.
I'm relaying intel as it comes in
to our response team and to Jack.
Good. Put it up on screen.
Okay, people.
We've ID'd the suspect we have in custody.
His name is Sergei Petrovich Bazhaev,
Ukrainian national, 61 years of age.
Now, we believe he knows the location
of the unsecured nuclear rods.
Now, tactical is on its way to transport him back here
for interrogation.
Agent Ortiz will coordinate operations from here.
Is it true? You found Jack?
Yeah. He's okay.
If you're finished with your statement,
I need to take you to medical.
No. No. I want to be here when Jack gets back.
I'll let him know where to find you.
Come on.
Mr. Bauer, this should hold you for now.
But you're going to have to go to the hospital.
- Okay.
- Excuse me, sir.
They uploaded the suspect's file right now.
How far out is CTU?
They're about five minutes out.
It's all right. I got it. Thanks.
Sergeant?
I need to speak with this man alone.
I knew you were a cop.
I should have trusted my instincts
and killed you on the spot.
Well, you can add it to your list of regrets.
CTU's already acquired a great deal of intel on you,
Mr. Bazhaev.
It's over. You know that, right?
You're finished.
I mean, at the very least, we've got you
on kidnapping and murder, and that's before
CTU rips this place apart and uncovers the rest
of your criminal activity.
Lucky for you, though, I'm only interested in one thing,
and that's the acquisition of those fuel rods.
So, if you were to cooperate,
that would go a long way to reducing
what is clearly going to be a very long prison sentence.
That offer extends to both of your sons, too--
Josef and Oleg.
Oleg is dead.
He was exposed to the rods.
Became ill with radiation poisoning.
He was suffering,
and I shot him,
as if he was just a sick dog.
I murdered my own son.
For nothing.
You want to know where the rods are?
I will tell you.
But I want full immunity.
Not just for me, but for my other son, Josef.
I don't think I can make that happen.
Then we have nothing to talk about.
I'll see what I can do.
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
I need to speak with Hastings.
I think he's in the middle of a briefing with President Taylor.
Even better. See if you can patch me in, okay?
Okay.
Mr. Hastings, it's Farhad Hassan I'm worried about.
How do we know he hasn't acquired
the rods already?
Based on the intel we have, the transfer hasn't
taken place yet.
Madam President, excuse the interruption.
Jack Bauer is on the line.
He wishes to be conferenced in.
Put him through.
Jack, it's President Taylor.
You're on with Mr. Hastings
and my chief of staff.
CTU's been keeping me apprised of your involvement in this.
I'm sorry that it's taken this long for us to speak.
I understand, and please forgive me
for getting straight to the point,
but the man that we have in custody,
Sergei Bazhaev, is willing to cooperate.
He said he would hand over the fuel rods
in exchange for full immunity for him and his son.
Is that all?
Why don't me give him a parade down Broadway, too?
Jack, you've been dealing with this man.
Is there no other way to get the location
of the nuclear materials out of him?
It says in his files that he did 12 years in a Russian labor camp.
In the time frame that we have,
we're not gonna break him, Madam President.
I can see it in his eyes.
Mr. Hastings, what is your assessment?
Well, at first blush, I'd say an immunity deal is premature,
but under the circumstances,
I'll defer to Jack's judgment on this.
Gentlemen, I have a peace deal that's going to fall apart
at any moment unless I can show President Hassan
that we have stopped his brother
from smuggling those fuel rods out of the country.
Make the deal, Jack.
Madam President, he's going to want this in writing.
He'll get it.
But in the interests of expediency,
put him on the phone with me.
Yes, ma'am.
The President of the United States
wants to talk to you.
You want to tell me what's going on?
What are you talking about?
You were implying something about Dana,
and I want to know what it is.
When she came over before and said
she had to talk to you, what did she tell you?
Nothing. She said she had a problem, and she'd handle it.
That's it?
Arlo, if you know something...
Okay, look,
it's none of my business,
and I didn't want to be the one to tell you this,
but I think she went to meet some guy.
You're out of your mind.
Take a look at this.
Who is he?
I checked with the gate.
They said his name is Kevin Wade.
Identified himself as a friend.
Okay, so he's a friend.
Cole?
Bazhaev's given up the location of the nuclear rods.
I've already scrambled a NEST team.
Meet your tactical unit at the helipad.
The coordinates will be relayed to you en route.
Yes, sir.
You think you can find her?
I could if all the drones weren't already committed.
What about a cell trace?
Just do it.
I don't know where you are or what you're doing, Dana,
but I need you to call me as soon as you get this.
It's important.
I love you.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Miss Kayla, no.
Get out of my way, Nabeel.
I want to see him.
Your father forbids it.
I'm sorry. I'm just doing my job.
A job that Tarin gave you.
He brought you into my father's
security detail, and this is how you repay him?
You're his friend, Nabeel.
You know he's innocent.
What would you have me do?
Just let me speak to him.
A few minutes is all I ask.
I can't let you in now.
Tarin's going to be readied for transport
to our embassy in an hour.
I will find a moment you can see him before then.
Thank you, Nabeel.
Now go before we're both in trouble.
Cole, the NEST team's ETA is two minutes from target site.
Now the HAZMAT crew will wait for your signal to move in.
Be advised the truck with
the fuel rods is being guarded by two armed hostiles.
Command, we have an immunity deal with their boss.
Why haven't they been ordered to stand down?
Well, Jack's understanding is that these men are hard cases.
They won't roll over easily.
We cannot take the risk that they'll flee with the rods.
Understood.
Now, when you secure the nuclear materials,
you'll transport them to Fort Hamilton.
We're clearing that air corridor as we speak.
Command, we see the truck,
but there's no sign of hostiles.
Approaching the weigh station now. Stand by.
Set us down there.
Picking up trace radiation.
30 millirads. It's safe.
Go, go. Move in.
We're clear.
Command, are you seeing this?
I am.
Where the hell are the rods?
We picked up trace radiation signatures.
The rods were here.
Right now all we have are two bodies, both shot.
Hey, Agent Ortiz.
Come on, man, you can have a good time.
It's okay. It's okay to laugh once in a while.
You can be a happy person.
This is Bauer.
It's Hastings.
Our team's at the truck stop.
The nuclear rods are not there.
What? H-Hold on. Say that again.
I said the rods are not there.
That's not possible.
Did your men go to the right place?
They went exactly where you sent them.
Now stop playing games and tell us where the rods are.
I told you, they were there.
I had two of my men guarding them.
We found their bodies, both shot.
And there was something else.
Some kind of necklace hanging
on the inside of the truck's door.
Like someone wanted to send a message.
What kind of a necklace?
A gold cross.
What does that mean?
Josef.
I have the fuel rods.
Really?
I wasn't sure I believed, Josef,
that you would betray your father.
You were upset that he was holding up delivery
of the rods; now I've gotten them for you.
It won't take him long to realize what's happened,
so let's get this done fast.
You're worried he'll discover
you've replaced him as our partner.
No, I want my father to know.
In fact, I made sure he will.
When will you get here?
Less than five minutes.
Subtitles by Brainquake
www.tvsubtitles.net