Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Hassan's security forces
in the Islamic Republic
are sweeping
through the capital,
arreing opposition
leaders.
And if he continues, it may
delegitimize the peace accord.
I can't vouch for you
as a reformer, Mr. President,
if you renege
on your human rights
obligations.
My brother tried to kill me,
helped by elements
within my own government.
Apparently,
killing President Hassan
was only part
of his brother's plan.
CTU now believes
he's also trying
to acquire weapons-grade
uranium.
When can I take possession
of the rods?
As soon as we have the money.
JOSEF: I found a doctor
who can treat him.
BAZHAEV:
No doctors.
The authorities know
about the nuclear material.
Putting Oleg
in a clinic would lead them
right to us.
Dr. Levine.
How did you get in here?
My brother is sick.
I'm gonna call you
an ambulance.
No.
No one can know about this.
(gasping):
No, no.
What do you want from me?
You're a data analyst
for CTU.
You got access to all sorts
of good stuff.
Yeah, but not unrestricted
access.
Payout's got to be at least
six figures.
You were undercover
for nearly two years
with the Russian Mob.
You're asking me to go back in?
Vladimir Laitanan was
completely obsessed with her.
It turned violent.
Did he rape her?
It looks like he tried
a couple of times.
Can we talk
about this deal now?
I wish it were that simple.
Tie her up.
What?
Look, you're making
a mistake.
This is the chance
of a lifetimK]
JACK:
This operation's over.
Vladimir didn't take the bait.
Renee, it's Jack.
I know you can hear me.
I'm on my way now.
You don't want
to do this deal,
then you might as well
just kill me,
because this deal is
the only thing that I have.
Do it!
Pull the trigger!
I had to be sure.
CHLOE:
Jack, are you there?
What's going on?
She's in.
They bought her cover.
JACK (over comm):
Renee, I've got a visual on you.
I'm going off comm
for a minute.
You all right?
(phone rings)
CHLOE:
CTU, O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack. I want you
to monitor Renee's comm.
I need to speak to Hastings.
Okay, I'll put you
through.
I'm here, Jack. Go ahead.
We need to pull
Renee Walker out now.
Based on what?
Because she's a danger
to herself and this mission.
Ten minutes ago, Laitanan
threatened to execute her,
and she said
she was sick of living
and wanted to die
and she meant it.
She must've been
playing him.
No. She doesn't care
what happens to her,
that's what makes
her dangerous.
She's like a bomb
ready to go off.
We need to get her out of there
before that happens. Look, I understand
your concern, but we can't
just roll up this operation
before we find those
nuclear rods.
We can arrest Laitanan.
If he knows how
to find the rods,
I will make him talk.
If you're saying
what I think you are,
we don't do that anymore.
Then you people do
what you do well-
offer him immunity
or something.
This is the Russian
Syndicate.
They're very secretive,
they protect their own.
It is highly unlikely
that Laitanan would
cooperate.
Then you better find
another way,
because I am not gonna
let Renee die
because CTU did
their job badly.
I will not let that happen.
Do you understand me?
Jack, if you can think
of something, I will listen.
But right now,
Renee's the only hope we have
of neutralizing this threat.
And on my order,
she stays in play.
Jack?
I'll find a way to get her out
when I go in as the buyer.
I'll sy under in her place.
Do we have a deal?
As long as you can do it
without risking the mission.
I give you my word.
Agent Ortiz will meet you
at the staging area
with a TAC team.
He'll have everything you need
for your cover.
Hold on.
They're moving.
I need to get
back on comm.
VLADIMIR:
We'll go back to my shop,
and we will discuss
this buyer of yours.
(engine starts)
(tires squealing)
HASTINGS: Dana... (gasps)
start forwarding mission
status reports to the Nuclear
Emergency Team at Fort Hamilton.
I want them ready to go
in as soon as we find
these nuclear rods.
I'm on it, sir.
(phone rings)
Ye.
It's me.
I've got something.
Damn, you're fast.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, go.
Let's hear it.
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
According to the manifest,
a local vice group
just impounded a stash
of drug money.
It'll be held there
for the next 48 hours.
How much?
$120,000.
All right, what's the plan?
You go in and take it.
(chuckles)
What do you mean,
break into a police station?
What, are you out of your mind?
It's not a police station.
It's a warehouse.
Most of the security
is automated.
I can manipulate it
from here.
You walk in, you walk out
with the cash.
I'll talk you through it.
I need to access
their security codes,
work up a keycard to get you
inside the warehouse.
How long?
Meet me outside CTU
in 30 minutes.
ARLO: Did you take care
of your situation?
Situation?
The big mystery you had
to leave work for.
Oh, yeah, it's fine.
What do you need, Arlo?
I'm getting five percent lag
in my Drone's ABS controls.
With everything going on,
I think I'm just running hot.
Okay, I'll make sure
to free up some memory space
on the auxiliary servers.
Thanks.
You know, if there's
something bothering you,
you've always got
my shoulder to cry on.
Or any other body part.
I will keep that in mind.
But, for now,
why don't you focus on
running aerial support
for Walker and Bauer?
Okay.
♪ ♪
Lugo, take a break.
I want to talk to her alone.
All right,
you have my attention.
Tell me about this buyer.
His name's
Ernst Meier.
German arms dealer.
Never heard of him.
He does most
of his business in Asia;
he just started
branching out
into North America.
What's he looking to buy?
Weapons-grade uranium.
You're serious.
Very.
Someone in the Russian
Syndicate smuggled nuclear
fuel rods out of the Ukraine.
They're planning on selling them
on the open market.
I... I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I don't, Renee.
But you can find out.
You're very well
connected.
I have always admired
your ambition,
but you're chasing
the devil.
Dealing AK-47s-
no one really cares.
But nuclear material?
But the profit is worth it.
You need money, huh?
You can always
come work for me.
No, I'm doing this so I don't
ever have to work for anyone.
Have a seat.
If I could find out...
...what would it be worth?
30% of the deal.
I don't have
to tell you,
that is more money than
you could possibly know
what to do with.
Look, Meier says these rods
are going to be sold soon,
so if we want
to make a counter bid,
it has to happen fast.
If you don't know anything, tell
me, so I can go somewhere else.
How well
do you know this man?
You trust him?
There's no one I trust more.
I've been with him
for two years.
What do you mean "with"?
It's professional.
Can you help us or not?
I'll make a few calls,
see what I can
find out.
But, uh,
I'm going to have
to meet this Meier.
And I need a good faith
payment up front.
How much?
Five million.
That's a lot of money, Vlad.
Look, I'm taking big risk
just making these calls.
Besides, 5 million is nothing
compared to what your
buyer will have to pay
for nuclear fuel rods.
Fine.
I'll ask him, but I can't
make any promises.
If he wants my help,
that's the price
of admission.
Okay.
There's a parking garage
on the corner of 12th
and Market Street.
Someone will meet him
there, on the roof.
Once the money is
in our account,
they'll bring him back here,
we will talk.
I'll give him a call.
It's good to see you.
You're going to make me
start losing sleep again.
I'll let you know
what Meier says.
I'll tell my men.
I'll give you privacy
for your call.
Jack, were you listening?
Yeah, we're ready to wire
the money to
his account.
When can you be there?
As soon as I finish
prepping my cover.
I'm almost at the
staging area.
30 minutes tops.
How you holding up?
It's hard to be
in the same room
with this
son of a bitch.
I can handle it.
I'll be there as
soon as I can.
Okay.
Don't worry, Oleg.
You're going to be fine.
It, uh... it might
help me if I knew
exactly what happened
to your brother.
How did he get exposed
to weapons-grade uranium?
Don't worry about that.
Just make sure he lives.
(phone ringing)
It's him again, isn't it?
The second time he's called.
You should
answer it.
Hello?
Why aren't you
picking up your phone?
I called you twice.
Must have been
in the tunnel.
Ulana says you're not
at the house yet.
Where are you?
Stuck in traffic.
Tell her it's going
to be a while.
How's Oleg?
He's okay.
Sleeping.
Let me know when you
get to the house.
I will.
It was him, wasn't it?
Hey.
Don't worry, okay?
By the time he finds out,
you'll already
have been treated.
Then it won't matter.
(knock on door)
Hey, it's just
your brother's test results.
Okay.
You say or do anything
that I don't like,
and my men will kill
your wife and daughter.
Open the door.
The blood work
you ordered, Doctor.
Thank you.
Uh, I noticed there was
no patient name.
Uh, yeah, you're right.
I forgot to put that down.
Oh, well, I can do it for you.
No, I'll take care of it later.
Is everything okay, Doctor?
Fine.
I'm just working a little later
than I expected.
Okay.
You did good.
What does it say?
Your brother has been exposed
to at least 400 rems,
and the chemical toxicity
of the radiation
is causing renal failure.
I know it's serious.
Can you help him or not?
He needs
a bone marrow transplant.
That requires
a six-man surgical team
in a fully equipped facility.
There has to be something
you can do
right here, right now.
There are some drugs
I could give him
that will help
flush out the radiation
and stimulate
white blood cell repair,
but that's a half measure.
I can't guarantee
he'll recover.
My brother is not going to die.
It's up to you, Doctor.
Now get to work.
Okay, got it.
That was CTU.
Your offshore
account's in place.
They're forwarding
instructions to your PDA
on how to wire
the money.
Excuse me.
I spoke
with Hastings.
He said, as soon
as you're under
and we have confirmation
that Laitanan can get us
to the nuclear rods,
we're pulling Renee Walker out.
That's right.
What's going on, Jack?
Hastings said something
about her being unstable.
I don't have time
to explain it.
Just follow my lead.
How do you want to work this
without breaking cover?
I don't know yet.
All right.
Well, I got two teams
running coordinated
drive-bys.
They'll be ready to extract her
when she's clear.
No.
These guys own
this neighborhood.
They'll have eyes everywhere.
Your men
will run the risk
of being spotted.
I've done this before, Jack.
I ran an operation just
like it in Fallujah.
And I'm in command.
You're going to do
exactly what I tell you.
RENEE (over comm):
Jack, stand by.
I hear him coming.
Laitanan's back.
I need to listen to this.
Excuse me.
(knock on door)
VLADIMIR:
Renee.
I spoke to my men.
Did you get your buyer
on the phone?
He agreed
to the money.
He'll be at the parking garage
in 20 minutes. Very good.
We have a little time
to catch up.
Do you still like
your single malts?
Uh, not right now.
You sure?
It's a 30 year.
No, thanks.
What you said earlier-
down at the river-
you were tired
of living,
wanted to die.
What happened to you?
It's not important.
It is to me.
Look, you don't have
to worry about it.
Once I make this deal,
none of it will matter.
Well, you're not the only one
who's been suffering
these past few years.
It's hard for
me to admit,
but, uh...
I never forgave myself
for what I did to you.
It's in the past.
Forget it.
VLADIMIR (over comm):
I don't want to forget it.
I had too much
to drink that night,
I wasn't thinking clearly.
Wow.
Never heard you apologize
for anything.
It's definitely
a first.
Look, I'm just trying
to make things right.
You dot have to be
such a bitch about it.
Was I being a bitch?
Maybe I should apologize.
Oh, you're
something else.
You never back
down, do you?
I've missed our
little arguments.
You're still
nervous around me.
I shouldn't be surprised.
It's not you.
VLADIMIR:
Someone else?
RENEE:
No.
VLADIMIR:
What is it, then?
Look, I'm just...
I'm just nervous about the deal.
Could be a lot of money
at stake.
There's more for you here
than just money,
if you want it.
Look...
I didn't come here
for this.
Really. All the people
you could've gone to,
you knocked on my door.
Because you're connected.
That's the only reason?
Yes.
I don't believe you.
That's your problem.
You should watch
your tongue.
You might lose
it one day.
Uh... you said
that I could get cleaned up.
Yeah.
Bathroom has a shower.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Agent Ortiz, we
need to move now.
Now!
(releases held breath,
breathes deeply)
Renee called her buyer.
He agreed to pay
the $5 million up front.
I want you
to meet with him.
Take a couple men.
This is a mistake, Vlad.
Getting involved
in nuclear arms-
it doesn't matter how
much money is at stake.
I have no intention
of pursuing this deal.
What do you mean?
When you've
picked up the buyer,
when the money has been
transferred into our account,
you kill him, put him
in the river, keep the money
for ourselves.
What about Renee?
She'll be working with us
from now on.
We are going to
kill her buyer.
She's not going to
be happy about that.
You heard what she said.
She's got nothing left.
Nowhere to go.
Desperate woman.
I give her reason to live.
Okay?
I'll take care of it.
President Hassan's
security forces-
they're still cracking
down on the opposition,
and they're not showing
any signs
of letting up.
ETHAN:
I'm afraid your warning
to President Hassan
has fallen on deaf ears,
Madam President.
Who filmed this?
Stringer for the BBC bought it
from an eyewitness.
And they've already seen it
on Downing Street.
That's why Ethan wanted you
to see this now.
The rumors have already started
that the British
are pulling out
as signatories to the accord.
Then I need to talk
to the prime minister.
It's not just the British,
Madam President.
The Germans and Egyptians
are also positioning
themselves
to pull out, and if we
lose their support...
The peace deal
is dead.
Maybe if they understood
the circumstances-
that Hassan is trying
to prevent his brother
from acquiring a nuclear weapon.
With respect,
Madam President,
sharing that intelligence
with the delegates
might spread a panic.
You're right, but I still need
to buy some time.
Assemble the representatives
from every signatory country
attending the conference.
I want to appeal to them myself
to stay the course.
What about President Hassan?
Shouldn't we include him?
Not until I've taken
the temperature
of the other delegates.
I don't want
to push him too hard.
What is it?
As you requested,
these are backgrounds
on all the detainees.
Our security police have
completed their initial sweep
of the capital city.
65 known members of the
opposition have been arrested
and are being
questioned.
Have you learned anything?
Were any of them working
with my brother?
It's too early to tell.
What's wrong, sir?
One of the suspects...
has family connections
to a member of my
delegation here at the UN.
Who?
Jamot.
They are cousins.
That doesn't mean that Jamot
is involved in any of this.
We need to make sure.
We'll check his phone records
and other recent activities
for any suspicious behavior.
Good.
But I also want him
taken into custody.
Sir?
Arrest him.
Take him to our embassy
for interrogation.
Mr. President, with respect,
Jamot is a trusted member
of your inner circle.
The evidence against him
is purely circumstantial.
I trusted my brother as well.
Are you sure
this is what you want?
He is
a public official.
It will not go
unnoticed.
I don't care!
I don't care what anyone thinks.
I was almost killed today.
Or have you forgotten?
I was in the car
with you, sir.
Then you should know
what needs to be done.
Yes, sir.
(clears throat)
ARLO:
Forget about me?
What?
My name's Arlo Glass.
I'm one of your
coworkers at CTU.
You said you'd free up
some memory space on
the auxiliary servers.
I'm getting to it.
In which century? We're in
the middle of an operation
and my aerial feed is
running in slow-motion.
It's next on my list, Arlo.
Where are you
going now?
To the bathroom.
Is that okay with you?
Hey, O'Brian,
you notice anything
weird about Dana?
Miss Perfect?
She seems
distracted,
always making excuses to leave.
Maybe she's avoiding you.
What?
Well, that's what I would do
if someone were drooling
over me all day.
You're lucky she
hasn't reported you
to Human Resources.
If you weren't so jealous,
you'd see I was asking you
a serious question.
Oh, yeah, I'm jealous.
Please, won't you stare
at my ass as I walk away?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Stay here.
This has the address
and schematic
of the evidence lockup.
You'll go through
the southeast entrance.
This keycard
will get you access.
How do we find the money?
The evidence bins are numbered.
You're looking for 4301.
This is a dedicated comm unit.
It's an earpiece; you'll
be able to hear me.
Do exactly
what I tell you to do
and you'll be in and out.
No one will know
you were there.
Listen...
I help you do this
and you never call me again.
That's the deal, right?
Sure, Jen, that's the deal.
I'll call you
when we get to the lockup.
Okay.
(water running, turns off)
You look thin.
Be out in a minute.
I don't want to wait that long.
Vladimir, please,
just let me get dressed.
Why waste the energy?
I'll just have to get you
undressed all over again.
Look, I already told you
I didn't come here for this.
That's what you say, but part
of you came here to see me.
Admit it.
RENEE:
There's nothing to admit.
VLADIMIR: Why is it so hard
for you to admit the truth?
You want this just
as much as I do.
I'm not going
to tell you again.
Leave me alone
and let me get dressed.
Come here.
I said come here.
(glass shatters)
Come here or get out.
I call my men
and the deal's off.
I'll, um... I'll take
that drink now.
Dry yourself off.
Come out when
you're ready.
JACK:
Renee, do you copy?
Yeah, Jack.
You don't have
to do this.
I've got a team
standing by.
We can get you
out of there now.
Where would that leave us?
I've got to stay under.
We'll find another way.
There is no other way.
Renee, don't do this.
Renee...
Go meet Vlad's men.
I'll see you when you get here.
Why won't you listen
to me?
I'm going dark.
Renee, wai...
These arrests are making
it very difficult
for my government
to continue
to support the
peace agreement.
President Hassan
can't ignore the repercussions
of what he's doing.
I know President Hassan.
He is a rational man,
a good man.
There must be a reason
for these actions,
and I'm not just speaking
as his delegate
but as his friend.
Well, as his friend,
you need to let him know
that my government is not the
only one with grave concerns.
This conference is at
risk of falling apart...
Excuse me,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Mr. Jamot, may I speak
with you privately?
Yes, of course.
Excuse me.
Of course.
What is it?
I've been ordered
to escort you
to the embassy to
answer some questions.
Regarding?
An internal
security matter.
Please come with us.
Well, I-I would like
to know
what this is about.
We'll explain everything
to you at the embassy, sir.
Well, it will have to wait.
I am about to go
into a meeting.
It cannot wait, sir.
We need to go
right now.
Are you arresting me?
It would be best
if we kept this discreet.
This is outrageous.
I demand to speak
with President Hassan.
President Hassan is the one
who gave this order.
I will not
ask you again.
Come with us.
Very well.
Take him
to the car.
I'll be
right there.
Is everything all right?
Everything is fine, sir.
Please excuse me.
(phone rings)
Hello.
It's me. Are you alone? Yes.
What's wrong?
You sound upset.
I didn't want
to burden you with this,
but I need to speak
with you about your father.
What is it?
I have to go to the embassy
right now.
I'll meet you in private
when I get back.
You're going to give him
vindesine twice daily,
morning and night.
Inject it right into
the I.V. bag,
just like I'm doing.
You're going to want
to be careful.
Radiation poisoning
is transferable
through bodily fluids.
Are you paying attention?
Yes, I see.
He's also going to get
cisplatin every other day,
but he can take
that in pill form.
I'm going to give you
three weeks' worth.
How will I know
if he's getting better?
If the treatment's working, his
symptoms will begin to subside
in seven to ten days.
We're going to be
leaving soon.
Where? To the country house.
The doctor's giving me
everything I need
to treat y.
You're going
to get better, Oleg.
(knocking on door)
That's the nurse with
the rest of the medicine.
(gunshot)
Throw down
your weapon, Josef.
Do what I said.
Don't make this worse
than it is.
Drop it!
You son of a bitch.
Who else knows about
Oleg's sickness?
Who else knows?
Just the doctor.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Undo him.
Hey, wait, stop.
What are you doing?
Your father sent us
to bring you home.
Now, Josef.
OLEG: Josef...
it's okay.
Just do what he says.
I have him.
We found them.
Where were they?
A clinic in Mount Vernon.
How many people found out
about Oleg?
Only one- a doctor-
but we've
taken care of him.
Nobody will know
we were here.
Good.
Now, bring my
sons to me.
Da.
Let's go.
Meier?
That's right.
You are from Germany.
Bremen.
But I grew up traveling
with my father.
(speaking German)
Are we going to do business
or not?
Where is the $5 million?
You don't see any money
until I talk to Laitanan.
If you
have questions,
ask me.
I don't want to talk to you.
Get him on the phone
or I drive away.
Now.
(phone rings)
Yes?
LUGO:
Meier is here.
He won't transfer
the money
until he speaks
with you first.
Put him on.
This is Meier.
Yes, Mr. Meier.
What's the problem?
After you
get your money,
how long till I get
my information?
Not very long; I just
have to make a few calls.
No more than an hour.
Where is Renee?
She's busy.
I would like
to talk to her.
VLADIMIR: You can see
her when you get here.
We have nothing
more to discuss
until the money's
in place.
Now, get Lugo
on the phone.
Fine.
Go ahead.
Once the money is confirmed
into our account,
you know what to do.
Yes.
I need your account number.
JACK:
I'm transferring the money
through multiple accounts
so it can't be traced.
This will take
a moment.
We'll wait.
Is it done?
Not yet.
My partner's good
for the money, Vladimir.
You should be making calls,
tracking down
the rods.
I'm not going
to make any calls,
'cause there isn't going
to be any deal
with your partner.
What are you talking about?
Once we have the money...
it's over.
We don't need him anymore.
And we'll be
$5 million richer.
You son of a bitch.
Hey, I'm not a fool, Renee.
I'm not about
to get involved with the kind
of people who traffic
in nuclear arms. Okay, Vladimir,
listen, you can't do this.
Why? This man
mean something to you?
No, but I worked for more
than a year to make this deal.
I'm not just going to let it go
because you don't have the guts
to see it through.
Hey, this isn't about guts.
This is about being smart.
Really?
Is it smart
to keep selling small arms
for the rest of your life?
I bring you the score
of a lifetime,
and you just piss it away?
For what- for $5 million?
How long is that
going to last you?
Long enough.
You're more
than all this.
I know it.
It's why I brought this deal
to you.
We can do this.
Together.
Once we've made the deal
and we have the money,
we can be together.
We could start over.
Make our own moves.
But I need my buyer.
Alive.
Sorry.
This is the
way I want it.
You'll see.
It's for the best.
What are you doing?
Making a call.
Put down the phone.
I said put it down!
Don't ever
go against me!
Renee, you should
know that by now.
Okay?!
How much longer?
It's almost done.
There.
The money's in
your account.
LUGO:
Thank you,
Mr. Meier.
(gunshots)
Drop the weapon.
Now! Drop it!
You really think
I'm that stupid?
That I'd come
here alone?
Call your man. Do it!
Give me the phone.
(phone ringing)
I see we have the money.
Is Meier dead?
Not exactly, but I've just
taken out three of your men,
and I'm ready
to take out the fourth.
Meier.
You really think you can
roll me for $5 million?
Where's Renee?
She's right here. She's fine.
I want proof now!
Say something to your partner.
Meier, are you okay?
Satisfied?
Renee told me you were ready
to take your organization
to the next level.
Apparently, she was wrong.
Not necessarily.
I'm willing to reconsider
the situation.
The only thing you should
consider yourself is lucky.
And I still want
this deal to happen.
Otherwise,
you'd be dead.
You try something like this
again, we're going to war,
and that's the last
thing you want.
Let me talk to my man.
Fine.
(breathing heavily)
Yes?
Bring him back here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
He wants to see you.
Get up.
Move to the driver's-side door.
Slowly.
Get in.
I'm sorry, Oleg.
(footsteps approaching)
Leave us.
I couldn't let him die.
He's my brother.
And he's my son.
Do you think this
is any easier for me?
It would've worked.
The doctor was treating him.
You disobeyed me, Josef.
You put this family
at risk.
at risk when you sent
those men into the clinic.
They killed
three people!
What do you think's
gonna happen when
the police start
to investigate?!
Who are you to question
my judgment?
You are my first-born.
You, of all people,
should give me respect.
I do respect you.
But this time you're wrong.
The doctor said that
Oleg could be treated.
He showed me how!
All we need is
the medicine!
There are rules, Josef.
(grunts)
They are simple rules.
(Josef grunts)
And they must never be broken!
Never endanger
the family; never.
And never disobey an order
from your father.
Papa... (speaks Russian)
JOSEF:
No, please,
No, please.
You made me do this, Josef.
Please. Please don't.
I'm sorry, my son.
Get up.
Get up!
Now, call Father Gregor.
He'll pray over Oleg.
When he's finished,
we'll bury your brother.
Never disobey me again.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net