Tell me what you know.
The hitter has someone on the inside.
Victor Aruz told me right before he died
that the assassin's working
with someone very close
to President Hassan.
Someone hacked into the U.N. database.
They downloaded the security protocols,
the schematics to the U.N.
and Hassan's personal itinerary.
Did you get a name?
The computer's owner is listed as
Meredith Michelle Reed.
She's a reporter.
Applied for security
clearance at the U.N.
We got a match.
Everybody move back!
Move back!
Mr. President.
I can't believe she's part of this.
If this affair becomes public,
it will destroy your credibility
and everything that you've worked for.
I just spoke to my brother.
I told him to deny the affair.
The reporter's claims
need to be discredited.
CTU needs to continue to think
she's my contact on the inside.
We might have the wrong person.
We've been scanning through
the traffic cam footage
from outside Meredith
Reed's apartment building.
This man was going into
the service entrance.
What if he went through her apartment
and used her laptop to
break into the servers?
He hailed a cab when he left.
See the medallion?
Phone the cab company.
Find out where it went.
Hands in the air now! Against the wall!
Chloe tracked the man in the
surveillance photo
to a second location.
We didn't think you'd follow
through with an investigation.
So you had no choice
except to steal weapons from the armory.
Would you follow through with
an investigation if I'd asked?
I'm not debating this anymore.
You want to waste your time
chasing ghosts, knock yourself out.
Hello?
"Dana Walsh." I like that.
I told you to stop calling me.
Yeah, I know what you told me, Jenny.
You must be mistaking
me for someone else.
That's funny 'cause you
sound a lot like this girl
I used to know from Rock
Springs named Jenny Scott.
Hey, Mike, what's going on?
Mind if I come in?
Oh, Mikey.
Call Captain Ravello.
Tell him you're sick,
and I'm filling in for you.
Now listen, you son of a bitch,
there's no way...
What's the matter with you?!
Next time I won't miss the bone.
Make... the call.
This is Hastings.
Tell me you've gotten something out of
- that reporter you arrested.
- No, sir.
I'm continuing to press her,
but she's maintaining her innocence.
She's a co-conspirator
in an assassination plot.
Of course she's gonna deny it.
Listen, I need to be able
to tell the president
we're making progress
toward averting this threat.
Sir, right now our only course is
to go after Meredith Reed with
the evidence we have in hand.
Our top analyst is decrypting a file
we obtained from her laptop.
We're hoping it
provides the intel we need
about the assassin she's working with.
Well, it'd better provide something
because if your people fail,
and President Hassan is killed,
this peace process dies with him.
Do you understand me?
I understand your concern, Mr. Weiss,
but I assure you we're
on top of the situation.
I've dispatched tactical personnel
to liaise with U.N. security forces
and stepped up the alert
with NYPD at the perimeter.
Fine. I'll have that
to tell her at least.
Let me know when that file is decrypted.
Dana, you got a minute?
I thought you were on
your way to the U.N.
I am. What's the status
on that file decryption?
We I.D.'d the cipher.
It's a standard Issacs-Adler algorithm.
Requires a 12-character decryption key
to unlock the data.
The search cycle has identified
two characters already.
Should have the rest in
about 30 or 40 minutes.
Why do you ask?
Jack Bauer just caused a
big scene with Hastings.
He thinks Meredith Reed
may have been framed.
He must have gotten that from Chloe.
I thought that she'd dropped it.
Apparently not.
She has surveillance of someone exiting
Reed's apartment building.
Jack thinks this same person
may have planted the encrypted file
- on Reed's computer.
- You believe that?
I'm not sure.
If that evidence was planted,
the file you're decrypting
is irrelevant at best;
at worst a misdirection.
Cole, I traced the U.N.
breach to Reed myself.
The biometric scans of her interrogation
all indicate that she's withholding.
I just don't see a frame here.
I hope you're right
because Jack's going after
this guy on his own.
Hastings sanctioned that?
Not exactly.
Agent Ortiz? We need to move out, sir.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Okay, I'm at the corner of
Broadway and West 23rd
in Queens. Any location on the suspect?
Negative. I talked to
the cab driver directly.
All he remembers is dropping
the fare at the corner.
Nothing shows up in the aerial archives.
Chloe, I need something to go on.
I know. I've been searching
for private security
cameras in the area.
Not all of them are registered.
Without the serial numbers,
I don't have access to them.
Okay, I'm gonna get out
and look around on foot.
Maybe we'll get lucky. Stay on the line.
It's all right, Mags.
It's gonna be okay, right?
Keep your hand on the
table where I can see it.
Who the hell are you?
You're not a cop.
How did you manage
to fool everybody, Mikey,
or whatever the hell your name is?
Talk to me,
you son of a bitch!
Shh-shh-shh.
Look,
I don't want to hurt
you, Jim, or Maggie.
I am just doing my job.
This is the captain calling back.
Just say what I told you to say.
Please don't make me do
anything I don't want to do.
Okay?
Yeah.
Hello.
Koernig, Captain Ravello. What's up?
Uh, yeah, Captain,
sorry to drop this on you last-minute.
I just came down with some kind of bug.
I got to take a sick leave.
You could have told me earlier, Jim.
You're due at the U.N. in 20.
Yeah, I know. It's okay.
I asked Mike Farmer to
cover my shift for me.
Farmer's already on in the morning.
He said he doesn't
mind working a double.
I guess he could use
the time-and-a-half.
Anyway, I already told
him he could use the bike
that I pulled from the motor pool.
All right, Sergeant.
I'll take care of the paperwork.
Look, you tell Mike
to get his butt to Midtown.
You got that?
Get better, will ya?
Yeah.
You did well.
I did what you wanted me to do,
all right, so...
Do what you got to do
and leave us alone.
We're not gonna make
any trouble for you.
You still there?
Jack, go ahead.
Hold on. Hold on.
Okay, I got two security
cameras overlooking
the park, one pointing
straight at the corner.
I'm gonna get you the serial numbers.
Hey, man, what you doing?
Chloe, I got to get back to you.
What's up? You lost, man?
Actually, I am.
I'm looking for a friend of mine.
Well, unless you a cop,
I suggest look somewhere else,
'cause this is our court.
We don't like strangers on it.
I ain't a cop, and I'm not
looking for a problem.
My friend was let off on that corner
by a cab 20, 25 minutes ago.
I guess you didn't hear
what I'm saying, did you?
I've got a hundred bucks;
anybody can tell me if
they've seen this guy.
Anybody?
I seen him.
Yo, shut up, Jay!
What was he wearing?
Green coat, black shirt.
Where'd he go?
That light blue house over
there across the street.
I seen him go up the steps to the stoop.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Yo, man, what you doing, Jay?!
You don't even know what's going down.
Man, I don't know about you,
but I got a hundred dollars.
It's your play. Let's go.
Man, I'm about to take
that hundred dollars.
Give me the ball, man.
All right.
Jim!
Hello. Jack?
Got a call from one of your neighbors.
Jim?
Hello, Jack?
Jack, what's happening?
Are you there...?
Put the weapon down now. Do it.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm working on behalf of CTU.
I'm investigating a threat
to the peace conference
at the U.N. If that's true,
drop your weapon.
I can't.
The man I'm pursuing killed
two people in this house.
If I lower this weapon,
I'll be sidelined.
That can't happen.
What are you doing? He's down.
Son of a bitch is a cop killer.
John, stop! We got to call this in.
Not yet we don't.
Help me get him in.
Come on! Help me get him in!
So where are we?
As of right now, we've got
half the decryption key.
That's all?
Can't we accelerate the program?
It's already running at capacity, sir.
- Mr. Hastings.
- Sir, we just found this
among Meredith Reed's personal effects.
It's a dedicated key card,
United Nations issue.
Issued to who?
President Hassan and his family.
It accesses their private residence.
We got her.
Dana Walsh.
Ms. Walsh, this is security
at Perimeter Gate 9. You have a visitor.
A visitor?
A Mr. Kevin Wade.
Says he's a friend of yours.
Ms. Walsh?
Tell him I'll be right there.
So this, uh... this CTU...
some kind of government deal, huh?
Law enforcement?
Ms. Walsh is on her way.
Thanks.
Hey, Dana.
Look at you, all pressed and pretty.
I think I like you as a blonde.
What are you doing here?
I thought I told you to leave me alone.
And I told you not to
hang up on me, Jenny.
Don't.
Don't call me that.
Oh, you... you... you
want me to play along?
Okay, I'll play along.
But I'm not going to let you pretend
that you don't know me.
Fine.
You found me, so now what?
You think we're just going
to pick up where we left off?
Why not?
We had a good thing going.
No.
No, we didn't.
I was naive, and I let
myself be taken in by you.
I am not that person
- anymore.
- Yeah?
CTU.
Senior Data Analyst.
Well, sounds like an important job.
I'm thinking you
always were the smart one.
How the hell did you pull this off?
What, you steal a dead girl's
birth certificate or something?
Look, I have money.
Not a lot, but some.
If that's what it'll take.
If you really still care about me,
you'll leave me alone.
Say my name.
What?
If you're gonna beg,
I want to hear you say my name.
Just like you used to.
Kevin.
Say, "Please, Kevin."
Please... Kevin.
There's my bad girl.
Damn it! What do you want from me?!
A place to crash for starters.
- I'm getting a little tired of living out of the van.
- No, that is not gonna happen.
Yeah? Well, now you don't want me...
to tell everyone you work with
your little secret now, do you?
You see, I don't want to do that.
Come on.
It'll be fun having me around.
It'll be just like old times.
You'll come home...
...and we'll catch up.
Fine, fine.
You can stay the night.
I want you out tomorrow.
Whatever you say.
Do you want my address?
I already got it.
I'm going to ask you again, Ms. Reed,
and this time I want an answer.
Now we know that this key card
was issued to President Hassan
and his family at the U.N.
I want to know
where you got it.
I'm not saying another word
until my attorney gets here.
You're already looking
at a life sentence
in a federal penitentiary.
So if this plot succeeds
and Hassan dies,
I promise you the death penalty.
If you give me the name of the assassin,
maybe we can cut a deal.
- I told you I don't know anything.
- You know who you stole
his key card from.
I didn't steal it.
Then you manufactured it,
cloned it somehow!
No.
And used it to gain access
- to the U.N. security data.
- I, I...
Where did you get it?! Tell me!
He gave it to me.
Who?
Who?!
Omar.
Omar gave it to me.
President Hassan?
Why would he do that?
So I could have access
to his private residence
when he wanted to be alone with me.
You really expect me to believe
that you're involved with him?
Believe what you want. It's the truth.
This is Hastings.
Put me through to Rob Weiss
at the U.N.
What are you doing?
I need to speak with President Taylor
to get permission to
talk with Omar Hassan.
Now if there's something you
want to say to me, Ms. Reed,
now is the time to say it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hastings.
Mr. Weiss is in a closed session,
but they're expecting to break shortly.
All right, just relay the message
to have him call me
back as soon as he can.
Yes, sir.
Looks like you have a bit more time
to reconsider your story.
You let me know when
you're ready to change it.
Mr. Hastings, I need your help.
I've lost contact with Jack.
He called me 15 minutes ago.
We got cut off.
I haven't been able to reach him since.
This is your operation,
Chloe... yours and Bauer's.
I don't see why this
should be my concern.
He could be in some kind of trouble.
You need to send for backup.
Even if I wanted to,
we don't have the manpower.
I dispatched all field
personnel to the U.N.
for Hassan's protection.
I watched the interrogation.
I heard what Reed said about
her affair with Hassan.
If that's true, it supports
our idea that she was framed.
And how do you figure that?
Because it explains why
the biometrics registered her deception,
and why the real insider
within Hassan's camp chose her
to divert our investigation.
Reed is lying.
There is no affair.
But what if there is?
If President Hassan
corroborates Reed's claim,
will you consider sending
units to find Jack?
All right, fine.
Just so you can hear for yourself,
I'll have someone alert you
when Hassan calls me back.
Is that good enough?
No, but it's better than nothing.
That couple you murdered upstairs
were friends of mine, dirtbag.
Good people.
- Mazoni, you can't do this.
- No, what I can't do
is watch another creep like
this walk on a technicality,
or because some lawyer
didn't file the right papers
to the right clerk.
- John!
- I've seen it happen more times than I can count.
You're new here, Phil. You don't know.
Wait till you spend
15 years of your life
grinding your teeth in this job.
You talk to me then.
What about that thing he said?
- About him working with CTU?
- Did we find credentials on him?
- No.
- That's because he is a lying piece of garbage.
This was a home invasion robbery.
Where nothing was taken.
Because we showed up!
Look, you got a problem with
what I'm doing here, Phil?
Then go upstairs and
wait till I'm finished.
Go. Now!
And remember, you don't call this in
until I say so.
You stick to the story.
He was resisting arrest.
You got that?
Just, uh... don't kill him.
I'll do my best.
Hey, Farmer, what are you doing here?
Koernig called in sick.
Stomach thing.
No kidding?
I talked to him this morning.
He was feeling fine.
Probably a few too many at lunch.
...continue to receive
real-time updates at the U.N.
CTU is confirming the link
between the Stinger missile attack
and the assassination plot
against President Hassan.
In response, we're gonna push
the traffic perimeter out
another six blocks and
close the Queensboro Bridge
in both directions until noon tomorrow.
Now, roadblock assignments
are on pages two and three
of your briefing packets.
Go ahead and double-check those now.
CTU has also arrested an
individual inside the U.N.
who we believe is a part of the plot.
Hopefully, this will yield
some information
about the assassin himself.
Until then, we have to assume
that he could strike at any time
and will stop at nothing
to achieve his objective.
He's already killed five
people that we know of,
including two CTU agents.
Whoever he is, he's a professional,
which means everyone is to be
on high alert at all times.
History is happening upstairs, people,
and it's on our watch.
Our position remains unchanged,
Madam President.
We will not allow NATO
to transit supplies
to Afghanistan through our territory.
What about non-military supplies?
It is our belief that
any NATO deployment
in the region, military or otherwise,
will lead to more extremism, not less.
Mr. President...
uh, my director
of Counterterrorism here in New York
is requesting to speak
to you on the phone.
Now?
It's an urgent matter.
It's relating to the reporter
who was arrested earlier.
Mr. Weiss will escort you
to the conference room.
That is, unless you have any objections.
No, not at all.
This way, Mr. President.
Do I have to remind
you of our conversation?
Omar, you must deny your
involvement with this woman.
She has a name, Farhad.
And I still can't believe that
she can be part of this plan.
That should not be your
chief concern right now.
If word of this affair gets out,
not only is your
political career over,
but so is the peace process itself.
You know what you have to do.
- Thank you.
- Mr. President.
Hello?
Mr. President,
this is Brian Hastings at CTU.
I appreciate you getting back to me.
What can I do for you, Mr. Hastings?
Well, sir, I have a matter
of some delicacy to discuss with you.
- Go on.
- Thank you, sir.
I know that your time is valuable,
so, I'll come right to the point.
I understand Meredith Reed
is writing an article on you
for the Sunday Magazine.
Yes, that's correct.
Do you know of any reason
she would be in possession
of a key card to your
residence at the U.N.?
Key card?
Yes, sir.
She claims that she got it from you.
And that your
relationship with her is...
perhaps more than professional.
Mr. President?
Is there anyone listening to
our conversation, Mr. Hastings?
Are we being recorded?
No, sir.
I'm speaking to you on a secure line.
Then I will tell you what Ms.
Reed said is true.
Omar!
What are you doing?!
Sir, are you confirming
a romantic involvement
with Meredith Reed?
Mr. Hastings, I trust
your complete discretion
in this matter.
And I'm sure you
understand the ramification
if what I'm telling you
becomes public knowledge.
Yes, sir, I understand.
I gave Ms. Reed this key card
for reasons I'm sure are clear to you.
I'm telling you all this
in the interests of justice
because I'm convinced
that Ms. Reed is not
part of this conspiracy.
Excuse me for asking, sir,
but are you basing that
certainty on anything
other than your personal feelings?
No, I suppose not.
I see.
Well, thank you for your candor,
Mr. President.
I assure you that nothing we discussed
will be disclosed from this office.
I appreciate that, Mr. Hastings.
Good-bye, then.
Good-bye.
Have you any idea what you've done?
The honorable thing.
You said you'd send
backup to Jack's location.
I said I'd consider it, and I have.
Confirmation of the affair does
not prove Reed's innocence.
For all we know, it's a
ploy she used to gain access
to the U.N. security files,
Hassan's itinerary.
In the meantime, Jack's still missing.
He's not missing.
You lost contact.
His phone battery may have died.
Or more likely, he's in an
area with bad cell reception.
There's pockets of them all
over the five boroughs,
which you would have known
if you were from around here.
Fine, if you're not sending someone,
I'll go myself.
No, you won't!
Your concern for your friend
is admirable,
but that file we got
off Reed's laptop...
it's almost decrypted,
and depending what we find,
I'm going to need you here.
- Is that clear?
- Yeah.
Now, earlier today,
you suggested that I speak to you
more clearly and directly.
You leave the building, you're fired.
Is that clear and direct enough for you?
Hello?
We have a problem.
My brother confessed to the affair.
I don't know if the
frame's going to hold.
That's unfortunate.
Don't you understand?!
CTU won't believe the file you uploaded
to Reed's computer is genuine.
I agree it isn't ideal,
but they will still have to act
on what they find in any event.
There's no reason to
diverge from the plan.
But you need to remain
calm and play your part.
How much longer?
I promise you.
Your brother will be dead
before the hour is out.
Don't move!
Drop that! Now!
Officer, everything I
told you before is true.
My name is Jack Bauer.
- I'm a former federal agent.
- He's lying, Phil!
Shoot the son of a bitch!
He broke my damn rib!
Contact Chloe O'Brian at CTU.
She'll verify my identity and the
threat to the peace conference.
What are you waiting for?
Shoot him already!
Sit back down, John.
You want to be pointing that gun
- someplace else.
- I said don't move, either of you!
What the hell? I'm your partner!
No, this has gone far enough.
I'm calling it in.
You don't want to do that.
Come on, Phil. Put the phone down.
Let's talk about this.
Shut up!
This is Patrolman Phillip Lu.
I need to talk to Lieutenant Sell.
The officer upstairs has to be
- connected to the assassination plot.
- Oh, you happy now?!
- You hearing what he's saying about Koernig?
- All I'm saying is
that there's a connection.
We need to find out what it is.
Both of you, shut the hell up!
Lieutenant, sir.
I'm at the scene of a double homicide.
One of the victims is a cop,
a James Koernig out of Midtown Center.
No, it's definitely murder.
Him and his wife.
We got a suspect in custody.
11447 Broadway. Cross street is Astoria.
Ask him what Officer Koernig's
assignment was today.
Please, innocent lives are at stake.
What have you got to lose?
And, sir?
I need a lookup on
Koernig's duty assignment.
Yeah, transfer me over.
- You screwed up.
- What?
Yeah, surprised me, too.
You forgot to upload a
Rijndael filter to my system.
Without it, I can't break
the last encryption layer
on the file remnant you gave me.
I'm sorry. I will upload
it to a disk for you now.
Or I can just do it at your station.
Okay, fine.
Everything okay?
What do you mean? I don't know.
It's not like you to make mistakes.
You seem a little distracted.
Wedding jitters, maybe?
No.
Just asking.
And Cole's a nice enough guy.
But I could see how you could
start having second thoughts.
I've always been curious
to know what you two
- find to talk about.
- Drop this, Arlo. I am not in the mood.
Hey, I don't mean anything by it.
All I'm saying is that
you and the boy scout
aren't exactly intellectual equals.
Or is that what makes him your type?
See now, you and me, for instance,
we have a lot in common.
We speak the same language.
Mostly techno-jargon granted,
but hey, it can always lead
- to something much deeper.
- Damn it, Arlo!
That's it.
We've got it.
Whoa. Is that what I think it is?
Yes.
Finish decrypting your fragment
and put it up on the screen.
I've got to go tell Hastings.
I don't care what he's demanding.
Tell Ms. Reed's lawyer
he's going to have to wait.
We can hold his
client for up to 18 hours
before formatly charging her.
- Sir?
- I have to go.
We've broken the encryption
code on Reed's file.
The primary file
component's up on screen.
Arlo's waiting for a second
piece to finish rendering.
So, what am I looking at?
Construction plans for work carried out
at the United Nations eight months ago.
- The U.N.? Are you sure?
- Positive.
Two I-beams were retrofitted
to provide structural support
for additional interpreters' booths.
- There and there.
- That looks like
- the Council Chamber.
- It's directly below it.
The decryption's just about complete.
It's loading to the main screen now.
It looks like a schematic
for an incendiary.
A bomb.
Pulse-detonated,
modified to fit between the I-beams.
Sir, judging by the
size, that's big enough
to drop the entire Security Council
into the East River.
Get me Cole and Manners at the U.N.
All stations!
We're implementing protocols
for an immediate evacuation
of the United Nations building!
We are Code Red.
I repeat: this is not a drill.
We are Code Red!
Mr. Hastings, you need to consider
the possibility that this intel is fake
and why they wanted us to find it.
I'm not taking any chances.
Sir, I've got Cole and
Manners on the line.
Gentlemen, we have intel
from the decrypted files
that an incendiary
device has been placed
directly below the Council Chamber.
S... Sir, I don't see how that's possible.
This building's been
vetted for weeks.
U.N. security have swept the
area thoroughly and repeatedly.
Then they missed it.
Mr. Manners,
you need to implement
evacuation protocols immediately.
Cole, I want you on President
Hassan, personally.
Yes, sir.
Hey! You, you, with me! Let's go!
Ladies and gentlemen,
forgive the interruption.
Your attention, please.
We are evacuating
immediately due to
a possible bomb threat.
Security personnel will be receiving
protocol confirmation on
designated channels momentarily.
Evacuation will proceed out these doors
and down to underground parking level B.
Please, speak only with your designated handlers.
- Omar...
Everything will be fine,
Madam President.
Madam President,
you and Secretary Kanin
need to move now.
President Hassan, if you'll follow me.
Traffic control, I need route
lockdown for northern exodus.
All units confirm.
Unit 2 in position.
Unit 3 in position.
Unit 4 in position.
Unit 5 in position.
Where are my wife and daughter?
They're coming down the
east stairwell now, sir.
No more than two minutes behind you.
I won't leav without them.
Mr. President, with all
due respect, my orders are
to evacuate you now.
Omar, I'll wait and go
with them. Don't worry.
I'll make sure they're safe.
Tarin, get my brother out of here.
All right, evac tunnel B! Move!
Yes?
He's in the third car.
The motorcade's coming up the ramps now.
Vehicles are in transit.
Current location: evac tunnel bravo.
Second Avenue teams should
have a visual in five minutes.
- Uncle!
- Where's Omar?
He went ahead. We'll take the next car.
Is it true there's a bomb?
It's just a precaution, Kayla.
Don't worry.
Everything's going to be fine.
Right this way.
Okay. Let's be quick.
Hurry.
The guy who took his place?
What was his name?
Mike Farmer.
Thanks.
Come on. Get out.
You were right.
There is a connection.
Sergeant Koernig was on
the U.N. security detail.
He called in sick about 45 minutes ago.
He was forced to make that call.
You said someone replaced him?
A patrolman named Mike
Farmer from the same unit.
That's your assassin.
Officer, you need to let me call CTU,
and I need to get to
the U.N. immediately.
Officer, this is going down now.
You can either stand
here and do nothing,
or you can help me stop it.
Make the call.
I'll drive you to the U.N.
Thank you.
Where the hell you think you're going?
He can't leave!
He's a material witness!
Jack, where have you been?
Chloe, please just listen to me.
The assassin killed a police officer
and took his place in
the U.N. security detail.
I need to alert Agent Ortiz immediately.
Okay. I'll patch you through.
He's in the middle of evacuating Hassan.
Evacuating him? Why?
Hastings' orders.
The evidence in Reed's computer
indicated that there's a bomb
in the building.
Where's Hassan now?
Hassan's motorcade is
heading up the ramps
in the parking garage,
about to pull out onto Second Avenue.
- Chloe, it's Cole.
- Hang on. I've got Cole.
Agent Ortiz, you're on with Jack Bauer.
What's going on, Jack?
Cole, you need to stop Hassan's car now!
What are you talking about?
The assassin is part of
the evacuation detail.
He's posing as an NYPD officer.
There is no bomb in the U.N.
They're just trying to lure
him out of the building.
Did you tell Hastings about this?
We don't have time.
You need to stop the motorcade
before it hits the street.
It's too late. Hassan's car
just exited the tunnel.
Cole, you need to stop that
car or Hassan's a dead man.
Cole?
Whose vehicle is that?
It's Cole, sir.
Cole,
what the hell are you doing?
Cole!
What was that?
What happened?
Cole, can you verify? Was Hassan hit?
Cole!
Waarez
www.bierdopje.com
www.tvsubtitles.net