Sir, we just found this among
Meredith Reed's personal effects.
It's a dedicated key card,
United Nations issue.
To who? President Hassan and his family.
It accesses their private residence.
We got her.
I want to know where you got it.
Omar gave it to me.
I gave Miss Reed this key card for
reasons I'm sure are clear to you.
Sir, are you confirming
a romantic involvement with Meredith Reed?
I trust your complete
discretion in this matter.
We have a problem.
My brother confessed to the affair.
I don't know if the frame's going to hold.
There is no reason to diverge
from the plan.
How much longer?
Your brother will be dead
before the hour is out.
What are you doing here?
I thought I told you to leave me alone.
CTU.
Senior Data Analyst.
Well, sounds like an important job.
Damn it, what do you want from me?!
A place to crash, for starters.
You can stay the night.
I want you out tomorrow.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're evacuating immediately,
due to a possible bomb threat.
Madam President,
you and Secretary Kanin
need to move now.
President Hassan, if you'll follow me.
Yes?
He's in the third car.
The motorcade's coming up the ramps now.
Officer, this is going down now.
You can either stand here and do nothing
or you can help me stop it.
Cole, you need to stop Hassan's car now.
The assassin is part of
the evacuation detail.
There is no bomb in the UN.
It's too late-- Hassan's
car just exited the tunnel.
Cole, you need to stop that car,
or Hassan's a dead man.
Cole!
What was that?! What happened?
This is a damn disaster, Brian.
What do you mean,
you don't know what happened?
How is Hassan? Is he all right?
We don't know yet, Madam President.
It appears the bomb threat at the UN
was a hoax designed to get
him out of the building.
"It appears"?
An IED was planted on
Hassan's evacuation route.
And you drove him right into it!
One of our agents detected the ambush,
tried to head him off
just as the bomb exploded.
Well, you better pray he got there in time.
Security there! Now!
Stand down! I'm with CTU.
Sir, we need to move you
to another vehicle. Now.
Sir, you do not want to stay here.
Go, go, go.
Move! Move!
Cole?
Yeah.
Thank God you're okay.
I got lucky.
Hassan escaped the blast; he's fine.
He's heading toward CTU,
eastbound on 48th Street
in a black SUV. Got him.
Mr. Hastings, here.
Hassan, he's safe.
Dana, the assassin was posing
as a part of the security team.
I know-- we got the info from Chloe.
The police are putting up a thre
e-bock cordon now.
Cole?
Cole? Cole, are you there?
I've got the suspect-
he's dressed as a cop.
Entering a white low-rise
north of the UN.
Call it in! I'm in pursuit!
Chloe, I need to put out a priority APB.
Move, move, move!
What is it now?
They've got a lead on the assassin.
4722 East 47th Street.
I'm gonna need my weapon.
Your bag's right behind my seat.
East 47th Street-- that's just above the UN.
You're gonna need to turn now.
Now! Now!
UN Four, come in.
UN Four, this is CTU Two. Come in, please.
I'm sorry, I can't reach him. Try again.
That's my husband in that car up there.
They're not answering.
I have to go to him. Dalia! Ma'am,
please, you need to remain in the car.
Stay calm.
I'll try another number.
Where are you?
Yes, we're safe.
Dalia, Kayla and myself.
I need to know about my brother.
He's alive.
He survived.
Farhad, how is he?
He's alive.
God is with us.
Can you tell me what happened?
A car in the motorcade
swerved in front of him.
They're locking down the entire area.
What would you suggest we do?
It's over.
Get out now.
It can't be long before
they realize it's you.
Farhad?
Sir, please stay in the car!
Please, sir.
Sir, I need you to get back in the car.
Oh!
Get on your knees.
Slide your weapon back to me.
Slowly...
slow...
Now... you're going to walk me out of here.
Call in.
Say the southwest corner is clear.
Tell them to move the search
team to the northeast.
Do it.
You want to live?
Make the call.
This is Cole Ortiz
in the southwest corner of the building.
I'm in pursuit of the assassin.
He's with me now.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Okay.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. President, Brian Hastings.
We spoke on the phone.
We're glad you're here. Please follow me.
Is my family here?
No, sir. We'll try and get
you all together shortly.
Are they all right?
Your wife and daughter are fine.
And my brother?
Was he hurt?
No, sir.
Mr. President...
It appears your brother was
involved with the attack.
My brother?
Yes, sir.
That can't be right.
Bring him to me. I need to talk to him.
Unfortunately, we don't know
where he is at the moment.
Then how can you be sure it was him?
Mr. President, after the explosion,
he killed one of my men to
facilitate his own escape.
There were witnesses,
including your wife and daughter.
He's the insider we've been looking for.
There's no doubt.
Excuse me, sir. I'm sorry for interrupting.
You asked for any updates
about the assassin.
And?
He's dead. Jack just called it in.
He uplinked some video
footage that you need to see.
I'll be there in a minute.
Don't let me keep you from your job.
Thank you, sir.
No, thank you. I owe you my life.
Conference room.
Uh, Mr. Hastings, uh...
Meredith Reed,
the woman you brought here for
questioning, where is she?
Still here.
Looks like she'll be
cleared of any wrongdoing.
I'd like to talk to her.
I'll arrange it.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I saw that. What?
The way you looked at me when he
thanked me for saving his life.
You think he should have been thanking you?
I was actually thinking
he should thank Jack,
then Cole, then maybe me.
I underestimated you, Chloe.
You saw what was really going on; I did not.
It was a major save.
And my report will state that.
Chloe said you have some video to show me.
Yes, sir. Take a look.
These are images uplinked
by Jack Bauer
from the bomb site.
It's the assassin who was targeting Hassan.
We have an ID? Not yet.
But I believe we do have a workable lead.
These are tattoos off the
two men who attempted
to take out our informant this afternoon.
Same as the assassin.
We believe they indicate membership
in a particular Russian crime syndicate.
What's a Russian gang have against
the leader of the Islamic Republic?
I don't know.
Could just be hired muscle.
But when the photos arrived,
I ran them by the FBI.
Turns out, they had an agent
undercover working with
the Russian mob here several years ago.
A woman. Contact her.
Already done. I have a
helicopter bringing her in now.
Chloe, I think you worked with her.
Renee Walker.
Says here she's no longer with the FBI.
It's true.
She resigned over an internal dispute.
Meaning she was fired
and her records have been sealed.
What are we getting into here?
Sir, we are only using her to brief us.
These Russian groups are secretive
to the point of paranoia.
She's the only one
who ever got close.
President Omar Hassan was
not harmed in the attack,
and has since been taken
to a secure location.
Confirmed fatalities now stand at three...
...including a police officer.
Yes?
Why is my brother still alive?
You're upset, Farhad.
Justifiably.
Your man failed!
Once you have the materials
in your possession,
your brother, his peace conference,
none of that matters.
Isn't that what you told me?
All you have to do is stay
calm and stick to your plan.
Or should I be looking for another buyer?
I'll be there soon.
Good.
We'll have a nice meal waiting.
And we'll talk.
I've been informed that the
bomb threat was a hoax.
That's confirmed, Madam President.
We've swept the negotiating
chamber with sniffer dogs
and ground- penetrating radar.
I can assure you, it's safe.
I'm glad to hear it.
Hassan is standing by at CTU.
How is he, Rob?
Well, he narrowly escaped
being blown to pieces by his
own brother, so not too well.
But your call to him can't just
be all sympathy and concern.
We need to know where he stands vi
s-à-vis the talks.
It's hardly the time.
No, it's exactly the time.
The signing is scheduled for tomorrow.
Dozens of world leaders are
already en route to New York.
We need to know if we still
have a peace process.
Put him on.
Sir,
I have President Taylor for you.
Madam President.
I cannot begin
to say how relieved I am
that you survived this
terrible attack, Omar.
Thank you.
I'm mortified that this
outrage happened on U.S. soil.
I'm the one who should be embarrassed.
My brother, Farhad, did this.
He betrayed me, and worse,
he put you in harm's way.
I should have realized what he's up to.
We can only be betrayed
by the people we trust.
He fooled all of us.
Sir, this is Rob Weiss.
You've heard Farhad escaped.
Can I ask what you think
his agenda might be,
aside from targeting you?
Uh, w-what I mean, sir,
is... does he have a plan?
Yes, he has a plan.
Regime change.
Isn't that what you Americans call it?
Mr. President, we're doing everything we can
to apprehend Farhad,
but while he's at large, I'd understand it
if you wished not to continue the talks.
However, I hope that I can
persuade you to reconvene.
We have come so far together.
And to let this moment slip...
Would be to hand Farhad victory.
I will not give him this satisfaction.
If you are willing to continue
with these talks, so am I.
I am delighted to hear it.
Uh, if you could persuade
Mr. Hastings here to release me.
We'll coordinate with CTU
so that you can return to
the UN as soon as possible.
I-I know that you want to be
with your wife and daughter.
Thank you.
Thank you, Madam President.
You want your office back, Mr. Hastings.
It's fine, sir.
Can I ask what you and
President Taylor agreed?
That I should return to
UN as soon as possible.
We'll make the arrangements.
Uh, before I leave,
I would like to thank
the young man who saved my life.
That would be Agent Ortiz.
He's returning to CTU right now.
You really should go to Medical.
Yeah.
Soon as I hand the body over to Forensics.
What are you going to do?
Finish my debrief, try and catch
that last flight to Los Angeles.
Thanks, Jack. It's been an honor.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Hey.
I'm glad you're okay.
Thanks. Me, too.
We ID'd the assassin
using your video footage.
We think he was working for
one of the Russian crime syndicates here.
Any idea which one?
Not yet.
But we're bringing in someone to brief us.
Good.
Jack, it's Renee.
What?
Why?
Six years ago, she worked
undercover with the Russian mob.
FBI says she's still one of
the best experts they have.
Have you spoken to her?
No.
I tried phoning her a few times,
she never returned my calls.
She made it clear she
didn't want to speak to me,
so I-I let it go.
I heard she had a rough time.
Yeah.
Like, a really rough time-
some sort of a breakdown.
She should be landing any minute.
Look, she didn't want to talk to me then,
she's not gonna want to talk to me now,
and I want to respect that.
So, please, don't tell her I'm here, okay?
You sure?
Yeah. Okay.
I'll be waiting for you
up in Debrief One.
We'll get you a full set of
photos as soon as possible.
Thanks. Mm-hmm.
Agent Ortiz.
Mr. President.
I want to thank you for saving my life.
You're welcome, sir, but it wasn't just me.
If it weren't for Jack Bauer
and Chloe O'Brian, I wouldn't have been
in place to make the save.
Well, I'll thank them, too,
but you risked your life for me.
You put yourself between me and the bomb.
My family and I
are in your debt.
What's that?
It's a hazardous materials alert.
Hazardous materials?
Please wait here, sir.
What's going on?
The body triggered a hazmat alarm.
We're reading radioactive contaminants.
What sort of contaminants?
Rad count's low, so it could be uranium.
It's just trace elements.
There's no danger.
U-235?
It's highly enriched uranium.
You mean it's weapons-grade?
Yes. How the hell did he
come into contact with that?
I don't know, but he had to
have been exposed to it recently.
I think I know the answer.
What is it, sir?
Sir, we're talking about nuclear materials.
If you know something, you need to tell us.
I need to talk to Mr. Hastings right now.
Hey, Renee.
It's good to see you.
This way.
Didn't know you were back at CTU.
Yeah. Morris lost his job a year ago.
I asked to be reinstated,
and this is where they assigned me.
So what about you?
I heard you've been working
for a security firm.
Uh, I was.
Didn't work out.
So it's confirmed and you're certain.
Thanks.
It's Forensics.
They confirmed the composition
of the radioactive material.
It's U-235, 94.7% pure,
weapons-grade uranium.
If you have an explanation, sir,
I'm eager to hear it.
Before we started this peace initiative,
my country was close to
developing a nuclear weapon.
Yes, our intelligence was aware of that.
You may also be aware
that we could not enrich
enough fissile material to arm it.
Soon after our countries began
to negotiate the peace process,
my brother came up to me
and said that someone
had approached him with
weapons-grade uranium.
Who?
Someone who had access
to decommissioned Soviet stockpiles.
You think it's
the same Russians who were
trying to kill you today?
Yes, I do.
I told my brother to stay away from them,
but obviously he had other plans.
Mr. President,
the nuclear material that you were offered,
you have any idea where it is?
That man was contaminated recently.
Doesn't that mean the materials are here
in the U.S.?
Farhad always used to tell me
that our country will always
be at the mercy of the West
unless we become a nuclear power.
You must find
the Russians
before they can get
the uranium to my brother.
We'll do what we have to do, sir.
I'll notify my security
forces to cooperate fully.
Patty,
get me the file on Renee
Walker's undercover operation.
The stars mean these men were
part of the criminal elite.
Vory v zakone.
This one spent time
in a Siberian prison camp-- IK-10.
The number of spires
means length of sentence.
Three years?
Three life terms.
Must have escaped.
Now these, broken cross,
here, here and here.
Same on all three.
So what does it mean?
Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
I appreciate that you came in.
So what does it mean?
It means you can break our arms,
you can break every bone in our body-
we'll never talk.
It's supposed to be the symbol
for a group called Red Square.
Supposed to be? We tried to find them
and never got close.
A lot of rumors that they're ex-military,
special forces, intelligence, whatever.
I'm not sure they actually exist.
They exist, Ms. Walker.
And we need to find them.
Why?
You're aware of the attack in midtown today?
You mean the smoking crater by the UN?
Yeah, it was hard to miss.
Well, we believe it's just the beginning,
and that the group responsible
is in possession of
unsecured nuclear materials.
Now Dana asked you here today
to brief on background.
But I have a much bigger ask.
You were undercover for nearly
two years with the Russian mob.
Your cover's still intact.
What are you saying exactly?
Are you... are you asking me to go back in?
Dana, Chloe, would you
give us a moment, please?
I wouldn't be asking if
it weren't important,
but yes,
I want you to go back in.
And this doesn't seem in the least bit--
I don't know, ironic to you?
I know that you left the FBI
under difficult circumstances.
Difficult doesn't even begin to describe it.
I can get you your badge back.
I laid down my badge, Mr. Hastings.
I took it from my pocket and I laid it down.
So why would you possibly
think that I want it back?
Well, what do you want?
What do I want?
Nothing.
You have weapons-grade uranium
in the hands of the Russian O.C.
I can do something about that.
So I'll go back in...
but not for a badge.
Thank you.
We brief in ten minutes.
Hey.
Just want to say good-bye.
You're off finally?
Yeah.
How did Renee's debriefing go?
It was going fine until Hastings
kicked me out. Why'd he kick you out?
It just started to get really uncomfortable.
Is that her undercover file?
Yeah. I'm just trying to get up to speed.
They found traces of
uranium on the assassin.
Hastings says there's
nuclear materials in play.
Yeah, I heard.
What's that got to do with Renee?
He asked her to go back
under with the Russians.
What is it?
Hey.
Jack.
Chloe didn't tell me you were here.
I asked her not to.
I didn't think you'd want to see me.
Right.
You tried to get in touch,
and I didn't call back.
Sorry.
I was so happy to hear
that you were okay, though.
Thank you.
I'm surprised that you're back at CTU.
I'm actually not.
I'm moving back to Los
Angeles with my daughter.
I'm supposed to be on a
plane with her right now.
Then what are you doing here?
An old informant knocked on my door.
Everything went downhill from there.
The attack in midtown.
That's why I'm here, too.
I heard Hastings wants you to go undercover
with the Russians again.
He does. I've agreed.
You really think that's a good idea?
They need me.
I'm not worried about them.
I'm worried about you.
I know what you did.
Really, Jack? What did I do?
You almost killed Wilson
during your interrogation.
In fact it was so bad,
the FBI had to let you go.
Even after everything you did that day.
Renee, I know where you are,
and it's a dark place.
Yeah, and I've come back.
It takes longer than you think.
I wouldn't have signed up
for this if I wasn't ready.
And I don't think you are.
Renee, this is too important.
You need to let them take
care of it. They will.
I appreciate what you're
trying to do, really.
You said you were going to Los Angeles
to be with your daughter, right?
Please don't do this.
Go to California, Jack.
I have a briefing.
You will receive an official apology
for your detention here, but in the meantime
I hope you can accept my
sincere personal regrets.
I'm sure you understand
that given the threat
to President Hassan,
we were under extreme pressure.
I would have thought that came with the job.
Along with the ability
to handle it.
Good-bye, Mr. Hastings.
Ms. Reed.
Thank God you're all right.
I was lucky.
I heard it was Farhad who
tried to have you killed.
I can't believe he would betray you.
He betrayed both of us, Meredith.
And then I betrayed you.
What are you talking about?
I told them about us.
I was scared. I panicked.
I hope you can forgive me.
There's nothing to forgive.
But you stood by me.
You didn't deny me.
Even though you had a million reasons to.
Before that moment, I...
I never really knew what you felt for me.
You should have.
Didn't I make it clear?
What? What is it?
I nearly died today.
And I saw how fragile it all is.
Not only my life, but
everything I've ever worked for.
Any good I might be able to do.
I just can't jeopardize that.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Meredith...
Six years ago I was
undercover with these men.
They were running an arms trafficking ring.
We broke up the ring and arrested everyone
except for the man in charge-
Vladimir Laitanan.
He's our target.
It was through him I first heard
about the group Red Square.
If anyone can connect us to them it's him.
Everything I've read about Laitanan
says he disappeared without a trace.
How are you going to find him?
Through this guy.
Ziya Dakhilov.
He's out on parole.
He'll take us to Vladimir.
The FBI offered Ziya full
immunity if he gave up Vladimir.
He turned it down and kept
his mouth shut and did his time.
I'm not FBI, I'm a former felon, remember?
I'll be offering Ziya
the deal of a lifetime.
Trust me, he'll take it.
Once I've made contact with Vladimir,
I'll tell him that I've heard whispers
of nuclear materials on the market.
I'll say I have a buyer for them.
Who's that going to be? Agent Ortiz?
You up for this?
Yes, sir.
How much money are we talking about?
For nuclear rods,
we need to show offshore accounts
of $100 million at least.
Probably twice that.
Okay, I'll get on that.
Chloe will work up a backstory to cover
the time after your release from prison.
Now you and Agent Ortiz need to figure out
where you met,
how long you've known each other.
Jack.
I thought you'd left.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But could I have the room with Mr.
Hastings alone, please?
You, too, Renee.
I think I'll stay.
So what's going on, Jack?
Agent Walker hasn't been
undercover for over six years.
I think you're making a
mistake by putting her in.
Why don't you tell him what's
really on your mind, Jack?
I'll tell him exactly what I told you.
I'm concerned about her,
and this operation.
So what does that mean?
She's not ready for this.
You must have other options.
Mr. Hastings,
no one else knows these Russians.
No one else can get you as close.
Unfortunately, I'm your only choice.
I appreciate your concern, Jack,
but she's right.
She's our only way in.
Fine, then I want to go with her.
I assume your plan is trying
to set up a competing buy?
I'll act as a buyer.
That won't be necessary.
Agent Ortiz has already agreed.
He doesn't have the experience.
Then this is how he gets it.
Not with nuclear weapons on the line.
Mr. Hastings,
I'm officially requesting
that you send me in
with Agent Walker.
Jack, if you're willing to do this,
I'd be foolish to object.
We'll work up a cover for you
and dovetail it with Agent Walker's alias.
We're going to have to work fast.
The Russians are going to want
to unload the nuclear fuel rods
as quickly as possible.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure this information is reliable?
MAN : It checks out.
All right then.
Farhad is here.
Bring him in.
You look worried.
Every cop in the country
is hunting this man,
but we let him come here?
So, how does looking like
a scared girl help us?
This man is our buyer.
Well, we found him,
we can find another.
Josef, my son, we are on the verge
of the biggest deal of our lives.
Farhad is paying us more
than anyone dreamed possible,
and you want to send him away
because he makes you nervous?
Sit down, please.
A drink first, then some food.
I want to see the rods.
They will be on the same ship
that will transport you
back to your country.
As soon as we have completed
our financial arrangements.
You'll be paid, Bazhaev,
after I have the rods.
They are in a secure place.
Show me.
You've seen the photographs.
That's not good enough.
I want proof that
the rods exist or you will not be paid.
You want proof, huh?
Okay.
Come with me.
Josef...
My younger son.
He was transporting the rods...
...and he was careless.
There. You have your proof.
How long will it take to
get the rods to the ship?
Five hours.
I want to be there to supervise the loading.
Whatever you want, my friend.
Now where is my money?
I'll make the call.
Agent Walker worked undercover
as Renee Zadan for 16 months
before the bust went down
and she was incarcerated.
We're focusing on the period
of time just after her release
when she's supposed to be
in Mexico working with Jack.
We're synchronizing two
years of travel materials
mostly to and from Mexico City.
What all do we know about
this Ziya character
that she's visiting?
Not much.
He pled out to a clas
s-three felony one month after the bust.
He's now in Long Island City
working in an auto parts store
as a condition to his early release.
That's where Jack and Renee are headed now.
Where exactly are they?
En route. Just leaving Manhattan.
Good. Chloe, download the
cover materials to them.
Walk them through it.
Make sure there's no surprises.
Jack, it's Chloe.
You should be receiving
a consolidated timeline
plus detail files for travel and residency.
Have they downloaded to your PDA yet?
Yes, we got it, Chloe.
Oh, and Dana would like for me
to review the facts with you,
if that's okay.
We're fine, Chloe.
I know how to prep a cover.
I'm sure you do, it's just that...
Chloe, it's all right.
As soon as we got something,
we'll get back to you.
Okay, I guess
I will leave you then. Good luck.
Thanks.
You got a problem?
No, just that you've got
everyone treating me like I'm an invalid.
No one's treating you like an invalid.
It's standard procedure.
They're trying to sync up two cover stories.
He's not gonna quiz me on the facts, Jack.
He gonna take one look at
me and decide if I'm lying.
I know. And whatever happens after that,
we need to be ready.
It's hard being with you
when you don't think
that I'm up to this.
I never said you weren't up to this.
I said I was concerned about you.
It's different.
Whatever you call it,
the fact is you don't trust me, not really.
So here we are.
Me and my babysitter.
How are we on aerial?
Already in place and
they're not even there yet.
Jack and Renee are five minutes from target.
They should arrive just
before he closes up shop.
Walsh.
Someday, you're going to have
to tell me how you picked that name.
I can't talk now.
I like your apartment, Jenny. Real homey.
And I gotta compliment you
on your housekeeping skills,
everything is in its place.
And I've been admiring your photos,
I hope you don't mind.
And I've noticed kind of a theme.
You and your boyfriend, I'm guessing.
Is that right?
Yes.
I hope it's not too serious.
We're getting married, Kevin.
Wow.
Who would have guessed?
When I saw you, you weren't exactly wearing
an engagement ring.
So tell me about him.
Kevin, don't.
Don't what?
I'm curious, can you blame me?
He's... he's just a guy that I met.
A guy you met.
What's that mean, a guy you met?
I just spent seven years
in prison with some guys.
Is that the kind of guy you mean?
You know what? I'm beginning to see that
we need to talk about this in person.
Look, I told you that I'm in
the middle of a crisis here.
I can't. I don't have time.
You know what, Jenny? In my experience,
when something's important,
you make time for it.
Don't you think?
Jenny, are you there?
Don't call me that!
What?
I said...!
You don't tell me what to call you,
what not to call you, you understand that?!
I'll call you whatever I want!
You don't tell me anything, Jenny!
Now get back here.
I said...
that I will
as soon as I can.
Yeah, well, it better be soon.
That's him.
Looks like he's closing up.
Okay, we'll use these for comm so I can
hear you in case you get into trouble. Okay.
Hey.
This is your last shot.
You do not have to do this.
I know, but I want to.
: We're closed.
What'd I say?
Renee.
Ziya.
Nice outfit. Not a lot
of men can pull off a skirt.
When did you get out?
I thought you were serving seven-to-ten.
They let me out early. Good behavior.
Good behavior.
With warden?
Well, eventually, yeah.
But it's like anything else,
you gotta work your way up.
So why you here?
I'm looking for Vladimir.
Got a business proposition I
know he'd be interested in.
What kind of business proposition?
Got a buyer, something big being sold.
Yeah? I don't know. Vlad disappear.
Hmm, maybe.
But you can find him.
Really? Why I do that?
Why do you think?
I don't know.
I'll cut you in.
Unless, of course,
you're making so much money here
that that's of no interest to you.
See? Your greedy little eyes are saying,
"Show me the money,
" so what's the problem, Ziya?
Parole bracelet?
They know where I am 24-7.
I'm like dog.
I leave yard, I get shock.
Well, then just help me out.
Make some calls.
Make calls?
You know what happen I make
call asking where's Vladimir?
Tomorrow, have accident on way for work.
No, sensitive information,
done face-to-face, you know that.
You're lucky.
You get out. Me, I'm still in prison.
Let me see the bracelet.
No.
Come on. No.
Let me see it, Ziya. Hmm?
Ziya... What?
Have I ever messed you up ever?
Come on.
Let's see.
I can get this off, guaranteed.
You screw with this, you know what happen?
Cops come running in.
In two hours, I'm back inside.
Parole violation. Shh...
What? That's not gonna happen,
I'm telling you.
I know how to get this off.
How do you know?
'Cause I'm constantly having
to deal with people like you, that's how.
I can get it off if I
can just hold it steady.
But... you can't cut bracelet.
I'm not gonna cut the bracelet.
What have you done?
What the hell have you done?!
Like he said, he was trapped here.
And think he's gonna help you now?!
That's it. This is over.
This is over!
Maybe for you, Jack,
but I'm just getting started.
Find something to cauterize that wound.
Damn it.
Waarez
www.bierdopje.com
www.tvsubtitles.net