u know him,
don't you?
Mr. Prady, we are in the middle
of a national security crisis.
I have to go back to my desk.
Okay, perhaps if I talk
to your supervisor,
he could let you
take a few minutes off.
It's over.
The parole officer looking
for Kevin is here in CTU.
He's after the raw feed.
I'm gonna give it to him, Cole.
Why don't you wait?
Do you hear me?
He knows everything;
he'll go to Hastings.
Do what he says and
you won't get hurt.
Who is he?
Another traitor?
The only traitor is your father.
We haven't disabled the American
radiological detectors yet.
Where are the nuclear rods?
They're still outside the city.
How will you bring
the rods to me?
It's been taken care of.
Let's go!
Stop them!
Tarin, no!
Oh!
Mr. Hastings, you better
take this; it's Kayla Hassan!
She's in a car; she's escaped.
They tried to kill me,
but Tarin got me out.
They shot him.
He told me to call CTU!
Ms. Hassan,
my name is Jack Bauer.
We need to know
where you were being held.
We got the location, Jack.
Targets are heading
north on Orchard.
They're getting into an SUV.
We ID'd one of the targets
as Tarin Faroush; Kayla said
he sacrificed himself to
save her, but he's still alive.
Chloe, the car that Tarin
got into-- where is it now?
Taking the first exit
off the Williamsburg Bridge.
You've gotta put
Hastings on now.
I'm on, Jack.
You cannot let Kayla Hassan in.
The terrorists faked her escape.
They wanted to get her to CTU.
She's in the tunnel.
Stop the car!
Whoa, whoa!
Put your hands where
we can see them!
It's an EMP!
What the hell's happening?
Contact NSA.
Terrorists just took down CTU.
Central comm node
is totally fried.
Reroute to peripherals.
I already tried that.
Try again, Chloe.
Sir, I can't give you
the status on the drones.
Everything's down.
Which means what?
That they're going to fall
out of the sky? Not yet.
The nav systems should
default to autopilot.
They'll circle until
they run out of gas.
But we've lost all
aerial surveillance
and radiological
detection capability.
Basically.
All right.
Agent Skaggs is heading
outside on foot.
Have him contact FAA with the
drones' default flight paths.
They need to be taken down
before they crash
into populated areas.
Yes, sir.
Are you okay?
Am I okay?
An EMP just took us
out of play
and now we're
dropping the ball
on a radiological threat
against New York City.
So, no, Chloe,
I am not okay.
And I won't be until
we find those rods.
Sir, Kayla Hassan is
finished in Medical.
Okay, I need her
taken back to the UN
so she can be evacuated
with her family.
Okay, I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
I need you to assemble
division heads.
Tell them that we have
a briefing in ten minutes.
Tell them to come with full
damage assessment reports.
Sir, their systems are down.
They can't generate reports.
Then tell them to use a pen
and a damn legal pad.
Phil Holden.
Phil, it's Jack Bauer.
Ah, Jack, I heard you
were back in play.
Phil, look, I don't have
a lot of time,
I need you to listen to me
carefully.
Go ahead. There's an IRK
splinter cell trying to smuggle
weapons-grade uranium
into the city.
Yeah, I just read
the threat assessment.
It says you've got
a CTU team tracking them.
We did, but we lost them.
CTU just got hit by some
electromagnetic pulse device,
wiped out all
our visual and comm.
I want you to try
and locate our hostiles
with one of your satellites.
We don't have any birds
over the metro area, Jack.
All aerial surveillance
was being routed through CTU.
What about traffic cams?
I can try.
Give me the hostiles'
last location.
They got off the
Williamsburg Bridge
at the West Broadway/
Roebling Street exit.
They're driving a gray SUV.
I'll call you
if we get a hit.
Phil, I also need you
to shut down
all bridge and tunnel traffic
into the city.
Thanks.
Done.
Where are you going?
NSA's shutting
all bridge and tunnel traffic
into the city.
There's only one way
for them to get in.
Across the East River.
That's right.
CTU is down.
You have confirmation?
I have a real-time uplink
to the power grid.
It recorded a pulse surge
and now nothing.
CTU is blind,
deaf, and dumb.
Have you secured this area?
As you ordered.
You've done well, Ali.
Thank you, sir.
Load the rods into the Zodiac.
I realize this was very
difficult for you,
but Hassan's daughter
was a necessary sacrifice.
Using her was the only way
for us
to get the rods into the city.
Agents Beck and Henderson
will escort you back to the UN.
First, tell me
what's going on.
Agent Beck will brief you
on the way.
Now, once you're there, we need
you to do something for us.
Your father gave us a file
of IRK covert agents
operating in this country.
We need you to identify
the men working
with Tarin.
I'm not doing anything until
you tell me what's happening.
The car you drove here
was rigged
with an EMP device.
It's a pulse weapon designed
to disarm electronics.
It's crashed all our systems.
I don't understand.
Tarin put me in that car.
He used you, Ms. Hassan.
He staged your escape,
put you in that car,
and sent you back here.
But he was shot.
I saw him.
He is alive.
We spotted him
a few minutes ago.
I know it's a lot
to take in,
but you need to go
with these agents
back to the UN and start
looking through those files.
You've seen
these terrorists.
If you can help us
to ID them,
we stand a chance
of finding them
before they carry out
their attack.
Ahman has prepared the bomb.
It'll be short work
once we get the rods
across the river.
MAN (over radio):
A vehicle is coming.
Where is it?
It's coming from the east.
Black SUV, no markings.
How many men have you got covering?
Three.
Wait until the SUV's
in the range,
then take them out.
Ali! Come!
Hold on.
What is it?
Thought I caught something
in the infrared.
Heat source down by the water.
Now it's gone.
See if NYPD can get
some units down here.
I'll contact NSA,
see if they've got
surveillance of the area.
That's weird.
I got four bars, but the
call's not going through.
Me neither.
We're being jammed.
They're here. Damn it!
Get down now!
(engine cranking)
Come on!
The engine's down.
Pass your weapons up front!
Cole, I want you to take
the sniper to your north.
Maintain coverage
until we're clear.
I want both of you
to get ready to unload
all the weapons from
the back, you ready?
Yes, sir.
Let's go, go, go!
How did they know
where to look for us?
They must have followed us
from the vault.
Cole, use your infrared!
Call out the snipers
as you see them!
Ten o'clock, high and low!
I'm counting four men.
I recognize one
from the hospital.
He was the one
that talked Marcos
out of detonating the vest.
It's Jack Bauer.
Ex-CTU. He was one
of their best agents.
Nine o'clock low!
We can still cross
with the rods.
As long as we're certain Bauer
and his men cannot warn anyone.
It's not a risk.
We started jamming
their communications
as soon as they were in sight.
Now they can't leave.
Not with the snipers
in position.
Good.
Make sure none of them
get out alive.
I'll call you
when we're across the river.
Let's move.
Reloading!
I've got two men,
leaving the dock in a boat.
One of them is Tarin Faroush.
They're carrying a box
the right size and shape
for the rods, Jack.
Copy that!
Went out of my range.
We got to notify NYPD
before they cross the river.
I tried cell
and radio frequencies.
They're all jammed.
There's a call box mounted
on the building. Ten o'clock.
It's gotta be a hard line.
We can call from there.
How do we get there?
The way the shooters are
positioned, they'll pick us off
one by one
as soon as we step out
from behind the vehicle.
Our vehicle's armored.
We can pull the panels,
use them for coverage.
Start now!
Eleven o'clock, Jack!
Casualty reports are
also coming in.
Three fatalities
from the bomb blast
in the motor pool tunnel.
Damn it.
What else?
Minor injuries for the most part.
Agent McCallan was burned
in a small electrical fire.
How is he?
He's going to be okay.
But with our infirmary down
we had to transport him
to the local hospital.
Says here we have
flooding.
Yes, sir, the pumps
are down,
and certain sections
of the basement
have about six inches of water.
Well, can you stop it
or are we all going to drown?
The repair crew's
working on it, sir.
Okay, give me another update
in 20 minutes.
Excuse me, sir?
Yes, what is it?
A team from NSA is here.
NSA?
Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
Frank Haynam, senior engineer
at the New York
field office.
I understand you've
been hit by an EMP.
Yeah, that's right.
I hope that you're here
to help because we can
damn well use it.
We are indeed.
Brought my best men with me.
I thought we'd start
by restoring
your aerial surveillance
and communications.
So, where's your server room?
It's downstairs.
I'll let my maintenance team
know what you're here.
You boys can put
your heads together.
I prefer to work
with my own people.
There's no one more familiar
with this facility than my crew.
Not exactly true.
I was part of the group
that helped design this place.
Can't say I'm thrilled
with what you've done with it.
How did you find out
we were hit?
Jack Bauer called our
regional headquarters.
Told us your situation.
Bauer was pursuing the men
behind this attack
when we lost contact with him.
Do you know
where he is?
NSA's been trying
to call him back.
He's not answering.
They're not sure why.
Right this way.
Chloe, we're supposed to be
writing damage assessments.
What are you doing?
There might be away to tap in,
get some of our systems
up and running.
Really? How?
I haven't figured it out yet,
and I won't if you
keep talking to me.
All right, people,
listen up.
This is Frank Haynam,
senior engineer of the NSA's
New York field office.
Now, he and his team
are going to help us
restore aerial surveillance
and communications.
So we can get back
to tracking the nuclear rods.
They also brought along a fresh
batch of cell phones.
Give them your
full cooperation.
Whatever they need,
make it happen.
Now, we have been knocked down,
but I promise you,
we are going
to get back up.
Let's get to work.
Agent Blochard, can you get
Mr. Haynam and his team
down to the server room?
Has NSA heard
from Jack?
Yeah. They spoke with Jack
and his team
about 20 minutes ago,
but haven't been able
to reach him since.
Why not?
They don't know.
He could be in some
kind of trouble.
You need to send men
out looking for him.
Even if I had agents available,
I wouldn't know
where to send them.
Jack was heading
toward the East River.
That's four square miles
of real estate--
too much for me
to commit resources
that we don't have.
He was pursuing the terrorists.
He's our best chance
at stopping this attack.
We're going to focus
on our efforts here.
When we get our eyes
and ears back,
we'll find them.
It might be too late.
If anyone can take care
of themselves, it's Jack.
Now, I want you to go
to the server room,
make sure Haynam has everything
he needs.
Worse than I thought.
90% of these components
are fried.
We're going to have
to swap them out
and install new server boards.
Mr. Haynam.
I'm Chloe O'Brian.
Mr. Hastings wanted me to make
sure you have everything
you need.
We're fine, Ms. O'Brian. Thank you.
You're going in through
the CLR processor?
That's right.
We're going to isolate it
from the main servers and
create a brand-new subnet.
Creating a brand-new subnet
from scratch?
That'll take forever.
Ms. O'Brian, thanks
for offering your help.
We'll take it from here.
Look, I think
there's another way.
I've been looking
at the CTU schematics.
Why not tap directly
into the trunk line?
Because I'm not insane.
Mr. Haynam, we need to make sure
those nuclear rods
don't get into
the city.
What I'm suggesting
wille a lot faster.
Yeah, and it could make things
a whole lot worse.
How could things be any worse?
You reopen that trunk line
without system buffers in place,
you could cause an overload,
wind up electrocuting
yourself,
not to mention starting a fire
that canurn down
half the building.
I'm aware of the risks.
I think I can create
a workaround.
You couldn't keep an EMP
from taking out
your whole operation.
Forgive me if I don't bow
to your expertise.
If you'd stop with the cheap
insults and just listen to me.
Look, I'm not here
to brainstorm.
I'm here to clean up your mess.
You need to leave.
Now.
I said now,
Ms. O'Brian.
I won't ask you again.
Start prepping the CLR
for a diagnostic.
Arlo, is there any other way
to get into the trunk line
besides the server room?
No, that's the only
way in. Why?
I think I have a faster way
to get us back online,
but Haynam says
it's too dangerous.
I think he's
a raging egomaniac.
Seems to be a prerequisite
for engineers these days.
You talk to Hastings?
If I tell Hastings,
he'll just shoot me down.
Maybe not.
And maybe the moon will fall
from the sky.
Just let it go.
These NSA guys seem to know
what they're doing.
And if they don't,
what happens to Jack?
What's Jack got
to do with this?
(sighs)
Never mind.
Hello?
Renee, it's Chloe.
Where are you?
I'm at Jack's apartment.
What's going on?
Everything.
All of our systems
CTU was hit bare down.
It's a real mess.
How did that happen?
I can't go into it right now,
but we think
the terrorists were trying
to take out
our radiological detectors.
Where's Jack?
That's why I'm calling you.
I think he might be
in some kind of trouble.
We need to find him.
Slow down, Chloe.
Uh, what-what do you mean?
What-what kind of trouble?
Jack was tracking the terrorists
when the EMP hit.
Uh, whHe called NSA, mean?
and they lost contact, too.
Does Hastings know
about this?
He's the one
who told me.
What's he doing about it?
Nothing.
He won't send anyone out
to look for them.
He says he can't
spare the men
and that Jack can take
care of himself.
Where was Jack
before you lost contact?
He took the first exit
off the Williamsburg Bridge.
I'm going to try
to find him, Chloe.
You need to get CTU back online
as soon as you can.
Once you acquire
Jack's position,
you can direct me to him.
Yeah, well, that might
take a while.
NSA brought in
a repair team
and they're going
about it all wrong.
I have a faster way
to get us back online.
Well, then tell them.
I tried.
They won't listen.
Then you need to make
them listen, Chloe.
Do what you have to do.
Okay. I will.
Call me when you're back up.
The EMP took out
all of our systems.
And since we don't know
how long it's going to be
until we're up
and running again,
we're going to have to evacuate
all nonessential personnel.
You're going to follow
Agent Combs
through our access tunnel.
I need to speak
with Mr. Prady, please.
Thank you.
Please.
Yeah.
I'm really sorry that it took me
so long to get back to you.
I've been a little busy.
I know. They briefed me
on what happened.
It's a terrible thing.
Yes.
And I have some bad news
because of it.
The surveillance video
that you wanted
has been erased
by the EMP.
Erased?
Yes.
Everything in the building
has been fried.
Well, that's a damn shame.
So what you're telling me is
whoever helped Kevin Wade
rob that evidence locker--
they just caught a huge break.
I'm afraid so.
Are you sure that it was
all erased, Ms. Walsh?
I mean, don't you have
a backup system?
Yes, yes, we do,
but it's on-site.
And like I told you, all the
servers have been wiped clean.
I know how much
Kevin means to you.
I really wish
I could do more.
So you're sure that there's
nothing else you can tell me?
Anything that would
help me find Kevin?
Believe me, I have told you
everything that I know.
I'm sure you have.
Mr. Prady, I really have
to get back to work.
Good luck
finding Kevin.
I hope that he's okay.
Me, too.
If anything changes
with those files,
I'll be in Little Rock.
You have my number.
Of course.
I hope you get your lights
back on.
Mr. Haynam, I think
I found a way to deal
with the safety concerns
you had with my idea.
Here's the workaround.
I thought I made myselear.
We're not going anywhere
near that trunk line.
I'm going to ask you
one last time.
We really need
to do this my way.
We have agents in the field
who are close to finding
the nuclear rods
and they need our help.
And I'm going to ask you
one last time.
Get out of here.
Get out or I'll
call security!
You get out.
Now.
What the hell...
All of you, get out now.
Look, look,
take a second to think.
Do you really want to do this?
Mr. Haynam,
I don't want to hurt you.
You're probably
an okay guy
when you're not at work.
And you're wearing
a wedding ring.
I swear to God,
if you don't leave right now,
I will shoot you.
Get out!
Go!
Go get Hastings and tell him
to bring security.
They're starting to flank us!
We're almost there!
Jack, they're almost on us.
We cannot stay here!
Just give me one more second.
Okay...
Okay, I'm ready.
We're gonna use these plates
to form a way
so that we can make it
over to the call box.
Remember, we need to move
slow and steady.
It is imperative that we
stick together for this to work.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
No matter how difficult
it gets out there,
this armor is gonna protect us.
You need to trust that.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Okay.
Cole, you're with Agent King.
Owen, you're with me.
Let's go!
The armor's not gonna hold up.
Yes, it is.
Maintain formation.
Can you get a shot?
Not from this angle.
It's not holding up.
We gotta go for it.
Yes, it is. Slow down!
We're almost there. Move!
No!
No, no!
(King groaning)
There's nothing
we can do for him now.
We can't just leave him there.
I'm with Owen.
We don't leave our men behind.
You try and bring him in
now, you're dead.
They're trying to draw us out.
Best thing
we can do for him
is make it to the hard line
and try and call for help.
We're almost there.
You cover the north,
Owen the east.
I can get there.
Owen!
Cover him!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't leave him behind.
You did great.
Is he all right?
Did he make it?
Did he make it?!
Yeah, he made it.
Come on. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Jack, they're repositioning.
Stay on them.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes, Mother, I'm okay.
I'm so sorry, Father.
(sobbing):
I'm so sorry.
You were right
about Tarin.
I should have listened to you.
You are safe.
That's what's important.
Mr. President,
CTU is preparing a subterranean
evacuation route.
If there is
a radiological attack,
you'll be shielded
underground.
When do we leave?
As soon as possible.
President Taylor's waiting for
you with the other delegates.
The files Mr. Hastings
requested are inside.
Thank you, sir.
Kayla, go with them.
She's strong.
She'll be all right.
We almost lost her.
And I... almost lost you.
All for a peace agreement that
could fall apart at any moment.
And it will only get
more difficult, Dalia.
My enemies will be waiting
for me once we return home.
Omar...
Despite everything
that's happened,
there's one thing
I've never doubted.
That what you are doing here
is an absolute good.
You have to be strong, too.
We need to get in there fast
before O'Brian
can do any more damage.
I understand the situation,
Mr. Haynam.
How long?
I just need to drill
into the locking mechanism.
It shouldn't take more
than a couple minutes.
This woman is out of her mind.
Where the hell do you find
these people, Hastings?
I can't believe she
pulled a weapon on me.
She was ready to use it, too.
I seriously doubt that.
I'm sure she was
just trying to scare you.
Yeah? Well, she did
a very good job.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yes, O'Brian's going off
the deep end.
She thinks she knows how to
get the CTU up and running.
But she's locked herself
in the server room to do it.
We'll be in there
in a few seconds.
What's she trying to do?
She's trying to tap directly
into the trunk line,
which I don't have to tell you,
is a catastrophe
waiting to happen,
Stop what you're doing, Chloe!
Let's see the gun.
Okay, don't shoot or anything.
I know what I did is crazy.
I know I'm in a lot of trouble.
You're damned right.
I wouldn't have done it
if I didn't think it could work.
I'm almost done.
I just need ten more minutes.
Get her out of here now.
Do me a favor:
let me give the orders.
She pulled a gun on me!
I know what she did.
Now just shut up
and let me handle it.
Chloe, what in the hell
were you thinking?
Jack's looking for those nuclear
rods and he might need our help.
I can get satellite
and comm back up.
I just need to finish tapping
into that trunk line.
I told Mr. Haynam,
but he wouldn't listen.
So I pulled a gun on him.
I didn't want to.
I don't even like guns.
Dana, what's your
take on this?
Mr. Haynam is right.
Tapping into the trunk
line is dangerous
and there's no guarantee
that it'll work.
What about Cole?
He could be in trouble.
Aren't you worried about him?
Yes, I am. That's why I can't
go along with your plan.
It's reckless.
I'm sorry, Chloe.
You've never been
my biggest fan.
Why start now?
Look, it's not as dangerous
as they're saying.
I've taken precautions.
This can work.
I just need ten minutes.
If I can't get the systems
online by then, fine, arrest me.
When you brought me
on for this job,
you said it was because
I didn't think like anyone else.
Ever since I got here,
I've been punished for that.
I've been right
more than once today.
I think I've proven myself
and I think I deserve
that ten minutes.
Ten minutes.
Thank you, sir.
You can't be serious about this.
You need any help?
No, just let me work.
All right, let's give
the lady some space.
That's all, gentlemen.
You are making a huge mistake.
Maybe, but I'm willing
to take that chance.
O'Brian proved
herself today.
I want to see what
she comes up with.
I'd appreciate it if you
and your men would stand by.
Yes?
What is it? Sir, there's a man
here who wants to speak
with you-- Bill Prady.
He says
he's a probation officer.
Probation officer?
From Arkansas, sir.
What does he want?
He didn't say.
Put him in Holding 2.
Tell him I'll be there
in 15 minutes.
All right.
Dana, stay here
in case O'Brian
needs anything.
I'll be in my office.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Hastings, are you there?
We're here, Chloe.
What's your status?
I'm into the
trunk line.
I'm about to activate
the bypass circuit.
Okay, what can we expect?
Well, if I don't
electrocute myself,
some of our primary systems
should start booting up.
All right,
whenever you're ready.
We've got power to comm.
And one of the sat links
is back online.
All right, that's good enough.
Start looking for Bauer.
Okay, Chloe, it's working.
You all right?
I just need a few more minutes.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Mr. Hastings, one more thing.
If you do locate Jack,
you need to call Renee Walker.
Walker?
She went out looking for him.
She should be in the vicinity.
Will do.
Why don't you go see
if Miss O'Brian needs a hand?
And be civil this time.
Come on, Owen.
Stay with me.
He's gone.
I lost two
of the snipers.
If we're gonna make a move,
we got to do it soon, Jack.
We can't lay down cover fire
for something we can't see.
We need to give them something
to shoot at.
I'll make a break
to the north,
try and draw their fire,
you make a run for the call box.
But that's a suicide play, Jack.
You'll never make it.
But you will.
No.
I can't let you do that.
I'm in command here.
That's what gonna happen.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
I need you to do me a favor.
What is it?
You make sure
that Hastings keeps his promise.
That he doesn't
bring Renee back in.
I give you my word.
You're not gonna have long
before they start firing on you.
Good luck, Jack.
You make it to that call box.
Clear!
Jack? Jack?!
Jack?
(gasps)
It's okay.
It's okay. It's me.
It's Renee.
It's okay.
(groans)
Shh.
(panting)
They got the fuel rods
in a boat.
They're heading
across the river into the city.
I can't breathe.
Shh.
It's okay.
Nothing went through.
Relax. You may have
a collapsed lung...
Jack, I got through to CTU.
They just got back online.
NYPD's sending choppers.
We still got a real good shot
at finding them.
Mr. Hastings, I just got
a call from Agent Ortiz.
The nuclear rods
are on a Zodiac
with two
of the terrorists aboard.
They were heading northwest
across the river toward the city.
Where are the choppers?
One second.
They just arrived at the port.
Okay, redirect them.
Start diverting
all available
NYPD units to that shoreline.
We need to lay down a cordon.
Yes, sir.
Chloe?
Thanks. You-You were...
I'm not good with praise.
What do you think you're doing,
going to my boss?
My job.
I've answered
all your questions.
Why won't you just leave?
I can't do that.
I know you were involved with
that robbery,
Ms. Walsh.
What?
I think you know
exactly where Kevin is.
I think you're protecting him.
You are out of your mind.
And you're a liar.
I'm not leaving here
until I know the truth.
This'll go a lot
smoother for you
if you just come clean
right now.
It's not too late,
Miss Walsh.
But I promise you, if you don't,
I'm gonna nail your ass
to the wall.
Contact CTU.
See if they picked 'em up
going across the river.
It's me.
CTU's back online.
I know. There are helicopters
searching the river.
They're getting close.
You should have
warned us earlier.
I didn't have time.
I was too busy
preserving my cover.
I don't know how much longer
I'll be able to stay under.
I thought
you took care of that problem.
So did I.
It came back.
Well, we can't stay here.
The police must already
be cordoning off the area.
We're going to need your help
getting clear.
I will get you
out of there.
Don't worry.
Stand by.
I'll call you in a few minutes.
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net