Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Listen, I've been thinking
a lot about what we talked about.
I want to move back to Los Angeles with you.
Really?
Yeah.
You're coming with us tonight?
If it's okay.
Dad, I don't know what to say.
I'm so happy!
Victor, what are you doing here?
How the hell did you find me?
I have information. I'm out.
I don't work for the government anymore.
Well, this you're gonna want to hear.
There's a big hit going down.
President Hassan at the UN,
he's getting taken out.
When? Today,
before he can sign this thing with Taylor.
My country agrees to abandon
the pursuit of nuclear weapons.
But our terms, Mr. President,
were that the inspectors themselves
would be American, not IAEA.
This is the message that you
send to the rest of the world,
and then you wonder why we
don't want to negotiate!
Farhad.
Please excuse my brother's passion.
We need to resolve this issue
before we can move forward.
Find a way to give him what he wants.
This man is a once-in-a-lifetime leader.
I'm, uh, stuck outside.
I'll take care of it.
This woman poses no threat
to me or the peace process.
But you are married.
I've done nothing reckless.
Just reinstate Ms. Reed's clearance now.
Unless you want to destroy
everything that he's worked for,
stay away from him.
The brother revoked my clearance,
but I had Hassan reinstate it.
I know I'm behind schedule,
but it'll get done.
Excuse me, Mr. Hastings.
Jack Bauer's on line three.
He needs to talk to you.
Bauer?
I'm with an informant
that I used to run
who's claiming he's got intel
on an assassination attempt
on President Hassan.
And what does Mr. Aruz want
in return for his information?
CTU protection and immunity.
I'll send a chopper to pick you up.
Don't stop for anything! Keep going!
(gasps)
You need to get him out of here!
He's losing a lot of blood!
Hastings wants to debrief you back at CTU.
I'm not going back to CTU.
I delivered him, I'm done.
No, Mr. Bauer...
I got a flight to catch.
That's it?
Get down!
Tell me what you know.
The hitter has someone on the inside...
close to Hassan.
(siren wailing)
It's done. Aruz is no longer a problem.
But we don't know how much he told CTU.
We need to accelerate the hit.
(phone rings)
Sir, Agent Ortiz is calling in.
HASTINGS: Put him through.
I want everyone on this.
Comm channel 235. All right, go ahead.
This is Cole. Where are those EMTs?
They should be there any second.
How's the rest of your team?
Earley's injured.
Torres and Johnson are dead.
What happened? Look, those drones
are supposed to have antiballistics.
Why didn't they take out the missile?
We're still running the diagnostic.
Sir, this should've never happened!
We should've had another team
checking those buildings!
We can discuss this at a later time,
Agent Ortiz.
Yes, sir.
Bauer wants to talk with you.
Put him on the phone.
Stand by.
Jack, I have Mr. Hastings on the line.
Mr. Hastings?
Victor Aruz told me right before
he died that the assassin is
working with someone very
close to President Hassan.
Did you get a name?
No, not before he died.
You believe him? Normally,
I wouldn't trust him
as far as I could throw him.
He was dying, sir.
He had no reason to lie.
All right. We're on it.
I need you and Cole back here to debrief.
Mr. Hastings, I already gave one
of your agents my statement.
I need you back here.
Yeah... Mr. Bauer?
Fine. We're on our way.
Mr. Hastings.
Yes?
I may have a lead on that insider.
What do you mean? I just picked up
an unauthorized access in
one of the secure databases
at the UN.
How do you know it's unauthorized?
Because they bypassed the main access page
and went through a back-end server.
The only reason to do that
is if you're trying to cover your tracks.
Stay on it. Let me know
if you trace the source.
And put O'Brian on this, too,
if you don't think she'll slow you down.
No. She's doing much better, sir.
I'm gonna call Taylor's chief of staff.
They need to know this insider
could be moving against Hassan.
Mr. President, you are under a
great deal of pressure at home
from an active opposition
to this peace agreement.
They believe that by dismantling
your nuclear weapons programs,
you're surrendering to the West.
How do you respond to those charges?
The only thing we are surrendering is
the cloud of antagonism and mistrust
under which we have lived for far too long.
This is a victory for my people.
It marks an end to isolation and
will bring economic stability
to my country for the first
time in decades. (phone buzzes)
(reporters clamoring)
How do you propose economic stability
when your people are so divided?
This is Weiss. Did you bring in Victor Aruz?
I'm afraid not, sir.
There was an ambush,
and Aruz was killed,
along with two of our men.
Damn it.
Before Aruz died, he shared
some very troubling information.
Now, he claimed that someone close
to President Hassan has been
conspiring with the assassin.
Now, we don't have a name yet,
but we are pursuing a lead.
Tell me how, and I'd better be impressed.
We're tracing what might
be an unauthorized entry
into one of the UN servers.
And you think this is the
person we're looking for?
Well, we're optimistic.
Yeah, you better hope that optimism
translates into results.
Sir, until we locate the insider,
you might want to consider
locking down President Hassan
and postponing this conference.
That is not an option, Mr. Hastings.
We are close to signing one
of the most important treaties
in the history of this country.
You were put in charge
of CTU because you said
you could get the job done.
"Lean, mean and fast," that's what you said.
President Taylor expects you
to deliver on those words.
Yes, sir.
I'll take this to the president.
Keep me posted.
TAYLOR: President Hassan and I still
have a great deal of work to do,
so we're gonna wrap this up,
but I would like to say that
the president and I chose
the United Nations as the
venue for these talks
because the problems facing
the Middle East have become
a world concern.
And President Hassan and I are confident
that this agreement will lay the foundation
for a lasting peace in the region.
And we thank you for your time. Thank you.
(reporters clamoring)
TAYLOR: Mr. President,
I'll see you after the break.
I look forward to resuming it.
Thank you.
Madam President, I just spoke with CTU.
There's been a development
regarding the threat to Hassan.
We need to speak in private.
That is really wonderful.
Thank you. I'll join you later.
Hello.
You were terrific.
(chuckles) It's not about me,
it's the message that's important.
I just hope no one could
see how nervous I was.
(chuckles) Well, you hid it well.
Are you here?
Yes, on my way up.
Do you still have time to see me?
I've been looking forward to it all day.
When?
What did you say?
When can I see you?
I've got half an hour before
the next session begins.
You meet me now, and we'll go up
to my private office together.
I'll tell my staff that
you requested an interview
Perfect. I'll be right there.
I just ran a systems check on the drone.
Sensors did pick up the missile,
but the drone didn't fire.
Why not?
I won't know until I have
a chance to take it apart.
Mr. Hastings,
I don't want to sound like
I'm covering my own ass.
but I did tell you that
the antimissile system
had not been tested in an urban environment.
I know what you said, Arlo.
You just find out what went
wrong and you get back to me.
Mr. Hastings, I was right.
Someone hacked into the UN database.
They downloaded security protocols,
the schematics to the UN and
Hassan's personal itinerary.
I was able to trace an IP address.
Did you get a name?
Chloe's into the computer's registry.
She should have it by now.
Almost there. Come on, Chloe.
Saying that isn't gonna
make it happen any faster.
There, the computer's owner is listed
as Meredith Michelle Reed.
She's a reporter working for
the New York Courier.
She's doing a profile on Hassan.
Applied for a security clearance at the UN.
Did she get it?
My God... What?
She's there now.
UN Security logged her in 15 minutes ago.
She's at the press conference.
Put me through to UN Security.
(device beeps)
You're clear. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Okay, go ahead.
This is Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
We have a possible o
n-site threat to President Hassan.
Do you have an ID?
Her name is Meredith Reed.
She has a press security clearance.
We're sending a photograph to your PDA.
We just got a call about a
threat to President Hassan.
The UN gave us access to
their surveillance feed.
Facial recognition software
is sweeping the area now.
Got a match.
Northeast corner, moving toward Hassan.
Located the suspect.
She's ten yards from Hassan,
east side of the press section.
Green top,
black skirt, black jacket!
There she is. Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Everybody, move back!
Move back! What are you doing?
(clamoring) I'm a reporter.
I have clearance.
Move back!
HASSAN: Meredith?
I'm a journalist! I'm a journalist.
I have credentials.
We got a call from CTU about
a threat to your life.
Keep moving, keep moving.
(clamoring)
Mr. President...
Come on!
You're making a mistake.
The suspect's name is Meredith Reed.
She's a journalist profiling Hassan.
Now, our operating theory is
that she's been using her access
to gain security intel,
which she's been feeding to the assassin.
Ms. Reed is being transported
back here right now.
My hope is that she will give
us the name of the assassin
so that we can put an end to this threat.
Refer to your digital briefing
packets for specifics.
Mr. Hastings, I just received a
preliminary report from the team
sweeping Ms. Reed's apartment.
And?
They recovered the files
stolen from the UN database off her laptop.
It looks like we found our insider.
They also found a large file
that couldn't be opened.
It's been encrypted with
intelligence grade software.
HASTINGS: I want you to find out
what's inside that file.
It's on its way over as we speak. Good.
Excuse me, does anyone think this happened
a little too fast and a little too easily?
You know, Chloe, things do
happen a little faster in here
than what you're used to.
I know, you keep reminding me.
I might not be up to speed
on all your software,
but I know if someone
doesn't want to be found,
they don't leave behind code fragments
that could lead to an I.P.
address. Unless, of course,
they were in a hurry and
they had to improvise.
Maybe, but then why would you
go through all that trouble
and leave a huge red flag
for everyone to find?
What is your point?
It's like someone wanted us to find her.
I just think we should continue
to vet this until we're sure
that we have the right person.
We are vetting this from every angle.
I appreciate your concerns.
We'll keep them in mind.
In other words, "Shut up, Chloe."
That's not what he said.
Well, that's what I heard.
All right, you made your point.
Chloe, thanks.
All right, one last thing.
Ms. Reed has spent a lot of time
on assignment in the Middle East.
I want to cross-check all of her movements
with those of known terrorist groups.
Let's get moving.
Chloe.
Jack Bauer should be here any second.
I want you to handle his debrief.
You're taking me off the floor?
I think you'll be better
utilized debriefing Mr. Bauer.
Go set up.
Thank you, sir.
(tires squealing)
I'm walking in now.
Give me the home phone numbers
for Torres and Johnson.
Nobody speaks to their wives before me.
Cole, before you make your report,
I want you to keep someing in md.
What's that?
I know you asked for
more boots on the ground,
but what happened happened.
There's nothing we can do about that.
You put your opinion on record,
it's going to flag an
internal review from division.
It's only going to hurt us moving forward.
We're clear.
Mr. Bauer, Brian Hastings.
Sorry about the loss of your men.
Thank you. You'll be glad
to know the lead you got
from Victor Aruz panned out.
You telling me that you've
already found the insider?
Her name's Meredith Reed. She's a
journalist who was covering the peace
conference.
She was stealing files off the UN servers.
Now, we wouldn't have gotten
this far without your help.
Thank you.
Now, Chloe O'Brian's waiting to debrief you.
Shouldn't take long.
I just need to make a phone call first.
Excuse me.
(phone dialing)
We need to be on the same page here.
I think you can understand that.
Sir, you're asking me to lie on the record.
I'm asking you to exercise some discretion.
There's an assassin out there.
We don't need people secon
d-guessing how we do things.
Well, maybe you'd like to debrief for me.
(phone line ringing)
(phone ringing) All right,
let's get you in here.
Hello.
Hey, sweetheart, it's me.
Hey, where are you?
CTU.
CTU? Does this have anythingo do
with what's going on at the UN?
Yes, but I promise I won't be long.
I just need to give them a statement.
But I'm going to have
to meet you at the airport.
Dad, what's going on?
It's complicated.
I'll explain when I see you.
Okay, but we're coming there to pick you up.
Sweetheart, you don't need to do that.
I want to. It's on the way.
Okay, I'll have Chloe
get you a security pass.
I'll see you soon. Bye.
Who was that?
My father.
Everything all right?
I'm not sure.
HASTINGS: Everyone said you were too young,
and inexperienced to head up field ops,
but I believed you could do the job.
Now I need you to show the same
faith in me that I showed in you.
Keep our little dispute off the record.
Where's Chloe?
She's upstairs. First room to the right.
Thank you.
Think about what I said.
Hey.
Hey, Jack.
Sorry, but we got to do this kind of quick.
I guess you heard about the
reporter they arrested.
Yeah. Well, I think we might
have the wrong person.
Meredith Reed could be innocent.
Hastings said they found
evidence on her computer.
I know, but I think those
files may have been planted.
Look, I've been scanning
through the trafc cam footage
from outside Meredith
Reed's apartment building.
Five minutes before the intrusion
to the UN server, this man was going
into the service entrance of the building.
Ten minutes later, he left.
What if he went into her
apartment and used her laptop
to break into the servers?
Sounds a little thin.
Don't you think we found her kind of fast,
and that it was a little too easy?
Why are you showing me this?
Why don't you just take it to Hastings?
Hastings doesn't think
I know what I'm doing.
He won't listen to me.
He might listen to you.
Chloe, I'm here for my debrief.
Kim's on her way.
I'm leaving on a plane to Los Angeles
with my family in an hour.
I'm just asking you to talk to him.
It'll take ten minutes.
If the assassin framed Reed
to create a diversio
that means we have the
wrong person in custody.
That he still has someone
inside Hassan's delegation.
I'm sorry, Chloe, it's not my problem.
Please, let's just
continue with the debrief.
NEWSCASTER: Nor will they
confirm any fatalities.
There is no evidence at this
time to support the theory
that the two incidents are related.
We're still waiting for
an official statement
as to why this reporter was arrested.
At this time we can confirm that
her name is Meredith Reed...
I'm so gd you're all right.
I can't believe this happened.
...has yet to comment. In other news...
It's hard to believe, Kayla.
I just don't understand how
this woman got so close to you.
She's a journalist.
She had security clearance.
Do all reporters get these clearances?
No, but she's writing an article on me.
You know that, Dalia.
She was given special access.
You gave her that access?
Yes, I did. I did it.
This article was important for me.
I wanted to get my message
across to the American public.
That's the only reason?
Yes, that's the only reason!
What other reason?
If you have something to say, then say it.
You should never have
let her into our lives.
You put us all in danger.
(knock at door) Please, stop.
Excuse me.
I just spoke to the UN press director.
We're going to make a public statement.
Make sure I see it first.
Omar, may I speak with you alone?
Excuse us.
They've taken Meredith Reed to CTU.
I can't believe she's part of this.
What reason could she have
to help someone kill me?
What reason does any American
have to do anything? Money.
They found incriminating
files on her computer, Omar.
Whether you want to believe
it or not, she is guilty.
And she's going to talk.
I need to know what she's going to tell them
about your relationship.
Be honest with me.
Tell me everything.
It started three months ago in B'Dar.
We met for an interview in her hotel room.
Dalia and I had been fighting that day.
She used you, Omar.
She almost cost you your life.
And if this affair becomes public,
it will destroy your credibility
and everything that you've worked for.
I don't need you to tell
me the consequences.
If she talks to the Americans,
you must deny it.
It never happened.
Look, Omar, I know you're thinking
you must do the honorable
thing and confess the truth.
That would be a terrible mistake.
I need to be with my family.
DAVROS: Yes?
I just spoke with my brother.
I told him to deny the affair.
What did he say?
He's going to consider it.
Press him harder.
The reporter's claims
need to be discredited.
CTU needs to continue to think
she's my contact on the inside.
I understand.
We only need another hour.
I'll be ready to move by then.
Arlo. Hey.
I need your help decrypting that file
they found on Reed's computer.
I broke off a section.
It should be on your screen.
What filter do you want
me to run it through?
Esquire Nine.
No problem.
And, Arlo--
you can stop staring at my breasts now.
So when are you going
to drop Captain America
and find yourself a real man?
I'm still thinking about it.
Well, don't take too long.
I might lose interest.
(phone ringing)
Let me know what you find.
Dana Walsh.
Hello?
I like that.
You picked a good name for yourself.
That's actually better than the
one your mama picked for you.
Whoever this is,
I told you to stop calling me.
Yeah, I know what you told me, Jenny.
My name is not Jenny.
You must be mistaking me for someone else.
Oh, am I?
Yes.
That's funny.
'Cause you sound a lot like this girl
I used to know from Rock
Springs named Jenny Scott.
She was a wild thing, man.
We used to do some crazy stuff.
The next time you call me,
I promise you I will contact the police.
Yeah? You know, I got a better idea.
Let's contact them right now.
I'm hanging up now.
Hey, don't hang up this phone.
I'm warning you, Jenny,
do not...
Hey.
Whoa.
I was just going to look for you.
I'm so glad that you're okay.
I'm sorry that I have
been so distant lately.
It's just...
I don't ever want to lose you.
Don't worry.
Why am I here? This is a mistake.
Damn it. Who's in charge here?
Tell Mr. Weiss there's nothing yet.
But I'll call him as soon
as we have news. Thanks.
Brian Hastings, director of CTU.
Look, I don't know who the
hell you people think you are.
But I want an attorney, and I demand to know
what I'm being charged with.
We found the files, Ms. Reed.
What files?
On your computer. In your apartment.
You searched my apartment?
We found six documents
on your laptop that were
stolen from the UN servers.
What documents?
Relating to the security arrangements
for the peace conference.
You're here because we know
that you're part of a plan to
assassinate President Hassan.
What? What?
Please don't waste my time.
The evidence against you is clear-cut.
No, no, no. Listen to me.
You're making a mistake.
If there are files
on my computer, then someone put them there.
HASTINGS: Now you listen to me.
I'm giving you a chance to help yourself
by telling us what you know.
I need the name of the assassin,
how to find them.
And we talk about you
avoiding the death penalty.
You're wrong.
You've got the wrong person.
Take her to interrogation.
Full biometric package.
I'll be there shortly.
MAN: This way, ma'am.
Mr. Hastings?
You're done with your debrief?
Yeah. Can I talk to you?
Not a good time, Mr. Bauer.
Meredith Reed might be
telling you the truth.
Is this coming from O'Brian?
I told her to drop this.
Yeah, well, she didn't.
She found this. They were
taken from traffic cams
near Ms. Reed's apartment.
Check out the time stamps.
It shows this man entering the
building through the service entrance
almost five minutes before the
intrusion into the UN servers.
It shows him leaving the building
almost immediately after. So?
Chloe talked to the building manager.
There was no scheduled maintenance today,
no packages delivered.
And this is your evidence?
I'm looking at an apartment building,
where dozens of people live,
coming and going all day long.
Look, I understand. All I'm saying is that
it is possible that someone
broke into the apartment
and used her computer
to steal the documents.
All you need to do is send a
couple agents to check it out.
I'm sorry, I just don't see it.
And I can't waste valuable resources
because Chloe O'Brian has a theory.
Chloe and I have worked
together for a long time.
And trust me. She's someone
you might want to listen to.
She's very good at what she does.
And if she's right, the assassin's
got you looking in the wrong place,
and you will get bit.
Mr. Bauer, I have a suspect in hand
with a file she felt
damning enough to encrypt.
That's where I'm going
to focus my resources.
Now, if you will excuse me.
I hate this place.
He's not going to help, is he?
We have to follow this lead.
If they have the wrong person...
Chloe, I did what you asked.
I talked to Hastings.
If he doesn't want to listen,
that's his mistake.
But it's not my problem.
To be honest with you,
it's not yours, either.
What about the threat against Hassan?
What about the peace conference?
Doesn't any of that matter to you?
What if Hastings knows something you don't?
Look, I'm sorry.
Kim's waiting for me outside.
I've got to go.
Jack!
You've come to me for help many times,
and I've never let you down.
You've asked me to do crazy things,
and I've always taken your side.
Please help me.
I can't do this by myself.
I'm sorry.
I-I can't.
Not this time. Not me.
Hey.
Look what I made!
Let me see.
That's Daddy. That's Mommy.
And that's me and that's you.
See? That's you, Grandpa.
It's beautiful, sweetheart.
Dad, we need to talk.
Yeah. Here, honey.
Why don't you get Daddy to
put you in the car seat?
We're ready to go.
What's wrong?
I spoke to Chloe.
She told me what's happening.
Chloe called you?
No, I called her because
you wouldn't tell me
what was going on, so I decided
to find out for myself.
I know about the threat
to the peace conference,
that CTU might have the wrong suspect.
What's happening?
Chloe had me make her
case to the head of CTU.
He wasn't convinced,
and he thinks he's got the right person.
But if he's wrong,
then there's still someone inside the UN
who's working with this assassin?
That's what Chloe thinks.
What do you think?
I think it's not my problem.
Dad! What?
I don't believe you.
I've never known you to walk
away from something like this.
If you have to stay, it's all right.
You're not letting me down.
I understand.
Sweetheart, I want to go with you.
I know you do.
And there's nothing I want more
than for you to come with us.
I have been waiting so long for this day.
We both have.
But if something terrible happens,
and you could have done
something to stop it,
I don't think you'd be
able to live with yourself.
Dad, it's okay. You can go.
As soon as I'm finished here,
I will get on a plane and I will
be in Los Angeles, I promise.
Just be careful, please.
Come here.
I will.
I should tell Teri.
No, no. Let me do it.
Go ahead.
Go.
Okay.
Go on.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, but we should go.
Sweetie...
Grandpa has some work to do.
He can't fly with us.
But he'll come as soon as he can.
But he said he was coming today.
No, not today.
But soon, okay?
All right, let's go.
Jack...
We need to find out where your suspect went
after he left Miss Reed's apartment.
Start checking traffic cams.
Okay. I need to get a baseline
on her respiratory,
cardio and dermal response,
so make her comfortable.
Start off with a few softball questions.
Miss Reed, I think we need a fresh start.
Now, you claim those files
were planted on your computer.
Fine. I'm willing to give you
the benefit of the doubt,
but you need to meet me halfway. Talk to me.
Help me understand your side of the story.
Fair enough?
, when was the first time
you met President Hassan?
(clears throat)
About six months ago.
At a conference
of oil ministers.
I requested an interview, and he agreed.
We met in his hotel lobby twice.
Hour, hour and a half,
at the most.
(elevator bell dings)
Madam President.
Mr. President.
I want to thank you
for wanting to continue our negotiations.
I know it's a risk.
Madam President, you are no stranger
to making personal sacrifices
for your beliefs.
If the price for peace is my lif so be it.
Now, we are doing everything in our power
to make sure that that doesn't happen.
We've tightened security measures here,
and CTU's top priority
is to find the people who are targeting you.
I appreciate that.
Madam President,
the woman you took into custody...
The reporter. Meredith Reed.
Yes. Is CTU certain that
she is part of this plan?
Well, from what I understand,
the evidence against her
is quite incriminating.
Have they found out her reasons?
Well, Miss Reed is being
questioned as we speak.
I'll make sure whatever
information we get from her
will be shared with your
people as soon as possible.
Jack, I've searched through
all the traffic cams
within a five-block radius
of Meredith Reed's apartment.
There's no sign of where the suspect went.
Can you check other sources?
CTU has drones all over the city.
I could look through their archives
and see if they picked anything up.
Where are they?
The archives are in Arlo's station.
I don't have the clearance.
Can you hack in?
Yeah.
Do it.
I'm glad you're here. Thanks for staying.
Yeah.
This will all be over soon
and you can get to California.
Okay. I'm in.
One of the drones picked him
up leaving Reed's apartment.
Play it forward.
Well, he hailed a cab when he left.
JACK: Can you track the cab?
No. It's beyond the drone's search grid.
Okay, back it up.
Stop.
Move in closer.
ere, that's what I want to see.
Closer.
See the medallion?
Call t cab company, find out where it went.
I'm not tracking this guy without a weapon.
The Armory's on Level C.
I have to input your palm print
through the hand scanner.
Erase this as soon as I'm clear.
(beeping)
I'll call you as soon as I'm on e road.
(dialing phone)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Ruth, it's me. Jenny?
I need to talk to you, are you alone?
Uh, just my kid. What's going on?
Haven't heard from you since Christmas.
Kevin Wade found me.
He's been calling me at
work the last two days.
Damn it, Ruth, you told him how to find me?
No, I didn't!
You're the only one who knows the truth.
The only one who knows where I am.
I swear, I never talked to Kevin.
I didn't even know he was out of jail.
Then how did he find me?
I don't know!
Okay.
And what does he want,
anyway? Why is he calling you?
He didn't say.
But he's threatening to tell
everyone the truth about me.
It'll destroy my career.
I'm about to get married, Ruth.
To a really great guy.
Well, there's gotta be something you can do.
You can't let this son of a
bitch just ruin your life.
I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid I'm gonna lose everything.
I gotta go, I'll call you later.
Where you been?
I've been trying to find you.
Did you decrypt the file? No.
I'm still working on it.
I found something weird, though.
Someone hacked into my station
and it came from inside CTU.
What were they doing?
Scanning the drone archives.
Track it down, see who it was.
And when you were in B'Dar,
profiling President Hassan,
were you ever approached
by anyone who was hostile to his regime?
No. No one paid you?
No. Pressured you into cooperating?
I said no.
So all you did was interview
President Hassan, that's it?
Yes, that's all.
Her answer prompted a leve
l-five autonomic reaction.
You're lying, Ms. Reed.
I'm not. I...
Tell me what really happened in B'Dar!
How is it connected to
the assassination plot?
I don't have anything to do
with any plan to assassinate
President Hassan.
My God, why would I?
Your reasons are irrelevant.
All I care about is stopping the assassin.
So do I.
So if someone really is
trying to kill Hassan,
you need to stop wasting your
time on me and find them.
(doorbell ringing)
Hey, Mike, what's going on?
Maggie, I-I'm so sorry for dropping by
without calling first.
Mind if I come in?
Sure, come on. Thanks.
Did, uh, Jim leave for work yet?
No, just got or. Oh, good.
'Cause I need to ask him
something before he leaves.
Kind of a favor. Okay.
Hey, babe?
KOENIG: Yeah? Mike Farmer's here.
Says he needs to talk to you.
Mikey! Hey!
What are you doing here? You're not on shift
till tomorrow. Yeah, that's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
All right, I'll be right down.
All right, take your time.
Want coffee? Sure.
Come on. NEWSMAN:...
during President Taylor's
press conference earlier this afternoon.
NEWSWOMAN: I wouldn't want to speculate
at this time, Bob, but as you know,
President Taylor's peace
negotiations with IRK president
Omar Hassan are highly controversial...
Sit down. Thanks.
...and are causing much political
dissent both in... (sighs)
Did you hear anything
more about what happened
at that press conference?
No, only what they're saying on TV.
I gotta tell you,
I'm so proud of you and Jim
and all those boys down at the precinct.
I mean, you're gonna be part of history.
Nah, I don't know.
We're just directing traffic, really.
You're on the UN security detail.
That's more than directing traffic.
Ahh... Hell, you might even get on TV.
Wow, yeah, wouldn't that
be something.
Yeah, it would!
Right.
(both chuckling)
(monitors beeping)
I need to speak with Mr. Hastings.
Uh, we're in session. It's important.
Excuse me, Mr. Hastings,
I have Dana Walsh out here.
She says it's important.
You're not leaving this room
until you tell me the truth.
No matter how long it takes.
I'm sorry to bother you, sir,
but I didn't think that this could wait.
What's this about?
Jack Bauer.
Come on...
(beeping)
(lock clicks, buzzes)
(phone ringing)
Yeah?
I spoke with the dispatcher
at the cab company.
His driver logged the dro
p-off at West 23rd Street
at the northwest corner
of Broadway in Queens.
Anything more specific?
An apartment number, an address?
Not from the dispatcher,
but I'll keep sifting
through the aerial footage.
Okay, Broadway and West 23rd.
I'll call you when I get there.
Hands in the air! Now!
Against the wall!
Don't move.
He had this, sir.
We'll take it from here. AGENT: Stand down.
I told you to leave this alone.
Chloe tracked the man
in the surveillance photo
to a second location.
We didn't think you'd follow
through with an investigation.
So you had no choice except to
steal weapons from the armory.
Would you have followed through
with an investigation if I'd asked?
I'm not debating this anymore.
You shut down a lead before you could
even assess whether it was good or bad.
Take him to detention.
Take him!
COLE: Let's go.
I'm sure President Taylor's
gonna be very interested
to find out what happened to my informant
when I tried to deliver
him to you. Excuse me?
Cole tried to secure that
landing zone with more men,
but instead you sent a drone,
which failed to detect
the missile that killed
my informant and two of your men.
Cole hasn't said anything about it.
And neither will I,
as long as you let me pursue this.
So now you're blackmailing me?
You forced my hand, now I'm forcing yours.
You don't want to be doing this,
Bauer. No, I don't.
I wanna be on a plane to
Los Angeles with my family.
But you're not giving me another choice.
You want to waste your time chasing ghosts?
Knock yourself out.
I've got to stop an assassination plot.
Give him the bag.
I need Chloe to run Ops.
Fine, she's all yours.
Thank you.
Anything to what he's talking about?
The only viable lead is sitting
in our interrogation room.
And she's the only way we're
going to get to the assassin.
What's going on, Mikey?
Hey, listen, um, something came up.
I can't make my shift tomorrow.
So, I was wondering if we could swap.
Oh, I'd be happy to, except Maggie and me
have a meeting with Sean's teacher tomorrow.
She said he's
acting out in class, but I don't believe it.
Jim keeps making excuses for him,
but if he needs help,
I want to give it to him.
Where is he? He's at his grandma's tonight.
I'm not making excuses.
So, what are you saying?
You can't trade shifts with me?
This is kind of important, so I'm sorry.
(sighing): Yeah.
Me, too.
Whoa, Mikey, what...
Maggie, I want you to sit down.
Jim, there's a roll of tape
in my bag.
Tear off a strip and put
it over Maggie's mouth.
Do it.
(Maggie panting)
I'm sorry, baby. Oh, my God.
Now, pick up the phone,
call Captain Ravello.
Tell him you're sick
and I'm filling in for you.
Now, listen, you son of a bitch,
there's no way...
Oh! Oh, what's the matter
with you?! (sobbing)
What are you doing?!
Next time, I won't miss the bone.
(Maggie sobbing)
Make the call.
All right.
All right, I'll call.
Please, just leave my wife alone, all right?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net