Mr. Bauer, you are ordered
to turn the aircraft around
and return to CTU.
Jack's descending.
Air Force choppers
are in pursuit.
We've lost him.
If Jack gets this evidence
and exposes the Russians,
the agreement is over.
The peace agreement
may not be the only casualty.
You covered up
the Russians' involvement.
That's grounds for impeachment.
There's still a chance that CTU
will find Jack.
Even if they do,
the evidence is still out there.
Eventually, it will surface.
You need to control the evidence
by keeping Walsh off the grid.
Classify her
as an enemy combatant
and incarcerate her
in a private facility.
I've authorized
a private interrogation team
to acquire the evidence.
Once we have it,
she'll be irrelevant.
I can't be a part
of this any longer.
Cite my health as the reason
for my resignation.
The president's
ordered your transfer
to an off-site
facility.
What do you mean
off-site facility?
It's a secure location.
Just do what he says, Dana.
Chloe, don't let them do this.
- Let's go.
- Please.
They're gonna kill me. Chloe!
Chloe, please!
You told Bauer
you have evidence.
I have got nothing to tell you.
There is no evidence.
The sooner you tell me,
the easier it'll go.
No!
Mobilizing a sting operation
to be led by Agent Ortiz.
The target is Jack Bauer.
Put your weapons down!
I can't do that, Jack!
Put your weapons down now!
I need you to help me
gain access to Dana Walsh.
I am giving you an opportunity
to make this right,
to make the people
that are responsible
for everything that
happened today accountable.
Chloe said she's in a safe house
a few miles from here.
All right, now it's imperative
that they think I
took you hostage.
Get up!
And though fate has prevented
my husband from being here today
at the culmination
of his life's work,
I know that he is watching us
now, looking down and guiding us
as we take the last steps
towards this historic agreement.
Finally, I would like
to express my gratitude
to President Taylor...
Whose integrity
and moral courage
have been unshakable
during the long course
of these negotiations.
She is someone on whom my
husband built an absolute trust.
And I want to make it clear
that her efforts and the efforts
of the United States government
to rescue him
were nothing short of heroic.
My husband wasn't perfect.
None of us is.
But he carried a perfect idea
in his heart:
That peace is possible.
On this,
the last day of his life,
may the world come together
and prove that he was right.
What a magnificent woman.
Okay.
Who was that on the phone?
Bledsoe.
It's not the best of news, sir.
Dana Walsh isn't being as
cooperative as he'd hoped.
Well, what does he expect?
She's a trained enemy agent;
she's not gonna to break
at the drop of a hat.
Look, I told
President Taylor
what might be necessary,
and she signed off on it.
Bledsoe's a professional, sir.
I'm confident
he'll come through for us.
He better.
Sir, there was one more thing.
Bledsoe wanted confirmation.
About what?
How to deal with Ms. Walsh,
post interrogation.
I thought we settled
that matter.
We did.
So why's he asking?
Just to double check we're still
committed to the same outcome.
And what did you tell him?
We're still committed
to the same outcome.
Not that I have any idea
what you're talking about.
You understand?
Perfectly, sir.
Let her up.
I'll give you a little tip.
Take short, shallow breaths.
You'll recover faster.
And then we won't have so much
downtime between sessions.
It's up to you, you know.
You can stop this
whenever you want.
All you have to do is tell
me what I want to know.
I told you
that I was making it up.
There is no evidence.
You told Jack Bauer
you had proof that elements in
the Russian government
were behind
the assassination
of President Hassan.
I was bluffing.
Stalling for time.
There isn't any proof.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not lying.
We begin again in ten seconds.
Seven, six...
Bring it on, you son of a bitch.
Put her down.
Where's the evidence?
Go to hell.
Gag her.
* *
Okay.
They got two sentries
out in front in a black sedan,
one lookout on the roof,
most likely another across the
street, but I couldn't see him.
We can access the back of the
building through that alley.
So, once we get Dana,
what then?
As painful as it is,
we got to cut a deal
in exchange for the evidence.
You mean let her go.
Cole, we both
lost friends today.
And Dana had a hand in that,
but only a hand.
If we can get
the people in charge,
the people that gave the orders,
it'll be worth it.
It's Chloe.
Answer it.
Otherwise, she'll know
something's wrong.
If she doesn't already.
Hello.
Cole, what's your ETA?
Ten minutes.
FDR Drive was a mess.
We're coming up
First Ave instead.
Is Jack with you?
Yeah, I got him.
He's locked down in the back.
I'm glad we found him
before he got hurt.
Or worse.
Yeah.
I've known Jack for a long time,
and I've never
seen him like this.
He threatened me;
he's never done that before.
You did the right thing, Chloe.
Thanks for saying that.
I'll talk to you
when you get here.
Yeah.
We're good.
She has no idea.
Don't be too hard on her, Jack.
She was only doing
what she thought
was best for you.
I know.
Almost forgot.
You're gonna need these.
I'm sorry, I just couldn't
take the chance.
Son of a bitch.
Yeah, I know.
You ready?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Keep your head down.
Go.
That's right, four hours prior
to the signing ceremony,
all available field units
will be redeployed to the U.N.
Mobile HQ is being
set up on the first floor,
adjacent to the
high commissioner's offices.
Hold on a second;
I got O'Brian on the other line.
Yeah?
Who's the psych officer on duty?
That would be Melissa Anderson.
She did all the
grief counseling last night.
Make sure she's the first person
Jack sees when he gets here.
I want a complete eval.
You really think
that's necessary?
I wouldn't have
ordered it if I didn't.
I'll let her know.
I got a visual.
They got one man on the roof.
Okay.
Wait till I get into position,
then you draw them out.
All units, this is Command.
Please report.
Command, this is unit one.
All clear.
Unit two. Street's clear.
Unit three. Back alley's clear.
Command, this is unit four.
Roof's clear.
All units, copy that.
Stay alert.
We're clear.
Let's go.
* *
You make that cover.
I'll draw him out.
Command, I'm taking
sniper fire on the roof.
The building across the street.
I need backup now.
Unit four, stand by.
I'm sending backup now.
Copy that. Hurry!
All units to the roof.
Unit four is reporting
sniper fire.
Repeat: all units to the roof.
Unit four is under sniper fire.
Go.
Command, we're on the roof.
It's quiet; there's
no sign of Mullins.
Come again?
All's quiet, but we can locate
Unit four.
Unit four, come in, please.
Where's Dana Walsh?
Where is she?
Command, Mullins is down, sir.
Last chance.
Repeat: Mullins is down.
First room on the left.
Thank you.
Command, do you copy?
Command, come in.
We're clear.
The first room on the left,
I've got it.
Put your gun down now!
No, you drop your weapon
or I'll put a bullet
in her brain!
I don't want to kill you,
but I will if I have to.
Put your gun down!
You won't take the shot.
It's too risky.
I'll kill her before...
Cole, untie her.
Cole, now!
Take her out the back.
We're gonna get company soon.
Hurry!
Cole, have you got her?!
Almost!
I got her!
Move! Move!
Stay covered.
Cole, take the stairs now!
Jack!
Get going!
I'll be right behind you!
Chloe.
In a second.
Just finishing rescanning
the field reports.
You need to hear this, Chloe.
Agent Beck just checked in
from the laundry.
He said he's been locked down
for the past half hour,
and only just now managed
to free himself.
What? Apparently, Jack
didn't fall for the trap.
Instead, he reversed the entire
squad and took Cole hostage.
I just talked to Cole.
Beck says Jack had him
at gunpoint.
Devin, pull up the satellite
on the lower East Side.
Address:
14633 12th Street.
It's where the private
contractors are holding Dana.
It's where
Jack's on his way to now.
What is going on, Chloe?
He's been two steps ahead of me
the whole time.
He probably knew what I was
gonna do before I did.
Hello, everybody!
Can I have your attention,
please?
Jack Bauer's no longer in
custody of CTU.
Agent Cole Ortiz is with him,
most likely as a hostage.
Our priority is
to find them now.
Satellite's online,
Ms. O'Brian.
Put it up.
We're too late.
Put the APB back out on Jack,
all agencies.
Get me the White House.
Where are we going?
You tell me. You said
you had a video file
implicating people inside
the Russian government
who are responsible
for Renee's murder.
I want that file.
And I said I'd give it to you
in exchange for immunity.
That deal's off the table.
The president decided
the peace agreement's
more important than the truth.
As far as she's concerned,
that file can never see
the light of day.
But I still want it.
What's the new deal?
You give us the file,
we let you go.
Go where, Riker's Island?
Dana, you're a small fish
in all of this.
I'm going after the people
who gave the orders.
You give me the evidence,
we'll let you go.
I give you my word.
Your word?
I'm sorry.
I don't believe you, Jack.
Fine.
You think this is a joke?
We'll do it another way.
Get out. Get out!
Jack!
Jack, Cole!
Oh!
Tell me where that
file is-- now!
That file's the only thing
keeping me alive!
No, right now
I'm the only thing
keeping you alive.
I'm gonna count backwards from three,
and then I'm gonna kill you.
Three! You're really not
gonna let him shoot me
in cold blood, are you, Cole?
Two!
Jack!
Back off!
One!
In a safety-deposit box!
Where?
First Unity Savings.
Cole knows.
We have a joint account there.
But the box is in
my name, which means I'm
the only one who can access it.
Where's the bank?
Lexington, off East 59th.
I had nothing to do
with Renee's death, Jack.
I didn't even know
she was a target.
Put her in the car.
I was in a CTU holding cell!
Put her back in the car!
Damn it! You see what's
happening here, don't you?
He's using you.
Using me? You're using me.
What do you think he's gonna
do once I give him that file?
He's gonna give the evidence
to the press
and expose everyone responsible.
Is that what you think?
'Cause I doubt that's
what Jack thinks.
He's gonna assemble
the evidence,
make a list of the guilty,
and then he's gonna execute them
one by one, starting with me.
This isn't about the
truth, Cole.
It's about revenge!
Cole!
Look, I can't do this!
She's just trying
to get inside your head.
I know that, damn it!
You got something
you want to say to me,
you better say it now.
Were you gonna pull
that trigger?
I need her to think I would.
Yeah, okay.
Mrs. Hassan, please
allow me to offer my condolences
for your loss.
Your husband was a great man.
Thank you.
How has news of his death
been received
back in the Islamic Republic?
And do people there
generally support your decision
to take his place
as head of state?
I'm confident that most
of my country is behind me.
Those who aren't,
probably never supported
my husband's policies
in the first place.
And what are your plans
after the treaty is signed?
Right now, I'm concentrating
all my efforts on the pursuit
of finishing what
my husband started
with this agreement.
But I want to return
to Kamistan.
Is this true?
I'm afraid so, ma'am.
The details are sketchy,
but as of 15 minutes ago,
Jack Bauer stormed
the safe house,
overwhelmed security
and took Dana Walsh.
Do we have any idea
where they are?
A hard target search
is under way.
Your note also mentioned
Charles Logan.
Yes, ma'am. He's been calling
and demanding
to speak to you.
He insisted that I interrupt
the press conference.
All you'll have to do is
hit redial.
Thank you, Tim.
Excuse me.
Yes, ma'am.
...the body be ritually washed
and draped...
Hello?
How in God's name could
this have happened?!
Madam President, the important
thing is not to panic.
You assured me that Dana Walsh
would be more secure
in the hands
of your private contractors.
We didn't move her out of CTU
solely for security reasons,
as I'm sure you remember.
Do you have me on speaker,
Charles?
Pick up the damn phone.
Forgive me, I wasn't thinking.
Apparently, neither was I.
It's a little late
for buyer's remorse,
Madam President,
especially because I was
calling with a solution
to our current problem.
Bauer may have Walsh,
but he can't have
the evidence yet.
We've still got a chance
to stop him.
How?
By putting somebody inside CTU,
someone whose loyalties
aren't split,
who won't hesitate
to see the mission through
no matter what the cost.
I've already replaced
one director.
I can't replace another.
No, not a new director.
Just someone to supervise
the manhunt for Bauer.
I'm recommending Jason Pillar.
Your aide?
He's Bureau-trained,
Madam President.
He was second in command at DIA
during the Daniels'
Administration
and he made a name for
himself in Afghanistan,
chasing high-value
targets behind enemy lines.
Of course if you
have a better idea,
I'll gladly take a step back.
Madam President.
Just a second.
What is it, Susan?
Mrs. Hassan is finishing up.
I'm on my way.
Look, I'll tell Tim Woods
that I support you
making an operational change.
But that's it, Charles--
no more excuses.
Thank you, Madame President.
And allow me to say that...
No, I understand completely.
And I appreciate
your confidence in Jason.
How soon can you leave for CTU?
Immediately.
Good. I'll handle the
arrangements on this end.
Congratulations, Charles.
You have recast yourself
as the great peacemaker.
I appreciate your help in
getting me this far, Mikhail.
So tell me what I'm doing here?
I had hoped to have this
conversation in private.
This is my attaché
Pavel Tokarev.
You can speak freely.
He is more than well
acquainted with the situation.
Well...
There's been
an unforeseen problem.
Apparently I'm not the only one
who can prove that elements
in your government conspired
to undermine the peace process.
Meaning?
Dana Walsh,
the mole you installed
inside CTU,
claims to have evidence
to that effect.
Not possible.
She was handled
with complete deniability.
So you say.
But, no one in this room
can take the chance
that she's bluffing.
Now... I tried
to contain this.
I had Ms. Walsh detained
and interrogated.
The problem is, Jack Bauer
just broke her out.
Apparently, he has
a personal interest
in exposing this evidence.
Then you need to stop him.
Surely President Taylor is
motivated to do the same.
She is, to a point.
But I know Bauer.
And I can promise you he
will never let this go.
And I don't think
the president is
willing to do what is
ultimately required.
So you expect me
to kill Bauer for you?
We both know
you have the covert assets
here to do the job.
Maybe I do--
but I don't have the resources
to find him, track him.
CTU does.
And the man in charge of
the search now reports to me.
How would this work?
This is a closed-channel phone.
It's impossible to intercept.
My man at CTU will use
it to feed your people
real-time information
as to Bauer's whereabouts.
And they can put an end to this
problem, once and for all.
We have to assume that CTU's
been getting my face out there.
You're going to have to take
her into the bank on your own.
I'll stand sentry in the lobby.
How well do you know
the layout inside?
Vault's in the back.
Tellers are on one side
of the room,
loan officers are on the other.
One of them's an old buddy
of mine from high school.
He was helping us
line up a mortgage.
Okay, you keep her inside your
strike zone.
If she sees an opportunity,
she's going to take it.
You trust her for nothing,
you understand?
I'll be fine, Jack.
Okay, let's go.
I know you hate me right now,
but I don't really believe
you want to see me executed.
Save it.
We both saw how close he came to
pulling the trigger back there.
That's just what he
wanted you to think.
If that's what he
told you, he's lying.
Just like he's lying about what
he's going to do with that file.
Jack wants to bring the people
responsible for this to justice.
Just like me. Who do you think
these people are, Cole?
They're Russian diplomats
with full diplomatic immunity.
They'll be indicted by
the World Court
and hauled up in front
of the Hague.
You really believe Jack Bauer
wants to trust some toothless
international tribunal
to mete out justice to
the people who killed Renee?
Keep going.
You're hurting me.
You'll live.
Confirm all traffic camera feeds
are being ported through us.
Up-res and route everything
through facial recognition.
Parameter-matching on
Jack, Cole, or Dana.
We don't have anywhere near the
bandwidth to do that citywide.
Then job the overflow to NSA.
Where are we on setting up
the search grid with NYPD?
In process.
They're giving us all
the personnel they can spare,
But they're going
on record that,
unless we narrow down
the search area,
it's "needle in
a haystack" time.
O'Brian.
There's a Jason Pillar
on his way to see you.
Pillar?
Yeah.
Tim Wood's office
pre-cleared him.
Send him up.
He's already on his way.
He wouldn't wait.
Never heard of this guy.
Who is he?
He was second in command at DIA
under the Daniel's
administration.
He's been working
the private sector for years.
Ms. O'Brian, Jason Pillar.
This is my associate
Eden Linley.
Okay.
So why are you here?
Frankly, the
White House is unhappy
with the way the manhunt
for Jack Bauer's been handled.
President Taylor's issued
an executive order
placing me in charge
of the search from here on.
What?! You'll retain your
position as acting director
for the time being
with authority over all
over CTU operations.
Arlo, give us a minute?
You got it.
This doesn't make any sense.
Excuse me?
Why are you here?
You have nothing to do
with Homeland Security anymore.
Ms. O'Brian,
all you need to know
is that I'm here under
the president's orders.
Well, you're wasting your time.
We've done everything
possible to find Jack.
If that were true,
then the trap you set
for Bauer would have worked.
It's not that simple.
Instead, you were more concerned
with making sure
he didn't get hurt.
It's all in the hourlies.
In fact, the last
operational command
you sent to Agent Ortiz was,
"Remember, non-lethal force."
Not exactly the
appropriate sentiment
when the president told you how
important it was that Bauer be stopped.
The president doesn't want
Jack to be hurt.
She knows what he'd done for
this country-- and so do you.
What Bauer's doing will destroy
the peace agreement.
And the president
cannot let that happen.
It's time to take off
the kid gloves.
We need all protocols
and encryption keys
transferred to us immediately.
As well as system overrides
and administrative privileges.
Understood?
Ms. O'Brian?
Yeah, understood.
Re-code the all-agency
bulletin on Bauer
to "armed and dangerous"
level eight.
And change the use of force
guidelines to "unrestricted."
Here we go.
Just make yourselves
comfortable.
I'll be right back with
your safety deposit box.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Something funny?
This. You and me--
it's not the way
that it was supposed
to turn out.
I'm serious, Cole.
Now that this is all over,
you deserve to hear the truth.
It's a little late
for the truth.
If you're even capable of it.
You don't have to believe me.
I was a kid.
A kid with five years
of prison behind me
and no future to speak of.
A guy came to see me--
a Russian.
Said that he could
give me a fresh start.
I had absolutely no idea
what I was getting myself into.
You could have come clean
anytime you wanted.
And go back to jail.
Not a chance.
Look, I know that
it's not an excuse,
but ever since I met you
I have been trying
to dig myself out
of this mess that I'm in.
You're right--
I don't believe you.
It's why I made that video file,
Cole.
I was going to use it
as leverage
to get the Russians
to leave us alone.
Us?
Yes.
There is no "us," Dana.
There never was.
It was a lie from the beginning.
That is not true.
Just stop playing me.
It's not going to work.
I am not playing you.
I loved you.
Here we go-- 14-05.
I'll be outside.
Thank you, Brian.
No.
You never give up, do you?
You guys all right?
Hey, Cole...
911. What is your emergency?
Hi. I'm at First Unity
Savings Bank on Lexington.
There's a guy by the front door.
I-I think I saw
him on the news.
I think he has a gun.
Oh, my God.
He's looking in my direction.
Oh, God!
Great. As quickly
as you can.
The 911 comm center
just confirmed the call.
Bauer was supposedly
I.D.'d by someone
at the First Unity Savings
branch on Lexington.
Supposedly?
What do you mean supposedly?
It means all we have
is the caller's word
that she recognized Jack
from the news coverage.
We don't have
secondary confirmation.
Then get it for me.
Request access to
the bank's video
surveillance system.
I've already contacted them.
I'm just trying to connect.
Having trouble getting
the CTU comm protocols to work.
You, what's your name?
Devon Rosenthal.
Help her.
Don't look at O'Brian.
I'm giving you the order.
Just follow it.
All right,
let's see what's going on.
All right, this is the...
Oh, good.
Got it?
Here we go.
Full access to
the bank's
video surveillance system.
We got him.
Call NYPD and make sure they
realize the priority here.
And tell them I want to be
looped in their
operation in real time.
Got it.
Be right back.
Yes?
We found Bauer.
He's at a bank.
First Unity Savings
on Lexington.
How do you know?
A 911 call confirmed
by video surveillance.
Then the police are
already on their way.
Can't help that.
But once they have Bauer,
I'll find out
where they're holding him.
You'll have to take him out
while he's in custody.
I'll wait for your call.
Brown jacket, freeze!
Police!
Get your hands up!
Get your hands up now!
Hands up!
On your knees.
Get down on your knees.
Put your hands
behind your head.
Interlock your fingers,
thumbs out.
Do not move.
We got him.
Take it easy.
You got no chance.
We got units coming in.
Shut up!
You know who I am?
Do you know who I am?!
Yes.
I don't want
to kill your partner,
but I will if I have to.
So here's what we're gonna do:
Slowly, you're gonna
put your gun down.
Drop your weapon now!
Kick it over to me.
I'm sorry.
Call an ambulance.
Call an ambulance now.
Tell them
two police officers are down.
Don't you move!
Slowly... turn around
and head back to me.
Now!
What happened to Cole?
Did you kill him?
I could never do that.
Where's the evidence?
It's in my pocket.
Show me.
Jack, we can make a deal.
Show me!
I want you to slowly
put it down on the floor.
Jack...
Tell me what I can do.
Nothing.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net