The Russian people join you
in mourning President Hassan.
We both know the opposition
that undid him had outside help.
I just got off the phone with
the Russian foreign minister.
He said that he would be
coming to the United Nations
in five hours
with the Russian premier
to sign the treaty
as scheduled.
The credit for that
is all yours.
LOGAN:
It's good to be
back in the game.
Elements inside
the Russian government
were behind
both the assassination
of President Hassan
and the supply of
nuclear material to his enemies.
TAYLOR:
The Russian government?
The Russians inserted
Dana Walsh
at CTU months ago.
She's their agent.
If Bauer gets to her,
this will all be finished.
I want to know who
killed Renee Walker.
WALSH:
Renee's dead? I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
(panting)
I can give you the hitter.
I want more than just names;
I want proof!
I have proof.
An audio file. Film.
Where?
First I want
my immunity deal back.
I'm sorry.
I won't give
Dana Walsh immunity.
I believe she knows the names
of the people who facilitated
the assassination
of President Hassan,
people working within
the Russian government.
TAYLOR:
I won't allow it.
You don't want
to know the truth.
What I want is to keep
the Russians at the table.
Allegations of this sort
will drive them away.
I've arranged a helicopter
to fly you from CTU
to McGuire Air Force Base.
You're locking me down.
I'm taking this helicopter.
Tell your men to drop their
weapons or you're gonna die.
(dropping weapons)
Out of the copter now!
All security to the helipad.
Security to the helipad now.
Call the FAA, Air Force,
say that we have
a stolen helicopter
that needs to be intercepted
and forced down.
WINNICK:
Yes, ma'am.
CHLOE (over comm):
Jack, it's Chloe.
What are you doing?
Talk to me.
Jack, talk to me.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, he can hear you.
Comm's on,
he's just not answering.
Damn it.
Air Force choppers are
closing in on his position.
PILOT:
Mr. Bauer, you are ordered
to turn the aircraft around
and return to CTU.
I repeat,
turn the aircraft around now.
Jack's descending.
Air Force choppers
are in pursuit.
CHLOE:
Jack, this is crazy.
Come back to CTU.
NYPD, this is Ranger One.
Suspect just landed
on the Cooper Building.
We're gonna circle
and maintain visual contact.
DISPATCHER:
Copy that.
We're cordoning off a two-block
radius around the building.
We have a
visual on NYPD.
Two units approaching
the building.
They're one block out.
(sirens wailing)
Suspect's on the fire escape.
He's descending
to ground level.
(sirens wailing)
We've lost him.
Attempting to reacquire.
Dispatch, this is unit 27.
We're at the building,
but we've lost the suspect.
DISPATCHER:
Copy. We'll widen the perimeter.
What the hell is Jack doing?
He's not letting this go,
that's what he's doing.
Dana told him she has
proof about the Russians.
He'll probably
come after her.
That's crazy.
She's locked down.
Jack knows he can't
get to her.
He'll either figure it
out or he'll die trying.
I want you in the field.
Meet with NYPD and coordinate
an interagency search.
Bring in whoever you need.
Yep.
Arlo, use satellite
and traffic cam.
Maybe we can
track him from here.
On it.
(sighs)
Keep me looped in
on the search status.
No, I don't want to be
updated in ten minutes.
I want a real-time uplink.
They still haven't been
able to lock Jack down.
They lost him.
He landed the chopper
and escaped on foot.
NYPD is securing a perimeter.
CTU is coordinating
an interagency search.
If Jack gets this evidence
and exposes the Russians,
the agreement
is over.
The peace agreement
may not be the only casualty.
Madam President,
you covered up
the Russians' involvement.
That's grounds
for impeachment.
Possibly a criminal
indictment.
You crossed a line,
Madam President.
But it may not be too late
to step back
and limit the damage.
How?
Expose the Russians.
Grant Dana Walsh immunity
in exchange for evidence.
We'll launch an investigation
through transparent
international channels.
Which will effectively end
the peace deal.
But it will save
your administration.
There is still a chance
CTU will find Jack.
Even if they do,
the evidence is still out there.
Eventually, it will surface.
Allison... I know
better than anyone
how much this means to you.
How much you've sacrificed
personally
to make it happen.
Ethan, we are so close.
And we will be again.
If not during
your administration,
then during the next one.
I wish I could believe that.
Ethan, I want you to prepare...
(sniffles)
a statement
announcing our withdrawal
from this accord.
We have a...
(clears throat)
a press conference
in 40 minutes.
I'll make the announcement then.
As hard as this is,
you're doing the right thing.
(sniffles)
(elevator doors squeak)
Madam President.
It's over, Charles.
I've decided not to go through
with the peace deal.
Because of Bauer.
Because the evidence
implicating the Russians--
evidence that
I helped cover up--
is-is potentially too lethal.
I agree, Madam President.
Doesn't sound like you
have much of a choice.
I'm surprised.
I expected more of
a fight from you.
I'm nothing if not pragmatic.
Although I am
disappointed.
I'm afraid you have to find some
other way to repair your legacy.
My own personal
disappointment aside,
it's a loss
for the world.
Yes, it is.
Ethan's drafting
my statement.
I need to call Dalia Hassan.
Hope that
she'll forgive me for
keeping the truth from her.
Before you do, there is one
thing you might consider.
A way to preserve
the peace deal.
The peace deal is over.
You said so yourself.
I said it was over
if the evidence
comes out.
Obviously, you
can't grant
Walsh immunity.
The evidence would
become public record.
You need to control the evidence
by keeping Walsh off the grid.
Off the grid?
Classify her as
an enemy combatant
and incarcerate her
in a private facility.
There is a private
security firm I can recommend.
They're effective
and discreet.
I have them standing by.
Sounds like you've been
giving this a lot of thought.
Madam President,
this evidence is
hanging over your head.
You need to deal with it.
We can't keep Walsh
locked up indefinitely.
You wouldn't have to.
Ms. Walsh may not give up
the information willingly,
but she will give it up.
And once we have it, it won't
matter what she claims.
You're talking about
using physical coercion.
I know how deeply
this offends
your public and private
sensibilities.
It is repugnant,
even immoral.
But isn't morality relative,
considering what's
at stake here?
You are still
talking about torture.
I'm talking about
preserving a peace accord
that is crucial to the
security of this nation.
And that can only
happen if you
acquire and control
the evidence.
Believe me, Madam President,
I don't make
these suggestions lightly.
I appreciate the implications.
I've tried to be as open
and candid with you
as I've been
with anyone.
And the truth is,
I regret many of my own actions
when I was president.
But I've also had the
time and the distance
to see past them to a place
of clear and deep understanding.
What do you understand, Charles?
Wielding the kind of power
that I once had and you have now
can change the world.
But that often
requires making
impossible choices
that challenge
our most sacred ideals.
If you're not
willing to do that,
you should take Ethan's advice
and pull out now.
This was taken eight minutes ago
on the corner
of 25th and Cleveland.
Give Cole this information,
have him redirect his search.
Ms. O'Brian.
I have President Taylor
calling for you.
Put her through.
CHLOE (on phone):
Madam President, Chloe O'Brian.
Have you made any progress
in finding Jack Bauer?
Not yet. We're
still searching.
I think it's
safe to assume
he's on his way
to CTU and that
Dana Walsh is his target.
That's, that's why
I'm calling, Chloe.
I want Walsh
transferred
to a safe house
off-site.
Madam President, I've doubled
the security around Dana Walsh.
I'm confident thiss
the safest place for her to be.
Your opinion notwithstanding,
I'd feel more comfortable
with her in a place
where she can't be tracked.
Agents from a
private security firm
are coming there
to pick her up.
A private security firm?
You know as well as I do
that Jack has contacts
throughout the
government, some of whom
might be sympathetic
to his situation.
I'm not suggesting that you're
one of those people, Chloe.
I just, I just want to take
every precaution.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sending over the
transfer order now.
The agent in charge
of the escort team
is named Mark Bledsoe.
Should be arriving
there in a few minutes.
Understood.
Thank you, Chloe.
I know this was difficult,
Madam President,
but you made the right call.
These men of yours, I want
them to use every method of
noncoercive interrogation
available to them.
I've already given
that standing order.
No one wants this to get ugly.
Oh, it's already ugly, Charles.
(car horns honking)
Thanks. I don't need
the chargers.
(phone line ringing)
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Jack. Please, come back now.
This has got to stop.
I need you to get me
access to Dana Walsh.
The president said she's lying.
No, it's the president
who's lying.
She's covering up the evidence
to protect the peace agreement.
Even if she is,
she must have good reason.
Besides, it's not your call,
it's the president's.
She's covering up evidence
of a terrorist attack
against this country.
She no longer has the call.
You don't want to go
against me on this.
Are you threatening me?
Chloe, I'm trying
to ask you for help.
I need you to put me in
a room with Dana Walsh.
You're being hunted by every
law enforcement agency
in the city.
You're not thinking clearly.
Right now,
I'm the only one who is.
You can't just
go against everyone.
Please, just come in here,
and we'll figure this out
before you get
yourself killed.
You know what,
forget it, Chloe.
I'll figure out
another way.
Jack, wait.
What?
If you do get the evidence
from Dana,
what are you gonna do with it?
(panting)
I just want the people
who are responsible for this
to be held accountable.
All I need to do is expose them.
The president's having her
transferred out of CTU.
Why?
I'm not sure.
She hired a private
security firm.
Where are they taking her?
I don't know.
Find out.
I'll call you back.
Chloe.
Okay. I will.
Thanks.
(phone ringing)
Yes?
Jim, it's Jack Bauer.
Jack Bauer.
From what I'm hearing, you got
the whole damn city after you.
Look, I need your help.
I'm running out of places to go.
Running out?
(wry chuckle)
I'd say gone.
What'd you do
this time, Jack?
The less you know,
the better.
For who?
For both of us.
Look.
I'm gonna need weapons and
equipment; I need it fast.
Can you make that happen?
I can make just about
anything happen, Jack;
you already know that.
The problem is that you're
a walking bull's-eye.
Last thing in the world I
need is you on my doorstep.
You wouldn't have a doorstep
if it wasn't for me.
I'm calling in a favor.
I'm gonna tell you
what I want,
and I want it ready
when I get there.
You understand me?
Well, I see you haven't
lost your personal touch.
I'm gonna need a comm unit,
two MP5s,
an assortment of assault rifles
and ammo, a full communication
and surveillance package.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
(phone line ringing)
Yeah?
It's me. We're at CTU.
You have Walsh?
Not yet. I wanted to
talk about something
before we proceeded.
Is there a problem?
We put this team
together on short notice,
and we never had a chance
to discuss what to do with
the prisoner once we've
extracted the information.
Hand her
back to CTU.
Without the evidence, she has
no teeth; she can't hurt us.
Well, she can make accusations.
Even without the evidence,
something might stick.
You can't afford that.
What are you suggesting?
We can make it look like
the prisoner was killed
while she was
trying to escape.
Wouldn't be difficult.
I'm not sure we're willing
to go down that path.
You hired me
to clean up this situation.
In my professional opinion,
that's what needs to happen.
Talk it over with the client,
but I need to know soon.
Sir?
Yes, okay, I'll let you know.
Mr. Bledsoe?
That's right.
Chloe O'Brian,
acting director of CTU.
Heard you've had a rough day.
Yeah, you could say that.
I'll take you to Dana Walsh.
Thank you.
Where exactly are
you taking her?
I can't disclose
that information.
The whole point of
this exercise is to keep Walsh
off the grid.
Yes, but I'm responsible
for this prisoner.
You were given a presidential
order to turn over the prisoner.
Actually, I'm gonna need
to see that order.
You should've
received it already.
Well, we didn't.
Like you said, we've had
a rough day.
We were hit by an EMP
and most of our systems
are still down.
Ms. O'Brian, we don't
have a lot of time.
Look, I can't let you take her
unless I see the order.
So, you can wait.
Might take an hour, maybe more.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to be
so by-the-book.
It's-- I was
just promoted
to this position,
and I just want to make sure
that I dot all my I's
and cross the T's.
Right.
Satisfied?
Yeah, great.
Good morning, Ms. Walsh.
My name is Mark Bledsoe.
The president's
ordered your transfer
to an off-site
facility.
You've been designated
an enemy combatant
by special
executive order.
What do you mean
off-site facility?
It's a secure location.
Chloe, what the hell
is going on?
Where's Bauer?
Where's my immunity deal?
Just do what he says, Dana.
We can do it the hard way
or the easy way--
your choice--
but you're leaving here with us.
Chloe, don't let them do this.
Let's go.
Please, they're gonna kill me.
Chloe...
Chloe, please.
Chloe!
Thank you
for your cooperation.
(sighs)
All right, let's get units
on these two intersections.
(cell phone ringing)
Have them run car checks
on anyone
passing through.
I'll contact
Transit Police,
see about getting these
subways locked down.
Chloe, we're still in the middle
of a grid search here.
No sign of Jack.
I just talked to him;
he called me.
What?
He wants me to
help him get to Dana.
What did you
tell him?
I told him that she's
being transferred to
an off-site facility and that
I would give him the address.
And I almost did.
But I can't.
I'm under presidential orders.
Besides, I don't think
he's right.
He's not thinking clearly.
We have to find him
before he gets himself killed.
What if Jack is
thinking clearly?
If he's right,
if the president's lying,
and this conspiracy
is real,
we might be on the
wrong side of this.
Bottom line is, we were given
orders to bring him in.
That's what we're gonna do.
All right.
I need everyone's
attention, please.
We're mobilizing a sting
operation in the field
to be led by
Agent Ortiz.
The target is Jack Bauer.
Let's get to work.
Did you get what I need?
Nice to see you
again, too, Jack.
Did you get it or not?
Yeah, it's right over there.
Everything you asked
for-- right there.
I've been checking
the scanners.
All the agencies
are looking for you.
But nobody will say
what you did.
It's not about what I did.
They're afraid
of what I'm gonna do.
I don't know what
they did to you, Jack,
but it must have
been pretty bad.
I got to make a phone call.
O'Brian.
Hey, it's me.
You find out where
they're taking Dana?
Jack, I want you to think
about what you're doing.
Just give me the
address, Chloe.
It's not too late
to turn yourself in.
Are you going to give
me the address or not?
Dana is being taken to a safe
house in the Middle Village.
It's an industrial laundry
at 141 Juniper Valley Road.
Okay, that's about ten minutes
from here. I'll leave now.
Call me when you arrive.
I'm working on pulling up
the interior specs.
I'll be able to guide you in.
Chloe, thanks. I know
I've put you in a spot.
Yeah.
I'll get back to you.
I need you to stay here.
I might need you later.
You can't come back
here again.
Besides that,
we're even now.
I'll let you know
when we're even.
Jim, please.
I need your help, okay?
Did O'Brian brief you?
Yes, sir.
We're drawing Bauer
to this location
where he thinks Dana
Walsh is being held.
It's an industrial laundry
the DEA seized a year ago.
CTU's been using it
as a safe house,
but there's no way
Jack can know this.
Understand, Bauer's
a highly skilled operative.
So we need to make everything
as credible as possible.
He'll be expecting sentries,
so Beck, you're out front.
Greer, you take the back.
You two will be
stationed inside.
Everyone stays out of sight
until Jack's
between our choke points.
We do the takedown when, and
only when I give the order.
We get this right,
we take Jack by surprise
before he has a chance
to fight back.
Gear up.
Cole.
Jack just called.
He's ten minutes out.
What's your status?
We're on-site and getting ready.
Remember, nonlethal force.
Look, I don't want anything
to happen to Jack either,
but I can't tell my men
not to defend themselves
if their lives
are in danger.
You know that.
He's calling me
when he arrives.
I'll let you know
when that happens.
All right.
Let's go, guys, let's go.
Madam President.
I have a final draft
of your statement.
I think it best for now to cite
President Hassan's death
as the reason
for your withdrawing.
Then after the dust has settled,
we can start prosecuting the
Russians through back channels.
Ethan, I've chosen
not to withdraw
from the peace agreement.
And I'm keeping the press
conference as scheduled.
I don't understand.
Dana Walsh is being moved
from CTU
to a private detention facility.
She'll be off the grid,
out of Jack Bauer's reach.
I've authorized a private
interrogation team
to acquire the evidence.
Acquire the evidence?
Once we have it,
she'll be irrelevant.
(scoffs)
Keeping the truth
from Jack Bauer is one thing--
but authorizing
the illegal detention
and torture of a prisoner?
How far are you willing to go
to protect this lie?
As far as necessary
to preserve this treaty.
It's vital to the security
of this nation.
And what I am doing
is for the greater good.
This was Logan's idea,
wasn't it?
The decision was mine.
And I stand behind it.
Now listen--
please listen to
what I'm saying.
I think this is about more
than the grÑater good.
I think your presidency
has cost you your marriage
and your children.
And you think
that this treaty
will somehow redeem
that loss...
Ethan, that's enough.
Now, listen, you've
made this personal,
and you've lost your way.
I've known you long
enough to see that.
I implore you--
take a step back
and look at this clearly.
I said that's enough.
I've explained
my reasons.
I appreciate your objections,
but the debate is over.
So, let's move on.
Madam President,
unless you stop what's
being done in your name,
I can't be a part
of this any longer.
Don't worry, I'll...
I'll keep it to myself.
Um, I'll cite my health as
the reason for my resignation.
After all, I'm here
against doctor's orders.
Ethan, please.
We are almost there!
You-you can't just abandon me
like this.
I'm not abandoning you.
I'm listening to my conscience.
Anyway,
you've got Charles Logan now.
Only room for one of us.
Madam President.
(door opens, then closes)
Look at me.
My hand is shaking.
I would be concerned
if it weren't.
What you've agreed
to take on
is not something
that could be treated lightly.
I keep thinking
that people will accuse me
of grabbing for power.
Exploiting my husband's death.
Which couldn't be further
from the truth.
Still, some people may
perceive it that way.
Remember what
father said?
He said the best
way to dispel
public misperception
is to address it directly.
Good.
I will take his advice.
Jamot, will you
excuse us?
Of course.
I just need to remind you
that the other delegates
are expecting you in 20 minutes.
I'll be ready.
Miss Kayla.
Jamot.
Mother, I'm sorry
for being so selfish earlier.
You were afraid.
You lost your father today.
And you were afraid
of losing me as well.
I still am.
This peace agreement
Father died for--
how can so many people be
so violently against it?
Some people are so invested
in their fear and hatred
that peace is the most
threatening thing
they can imagine.
Chloe, you still there?
CHLOE (over comm):
Yes.
I'm at the site.
I only see one man out front.
I found a schematic
of the building.
There's a side entrance to the
north of the loading dock.
I got it.
It looks like it's out of
the sentry's line of sight.
According to
the schematic,
there's an enclosed room
at the southwest corner
of the building.
That must be where
they're keeping Dana.
Copy that. Chloe, I got go.
I'm moving in.
Cole, he's going into the
loading dock entrance
heading towards
the takedown point.
COLE:
I see him.
Hopkins, Lee,
Jack's moving into the building
and headed toward your position.
Stay sharp.
Copy that. We're ready.
(clattering)
(taps twice)
Chloe, it's Jack.
I got a visual
on the room.
No hostiles in sight.
I'm going to try
and grab her.
Be careful, Jack.
Okay, copy that.
(panting)
(grunts)
Cole, he's almost
at the takedown point.
Copy that.
On my way.
Hopkins, we're moving in.
Son of a bitch.
Put your weapons down!
Put your weapons down now!
I can't do that, Jack!
Cole, tell them to put
their weapons down or
I will kill him!
COLE:
Put that gun down now!
Put your weapons down now!
Now!
Put 'em down!
Tell your men to get down.
Do it.
Get on the ground.
Now!
Cole, slowly advance towards me.
Kick the guns over
in my direction.
Get out of my line of sight.
How did you know?
I know Chloe.
You're gonna call CTU.
You're gonna tell her
that her plan worked,
and you've got me locked down
and ready for transport.
Put it on speaker.
CHLOE (on speakerphone):
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Cole.
Cole, go ahead.
What's happening?
We've got Jack.
He's locked down.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
What about your men?
They're all right.
I know I should feel relieved,
but I just feel worse.
Like you said, Chloe,
it's for his own good.
I'll talk to him
when he gets here.
Lock your men down.
What are you
planning on doing?
Lock 'em down!
All right, Jack,
what now?
JACK: Follow me.
Take a seat.
You're why
I'm here, Cole.
I knew Chloe
would send you.
You're the only
reason I risked it.
What do you want with me?
I need you to help me
gain access to Dana Walsh.
I know you well
enough, Cole,
that I know you
don't want
to be a part of
this cover-up.
And right now
President Taylor
wants the peace agreement
to move forward so badly,
she's willing to lie about
the Russian's involvement
in today's terrorist attack,
and I can't let
that happen.
How can you be sure
the President is lying?
Because she told me to my face!
She said the agreement
was more important
than the Russians
could have done today.
Why the hell do you think
she came down
to CTU to talk to me?
She didn't want me
to give the evidence
from Dana.
She wanted to shut me up
and lock me down
Damn it, Cole, your hands
aren't clean in this.
You protected Dana
while she was
operating for
the Russians.
You lied for her,
which enabled the Russians
to provide nuclear materials
to Hassan's opposition.
They facilitated his
assassination and what,
you lost four
of your men today, right?
I am giving you
an opportunity to
make this right,
to make the people that are
responsible for everything
that happened today
accountable.
You got a decision to make.
Now, what if you're wrong?
I'm not.
Look, I can't do
this on my own.
Your call.
Chloe says she's in a safe house
a few miles from here.
We'll notify CTU
about your men
within the next two hours.
Right now it's imperative that
they think I took you hostage.
Get up!
REPORTER:
We've been hearing speculation
that Dalia Hassan
will be making
her first official statement
as the provisional head
of state
of the Islamic Republic
of Kamistan.
Earlier, we spoke to a UN
official who confirmed
that under the IRK's
constitution,
Mrs. Hassan would have
the authority
to sign this treaty.
Ethan! (turns TV off)
I, uh, I heard about
your resignation.
I'm glad to see you're putting
your health first.
We all just want
you to get well.
I'm leaving
because of you.
Because of what
you've started here.
You've deliberately
played this out
to maneuver the President
into a corner.
I brought the Russians back
to the table.
But you didn't tell her
how you were doing it.
She didn't ask.
Because she knew
it was best for her
to preserve her own deniability.
The President knows
exactly what she's doing.
She's smart.
She's smarter than either of us
ever gave her credit for.
I see.
So, uh, you just
provided counsel.
That's right.
Well, let me counsel you.
Stop this cover-up
before it's too late.
This peace is no good.
There's too much blood
on this treaty
for it ever to hold.
We've both been in this game
a long time,
and we both know damn well
that every treaty ever written
had blood on it!
Not like this.
You got Allison so far
into the woods,
she'll never be able
to find her way out.
She wasn't like you.
Wasn't like any politician
I've ever known.
That's right.
She's finally got some teeth.
You listen to me.
If she suffers for this,
I will come after you
with everything I have.
You're threatening me.
I'm warning you, Charles.
Do you need to sit down?
(scoffs) I'm fine.
Well, then, if you don't mind,
Allison will be taking
the podium any second now.
(turns TV on)
Get some rest, Ethan.
You need it.
(Dana gasping)
You told Bauer
you have evidence.
I need to know
where it is.
Come on, Miss Walsh.
You know the deal.
The sooner you tell me,
the easier it'll go.
Please, I have got
nothing to tell you.
There is no evidence.
If that's the way
you want
to play it, fine.
(gasping)
PRESS SECRETARY:
Ladies and gentlemen,
no questions will be taken
until after
this morning's address.
Madam President, I want
to thank you for
your thoughts
on my speech.
They were very helpful.
I'm glad.
My husband would have been
grateful for the support
that you have given me.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President
of the United States.
My fellow Americans and friends
in foreign lands,
I speak to you this morning
with a heavy heart.
The brutal and cowardly murder
of President Omar Hassan was
a blow to every civilized person
in the world
and a stark reminder
that the pursuit of peace
sometimes comes
with a steep price.
President Hassan understood
that, yet still had
the fortitude to pursue a better
tomorrow against so many odds.
I join with the American people
in mourning him
and every other innocent life
that was lost
during this crisis.
But let it be known here and now
their sacrifice will not have
been in vain.
Peace must and will prevail
no matter the cost.
No matter the cost,
no matter the compromises.
We have waited too long
and worked too hard,
to allow this opportunity
to pass us by.
And that is why in Omar Hassan's
name, I am choosing
to move forward with this
historic summit.
One that was made possible
by the shared hopes and ideals
of the IRK leadership,
(gasping)
and will continue
under its new leader--
a woman of unparalleled courage
and grace,
who has been chosen
by her people
to carry on the mantle
of her late husband...
Dalia Hassan.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net