Re-sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Let's get the other
body and get cleaned up
before we head back to CTU.
I'm trying to locate an
individual by the name
of Kevin Wade.
Kevin's probation
officer just called me.
He has records that
show him calling my cell
several times.
Look, you just have
to handle this, okay?
I don't know if I can do this.
Lie. Come on, we both
know you're good at it.
Put your hands where
I can see them!
Do not move!
Samir, Marcos is
out of the chamber.
Hang up right now and
transmit the fail safe!
What's happening? What is that?
! Marcos, I don't know
if I'm gonna be able
to do this in time.
How were they gonna smuggle
the fuel rods into the city
past the radiological detectors?
I don't know!
Damn it, Marcos, give me a name!
President Hassan's head of security,
Tarin Faroush.
Right now you need to call UN
Security and have them take
Mr. Faroush into custody
until we get there.
Tarin's not here. Where is he?
I don't know.
Somewhere with my daughter.
Tarin is working with
your father's enemies.
You must tell me where you are.
The Teodore Hotel, Suite 514.
Just stay where you are.
The police will be there shortly.
I thought we agreed
you weren't gonna take
your mother's call.
I'm sorry, my love,
I just didn't want her to worry.
Did you tell her where we are?
Of course not.
We're arriving at the landing now.
Soon we'll be able to transport
the rods into Manhattan.
Are CTU's radiation sensors down?
Not yet, but we'll be ready.
All right, listen up!
This is what we know.
IRK nationalists are targeting
New York with a dirty bomb.
We have one lead:
Hassan's former head of security,
Tarin Faroush.
We believe he wants to
disable our defenses
so they can smuggle the
bomb into Manhattan.
Chloe?
Latest intel is that Tarin is
staying at the Teodore Hotel
with President Hassan's
daughter, Kayla.
Kayla has been warned by her mother
that Tarin is working
with the terrorists.
She'll be trying to
keep him at the hotel
until our Tac teams arrive.
What's our ETA othat?
NYPD is approaching
the staging area,
CTU still ten minutes out.
Chloe, you liaise with NYPD.
Actually, Dana is better at the
inter-agency protocols than I am.
Fine.
Jack Bauer's heading Field Ops,
Dana's on point with NYPD,
Arlo will run aerial.
Let's get to it.
All the changes going
on around here,
who do I report to exactly,
you or Dana?
What does it matter?
I just like to be clear.
The only thing you need to be
clear about is that there's
a dirty bomb about to go off
in Manhattan, so just do your job.
Drone's in position
over the Teodore Hotel
awaiting your instructions.
Kayla, we have to go.
Nearly ready.
What was that? Are you all right?
It was nothing, I'm fine.
Hello?
The Americans got Marcos to talk.
He may have compromised you.
Did the girl receive
any phone calls?
Yes, one- her mother. Get out now.
And bring her with you.
We're moving to the next phase.
I'll need a vehicle.
Hamid is on his way.
Kayla,
we must go now.
Just one more minute.
Hurry up, please.
Jack, I'm uploading Tarin
Faroush's file to you now.
Copy that.
Okay, I've got it.
We're also gonna need
hotel schematics and access
to their security systems.
Coming to you now.
Target is in room 514.
Hotel security is standing
by to give NYPD access.
Jack, Brian Hastings.
What's your ETA?
About eight minutes.
Can you patch me through
to our point man at NYPD?
We're doing that now.
Name's, uh, Sergeant Amis.
Sergeant Amis, Dana Walsh, CTU.
Been waiting on you, Ms. Walsh.
We're in our staging area already.
Go ahead, Jack.
Sergeant Amis, Jack Bauer.
Our target, Tarin Faroush,
is in room 514.
He has a female hostage,
Kayla Hassan.
She's the daughter of
President Hassan of the IRK.
We'll handle him, Mr. Bauer.
We'll make sure that girl
doesn't come to any harm.
The priority is to
take Tarin alive.
He's our only lead to a major
terrorist threat against New York.
Like I said, we'll handle him.
Sergeant, don't
underestimate this man.
He was President Hassan's
head of security.
He knows what he's doing.
I want your men to set up a
perimeter and wait for us.
We're monitoring hotel security.
We'll give you a heads-up
if we've got any
action from the room.
Kayla, my friend from
the State Department
is waiting for us! We must go now.
Just one more second, please.
Kayla!
Tarin, what are you doing?!
Stop this game.
We walk out of here right now.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Just move! Oh, no!
Where are you taking me?
Believe me, the last thing
I want to do is hurt you,
but I will.
Got movement on the fifth floor.
Are you getting this, Jack?
Yeah, someone must've
tipped him off. Sergeant?
Yes, I know, target's on the move.
I'm going in.
Negative. We're five minutes out.
I want you to hold your position.
I'm on the ground, Mr.
Bauer; it's my call.
No, it isn't,
this is a CTU operation.
I am telling you to
hold your position.
I'm going in. Sergeant!
Tarin's at the elevators.
Lost picture on the fifth.
Sergeant, target has
taken out elevator security
camera and is armed.
I am ordering you to stand down.
I'm right on him.
Sergeant, that was an order!
Sergeant Amis, can you hear me?
Ser- Chloe, have you got anything!?
Nothing.
OFFICER Shots fired, shots fired.
We have shots fired.
All NYPD units report status.
Repeat, report status.
This is Faulkner. I'm hit.
Amis and Martin are down.
Where's the target?
He's heading toward the fire
escape on the south side.
He's got the girl.
ESU, this is Agent Ortiz.
Cover the south fire escape now!
Medics, men down
on the fifth floor.
That doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Tarin just took out three men.
Why's he using the fire escape?
He should be heading
down the stairs.
Son of a bitch.
NYPD, target is impersonating
an officer; he has the girl.
I want you to fall back
and cover all exits.
I repeat, target is
impersonating an officer.
Cover all exits!
Chloe, do you see anything?
Nothing.
Send us back the drone feed.
Roger that.
Drop the gun!
Put it down! No, no!
Drop it now! This is Bellow.
Target's at the Allen Street exit.
He's got the girl.
Chloe, we need that drone feed.
Coming through.
There's a cab pulling up.
Officer Bellow, behind you!
They're heading for the cab.
All ESU, we have
two officers down in the
alley behind the hotel.
Target is moving to Allen Street.
He's escaping in the yellow cab.
Tracking the cab.
Go!
Advise all NYPD mobile units,
we cannot lose that vehicle.
On it. Taxi's in the
Delancey underpass.
I'm blind. Do we have traffic cams?
Not in the underpass.
We're two blocks from Delancey.
Any sign of the cab?
Still in the underpass.
The underpass is less
than half a click.
Where the hell are they?
NYPD mobile units, 90 seconds out.
Go left, Jack, go left right here!
There it is. I got the cab.
I got the cab.
Driver!
I want you to slowly
open your door!
Open the door now!
It's empty.
It's empty!
Chloe, backtrack drone footage.
Trace every vehicle
that left the underpass.
Get NYPD to set roadblocks.
They were here less
than 30 seconds ago!
Arlo? Got it.
We should join the sweep.
No, they're gone.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do, they're gone.
Chloe, it's Jack,
I'm gonna need a kidnap
and an electronic
intercept package.
Have it meet me back
at the UN. Copy.
I need to talk to President Hassan.
That's who the terrorists are
gonna want to contact next.
That's why they
kidnapped his daughter.
Tarin just called.
He has the girl.
Hello.
Ahman. Samir,
where are the nuclear rods?
They're still outside the city.
We haven't disabled the American
radiological detectors yet.
Then how will you
bring the rods to me?
It's been taken care of.
Here, Mr. Prady. Thank you.
Give me one moment. Yeah.
We've backtracked through
drone and traffic cam footage
looking for Kayla and Tarin.
Nothing's come up yet.
What's Bauer's status?
He's two minutes from the UN.
An electronic intercept
team is en route to him.
Keep me informed.
Copy.
Ms. Walsh.
There's a Mr.
Prady here to see you.
Says he spoke to you on the phone.
Thank you.
Chloe.
Would you mind covering
for me for a few minutes?
Mr. Prady.
Dana Walsh. A pleasure, Ms. Walsh.
It'll be quieter in here.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, this is, uh...
this is some impressive facility.
What, uh...
what is it you do here?
Intelligence analyst.
Mr. Prady, we've got a
major situation here...
I understand. I won't
take up much of your time.
Okay.
It's 3:00 in the morning,
you're 2,000 miles from home.
You mind telling me
what's so urgent?
Yeah. It's about the young man
I mentioned on the phone-
Kevin Wade.
This is him right here.
You know him, don't you?
Yes.
I should have been honest
with you on the phone.
I met Kevin a couple
days ago at a bar.
Was there another man with him?
He was traveling
with an ex-con named Nick Coughlin.
Bad news.
Done time on robbery,
attempted murder.
No. No, I've never seen him.
Okay.
So, what happened...
with you and Kevin?
Um...
we talked for a while.
I drank more than I should,
and we ended up back in his van.
You had sex with him.
Yes.
Do you know where he is now?
No. I didn't see him again.
The whole thing was a mistake.
Why so?
Because I am getting
married in a few weeks.
It was the pressure.
I- I don't know.
All the wedding plans.
I went out for a drink.
I didn't intend to...
Maybe I did. I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore.
All that I know is that
if my fiancÃfÂ© finds out,
he will never forgive me.
I'm not looking to ruin your life.
I just want to retrieve Kevin
before he gets in more trouble
than violating his parole.
I understand.
I... I hope that you find him.
Yeah, thing is, Miss Walsh,
I got a call a couple hours ago
from my NYPD friend, Tom Hardiman.
Seems like there was a...
a break-in
at a police evidence lockup.
Again, bad business.
Officer got beaten up,
left in a coma,
but guess whose prints
were on the assault weapon?
Yeah, that nasty SOB,
Nick Coughlin.
Now, what I'm afraid of is...
where Nick is, Kevin is, too,
and I really need to find him.
And, like I told you,
I only saw him the once.
I have no idea where he is.
And you're sure about that?
Mr. Prady, we are in the middle
of a national security crisis.
I have to go back to my desk.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps, if I talk
to your supervisor,
he could let you take
a few minutes off.
Or I could wait here,
stay out of your way
till you have some time.
Fine.
You have to stay here, though.
Of course.
Okay. Mm-hmm.
I don't understand.
The Americans knew where Kayla was.
How did they lose her?
Before we blame them, remember...
it was our people- our own people-
who kidnapped Kayla,
not the Americans.
Mr. President, CTU is here.
Mr. President, I'm Jack Bauer.
You already know Cole Ortiz.
We deeply regret not being able
to find your daughter,
but I promise you,
we're going to do everything
in our power to recover her.
How did you lose her?
How did that happen?
Tarin had been warned, ma'am.
We arrived too late.
It was your people...
Dalia, please.
What do they want with Kayla?
We were hoping you
could tell us, sir.
Tarin Faroush was
your head of security,
meaning he knows
everything that you know.
He took your daughter
because he's trying
to leverage something from you.
Do you have
any idea what that could be?
I don't know.
Sir,
we believe the kidnappers
will contact you directly.
We need to set up monitoring
devices on your phones
so we can track their call.
Do what you need to do.
Just, please,
get our child back.
Dalia.
Please.
Thank you.
With me.
Set up tech here.
Tarin! Don't.
Please.
Don't. Come on.
Do what he says,
and you won't get hurt.
Who is he?
Another traitor?
The only traitor is your father.
Tie her up.
No.
No. No. No.
Do you recognize the number?
There isn't one.
Chloe, we've got a call
coming in on the
mother's cell phone.
We're working on it.
Answer it.
Keep them on the phone
as long as possible.
Yes?
Your husband is a traitor to
the people of the Republic.
He alone has made our
actions necessary.
He cannot be trusted.
Where is my daughter?
I want to talk to her.
Whether you ever see
her again depends
on what your husband
does right now.
Put him on. Dalia?
They want to talk to you.
Here, give me the phone.
We need to be hearing this.
We're still working on it, Jack.
Okay, we've got it.
You should have audio.
This is President Hassan.
Who are you?
I'm a loyal servant of the Republic
you are trying to destroy.
Now, shut up, Omar, and listen.
I want to lk to my daughter.
Let me tell you what I want.
File 33.
That is the price of your daughter.
I don't know what that is.
You had to say that.
Of course.
You're a vain man,
concerned about appearances,
and the Americans are listening.
But please...
do not insult me by
saying this again.
I won't say anything until
I talk to my daughter.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
I'm sending you an IP address.
Give it to one of the
people listening in.
Okay, got it.
Don't hurt her.
It's me you want.
I told you what I want.
File 33.
I told you-
I don't know what that is.
Take me instead.
You have 15 minutes.
No excuses, no stalling.
15 minutes or she dies here,
like this,
while you watch.
Stop it.
Stop it!
I'll find the file. Whatever it is,
I'll get it for you!
Mr. President,
what is File 33?
Omar! Mr. Bauer,
I've got Brian
Hastings on the line.
Yeah.
Jack, you know anything
about this file?
No, but I'm standing here
with President Hassan.
I'll put you on speaker.
Go ahead.
Mr. President,
this is Brian Hastings.
I have no intel on the
file they're talking about.
Can you tell me what this is?
Sir, they gave you 15 minutes.
If you want to see your daughter again,
you don't have time
to waste.
Omar, what is this file?
Show them.
Show them!
Dalia,
I'll do anything for Kayla.
I would give
my own life.
Then give them this file.
Sir?
Put it up on the screen,
mirror it over to CTU.
Hastings, are you seeing this?
Yes, I am.
Mr. President,
this file appears to
contain operational details
of all U.S. anti-nuclear defenses.
That's correct.
Including our radiological
detection arrays.
This is highly-
classified DOD material.
I need to know how you got this.
How do you think, Mr. Hastings?
For 20 years, your nation
has threatened mine
with everything from
economic sanctions
to military attack.
So we gathered intelligence
and found weaknesses
in your defenses.
We did what any other
country would do.
Mr. President,
that file shows the fatal flaws
of our nuclear
detection capabilities.
If the terrorists were to get that,
they could smuggle the
fuel rods into Manhattan.
Surely you understand,
we cannot let you
give that to them.
We're talking about the lives
of tens of thousands of people.
And what of my daughter?
What of her life?
With all due respect, madam,
your family brought this threat
to my country.
We're doing the best we can.
Jack, you still on?
Yeah, we all are.
Jack, we may have a lead
on the daughter's location.
Arlo isolated a subway
noise from the video feed
at the end of the transmission,
cross-referencing it with
the real-time train
positions as of this moment.
There aren't a lot of
trains this late at night,
especially within the radius that
they could have traveled to. They were
heading southeast when they left the hotel.
They've got to be
near the F train stop
by the Williamsburg Bridge.
Copy that. Cole and I
will head down there now.
We'll bring Tac from here.
You need me to send a second team?
Yes, and aerial.
Everything you've got.
Have your men ready and assembled
in five minutes. Right away.
Mr. President, we're going
to need you to stall them
when they call back. How?
We'll set up a fake file
that you can transmit.
They'll see through that,
Mr. Bauer.
Eventually, but right
now we just need you
to stall them long enough so
we can locate your daughter.
Stall them any way you can,
but you need to make this work.
We will do whatever we have to.
Thank you.
Tarin.
Please, don't say...
Why are you doing this? Please.
Why are you doing this?
Please don't say anything more.
Please.
Is there trouble? No.
Why would there be?
What's the problem?
They're never going to
hand over that file.
They have to. And if they don't?!
Killing her was not
part of the plan.
You were willing to die
in Hassan's limousine
earlier today.
You were willing to do
anything for our cause.
I still am.
You assured me your feelings
for this girl would
not get in the way.
So tell me,
do I need someone else
to take care of her?
No.
Stay strong.
We're almost there.
Arlo, what's the status
on our target area?
Still looking at almost
six square blocks.
How far out are Jack and Cole?
Six minutes.
That leaves us about 30 seconds
to find her.
We've got to narrow this down.
Where's the second Tac team?
Leaving now.
Uh... Dana?
Huh?
Who is that?
Nobody.
Mr. Prady, this is a secure area.
If you're not gonna
wait in holding,
I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave. I'm sorry.
I had a question.
And I'm in the middle of a situation.
I don't have time.
Well, I wouldn't be bothering you,
but I just got off the
phone with my NYPD friend.
He said I absolutely
have to ask you
about the security cameras at
the police evidence lockup.
Because you know what?
It turns out they malfunctioned
for the exact duration
of the incident.
Well, somebody obviously
disabled the cameras.
Well, yeah, but not Nick and Kevin.
I mean, a crowbar is about as
high-tech as those two get.
Now, that's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
See, I'm thinking that someone
must have helped them.
Now, my friend says
that all the raw video
from every government facility
feeds right here into CTU.
Am I understanding that right?
Yes. He also said-
correct me if I'm wrong- that
the digital images
are archived every
eight hours, and metadata-
is that what it's called,
metadata?-
that allows you to trace
the exact source of
any service outage.
So, everything I need to
solve this is right here.
You can get it for me, right?
Mr. Prady, we don't just give
data to people off the street.
Well, now, that's right.
That's right.
You need, uh,
an IDRAN- an Interagency
Data Request Authorization Number.
Yeah, Hardiman gave
me one of those.
He said everything should fit
on a 100-gig thumb drive.
So is that going to be a problem,
getting that for me?
No.
Good.
They reprocessed the subway noise,
managed to narrow
down the search grid.
How big?
About 12 buildings total.
Apartments, offices, retail.
It's still too much
ground to cover.
Agent Ortiz.
Dana?
Cole... it's over.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure I heard you.
The parole officer looking
for Kevin is here at CTU.
Knows about the robbery,
the cameras, everything.
Are you certain?
Yeah.
He's after the raw feeds.
He's got an interagency request.
I'm going to give it to him, Cole.
I'm sorry to call you.
I just thought
that you should know.
Why don't you wait?
Do you hear me?
He knows everything.
He'll go to Hastings.
Don't do anything.
We'll talk about it
when I get back.
I can't wait.
If you're here,
you'll just get in more
trouble trying to protect me.
I can't let that happen.
I love you, Cole.
Dana? Dana?
You got a problem? No.
Good, 'cause I need you
to keep your head in this.
You understand?
You got it.
Omar.
We're running out of time.
The technicians have prepared
the file I'll be sending.
But these people who have Kayla-
they won't believe a fake file.
No.
But they might believe you.
You have a gift, Omar.
When you talk, people listen.
You need to convince them,
for our daughter.
Say whatever you
need to to buy time.
I have seen you
move so many people.
You can do this.
I know it.
Yeah.
Mr. President?
I'm sorry.
It's time.
The deadline is here.
Your father has not responded.
You hate him that much,
you would do this
to me?
Tarin...
I don't want to die.
Please.
Then let us pray
for once your father
does the right thing.
Tarin, you can't let them do this.
I know you.
Shh.
This is not you.
And I know in my heart
that you love me.
In my heart I know.
And so I don't understand why...
Nearly there, sir.
Okay, the uplink's ready.
Let's go.
Stop them!
W- Wait, wait, wait.
Follow me.
This way, come on.
My father will help us.
He's surrounded by traitors.
We have to get to CTU.
Here, the number is
in this cell phone.
Call them.
Tarin, no, no!
Tarin, no!
Tarin!
No.
Omar, what has happened to her?
Did the Americans stop the call?
I don't know.
Maybe they were afraid we'd
hand over the real file.
They could have gotten
our daughter killed.
Why aren't we seeing anything?
We're not sure.
Arlo's been scanning
the audio source.
Four minutes ago there
was a spike- very faint-
sounded like a gunshot.
Did Jack hear anything?
No, but he's still a
quarter of a mile out.
Mr. Hastings, you better take this.
It's Kayla Hassan- she's in a car,
she's escaped.
What?
Go.
Ms. Hassan, Brian Hastings,
Director of CTU.
You all right? No, no,
I'm not all right.
I'm driving.
They might be chasing me,
I don't know.
Where are you? I don't know!
Track her cell phone;
patch Jack in.
Ms. Hassan, we're tracking
your cell phone right now.
Do not turn it off.
Just tell us what happened.
They tried to kill me,
but Tarin got me out.
He found a car, but they caught us.
They shot him.
He's dead.
He told me to call CTU,
that it was the only safe place.
Ms. Hassan, my name is Jack Bauer.
We need to know where
you were being held.
I don't know.
Ma'am, look, I know you've
been through a great ordeal,
but please, this is very important.
Can you at least try to remember
what the building looked like?
It was dark, and it was empty.
It-It had a vault,
like a bank, but abandoned.
Chloe, did you get that?
Got it.
You need to tell my father that
Tarin Faroush helped me escape,
that he sacrificed his life for me.
We've got the location, Jack.
Republic Commerce Bank,
9621 East Broadway.
It closed a year ago.
It's the only bank on
the grid. Copy that.
We're going to need drone support,
and send a second
team over to the bank.
We got 'em.
Ms. Hassan, we've got you on
First Avenue and East Fifth.
Continue going straight,
I will tell you when to turn.
Okay.
You two cover this exit.
When the second team gets here,
you send them down.
Cole, you're with me.
Let's take the door.
Cole.
Chloe, it's Jack.
We're in the basement of the bank.
There's some kind of tunnel system.
I've got the schematics,
I'm seeing it now.
We're going to head
down a spur southeast
from the vault.
How many exit points?
Two exits- no, three.
Have the drone cover
all the exit points.
Arlo, I'm sending
you my screen now.
Can you get eyes on all the exits?
Yeah, ascending to 5,000.
I got movement at the south exit.
I've got four hostiles
approaching Division Street
on foot, heading northeast.
You copy? Yeah.
Cole, they double-backed
up top.
Chloe, we're moving to intercept.
Where's Kayla? She's approaching
the tunnel entrance now;
she'll be with us in two minutes.
Security is standing by.
Good work, people.
Dana...
good work.
Thank you, sir.
If you'll excuse me
for a few minutes...
Targets are heading
north on Orchard.
Okay, they're getting
into an SUV, Jack.
Do you copy? Yeah.
Just stay with them, we'll follow.
Owen, King, you're coming with us.
You take King's vehicle,
you two double-back around Orchard.
Chloe, I've got a shot here
for facial recognition.
Send it to me.
It's Tarin Faroush.
He's supposed to be dead.
Kayla said they shot him.
You did the right thing, Tarin.
I know.
She will die for a good cause.
Jack, Cole, come in.
Go ahead, Chloe.
We ID'd one of the targets.
It's Tarin Faroush.
Kayla said he sacrificed himself
to save her, but he's still alive.
Are you absolutely sure?
Yes.
What the hell's going on?
The terrorists asked
us to give them a file
they knew we would never give them.
They never expected us to.
Chloe, you got to
put Hastings on now.
I'm on, Jack.
You cannot let Kayla Hassan in.
The terrorists faked her escape.
They wanted to get her to CTU.
For what purpose?
What's the best way to disarm
New York's radiological defenses?
Taking out CTU.
There's got to be something in the car,
some kind of a bomb.
You need to stop her now.
Where is she?
Oh, my God.
She's in the tunnel.
Security!
Dana, with me!
Chloe, the car that Tarin got into,
where is it now?
Crossing into Brooklyn,
taking the first exit off
the Williamsburg Bridge.
We cannot lose
that car, do you understand me?
Copy.
Stop the car!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Put your hands where
we can see them!
Dana, call the bomb squad!
Get out of the car!
Take her.
Bomb squad to the tunnel entrance.
Get her away from here.
Hastings, have you
stopped that car?
Not in time, Jack.
Hold on, just hold on.
It's an EMP.
It's an EMP!
You need to shut down your
systems to protect the drones.
There's no time, Jack.
Get away from the car!
I can move it.
Come on, get out of there!
Get out of there!
Chloe, can you hear me?
Those drones right now are
our only way of tracking
down those terrorists.
You need to pass
them off to the NSA.
Damn it, we're blind.
Chloe, did you cop... Chloe?!
What the hell is happening?
We need to contact NSA.
The terrorists just took out CTU.
Re-sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net