Who is it
you're looking for?
Someone who can give me the
names of everyone else involved.
I need you to write the story
in case I don't make it.
If Dalia Hassan finds out
that the Russians had a hand
in the death of her husband,
she'll never sign the agreement.
MEREDITH:
I need to speak to your mother.
It's about the people
who really murdered your father.
We know who is responsible.
What you don't know is,
those people
were working under
the orders of Russian agents.
Bauer made contact
with Meredith Reed.
My God.
You need
to call her
publisher and demand
that they do not
run the story.
You're suggesting
muzzling the press?
If you don't use the
power of your office
to shut this story down,
your peace agreement
won't be the only casualty.
I need you to contact the FBI.
Have them locate Reed
and seize whatever evidence
she purports to have.
Meredith Reed? FBI.
You're under arrest.
Let's go.
But I...
You were right
about Jack.
He is working
with somebody.
It's James Ricker,
ex-CIA op.
We found him living in a place
on Mercer Street.
He's not gonna be happy
we tracked him down.
I need you to talk to him.
Get him to tell us
where Jack is.
Are you good with that, or
have you still not taken sides?
I want to expose this cover-up
as much as you. I'm in.
(tires screech, horn honks)
That's Jack Bauer!
(coughing)
Get up. I could just
kill you right here.
Do you know the name
of the person inside
the Russian government
who's giving the orders?
I want that name.
Jack.
Give me the name!
I'll tell you.
Four.
Three.
Mikhail Novakovich!
Where's Novakovich?
He's dead.
Bauer just came in shooting.
Mikhail Novakovich
was just murdered
by Jack Bauer.
What?
LOGAN:
As far as, uh,
Bauer is concerned,
the trail ended
with Novakovich.
Then Bauer has no idea
that Novakovich was operating
under my orders?
None.
If you're so worried about
Bauer, you never should have
given the order
to kill Renee Walker.
(phone ringing)
Arlo.
Cole, I just picked up
a preliminary flash.
Jack murdered Novakovich
at his hotel,
and six of his security guards.
According to a witness,
Jack killed all seven men
on his own.
Then fell right back
off the radar.
Eden can't find
any trace of him.
Does Chloe know about this?
I just talked to her,
and she should be
at the U.N. any minute.
Cole, I know that we need
this evidence that Jack has,
but this crime scene
is a slaughterhouse.
Does Chloe really still
think she can pull this off?
If anyone can talk Jack down,
it's Chloe.
And if she can't?
Then we're both
prepared to do
whatever it takes
to stop him.
Even when Novakovich's
whole security staff couldn't?
What do you want me to do, Arlo?
The truth about what went down
today needs to get out,
and that's not going to happen
unless we get to Jack.
Look, I'm coming up
on Ricker's apartment.
I'm going in.
Cole. COLE: What?
Ricker went to a lot of
trouble to disappear.
He's not going to like
that you found him.
I'm not expecting him to.
TV REPORTER: You're looking
at the U.N. Plaza gardens
and the podium from which
all three co-sponsors
of the peace treaty
will address the public
following a private signing
ceremony inside the U.N.'s
Council Chamber.
Russian President Yuri Suvarov,
the third co-sponsor
of the treaty,
is en route to the U.N.
where he will join
President Taylor
and acting IRK President
Dalia Hassan...
(computer alarm chimes)
(alarm chiming stops)
(knocking) COLE: Mr. Ricker,
this is Agent
Ortiz, CTU!
Open that door.
(gun cocking)
Before you pull that trigger,
there's something
you ought to know.
I don't place a call
in 15 minutes,
every intelligence agency in the
country gets alerted about you.
Weapon charges alone
will get you locked up
for the duration,
Or you can help us
find Jack Bauer,
and we'll keep our mouths shut.
You think you're protecting him?
The order on Jack Bauer
is shoot to kill.
He knew what
he was getting himself into.
Jack's not thinking straight.
Look, I read
your file.
I know Jack saved your life
in Damascus.
This is your opportunity
to pay back that debt.
You know how this
is gonna end, right?
Do you?
If Jack dies today,
it's on you.
Hey.
Wait a minute.
(garbled radio transmission)
Thanks, Adam.
(text alert tone)
Director O'Brian,
Agent Burke.
I have the revised security
assessment for you.
Ma'am, I noticed that
Agent Ortiz's name
was back on the duty
roster. That's right.
He was arrested for
helping Jack Bauer.
I got him a temporary clearance
so he could help us out here.
He was the one who designed
the U.N. protocols
in the first place.
I know.
Do you really think
we can trust him?
I wouldn't have gotten him
a release if I didn't.
(phone ringing)
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
(Burke clears throat)
What happened?
COLE:
Not good, Chloe.
I think Jack's
targeting Suvarov.
Is that what Ricker said?
Yeah. Jack planted a bug
on Charles Logan,
overheard a conversation
between the two men.
Turns out Suvarov's the
one who gave the order
for Renee to be killed.
(sighs)
Does Ricker have a recording
of that conversation?
No. He wiped his system clean
as soon as he saw me coming.
But the surveillance rig
he gave Jack records everything
to a backup,
so Jack has a copy.
Good. We're
gonna need it.
Why?
The White House
just arrested Meredith Reed.
They confiscated a data card
from her.
Dana's evidence.
Exactly. The recording
that Jack has
is the only proof
we have now.
(sighs)
Chloe, I don't know
that getting proof is
our first priority anymore.
We have to put an alert out
on Jack.
If we do that, then Pillar
will get to him first.
He'll kill Jack,
and he'll destroy the recording.
Chloe, we
can't stand by
and let Jack assassinate
the president of Russia.
No, but we can
buy ourselves time.
Can change Suvarov's
motorcade route,
sequester him in the U.N.
Make it impossible
for Jack to get to him.
Yeah, except Suvarov's gonna
be standing at that podium soon,
and once he's exposed like that,
we can't protect him.
That's not happening
for over an hour.
If we haven't found Jack
by then,
then we can put out the alert.
It's still taking a big risk,
Chloe.
I know.
All right,
get Suvarov's route changed.
But you're putting me
in charge of his security
as soon as he gets to the U.N.
How far out are you?
I'll be there in ten.
(car engine starting)
(tires squeak)
(garbled radio transmission)
Okay.
Sir, the flash
about Novakovich is going out.
You wanted to speak with the
president before that happened.
Ah.
(exhales)
Thank you, Jason.
Oh, um...
do we know anything about Bauer?
No. Nothing.
If you don't mind
me asking, sir.
What are you going
to tell the president?
I think it's time she...
she knows everything.
All the delegates
are present
with the exception of Suvarov,
who's still in transit.
He'll be given the details
once he arrives. (phone ringing)
Excuse me, Tim.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm about to go
into the protocol meeting.
What's going on?
I wanted you to hear this news
from me first.
What news?
I tried to
insulate you as long as I could,
preserve your plausible
deniability, but...
Just tell me what
you're talking about, Charles.
Jack Bauer isn't just trying
to gather evidence
about the conspiracy.
He's...
He's seeking retribution.
Go on.
Bauer just murdered
Mikhail Novakovich,
along with a good
number of his staff.
(whispering): So Novakovich was
responsible for the assassination
of President Hassan?
Yes. Yes, ma'am.
Novakovich was
the ranking member
of the Russian Delegation.
President Suvarov is going
to demand an explanation.
Actually, he's not.
Are you telling me
that Hassan's murder goes
all the way up to Suvarov?
Yes.
But the good news is
that Bauer doesn't know that.
How can you be sure?
Because according to a witness,
Bauer killed Novakovich
before he could talk.
And aside from me, Novakavich
is the only person who ever knew
that Suvarov
was calling the shots.
Madam President,
Bauer's finished
what he started,
an-and Suvarov will be happy
to sweep this under the rug.
An-and the peace agreement
can go forward
as planned.
This is...
Really, we couldn't have
asked for a better outcome.
Except that I am asking
Dalia Hassan to shake hands
with her husband's murderer.
Madam President...
Call Suvarov.
Tell him that I am aware
of his involvement in this,
and that I will see him
at the signing.
(snaps cell phone shut)
My apologies.
Thank you for waiting.
How did the call go?
I told the president
about Suvarov's
involvement, and, um...
she understood- not that
she has an alternative.
Well, that's
good news, sir.
PILLAR: Your new Secret
Service detail's here
to escort you to the U.N.
Thank you, Jason.
It's been a long
road, but, uh...
(chuckles):
we're almost there.
(Logan groans)
(slaps car twice)
(phone auto-dialing)
Anything new on Bauer?
A security camera picked him up
leaving Novakovich's hotel.
Confirmed what Berkov told us.
Bauer was definitely wounded
during the attack.
How badly?
Badly enough that he's
gonna need treatment.
Getting alerts out
to medical facilities now.
All right, also let
Port Authority and INS know
Bauer might be trying
to get out of the country.
We'll find him- it's
only a question of time.
Maybe a little quicker
than you thought.
Slowly, take your weapon out
and pass it back to me.
Slowly.
Start the car and drive.
You saw what
I did to Pavel.
I didn't have
a lot of time with him.
You, I've got all the time
in the world.
So you either do what I say,
or I will take you apart
piece by piece.
Now, drive!
(panting)
Where are we going?
The U.N.
Why? You already
got what you wanted.
You killed
everyone involved.
Save your breath.
I know about President Suvarov.
Your delegations will be joining
you at the reception
after the post-signing ceremony.
And finally, on behalf
of the U.N. staff,
I would like to say
that we are all
honored to be part
of this historic occasion.
Thank you for your time.
Your daughter's been waiting
inside to speak to you.
She says
it's important.
(exhales)
Let her know
I'll be right there.
Yes, ma'am.
Madam President.
I have something for you.
It's from Omar.
He wanted to
give it to you
to sign the agreement, and...
I'm grateful that I can
do so on his behalf.
It reads:
"All religions,
"all this singing,
"one song,
peace be with you."
It is a verse
Omar would quote
from Rumi
when he was talking about what
you and he were trying to achieve.
Thank you for
seeing this through
and for helping us all
do justice to his memory.
Dalia, I am...
I am honored.
I'm very honored.
Th
Kayla, what is it?
Meredith Reed called
the residence looking for you.
I am not interested in
that woman's condolences.
That is not
why she called.
She says she
has information
about the people who are
behind Father's murder.
But we know who was behind
your father's death-
extremists in our country.
(whispers): She claims
that they had outside hKYp.
That the Russians were involved.
Why would she say such a thing?
Does she have evidence,
or is this just a rumor?
I don't know, but it can't have
been easy for her to call you.
I don't think she would have
done so because of a rumor.
What else did she say?
She wouldn't say anything more
until she talked to you.
She left her number.
Let's call her
from the residence.
(indistinct radio transmissions)
Ann, President Suvarov's
motorcade is delayed
five minutes because
of the new route- put out
an all-agency.
How do you want it coded?
Eyes only.
Yes, ma'am.
(sighs)
Lanza, make sure
Burke reports here
with a set of tactical gear
for Agent Ortiz. Yes, ma'am.
Arlo's at CTU, running
the surveillance video
through facial recognition
software.
Still no sign of Jack.
Look, I've been thinking.
Let's say we do get this
recording from Jack.
What are we supposed
to do with it?
I mean, if the
president's willing
to lock down
Meredith Reed...
She can't shut down
every media outlet in the world,
which is where
we're gonna send this file.
We're also gonna send it to every
government employee in the country.
Legislative,
military, judiciary-
that's over
a hundred thousand people.
How are we doing this?
By using CTU servers,
we can distribute it
simultaneously to everyone.
President Taylor won't
be able to stop the truth
from getting out.
Burke.
Good to see yo
Sir.
Did you use the
revised protocol
for President Suvarov's arrival?
Yes, ma'am.
We're now bringing the motorcade
into the FDR Drive ramp. Good.
Make sure that Agent Ortiz
has the revised protocols.
He's back in charge.
Let's take a look.
We're going
to the Hart Building.
I want you to park underground.
This guard's life
is in your hands.
You make one move that
I don't like, I'm gonna
kill you both,
you understand?
Jason Pillar.
There's no one inside.
They left the building
two hours ago.
Yeah, I'm just running
a last-minute
security check.
Of course, sir.
Is there anything
else, sir?
No. Thank you.
Drive.
(grunting quietly)
(panting)
Pull in over here.
Slowly, with
your right hand,
take the keys
out of the ignition
and pass them back.
Get out of the car.
(panting)
Now!
Close the door.
Put your hands
on the roof.
Don't you move.
Suvarov's not gonna be out on
the podium for another hour.
You're not gonna
make it that long,
not the way you're bleeding.
(panting)
Slowly,
back up towards me.
Stop. Turn around.
Good.
You're gonna
suture me up.
(groans)
You try and make
a move on me,
the slightest twitch,
I will put a bullet
in your brain.
You got it?
Yes.
(groans)
(Jack panting)
(gasps)
I don't understand
something.
You've spent your entire career
working outside the system;
you've always had a good reason.
But this...
it's just blood lost.
You're destroying an agreement
that took years to put together.
An agreement made by
murderers and liars.
(gasps)
Murderers?
You're the one killing
people in cold blood.
Everybody I took out had
a hand in today's attack.
But who makes you
judge and jury?
President Taylor,
when she agreed
to the cover-up.
I would have accepted
justice by law...
but that was taken away
from me by people like you.
So you're right-
I am judge and jury.
Now, step back.
Turn around.
Start to move back
towards the car.
Look, I came in after
Hassan and Renee were killed.
I didn't have anything to do
with that, you have to believe me.
Get on your knees! Please,
Bauer, I'm telling you the truth.
I've got a family;
I've got a little girl.
Shut up.
Please...
(muttering): I'm
telling you the truth.
(grunts)
(loud thump)
(panting)
(yells)
Still no answer.
Are you sure this is
Meredith Reed's number?
It's the number she gave me.
Then why isn't she answering?
I just talked to Gary
Klausner, Ms. Reed's editor.
He doesn't know where she is
and has no way to reach her.
He seemed very anxious
to get off the phone.
Where are you going?
President Taylor and I
are supposed
to be sitting across the table
from Yuri Suvarov
in less than an hour.
If his government was involved
in murdering your father,
President Taylor needs to know.
TV NEWS ANCHOR: Following
the death of Omar Hassan,
President Suvarov
was reportedly pessimistic
about the viability
of the peace treaty.
But rumors of
a Russian withdrawal
were soon dismissed
by the White House,
and President Suvarov
is expected
to arrive at the U.N. shortly.
(knocking)
Yes?
Excuse me,
Madam President.
It's Dalia Hassan.
I'll have to call her back.
She's outside, ma'am.
She says it's urgent.
Send her in.
(clears throat)
(footsteps approaching)
(sighs)
Madam President, forgive me.
I have just heard something
that is very
disturbing.
What did you hear?
That the Russian government,
or people within
the Russian government,
were involved
in the murder
of my husband.
Where did you hear this?
My daughter
received a phone call
from the journalist,
Meredith Reed.
Have you spoken
with her yourself?
No.
I've tried everything,
but I've been
unable to reach her.
I came here to ask for
your help finding Miss Reed.
I need to know
if there is any truth
in what she said.
Dalia, we heard a rumor
about the Russians
being involved as well.
And you didn't tell me?
No. Because we looked into it
and found that there was
nothing backing it up.
It was just
a frivolous accusation.
Whatever else she may be,
Meredith Reed is not
a frivolous woman.
She came to me,
someone she knew would have
every reason to doubt her.
(clears throat)
Dalia...
I know that you want answers...
but we are signing the agreement
in less than an hour.
Madam President, I feel like
you're not listening to me.
Before I sign a treaty
with people who may have
murdered my husband,
I need help finding this woman.
Please.
I will do the best I can
in the time that we have left.
I don't think
I'm making myself clear.
Until I determine
if her allegations are true,
I will not sign this treaty.
Dalia...
please, be reasonable.
This is my position,
Madam President.
I will not change my mind.
(inhales and exhales loudly)
Then you...
You leave me no choice.
I had Meredith Reed arrested.
Why?
Because her allegations
would be too damaging.
That doesn't make any sense.
You wouldn't arrest someone
for making
false allegations.
Unless they aren't false.
You knew!
You knew the Russians
were behind my husband's death,
and you said nothing?!
Dalia,
I am so sorry.
(sighs)
It-it was an
im-impossible situation.
(sighs)
I was trying to protect you.
Protect me?
You betrayed me!
Dalia, we are about
to complete the most important
diplomatic action
in generations.
Your husband
sacrificed his life to preserve
this agreement...
How dare you invoke my husband!
He never would have stood
for this!
This treaty happened
because he trusted you.
And even though every fiber
in my being wanted to go home
and grieve, I carried on
because I trusted you.
But not anymore.
I will not make peace
with the people
who murdered my husband.
Or with you.
There will be
no agreement.
I will be entering
a formal complaint
with the United Nations,
demanding that you
release Ms. Reed,
and disclose whatever
evidence you've kept from me
and from the rest of the world!
Stop!
In one hour, you will stand
beside me
in the council chamber,
and you will sign the treaty
your husband and I agreed to.
I will not!
You will!
Because if you don't,
my administration will disclose
hard, indisputable evidence
that agents inside
your intelligence service
attempted to detonate
a nuclear device
on our soil,
which will give me
all the justification I need
to retaliate against the IRK
with the full force
of the American military.
It will be decades before
your country recovers.
But it doesn't need
to come to that.
All you have to do
is sign the agreement.
Dalia?!
(door slams)
(clattering)
(panting)
First they murder my husband,
and now this woman
who has lied to me
is threatening my country!
(panting)
I don't see a way out of this,
Madam President.
We can tell the world
what these Russian bastards did,
and how President Taylor
protected them.
We can take our case
directly to The Hague.
There is no case.
No proof to support any
of these accusations.
More important,
there are President Taylor's
threats to consider.
We cannot dismiss them.
Our military can protect us
from incursion.
And if necessary, we can
reactivate our nuclear program!
Giving your husband's enemies
exactly what they wanted
in the first place.
In addition to providing her
with even more of an excuse
to launch a preemptive
military strike against us.
I don't care what President
Taylor said; she wouldn't dare.
Can you really take that chance?
(phone rings)
Yes?
Thank you.
Yuri Suvarov's delegation
will be arriving any moment.
President Taylor is expecting
you there to greet him.
(panting)
CHLOE:
Agent Ortiz?
What's going on?
I spoke with Arlo.
He got a facial recognition hit
on Jack.
Where?
Inside our perimeter.
He's here, Cole.
He's been
careful to avoid
all the security cameras,
but Arlo found this.
It's from the 22nd floor
of the Hart Building
across the street from the U.N.
The software picked up
his reflection.
How did he get
into the building?
According to the logs,
the only person
that entered the building within
the past 20 minutes was Pillar.
Jack must have
taken him hostage.
The windows on the east side
of the building give him
a clean line of sight
down onto the podium.
I'm going to
go find him.
I'm going with you.
You can't.
It would just
cause a fight.
I'm the only one that Jack will
listen to. And what if he doesn't?
(sighs)
Give me 20 minutes.
If you don't
hear from me,
we'll follow through
with our plan.
Sound the alarm about Jack
and secure Suvarov.
20 minutes.
Okay.
And keep your comm open.
I want to know what's
going on. I can't.
CTU is monitoring
all frequencies.
It's too risky.
All right.
At least take this.
Thanks.
Be careful.
(switch clicks)
(computer chirps)
Where's O'Brian headed?
She's running a last-minute
perimeter sweep.
By herself?
Keep a real-time uplink open
with Suvarov's security people.
Let me know
when it's up and running.
Yes, sir.
(sighs)
Okay.
(beeps)
Hey.
(sighs)
As long as I can remember,
every time
I've had to talk to you,
it seems,
for one reason or another,
I've started out
by telling you how sorry I am.
I'm not going to do that
to you now.
You're going to hear a lot
of stories
about what I've done today.
Some of them may even be true.
But no one, and I mean no one
can tell you why I did
what I did except for me.
And a lot of good people died
today.
Not just President Hassan.
Operatives from CTU, members of
other law enforcement agencies.
ReneWalker.
Who I was very close to.
Yes?
Thank you.
President Suvarov's motorcade
has just rounded the corner.
Was Mrs. Hassan notified
of his arrival?
I believe
so, ma'am.
Yes or no, Tim?
Which is it?
Is she coming or not?
Why wouldn't she be?
♪ ♪
President Taylor,
that we are all here together
is a tribute
to your persistence.
Mrs. Hassan, I am
sorry for your loss.
I admired your husband
very much.
We're wanted upstairs
for the press conference.
Yes, of course.
Mr. President.
Dalia, I know that this is
very difficult for you.
There is nothing left
for either of us to say,
Madam President.
(garbled radio transmission)
Chloe O'Brian,
Director of CTU.
Yes, ma'am.
Master key and building
schematics you requested.
(beeps)
(applause)
Good afternoon,
fellow delegates
and ladies and gentlemen
of the press.
The last 24 hours have been
the most difficult in this
long and challenging road
that we've all traveled together
to reach this moment.
Now, the eyes
of the entire world are looking
to the leaders
standing here with me now, ready
to usher in a new era
of transparency, honesty
and trust.
President Taylor,
President Hassan
President Suvarov
have each risen
to this challenge
for the sake of world peace.
And the treaty
that they have created together
represents the culmination
of their courageous efforts.
(applause)
Agent Burke?
Sir.
I need you to assemble
a ten-man squad
and deploy them to Sector C-7.
The Hart Building, sir? We
already have men on post there.
Not nearly enough
if there's a threat
anywhere along that corridor.
Keep your men
outside the building
until you hear otherwise.
Yes, sir.
(sighs)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(gasps)
What the hell
are you doing here?
You don't have to kill Suvarov.
There's another way.
Who else knows
where I am?
Please listen.
Who else knows?!
Cole and Arlo.
If I don't get you
out of here
in ten minutes,
Cole's gonna send in
every agent we have.
(panting)
Jack, they're going
to kill you.
There's a standing order
to shoot you on sight.
I couldn't let that happen.
You shouldn't have come
after me.
You're my friend.
I didn't have a choice.
Neither do I.
(gagging)
Don't fight it.
(coughs)
(gasping for air)
(gasping stops)
(Jack sighs)
(rifle cocking)
(phone ringing)
Jason, you watching this?
Jason?
JACK: I have a five-five-six rifle
pointed straight at your head.
Bauer.
The bullet travels
2,900 feet per second.
If you try and move,
you're a dead man.
Which means you need to
do exactly what I say.
Do you understand?
(gasps)
Uh, Jack, I told you
everything I know.
And you thought I believed you?
(recorder clicks on)
LOGAN (on tape):
And aside from me,
Novakovich was the only one
who knew that Suvarov
was calling the shots.
(recorder clicks off)
What do you want?
I want you to call
President Suvarov
and have him meet you
where you are as soon as
the press conference is over.
What am I supposed to tell him?
Try the truth for a change.
Tell him
you've got credible intelligence
about a threat to his life.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net