Transcript by www.addic7ed.com
Someone needs to take the reins
of the IRK government.
Someone who believes
in the same ideals
and principles as Omar Hassan
and who shares his strength.
If it is the will of my people,
I will take my husband's place
at the peace conference.
Did you find him,
President Taylor--
the man who killed my father?
Samir Mehran, yes.
He was badly wounded,
but he'll live to stand trial.
I took care of him.
So there is no connection to us.
We're in the clear?
Maybe not.
There was a woman there
who might have
recognized me.
What woman?
She may be CTU.
I'm not sure,
but I've seen her face before.
Once again,
Mr. Novakovich,
you're giving
every indication that
Russia has no interest
in this peace ac
I don't understand
how you can believe that
installing Hassan's widow
will alleviate our concerns
about the instability
of the IRK government.
I have close friends in Moscow.
Do you honestly think
your relationships
can change their minds?
Let's just say I'm going to be
able to exercise some leverage.
Jack thinks that
someone inside of CTU
is working for the terrorists.
I spoke to Hastings.
He cleared me through.
Stay where you are and keep
your hands where I can...
She just entered
the parking garage.
Who are you, you lying bitch?
Don't move.
Renee!
You were on the phone
with her right before
she got shot.
What were you talking about?
Samir Mehran was given
a lethal injection at the scene
of his capture.
Renee thought she recognized
one of the EMTs from her days
undercover with the Russian mob.
I, I've got to get back to you.
I'm sorry.
She didn't make it.
Sir?
Sir, I'm so sorry,
but we need to move her now.
Sir, are you the husband
of the deceased?
No.
Well, we need to contact
her next of kin.
Can you help us with that?
Do you know where
her parents live?
Are they alive?
I don't know.
Sir, are you gonna be
all right?
I don't know if these will fit.
I got them from an intern.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Jack, I heard about Renee.
I'm so sorry.
What can I do to help?
Tell me who did this.
You told me earlier
Renee thought she
recognized someone
at Hassan's crime scene.
An EMT?
Let us deal with that.
We have everyone here
working on it.
Don't try and handle me,
Chloe, not now.
Who did she see?
She thought
she recognized somebody
from the Russian mob--
Red Square.
Bazhaev's group?
Right.
I want to talk to him.
Like I said, I'm already on it.
He's in custody
somewhere, Chloe.
I brought him in myself.
Where is he?
There's something
that you need to know.
Division replaced Hastings...
with me.
That means I'm responsible
for what happens to Bazhaev.
I know you're upset about Renee.
So am I.
But Bazhaev's our only lead.
I need whoever talks to him
to be in complete control.
I don't think
that's you right now.
I won't interfere
with your investigation.
You think
you can stick to that?
I give you my word.
Chloe, I'm gonna ask
you one more time:
Where is he?
He's in federal court downtown.
He's being arraigned right now.
Plan was for this chamber
to be full by now.
Ethan, what in the world
are you doing here?
You should be resting.
The doctor said
it was my call.
Ethan...
I'm fine.
I was thinking,
Madam President,
our discussion
about enlisting Charles Logan.
It's done.
You've contacted him already?
He's on his way to talk
to the Russian Foreign Minister.
Whew! That was fast.
The Russians
were about to announce
they were pulling out
of the talks.
I didn't see
a lot of options.
So,
what's his angle?
Madam President,
you said he's on his way
to talk to Novakovich.
How does he intend
to get the Russians to stay?
I assume he uncovered something
in his business
dealings with them.
But you don't know what it is?
Not exactly.
Madam President,
he's operating in your name.
Shouldn't we find out?
I agreed I wouldn't.
Don't ask, don't tell was the
price for Logan's cooperation.
Mikhail!
Mr. President.
The Russian people join you
in mourning President Hassan.
His death was a tragedy
for all peace-loving nations.
You can save your platitudes.
You want the truth.
Why not... for a change?
Espresso.
I assume President Taylor
sent you here
to bring my country back
to the bargaining table.
She is going to be disappointed.
President Taylor lured the whole
world here with the promise
that Hassan had united the IRK,
that there would be peace
for the first time in decades.
Well, now it is clear
that was a lie.
There was no unity
even with Hassan,
and now that he is gone...
...his widow Dalia can pick up
the mantle.
Not in our estimation.
Hassan was undone
by his own opposition.
How could his widow possibly
succeed where he failed?
'Cause we both know
the opposition that undid him
had outside help.
Nuclear threats,
assassination plots
against a heavily guarded
head of state.
This was not some
Third World malcontents
lashing out.
This was a highly
organized effort
orchestrated by a major rival
to the United States,
a rival convinced
that their best interest
was to stop the peace process
by killing Hassan.
If you are insinuating...
Insinuating, no.
I'm saying it was people
inside your government,
first among them you.
That is an
outrageous accusation.
It's a fact
for which I have proof.
I don't believe you.
Well, that's your right.
But I'll tell you this:
you don't want to test me.
Because what I have, I will
share with President Taylor
if you and I fail
to come to an
understanding here.
Espresso, sir.
At this point President Taylor
knows nothing about any of this.
I didn't see what
good could come out
of inflaming the situation
between our countries further,
not without talking
to you first.
And now I have.
The president's expecting me
at the UN.
I need to go.
What will you tell her?
What I'd would like
to tell her is
that Russia is back at the table
and her peace process
is on track.
But if neither of us
hears from you
before I get there,
I'm afraid what I'll have
to tell her instead
is the unvarnished truth.
"Sergei...
Buh-zay-off."
Bazhaev, Your Honor.
We'd like to waive reading.
I'm sure you would,
given the charges here.
I can tell you right now
I'm gonna deny bail.
Judge Ruffin, Sergei Bazhaev
is a businessman
with deep ties
to this community.
He's a foreign national.
That's true, Your Honor,
but he has lived
in this country continuously
since 1985.
His entire family lives here.
In fact, several members
of his family are represented
in court today:
his wife,
daughter-in-law, grandson,
for whom incidentally he is
the sole means of support.
According to the charges,
he's their sole support
because he killed
the boy's father,
not to mention the other counts:
trafficking in
nuclear materials,
assassination, conspiracy.
Like I said,
I'm going to deny bail.
I'm remanding him
to Marion immediately.
Your Honor, may I have five
minutes with my client, please?
Fine. You have five minutes.
Court will recess
for 30 minutes.
Clear the courtroom, please.
My client would like
to have a word with you.
If you touch my family,
I swear to God I...
You're not really sitting in
the right chair
to be making threats.
Who shot Renee Walker?
I don't know that name.
She was a former FBI Agent.
Approximately six years ago,
she worked undercover
in your organization.
Earlier today, she recognized
one of your men as Red Square.
There is no Red Square.
Not anymore.
Let me explain myself.
This Agent, Renee Walker--
I considered her
to be my family.
So take a long hard look
into my eyes
and realize that I will have
no problem taking out
each member of yours
before they even get home today
unless I get
the information I want.
Whoever killed her
had nothing to do with me.
Enjoy your time at Marion.
I'll tell your wife and your
daughter-in-law you said hello.
Wait.
Wait!
If I tell you,
they'll kill my family anyway.
We'll provide them
with witness protection.
I give you my word.
Moscow.
The Russian government--
they're behind it, not me.
Everything that happened today,
all of it, was them.
Who inside the government?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know? You're talking
about 100,000 people.
I need names.
I don't know names.
They never let me get close.
The woman working for them
arranged everything.
What woman?
The one they planted at CTU.
Dana Walsh.
Sir, let's go.
You promised.
Nerve-wracking, isn't it?
Waiting.
I only saw
Novakovich's face, sir,
but you definitely
had his attention.
It's the president.
Charles Logan.
Charles.
Yes, Madam President.
I just got off the phone with
the Russian foreign minister.
You did?
And what did he say?
He said that the two of you had
a very interesting discussion.
And that he would be coming to
the United Nations in five hours
with the Russian premier
to sign the treaty
as scheduled.
He also said the credit for that
is all yours.
Oh, uh, he was in the mood to be
convinced, Madam President.
Mr. President,
Ethan Kanin here.
So you're back on your feet.
Yes.
And I'm curious.
What did you say
to the Russian minister
to convince him
to come back to the peace talks?
I told him that peace
is in all of our interests.
Seriously,
I'd like to know how you did it.
Madam President,
those-those details
are for me alone.
That was our agreement.
Am I right?
Yes, you are.
So, Ethan, um,
let's not do anything
to-to sully our victory.
And it is a victory.
For all of us.
It's a good feeling, isn't it?
What?
Being of service.
To your country.
Yes, it is.
I'll see you at the UN shortly.
O'Brian.
Hey, it's me.
Bazhaev's family
just left the courthouse.
They're going to need
witness protection.
I want you to pick them up
and bring them in.
What did he say?
He said the people who
are behind Renee's murder
weren't Russian mob.
Said they were people
inside the Russian government.
He claims that Moscow is behind
everything that happened today.
I thought the IRK opposition
was trying to stop Hassan.
No, he said the Russians
were just using them.
He didn't have time to explain
why they don't want the
peace accord to go through,
but he did say
something important.
He said Moscow's main contact
on the ground was Dana Walsh.
Dana? You believe that?
That would explain
how she managed to breach CTU.
Anyways, I'm on my way in.
I want to talk to her.
I'll set it up.
Thanks.
Cole, I need your help.
Jack's on his way here
to interview Dana.
Dana? What about?
According to Jack,
she's some kind of Agent
with the Russian government.
He says they're
behind everything
that happened today,
including Renee's murder.
Listen,
if Dana knows who killed Renee
or Jack thinks
she's in any way responsible,
there's no telling
what he might do.
Jack respects you.
You might be the only one
who can deal with things
if he gets out of hand.
I know this is difficult
for you,
but during the questioning...
Yeah, I'll be there.
Thanks.
It's good to be back
in the game,
even if it is
through the rear entrance.
President Taylor's worried
about her image.
Huh, believe me,
I of all people understand that.
She can't keep you
hidden away forever, sir.
That's right.
Credit given
where credit is due.
Publicly.
That's our deal.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
No, no, believe me,
the president will
be grateful to know.
Okay.
Who is that Agent?
I want him reassigned.
Sir, that was one
of my contacts
at Justice just...
Did you hear me?!
Yes.
I'll take care of it.
But we have a more
immediate problem:
Jack Bauer.
Bauer?
What does he have to do
with any of this?
He was just downtown at
the federal courthouse,
the arraignment
of a Sergei Bazhaev.
Bauer got to him behind closed
doors and got him to talk.
How much does
this Bazhaev know?
He knows about
Dana Walsh, the mole
the Russians planted at CTU.
I know who she is.
Bauer's headed to CTU,
presumably to talk to her.
Sir, my sources tell me
Walsh hasn't given up anything
about Moscow's involvement.
Not yet.
But she knows enough
to bring everything down.
If she gets in a room
with Bauer...
Obviously, that can't happen.
We need to stop Bauer
before he talks to her.
That won't be easy.
He may have a personal
stake in this.
Apparently, he was asking
Bazhaev about a Renee Walker.
She was shot dead
in Bauer's apartment
less than an hour ago.
Sir, this could easily
get out of hand.
You may need to ask
President Taylor to intervene.
What are you suggesting,
that I tell her the truth?
If she finds out
what the Russians have done,
she'll be furious
I kept her out of it.
She might back out of our deal.
Sir, you really need
to stop Bauer now.
I don't see any other way.
You have to talk
to the president.
Bauer torpedoed my presidency.
Tried to ruime; almost did.
There's no way I'm gonna
let that happen again.
Thank you.
Dana Walsh ready?
Yes, I'll take you to her.
I'm so sorry about Renee.
I don't even know what to say.
Dana know I'm going to be
interrogating her?
No, I didn't want
to give her a heads-up.
Good.
Jack.
I'm sorry about Renee.
I have to leave
the cameras on, Jack.
You think I'm gonna kill her?
I wouldn't blame you if you did.
If I wanted her dead, Chloe,
she'd be dead.
I'm just gonna wake her
up to the idea of it.
Open the door.
What do you want?
I want to know
who killed Renee Walker.
Renee's dead?
Yeah.
That doesn't make any sense.
It... it must have
been a mistake.
No mistake.
I'm sorry... Jack.
Really.
You're sorry?
I want to know
who the shooter was!
I want to know ordered it!
I want names now!
Stop him!
Let it play, Chloe.
You hit me, and you get nothing.
You think you get
to make demands here?
I can give you the hitter,
the man behind him,
all the way up to the top.
I want more
than just names. I want proof!
I have proof:
an audio file, film.
Where?
First I want
my immunity deal back.
Soon as I start talking,
I'm dead.
Your move, Jack.
If you lie to me...
I'll find you
no matter where
you try and hide.
You understand that?
Good.
We've had such little good news
these last few hours,
I wanted to tell you
right away.
The delegates have voted
unanimously to accept you
as the representative
of the IRK
at the signing of the treaty.
I'm pleased.
Thank you for all your efforts.
You're welcome.
There is one proviso,
of course.
That my own country accept me
as signatory of the treaty.
I know you've had
very little time
to pursue this.
Jamot and I have
been making progress.
In the next hour,
our constituent assembly
will vote on the issue,
but as we've already received
pledges of loyalty
from most
of my husband's coalition,
I believe we have a good chance
of success.
Excellent. Dalia,
we might just make it yet.
We might.
Madam President,
Mrs. Hassan.
I need a word.
Excuse me.
Logan wants to speak with you.
About what?
He wouldn't say
except that it's urgent.
He's waiting in your office.
Following President Hassan's
death, the expectation was
that the delegates
to the peace conference
would have to pack up
and go home,
but the latest rumors
coming out of the UN
are pretty sensational: that
Dalia Hassan might be stepping
into her husband's shoes.
In fact, there are already
street demonstrations
taking place in Kamistan
in support
of Dalia Hassan's candidacy.
Does this mean the...
Mr. Logan,
the president is here.
Thank you.
We don't know, but...
Thank you for seeing me,
Madam President.
Ethan said you wanted
to speak with me.
Um, can we have
the room, please?
What's this about, Charles?
Jack Bauer--
he's out of control.
He's already pressured
a Russian mafioso
in federal court,
and now he's on
his way to question a woman
in custody at CTU: Dana Walsh.
Why does he want to talk to her?
He thinks she knows who's behind
the, uh, the shooting
of a Renee Walker.
Agent Walker?
She's dead?
How did this happen?
That's still being
investigated,
but in the meantime,
what I'm saying is
Bauer needs to be stopped.
Why?
You're going
to have to trust me.
What we need to do right now is
lock Bauer down.
You better tell me exactly
what's going on.
Madam President...
No!
I won't do a thing
about Jack Bauer
until you tell me the truth.
Elements inside the Russian
government were behind
both the asssination
of President Hassan
and the supply
of nuclear material
to his enemies.
The Russian government?
Why do you think
they're back at the table?
Because I threatened to expose
their role in today's events.
You knew about this
and you didn't tell anyone?
I was trying
to protect the president.
Protect her?!
You've compromised her
hopelessly!
Why didn't you say anything
before?
I told you that I had leverage
with the Russians.
You-you must have understood
it was significant.
Significant, yes!
Evidence of a sex scandal,
some kind of
financial malfeasance,
not this, for God's sake!
If I find that you were
in a position to prevent
anything...
Absolutely not.
This information came to me
only very recently.
From whom?
I can't tell you.
You will tell me.
I can't, Madam President,
because it would do no good.
My sources would plausibly deny
even knowing me.
The Russian involvement--
that's what Jack Bauer is about
to bring out into the open?
If he talks to Dana Walsh, yes.
The Russians
inserted her at CTU
months ago.
She was their Agent.
If Bauer gets to her,
it will all come out,
and then, and then
this, this
will all be finished.
It's finished anyways.
Do you think the president
wants anything more to do
with the Russians
after what they've done?
Yes, yes, you do,
Madame President,
because you are
looking at the bigger picture,
the greater good.
How can you call
any of this good?!
Because it is good,
an undeniable good!
A peace that's escaped
the world for generations!
That's what you're on
the verge of achieving.
Do you really want
to throw it all away?
Do you really think
Dalia Hassan will sit down
at the table
with the people
who murdered her husband?
Who says she has to know?
Believe me, I know
how hard you worked for this,
how you sweated and prayed,
the sleepless nights.
I know.
The power
to make a difference-- that's
why we came into politics.
How few of us
get to achieve it,
but you have...
You so nearly have.
Ethan will tell you
to make a stand.
I applaud his-his
moral clarity,
but then he's on the sidelines.
He can afford it.
That's enough!
Is the situation ideal? No!
Far from it,
but you have a real chance
to make the world
a better place.
Don't listen to this, Allison.
If the treaty's not signed
today, it's not the end.
You can build a better peace,
with honest partners.
"There is a tide
in the affairs of men,
which, taken at the flood,
leads on to fortune."
What the hell does that mean?
The president knows.
It's from Julius Caesar.
It means "Now or never."
Madam President,
I have Jack Bauer for you.
Where is he?
He's at CTU.
He wants to talk to you
about an immunity agreement
for a Dana Walsh.
I'll have to call him back.
Yes, ma'am.
Madam President,
there is no choice here.
But there is a choice, Ethan,
and unfortunately,
only I can make it.
I'm going to CTU.
To do what?
To see Jack Bauer.
Has the president
called back yet?
Not yet.
Jack, are you sure
you want to do this to yourself?
We can take it from here.
The minute Dana's immunity deal
is back in place,
we can roll up the names,
close this out.
I need to see this through.
Excuse me.
The president's
on the phone, line 3.
She asked for Chloe.
Madam President.
Ms. O'Brian,
I'm on my way to see you.
You're coming to CTU?
Yes, I'm almost there.
I need to talk to Jack Bauer.
Make sure he doesn't leave.
Yes, ma'am.
Let Security know the president
will be here any minute.
She's coming here?
That's what I just said.
Have them standing by.
Why's she doing this?
She said she wants
to talk to you.
Why doesn't she just talk to me
on the phone?
I don't know.
You should probably meet her
in Hastings' office.
Fine.
Madame President,
welcome to CTU.
I'm Chloe O'Brian.
Thank you, Ms. O'Brian.
Is Jack inside?
Right this way.
I want to say how grateful I am
for all your efforts today.
We've taken
some pretty hard hits,
but we've managed to keep
ourselves in the game.
The peace process
is still alive,
and I am counting on your hard
work and your vigilance
to keep it that way.
I know you won't let me down.
Thank you, Miss O'Brian.
Um, I'll go up alone.
Hello, Jack.
Madam President.
I am so sorry
about Agent Walker.
I gather she meant a lot to you.
Yes, ma'am.
Which makes what I'm about
to ask so very, very hard.
Please, Jack.
I need you to stand down.
I-I'm sorry. I don't understand.
I do not want you
to question Dana Walsh.
Madam President, the information
that I can extract
from Dana Walsh is not limited
to the murder of Renee Walker.
I believe she knows the names
of the people who facilitated
the assassination
of President Hassan,
people working within
the Russian government.
That is pure speculation.
Then grant her immunity.
Let me question her.
If she's lying,
you lose nothing.
I'm sorry. I won't give
Dana Walsh immunity.
I can't.
The peace process
is back on track.
Dalia Hassan will represent
her country at the signing.
The Russians have accepted her
and have undertaken
to support the treaty.
Madam President,
the Russians have been trying
to destroy the treaty.
You can't trust them.
You don't know that.
The information that I have
came from Sergei Bazhaev,
and I believe him.
If you let me question
Dana Walsh,
I can prove it to you.
No.
I won't allow it.
You don't want
to know the truth.
What I want is to keep
the Russians at the table.
Allegations of this sort
will drive them away.
What if the allegations
are true?
If I keep the Russians
at the table,
I can bring peace
to a part of the world
that has known nothing but war
for generations.
That is the greater good
that I am working toward.
And to achieve it,
there have to be sacrifices!
With all due respect,
Madam President,
these people gave
nuclear weapons to terrorists
who were willing to obliterate
half of Manhattan!
You don't know that!
And I'm telling you,
we have to move on.
Even Hassan's widow
has picked up the torch
and is continuing
the peace process.
Does she know the Russians
helped murder her husband?
Do you think she'd be
willing to sign that treaty
if she knew that?
Have you even told her?
That's enough.
Have you told her?!
I said that's enough!
This peace treaty
is in the interests
of the United States
and of the world.
That makes it a good in itself,
and certainly
more important than
your desire for revenge.
Madam President, I don't
want revenge; I want justice.
And I want peace.
If there were another way,
I would take it,
but there's not.
That's my decision.
Do you understand?
Do you understand, Jack?
Yes, ma'am.
I've arranged a helicopter
to fly you from CTU
to McGuire Air Force Base.
You're locking me down.
You'll be debriefed there.
Good-bye, Jack.
I'm sorry.
I had them gather your things.
Thanks.
What happened up there?
Nothing.
What do you mean?
I mean nothing.
Nothing happened.
What I need is a meeting
with Dalia Hassan
to coordinate our response
to the likely questions.
Will you set that up?
Thank you.
I'm leaving CTU now.
I'll be with you
in ten minutes.
They said you wanted to see me.
Yes.
Dana Walsh is to remain locked
down until further notice.
No one gets access
to her without
my express permission.
Is that clear?
I guess.
What about Jack?
Jack is going to McGuire
Air Force Base to be debriefed.
He didn't seem very happy
about that.
He was disappointed
that I wouldn't grant
Dana Walsh immunity
in exchange for her testimony.
But Dana knows who's responsible
for everything
that's happened today.
She is a sociopath.
She'll say anything.
And the last thing
we need right now
is a bunch of
unfounded allegations
derailing the peace that
we've all worked so hard for.
Do you understand, Chloe?
We're having a press conference
at the UN in two hours
to present Dalia Hassan
as the new leader of the IRK
and to announce that the
peace talks are still on track.
What we need CTU to do
is to make sure
security is airtight.
Yes, ma'am.
Tim Woods speaks
very highly of you.
When the situation
got out of control,
he was quite adamant
that you were the one
to take over.
I'm surprised
he even knows who I am.
It was a pleasure
to meet you finally, Chloe.
Thank you.
Cole, we're gonna be
back on UN detail.
What's happening with Dana?
As of now, nothing.
What about
the immunity agreement?
There isn't gonna be one.
Why not?
The president says that
Dana's a lying sociopath
who will wreck the peace treaty.
What's Jack say about that?
I don't know.
He's being choppered to McGuire
for debriefing.
Chloe, what the hell's going on?
There's gonna be
a press conference soon,
and the president needs us
to guarantee security.
You'll need to get
your teams ready.
Okay. Fine.
So Jack's being taken away
for a debrief?
About what, may I ask?
No.
Director O'Brian,
this is Falcon One.
We're touching down
at CTU, ma'am.
Copy that.
Security personnel en route
to the roof with Jack Bauer now.
Mr. Bauer,
Agent Winnick.
The White House has
instructed me to escort you
to McGuire Air Force
Base for a debrief.
Heard a lot about you, sir.
I'm sorry we had to meet
under these circumstances.
There's no reason to be sorry.
Get in this helicopter.
Tell your men to
drop their weapons
or you're gonna die.
Arlo, pull up the audio.
Something's happening.
Coming up.
Put your weapons down now!
I will kill him!
Everyone to the helipad.
All security
to the helipad now.
What the hell is going on?
He's gonna steal
that helicopter.
We have a hostage situation.
Out of the copter now!
Bauer took a hostage.
Hijacking the helicopter.
Hold your fire!
Lower your weapons!
Give me your walkie.
Jack.
Please land the chopper now.
Jack, you know I have
to call this in.
The Air Force will
force you down.
This is a bad idea.
Land the chopper
now.
Call the FAA, the Air Force.
Tell them we have
a stolen helicopter
flying West over Manhattan
that needs to be intercepted
and forced down.
Yes, ma'am.
Transcript by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net