As we gather together
for this great occasion,
we must not forget
that we all stand in the shadow
of Omar Hassan's
tragic death.
But...
the peace agreement we're
about to sign will be
his living memorial.
His courage brought us all
to this historic day,
and his vision
will continue to guide us
as we move into the future...
together.
So on behalf
of the people of Russia,
I extend the open hand
of friendship
to my partners in peace:
President Taylor,
President Hassan.
Thank you very much.
(reporters shouting questions)
SECRETARY GENERAL: There'll
be time for questions
after the signing
ceremony. Please, please.
DALIA: If there's
nothing more,
I will see you both
at the signing.
It appears I am not the only one
who does not want to be here.
Mrs. Hassan is distraught.
Understandably- her husband
was killed six hours ago.
Is that why she refuses
to look at me?
She knows.
A reporter told her
of your complicity
in her husband's murder.
Dalia came to me.
And you confirmed
this journalist's allegations.
I told her the truth.
And yet, knowing what she knows,
she's still here.
Mrs. Hassan understands
the benefits of peace.
Because you helped her
come to that understanding.
Excuse me, Madam President.
(speaking Russian)
Whatever it was you said
to Mrs. Hassan to keep her here
must have been very convincing.
Take your call, Yuri.
(speaking Russian)
Charles.
Yuri. We need to talk.
So talk.
Uh, it's a
sensitive matter;
something that, uh, that can't
be discussed on the phone.
All right.
SUVAROV:
Come to my suite.
LOGAN:
No. You need to come to mine.
SUVAROV:
Why?
LOGAN:
Just trust me, Yuri.
SUVAROV:
Trust you?
I don't need
to remind you
that it is in our
mutual self-interest
to make sure that certain
secrets stay secret.
Stop talking
in riddles, Charles.
I don't have
time for this.
There's a possible leak
inside of your camp,
which is why we need
to discuss this in my office.
I'll be right there.
(phone beeps)
I hope I was
convincing enough for you.
You're a world-class liar;
I would have expected
nothing else.
What exactly do you
think you're doing
by killing Suvarov?
Getting justice
for Renee Walker?
Yes, and for all the other
people that died today
trying to protect this country.
Now, sit at the desk
and keep the line open.
Jack, the audio file you
recorded- we can use it
to expose Suvarov.
We can use the CTU servers
to distribute it
to every government agency
and media outlet. President
Taylor's already censored the press.
NSA's putting up firewalls.
Arlo's working on getting
through them right now.
The president can't lock down
every media outlet.
(phone ringing)
That's Cole.
If I don't answer that,
he's sending a
TAC team in here.
It'll be too late.
I'm gonna finish
what I've started.
You've reached
Chloe O'Brian's voicemail.
Please leave a message.
(phone beeps off)
(indistinct radio chatter)
Delta groups, this is base.
Come in, Delta. This
is Delta One. Go ahead.
I need you to deploy
all available TAC units
to the 22nd floor
of the Hart Building.
I have intel on a possible sniper.
You got I.D. on this hostile?
Affirmative.
It's Jack Bauer.
With regard to Bauer, sir,
the standing order
is to use lethal force.
The order stands.
Copy that.
We're on our way.
Delta teams two and three,
this is a priority mobilization.
The suspect is Jack Bauer.
Considered armed and dangerous.
Maintain
shoot-on-sight protocol.
TAC AGENT: Copy that. We have
authorization for lethal force.
CHLOE:
Listen to me, Jack. Please.
Jack, put down
your rifle,
and let me walk you out of here
before they get here.
Killing Pavel and Novakovich
was one thing,
but killing Suvarov?
The Russians will consider an
assassination of their president
on American soil an act of war.
He facilitated a terrorist
attack against this country.
That's an act of war.
He's a murderer.
You're provoking a war
with a nuclear-armed country.
Shut up, Chloe!
Or what?
You're gonna kill me, too?
These people need to be stopped.
They need to be
held accountable.
They brought this on themselves.
I don't need to remind you
of the collateral damage
you're causing.
Not to mention
the innocent lives
that are at stake.
(footsteps approaching)
(knocking)
Sir, uh, President
Suvarov is outside.
He says you're expecting him.
Excuse me, sir?
Yes.
I heard you.
Send him in.
You're gonna start a war
because you lost someone?
This isn't about me.
Renee wouldn't
want you to do this.
I said shut up, Chloe!
You know she wouldn't.
She would want you
to use that data card
to get justice.
The last thing
Renee would want is for you
to start a war in her name.
Jack, please, don't dishonor
her memory like this.
We should
speak alone.
Yes, of course.
(panting)
This person, the one you say
is leaking information...
who is it?
SUVAROV (slowly):
I'm talking to you.
(Jack panting)
Okay, we'll do
it your way.
But you got to promise me
you'll see this through.
Because there's no way I'm
getting out of this building alive.
Jack... You got
to promise me that
you will see this through
and that you will do
exactly what I say.
I need to hear it!
I promise.
I'm, uh...
I'm sorry...
for calling you so urgently.
I was, uh, mistaken.
My concern appeared
to have been unfounded.
I- I got a call from my
source just a moment ago.
Um, um...
his information was wrong.
I'm so sorry for wasting
your time, Yuri.
Gregor. Vasily.
LOGAN:
See you after the signing.
Find Pillar.
Sweeping equipment 22nd floor!
CHLOE: Jack, the TAC
team's almost here.
I just need to make it
to mobile command.
You won't even get that far; you
won't make it out of the building.
You and Cole found me first
by circumventing CTU.
If Logan hasn't figured that
out yet, he will soon enough.
CTU gave you a standing order
with regards to me:
to terminate
with extreme prejudice.
If you don't shoot me,
that file's not going anywhere.
You need to shoot me
and shoot to kill!
Point it at me.
Point it!
And when they come
through the door, tell them
you found me at the sniper
rifle, I turned on you,
and you opened fire. Don't ask
me to do something I can't do.
Damn it, Chloe,
pull the trigger!
We are running
out of time.
They are gonna
find us soon.
You said you'd do
exactly what I would say,
that you would
follow this through.
Now, pull the trigger!
I can't!
Yes, you can,
and you will!
Now, pull the trigger!
No!
Damn you, Chloe,
pull the trigger!
Jack...
We are running out of time!
Pull the trigger!
Please don't make me
do this. Chloe, I know
how hard this is for you,
but if you care
about me at all,
you will pull the trigger.
Do it! Chloe,
I'm sorry, I can't.
pull the trigger!
No, Jack!
Pull the trigger!
I'm not gonna do it!
Damn you!
(gunshot)
(door bursts open)
What happened? He
drew his weapon.
I shot him first.
Jack Bauer's down
with a gunshot wound
to the upper chest.
Send medical to our position.
I repeat, Bauer is down.
(phone rings)
Chloe, I've been trying
to reach you.
Burke's reporting you shot Jack.
I had to. Listen...
I'm on my way there right now.
No.
I need you at
mobile command.
Tell me what's happening.
I have the recording
of Logan and Suvarov's
conversation.
Jack gave it to me.
If he gave it to you,
why did you shoot him?
I'll explain later.
Right now, you need to make sure
that Arlo is ready
to upload that file.
Yeah, okay.
Just...
What's Jack's status?
EMTs are working
on him right now.
Is he going to make it?
I don't know.
I'll explain everything
to you when I get there.
I'll see you soon.
BURKE:
Ms. O'Brian!
NYPD found Mr. Pillar
in the garage.
He was locked in the back
of his SUV.
He wants me to
hold you here. Why?
He's been apprised
of the situation,
and he wants
to debrief you.
We can do it later at CTU.
I'm still running
security here. I'm sorry.
Ms. O'Brian, he was adamant.
I've got to get back
to mobile command.
Ma'am, his authority,
comes from the president.
If you want
to make a call
to the White House,
we can do that.
When will he be here?
He's on his way up here now.
Hmm, I'm sure it was a terrible
ordeal, Mr. President.
But they told me Bauer's down.
It's over.
No. No.
It's not over, Jason.
Bauer has a recording
that implicates me
along with Suvarov.
How do you know?
Because the son of a bitch
played the damn thing for me.
He must've put a bug on me
somewhere
when he attacked the car.
For all I know,
he has recorded every
conversation I've had
for the past two hours.
I'm on site now.
I'll recover whatever he's got.
Hey!
You're on the line here, too.
If this evidence gets out,
we all go down together.
Yeah, I understand what's
at stake, Mr. President.
I'll call you back when
I have the recording.
Yeah.
(exhales forcefully)
Is he stable?
Yes, sir.
Sir,
as you requested,
I searched Bauer.
We're still combing the site,
but that's what we found so far.
PILLAR:
Are you sure that's it?
BURKE: Like I said, sir,
we're still sweeping.
I believe this
phone is yours.
(under breath): Yeah.
It's a, uh,
digital recorder, sir,
but it's clean.
There's nothing in it.
Come here.
Excuse us.
The data card is missing.
Bauer has a digital file
that poses a threat
to national security.
We need to find it.
Yes, sir. We'll keep looking.
PILLAR:
What happened up here?
He drew his gun
and I shot him.
What more do you
need to know?
Did Bauer give you anything?
What would he have given me?
Bauer had a digital recorder.
The data card's missing.
I thought you might
know where it is.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You didn't see him
stash it anywhere?
If I did, I would've taken it
and already logged it
as evidence.
Then you don't mind
emptying your pockets.
Um...
I just shot my friend, so...
Unless you want me
to do it for you, I need you
to empty your pockets now.
On what grounds?
National security.
Let's go.
(sighs)
If I search you,
will I find that data card?
This is ridiculous.
Put your hands up here.
I just told you, I shot Jack.
Why would I be helping him?
Sorry, Ms. O'Brian, I have
to be absolutely sure.
Okay.
Hope you enjoyed yourself.
(elevator bell dings)
It's over, Jack.
You need to talk to me;
maybe do yourself some good.
Where's the data card?
(sighs)
Is he stable enough
to be treated at CTU
instead of the hospital?
He should be.
He got lucky.
It's a through and through.
Through and through.
Bullet didn't hit any
of his organs or his
arteries. If you're going
to get shot anywhere, that's
where you want it to happen.
Son of a bitch!
Get me mobile command.
(mumbling)
What?
You got something
to say to me?
If you've got something to say,
you'd better say it now.
Talk to me.
(panting, muttering)
What?
(whispering)
(Jack grunting,
Pillar screaming)
(screaming continues)
(spits)
(yells)
Get him out of here!
Lock down O'Brian!
(groans loudly)
Arlo's ready
to receive the file.
Chloe, you need to tell me
why you shot Jack.
Jack said they'd suspect me
if I didn't; He said
my only way out of there with
the evidence is to shoot him.
Medical report said
it went clean through.
That no vital organs were hit. You're
telling me you meant to miss them?
How did you know
you wouldn't kill him?
I didn't.
It's uploading now.
It shouldn't take long.
Chloe...
I just need a few
more seconds.
What's going on?
Just got orders
to lock down Chloe O'Brian.
What orders?
Please step aside.
I'm not going anywhere
till you tell me
what's going on.
Sir, we're not going
to ask you again.
Step aside.
Don't- I order you- stop!
I'm ordering you to stop! Don't!
Ms. O'Brian, is this
the data card
that Jack Bauer gave you?
Yes. You need to listen
to what's on it.
Mr. Pillar will make
that determination.
Pillar is part of the cover-up.
That data card will never
make it to evidence.
Please!
Hold them here.
Don't do this!
Burke!
Burke, stop what you're doing!
Think about what you're doing!
Burke, stop!
(phone rings)
Pillar.
BURKE: Mr. Pillar,
I locked down O'Brian.
Looks like she was working
with Agent Ortiz.
He's in custody, too.
Get the data card?
Yes, sir.
O'Brian was trying
to upload the file
to the main
servers at CTU,
but I stopped
the transmission.
Good work, Agent Burke.
All right, send O'Brian
and Ortiz to CTU lockdown
and talk to no one.
Get that data card
to President Logan.
Yes, sir.
Take them to CTU.
This is it.
(sighs)
This is the recording
that Jack Bauer made.
Bauer was working
with Chloe O'Brian and a field
agent called Cole Ortiz.
They were planning
to use CTU's servers
to disseminate this recording
to news organizations,
and-and government officials
and watchdog groups
on a massive scale.
It almost worked.
My people, they never gave up,
and now it's over.
You won.
Congratulations.
Have you listened to this?
Yes, yes, but frankly,
it's not worth hearing.
Where is Jack now?
He's about to be transported
to CTU under heavy guard.
I realize that this
is a difficult area,
but the one thing
we can be certain of
is that Jack Bauer will never
let this go.
No.
I don't suppose he will.
All great achievements
in state...
are fragile things,
Madam President.
Especially
in their infancy.
They need
to be protected.
Our peace agreement-
very vulnerable.
As long as Jack Bauer
is out there,
the agreement will
never be safe.
Then we will lock him away
in a black site halfway
around the world.
He will find a way,
Madam President.
Mark my words.
He will rise out of the
deepest hole in the ground.
He will claw
his way back
from the ends
of the Earth,
unless we stop him
before that can happen.
Pending approval,
I have taken upon myself
to, uh... put a plan in motion.
Of course you have.
I will take your silence
as tacit approval.
(door opens)
(Taylor exhales sharply,
door closes)
(sighs heavily)
(sniffles)
(inserts data card
into laptop port)
A lot of good people
died today,
not just President Hassan.
Operatives from CTU, members of
other law enforcement agencies.
Renee Walker.
Who I was
very close to.
These people died today
because President Suvarov
wanted to destroy the peace
treaty for his own interests,
and President Taylor knows
this because I told her,
but she's willing to cover
it up because she believes
the peace accord will serve the
greater good. (phone ringing)
She is wrong; it
won't. (sniffles)
Yes.
Both delegations are here,
ma'am.
What about
the secretary general?
He's just outside
in the atrium.
Thank you, Tim.
(hangs up phone)
(taps computer key)
(sighs)
Lasting peace
cannot simply be political.
It has to be born out of trust
and honesty and understanding
and most importantly, a will
on both sides to move forward.
Currently,
that will does not exist.
This peace is fraudulent,
and I cannot
in good conscience
allow the people
that lost their lives today
to go unspoken for.
Kim, you reminded me
of that earlier today.
That's who I am.
(Taylor sniffs)
(sighs)
Bauer is
being handled.
Is it done?
Yes, sir.
All right, then.
(both sigh)
(pats back)
You know, I wasn't sure
the president had the balls
to see this through.
Clearly,
I underestimated her.
We both did, sir.
(door opens)
Good luck,
Madam President.
This calls
for a celebration.
Huh, a little something
to numb that ear pain?
(chuckles)
What are you
drinking?
Whatever you're having,
Mr. President. Yes.
(pouring)
You did well, Jason.
You kept your eye
on the prize.
Thank you, sir.
Here's to, uh, all
the political capital
the president is
about to bank
downstairs.
And here's
to helping her spend it.
(quiet chatter)
(whispering): I keep having to remind
myself that we will be home tomorrow,
and this day
will be behind us.
(applause)
SECRETARY GENERAL: Ladies
and gentlemen, please, please,
please take your seats.
Honored delegates
and distinguished guests,
on behalf of the United Nations,
please allow me
to welcome you
to this great occasion
of hope and peace.
Today we bear witness
to an extraordinary act
in one of the world's
defining dramas.
If you would
allow me now just to offer a few
private words to those of us
that are fortunate enough
to be here now.
May we all pledge
to make the spirit
of this moment...
a new chapter in the history
of all nations.
The President
of the United States of America,
please, would you join me?
The President
of the Russian Federation
and the President of the
Islamic Republic of Kamistan,
would you please join me?
Before you is the final draft
of the agreement
that has been negotiated
by you and your representatives
in good faith.
By signing its pages, you commit
your respective countries
to abide by the terms
set forth therein, as stipulated
by international law.
President Suvarov, I believe
you are to go first.
(applause)
SECRETARY GENERAL:
President Hassan.
(applause)
♪ ♪
(sniffs)
Your husband wanted
me to have this.
I cannot accept it.
Madam President,
what are you doing?
What I should have
done hours ago.
I urge you to stop
what you are about to do.
Mr. Secretary General,
my fellow delegates.
Grave crimes have been committed
in the run-up to this treaty.
I have participated
in a conspiracy
to hide those crimes.
Before there can be
a meaningful peace,
justice must be served.
(sniffles)
I will be
giving a more complete statement
within the hour,
but for now,
this peace process has come
to an end.
(delegates murmuring)
Contact CTU and
have them alert
Jack Bauer's
medical transport.
Madam President...
He is about to
be ambushed.
Just make the call, Tim!
We may already
be too late.
Dispatch, this is Tim Woods.
I have an emergency.
The convoy transporting Jack
Bauer is about to be ambushed.
Alert Medical One
immediately.
W- do it.
(shuddering)
Madam President,
talk to me.
Tell me
what's happening.
Ma'am.
I have made
a terrible mistake, Tim,
one that I can
never undo... but I need you
to help me stop it
from becoming worse.
Yes, ma'am.
(coughing)
DISPATCHER (over radio): Medical
One, this is CTU Dispatch.
(coughing)
Medical One, I have a priority
call from Homeland Security.
Come in, please.
(Jack groans)
(panting)
(phone rings)
This is Woods.
Thank you.
We didn't make it.
They got Bauer.
(groans loudly)
My statement is brief,
and I will take no questions.
Moments ago,
President Taylor
declined to sign
the peace accord and excused
herself from the proceedings.
She did so after making
allegations of crimes
which she did not specify,
and which the United Nations
has no knowledge of.
President Taylor said
that she would come forward
within the hour to explain
the reasons for her actions.
Until then, please,
direct all queries
to the White House
Communications Office.
(phone ringing,
press corps clamoring)
TV REPORTER: President
Taylor herself, after...
(TV turns off)
(phone ringing)
That's the President
asking about Bauer.
(ringing continues)
No.
Let it ring.
With due respect, sir,
what good will it do?
(ringing continues)
It's over.
Let's not add murder to the list
of charges already against us.
(ringing continues)
You know what, Jason?
You're right.
Go ahead. Pick it up.
(ringing continues)
(Pillar clears throat)
PILLAR:
Hello?
This is President Taylor.
I need to speak
to Charles Logan immediately.
(blow lands)
(groans)
Charles!
This was my last chance,
and Bauer took it away.
It's come to this
because of him.
(silenced shot)
It's locked.
(banging)
Open
the door, Charles!
This is Tim Woods.
I'm with the President
on the 22nd floor.
We need the master key
to room 2206 immediately.
(banging resumes)
TAYLOR: Damn it,
Charles! Open the door!
(gunshot)
Madam President,
this way! Now!
Tim, I need Logan alive!
Can they save him?
They think so,
but Madam President,
they're saying that even if
he regains consciousness,
he's probably suffered
severe brain damage.
He knew he was
the only one who could
locate Jack.
Not necessarily.
CTU's drones have been in the
air for the last four hours.
They may be able to back-trace
Jack from the ambush site
using archived
surveillance video.
Where is Chloe O'Brian?
She and Agent Ortiz
returned to CTU
about ten minutes ago,
under arrest. I want
them released immediately.
Tell Chloe to use
whatever resources are at her
disposal to find Jack.
I've already done that,
Madam President.
Thank you, Tim.
Thank you.
EDEN:
Let go of me!
O'Brian, you have no authority.
I don't know what you
think you're doing.
Shut up and keep moving.
What the hell
is going on?
What the hell is going on?
President Taylor
didn't sign the agreement.
She backed out at the last
minute, but she had already
ordered the hit on Jack.
Did she call it off?
She tried, but his
ambulance has
been ambushed. She has no
way of contacting the hitters.
How does she even know Jack's
still alive? She doesn't.
She's had everyone
cleared from the floor
except for you, me and Arlo.
Arlo's redirecting the drone
to over the ambush site.
We just got police reports
of an incident downtown.
CTU convoy ambushed,
three agents wounded,
but they didn't find
Jack's body on site. Can
you pull up archived video
of the same location?
Already on it.
COLE:
When did this happen?
ARLO:
Five minutes ago.
Shuttle forward.
Come on, Arlo.
Give me something.
Okay, 30 seconds ago,
the van pulled off of Delancey.
Damn it.
What?
Lost it under
the Williamsburg Bridge.
Go to real time.
♪ ♪
ARLO:
That's it. That's the van.
Have NYPD send all units
to the vicinity.
They're never going
to make it in time.
Um...
Okay, uh, hold on.
Prepare for departure run-through
with Team B in 20 minutes.
I got this!
Come on.
Turn around.
Down on your knees.
(panting and groaning quietly)
I know who you are.
So I'm going to make this,
uh, quick and clean.
Am I supposed to say thank you?
(grunting)
Stand down! Stand down!
I really don't want to do this,
but orders are orders.
It's all right.
Pull the trigger.
Sir!
Wait! Hold your fire!
It's President Taylor.
I don't have positive
confirmation,
but it sounds like her.
She says CTU
has a drone overhead.
They're got a directed
microwave signal.
That's how they got
through to the phone.
Madam President?
I am ordering you
to release Jack Bauer
immediately!
Ma'am?
You heard me!
You and your men are
to leave Mr. Bauer where he is.
Stand down and withdraw
outside the west gate
until the FBI arrives.
If you have any thoughts
of fleeing before then,
the drone is equipped
with two AGM-114
Hellfire missiles. I will
not hesitate to use them.
Are we clear?
Yes, ma'am.
Now, put Mr. Bauer on the phone.
Uncuff him.
Sir?
I said, "Uncuff him."
(handcuffs unlocking)
(panting)
You're ordered
to stand down and evacuate.
We're rolling up
and evacuating.
Let's get in the van.
Let's move. Now.
The President wants
to talk to you.
TAYLOR (over phone):
Jack?
You should've
let them kill me...
...'cause I'm not going
to quit until this is over.
It is over.
I withdrew 15 minutes ago from
the signing of the peace treaty.
Within the hour,
I will tell the world
what happened today.
I will tender
my resignation
and remand myself
to the attorney general...
and face the consequences
of my actions.
Unfortunately, you will
have to do the same.
I wanted this peace
so badly, Jack.
And for that, I have betrayed
every principle
that I have ever stood for.
And I betrayed you.
If I had listened to you,
none of this
would have happened.
We've both made mistakes we're
going to have to live with.
I would give anything
to take back the time.
But all I can do is tell you
to leave the country
while you still have a chance.
The Russians will
be coming after you.
And so will we.
Jack, I am so sorry.
I don't know what else to say.
♪ ♪
(phone ringing)
Jack?
Chloe, the president just told
me what was happening.
She said she was going
to give me a little time
to try and get
out of the country.
I know. I was on the call.
My daughter...
her family- they're going
to try and use her to get to me.
I'll make sure
they're protected.
No. Chloe, you've got
to promise me.
You've got to promise me
you'll keep them safe.
I'll make sure they're
protected. I promise.
How much time
do you think I've got?
I don't know.
I'll get you as much time
as I can.
Chloe...
What?
When you first came to CTU...
I never thought
it was going to be you
that was going to cover
my back all those years.
And I know that everything
that you did today
was to try and protect
me. I know that.
Thank you.
Good luck, Jack.
Yeah...
Bring the drone
back to the base.
Whatever happened here
didn't happen.
Understand?
Shut it down.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net