It's him.
Damn it.
(over headset): I couldn't get off a shot.
Stand by.
We'll get him on the way out.
Manuel!
Hey, Manny!
Manny!
WOMAN: Yes?
Put Mauricio on the phone.
Victor? Just put Mauricio on!
He's dead.
What?
Someone shot him in the head.
What the hell is happening?
I see him.
He's leaving the building.
I'set.
Stop.
SPOTTER: It's not him.
He can't be far.
Coming at you! Gray sedan!
Target is out of range.
Move out.
OPERATOR: 911. What's your emergency?
Yes. I want to report a stolen vehicle.
License plate SNE15C5.
Jack?
Oh.
Sweetheart, we already
talked about this, remember?
You're supposed to call me "Grandpa."
You don't look like a grandpa.
Couldn't agree with you more.
The cartoon I turned on is boring.
Okay. We'll find another one.
This is the boldest diplomatic initiative
we've seen in a generation.
It could finally lay a
foundation for real peace
throughout the entire region.
Well, you know, Bob, the president's
certainly betting her legacy
on the success of these negotiations...
Grandpa!
This isn't a cartoon!
Okay, okay.
*A sloth of bears... âTª
This one! I like this one!
*A mob of cows âTª
*A herd of sheep... âTª
Yeah?
Hi, Dad. Sorry we're late.
They're redirecting everyone around the UN.
It's all right. We're doing fine.
How was the zoo?
Well, to be honest with you,
we spent most of our time
just going back and forth
between the black bears and the polar bears.
I forgot to mention that she's
going through a bear phase.
Well, she certainly knows what she wants.
She reminds me of you.
Well, that's funny.
I always tell Stephen how
much she reminds me of you.
Anyway, we'll be there in a few minutes.
Okay. Don't worry.
We'll meet you in the lobby.
Great.
Sounds like they had fun.
They always do.
What's wrong?
We talked to him about moving
to LA the night we got here.
Yeah. He said he'd think about it.
Yeah, and he hasn't mentioned
one word about it since.
And we leave tonight.
Well, maybe he has to
check with his doctors.
No, they cleared him two weeks ag
He's finished with treatme.
I don't know.
My father has been on his own for so long.
Maybe he doesn't know how
to live any other way.
Why don't you just ask him again?
My father is not the type
of person you ask twice.
If you want, I can do it.
REPORTER: Here at e ited Nions,
a White House spokesman just confirmed that
Presiden
Taylor and Hassan will be
hoing a joint press conference
later this hour.
It is widely expected that
President Hassan will announce
the dismantling of his country's
nuclear weapons program.
esident Hassan has stated that
he conside these negotiations
a historic success and a new
beginning for his country
and the entire Mideast region.
I believe that that is a
reasonable compromise.
Now, Mr. President, let's move
on to the issue of verification.
Now, the language in your
latest proposal is vague.
Let me be clear.
My country agrees
to abandon the pursuit of nuclear weapons
with full International Atomic
Energy Agency safeguards.
But our terms, Mr. President,
were that the inspectors
themselves would be American,
not IAEA.
With respect, Madam President,
your side pushed the point,
but we never conceded.
With respect, your side
has refused to negotiate
the point in good faith.
Without Americans on the ground--
Surely, we're not going
to let the nationality
of a few hundred men--
...verification has no teeth.
So, only the United States can
be trusted, Mr. Secretary?
This is the message that you
sent to the rest of the world
and then you wonder why we
don't want to negotiate.
Farhad.
Madam President,
please excuse my brother's passion.
He only wants what is best for our country.
I understand.
But we need to resolve this issue
before we can move forward.
And ideally, before
the press conference, which gives us
less than an hour.
HASSAN: Madame President...
what would your Congress say
if my Revolutionary Guard
was stationed on your soil?
It's the same with my
National Assembly.
Even if I agreed to this,
they would not ratify it.
After all, I'm not a king.
Nor I a queen.
Too bad for both of us.
I'd like to adjourn
and discuss this issue
with our respective teams.
Of course.
You are aware he was a salesman
before entering politics.
Household appliances.
You want to bet he sold
a lot of refrigerators?
Find a way to give him what he wants.
Madam President...
You heard me.
Try to make the inspections work.
This man is a once in a lifetime leader.
And he has already
suspended his support for
terrorist organizations,
and privately, he's advocating
for a two-state solution.
How much further can we expect
him to stick his neck out?
Hey, come here.
Did you name him yet? Bear.
"Bear." KIM: There she is.
Go get your mom. Hi!
Hey! I heard that you
and Grandpa were hanging out with the bears.
Then we had ice cream,
but I didn't like mine, so Grandpa
gave me his.
That's nice. STEPHEN: Here, I got her.
Thanks for watching her, Jack. Of course.
Listen, I've been thinking a lot about
what we talked about.
And I've made up my mind.
I want to move back to Los Angeles with you.
Really? Yeah.
I got a friend who's got
a private security firm.
Said he'd give me some consulting work.
He's also got a place I can rent.
Dad, I don't know what to say.
Come here.
You don't have to say anything.
Just give me a ride to the airport tonight.
Wait, you're coming with us tonight?
If it's okay.
Of course. Stephen.
Yeah? He's coming with us tonight.
And I've just got a few more things to pack.
I don't have very much.
I can be at your hotel in about an hour.
That's perfect. We can get back
and finish packing ourselves.
It'll be all right if I fly back
to Los Angeles with you?
Yay! Yay!
Come on. I'll walk you to the car.
Okay. Let's go.
Yay! I got her.
Okay. *We're going in the car. âTª
Get your belt done up...
Dad, I am so glad that you're doing this.
Me, too.
I love you. Love you.
Okay, guys, I'll see you in an hour.
TERI: Okay. Bye, sweetheart.
TERI: Bye!
(gasps, groans)
Good afternoon, everyone.
Good afternoon.
All right, just a few things
before we get started here.
Presidents Taylor and Hassan
will each make a statement
after they've been introduced
by the Secretary-General.
The Q&A will follow,
but I want you to keep your
questions strictly on topic.
For obvious reasons, we're all operating
under heightened security measures,
so, unless you've been dying to know
what a chokehold feels like,
keep your credentials visible at all times.
All right?
That's all for now.
Meredith Reed, press.
It's invalid.
What?
It can't be invalid.
Can you double check?
I did, ma'am. Your credentials
have been revoked.
Revoked by whom?
I don't have that information.
Okay, this has to be some sort of mistake.
You do remember me.
I've been here every day.
Please step aside, ma'am.
I just talked to Secretary of State Kanin.
He's agreed to IAEAnspectors.
That's good news.
There is a condition attached.
They're insisting
that the head of the
verification team be an American.
I think we can live with that, don't you?
You know where I stand.
We've already surrendered too
much in the name of peace.
Surrender is a strong word, Farhad.
And what have we surrendered really,
apart from our nuclear ambition?
Isn't that enough?
Spinning 6,000 centrifuges
is good for political maneuvering,
but it's helping to bankrupt our country.
The truth is,
we are not the ones being so generous.
President Taylor is lifting
economic sanctions,
and offering an aid package
worth billions of dollars.
We got everything we wanted, Farhad.
As long as it's not a trick.
Hello.
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you
with something so mundane,
but I'm stuck outside.
Stuck?
My press credentials
have been revoked.
I dI'll take care of it.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Thank you.
Will you, uh, will you still have
time for the interview later?
Yes. After the press conference.
I'm looking forward to it, Mr. President.
So am I.
Reinstate Miss Reed's clearance.
I was only...
Just do it.
Omar, people are starting to talk
about you and this reporter.
And saying what?
Miss Reed is a journalist
and she's profiling me for her newspaper.
But you have feelings for her.
I'm friendly with her.
Think whatever you like.
This woman poses no threat
to me or the peace process.
Not here maybe, but back in our country
you'll be torn apart.
The mullahs will say that you
have been corrupted by the West.
What do you say, Farhad?
Have I?
Have I been corrupted by the West?
You know I don't believe that.
But you are married.
Dalia hasn't been a wife
to me for a long time.
That's no excuse to be reckless.
I've done nothing reckless.
Just reinstate Miss Reed's clearance now.
I'll see to it.
Victor.
What are you doing here?
How the hell did you find me?
I was always resourceful, Jack.
That's what you liked about me. Get in here.
Take a seat.
What happened?
I need help.
You need an ambulanc
No, no, don't call.
That's what he's waiting for.
He's listening to the emergencchannels. Who?
Just listen to me, Jack. I have information.
The best I can do for you, Victor,
is get you an ambulance.
I'm out. I don't work for
the government anymore.
Oh, this you're going to want to hear.
Why?
Why? Because you're the guy who
always does the right thing.
There's a big hit going down.
On who?
President Hassan at the UN.
He's getting taken out.
When? Today.
Before he can sign this thing with Taylor.
You see? I told you you'd be interested.
How do you know this?
I'm the one that got the
hitter into the country.
I've been setting him up with what he needs.
And then he tried to take you out.
Look, Jack, you're the only one
at CTU I ever did business with.
I need you to call them, vouch for me,
so I can cut a deal.
Come on, Jack.
(groans) Keep your seat.
Look, I swear, this is real.
Someone is trying to make sure
that this peace agreement does not happen.
I'm not doing anything until
you give me your weapon.
Better not be screwing with me.
I'm not. I swear, I'm not.
Who's the hitter? What's his name?
Who's the hitter?!
I don't know his name.
He's Russian or something. Not good enough.
Who is the hitter?! Look.
I know how to find him and stop
him before he makes the hit.
But I'm not saying another
word until I make my deal.
You're lucky I'm retired.
This is Cole Ortiz.
Move Singer's team to the northeast
quadnt, and tell him, from now on,
I want updates every quarter hour.
Get back to me with confirmations.
Hastings wants you to
expand the patrol perimeter
around the UN another quarter mile.
I'm glad that's what he wants,
but I barely have enough men to cover
the perimeter now.
I'll see if I can get
NYPD to help you cover.
Uh, Dana?
My sister--
she said she lt you a couple of messages.
Something about bridesmaids' dresses.
I told her there was probably
something wrong with your voicemail.
I got her messages.
I just haven't had a chance.
These double shifts...
I revised the patrol protocols at the UN.
Thought you might like
to take a look at it before
I distributed it. Yeah.
Yeah, I do. I will call your sister
back, I promise.
Thanks.
Damn it, what is the problem?
Percussive maintenance?
That's what my network apps professor
called it when I hit my computer.
Can I help?
I just got the revised attendee list
for the press conference.
I can't get the facial
recognition done in time.
Oh, you're running each
person through individually.
You can do them in a batch.
Not if the data's in different formats.
Well, that used to be true, but here.
Like I said, there's no reon
to be shy out asking for help.
Okay? Don't worry.
You'll catch u You're doing great.
Excuse me.
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Jack.
How's Kim? Did you tell her about LA?
Yeah, but I can't go into that right now.
I need to speak to the director.
Mr. Hastings is on the phone,
and he really doesn't
like to be interrupted.
Well, tell him it's regarding a plot
to assassinate President Has
See if that ts his attention.
Oh. Okay, hold on.
All right, now,
give me an overlay on the UN,
view from the west.
Now, overlay the distribution
of security teams, please.
That looks good.
Now, give me a comp with
incident reports and
satellite imaging. Excuse me, Mr. Hastings.
Gary, hold on for a second.
Jack Bauer's on line three. He says he nds
to talk to you. Bauer?
It's about a plot against President Hassan.
I thought you'd want to take the call.
Gary, I'll call you back.
Mr. Bauer, thiss Brn Hastgs.
Mr. Hastings, I'm with an
informant that I used to run
who's claiming he's got
intel on an assassination
attempt on President Hassan.
He says it's going to take place today.
We've received several ats
in regard to the peace conference.
I can only imagine.
My informant's name Victor Aruz.
I used him in the Salazar op.
You should be able to
pull his file Pull it up.
He's been shot in the arm-
he claims byhe assassin.
Look, I don't think
this is something you should take lightly.
And what does Mr. Aruz want
in return for his information?
CTU protection and immunity.
That's a lot to ask, Mr. Bauer.
Have you pulled his file yet?
No. JACK: Mr. Hastings,
I know this son of a bitch,
and my instinct is telling me
that you need to pay attention to this.
I need more than your instinct, Mr. Bauer.
CTU isn't the organization you knew.
Okay, fine, but understand this:
If anything happens to President Hassan,
I will be obligated to call
President Taylor and tell her
that I tried to provide you with this intel,
and you ignored it.
What is taking so long for the file?
Sorry. I'm still searching
through the archives.
Mr. Hastings, I need your answer now.
Are you bringing Aruz in or not?
(sighs)
Let me talk to him.
I'll put you on speaker.
Go ahead.
Mr. Aruz, I'm gonna need some other details
to corroborate your story.
The hitter took out two of my guys.
Manuel Escobar and Mauricio Tellez.
Check with t cops.
We will.
Mr. Bauer,
where are you?
1145 West 18th.
I'll send a chopper to pick you up.
The closest helipad
to you is... the 12th precinct.
That's five blocks away.
Can you t him there,
Mr. Bauer?
Yeah.
I'll have a team there in 20 minutes.
Make sure you don't use official channels.
We believe the assassin is
monitoring emergency bandwidth.
Got it.
Gather comm and tactical,
tell them we've got a situation.
JACK: Let's go.
There you are.
Now that doesn't suck.
Arlo.
Yeah.
Come on. Hastings called
an emergency briefing.
And if he ever catches you
doing that, you're gonna be out of a job.
Be worth it.
I think this mig be love.
Now.
This is CTU
transferring control of drones A31 and 32
to HS aerial command.
Yeah, roger that.
Offload confirmed.
l right, we've got a situation.
Cole, I need you to scramble
a chopper for a pickup.
Yeah. I haven't finished distributing
the new patrol parameters.
This is a priority.
Who am I picking up?
Someone who claims to have intel
about a threat to President Hassan.
How good is the intel?
Well, according to Jack Bauer, very.
Jack Bauer?
He's delivering the informant.
Who is Jack Bauer?
Location downtown; Chloe's
sending you the coordinates.
Take a small team with you.
Torres' people are free.
Yes, sir. And I'll need a second
team to secure the landing.
One team will be enough. We'll use a drone
to protect the ground operation.
Arlo, scramble a drone
alongside the chopper.
Full spectrum coverage of the landing zone
as well as the air corridor.
Done.
We're clear.
Dispatch, this is Unit 2354.
DISPATCH: Go ahead, 2354.
Got a plate match on a stolen vehicle.
(various overlapping radio communications)
(tuning in):...03 Pontiac.
Plate: Sierra, November, Echo,
one, five, Charlie, five.
Got bullet holes in the windshield and body.
That's him.
DISPATCH: Roger that.
What's yr location?
Vee's parked o18th,
just west of Ninth Avenue.
We'll take care of it.
Will you?
Or am I going to have to step in?
Now would be the time to tell me.
Aruz is a dead man, sir.
You have my word.
Good.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Madam President.
President Hassan accepted our
counterproposals on inspections.
That is great news.
By the end of this next session,
we may have a signed agreement.
It's an extraordinary
accomplishment, Allison.
(sighing)
Is something wrong?
I was thinking about Henry.
Achieving a comprehensive peace agreement
with the Islamic Republic
was was something that
he and I talked about years ago.
I wish that he were here
to share the moment.
You surprised?
Considering his behavior during the divorce,
yes, I am surprised.
He went out of his way to hurt you,
especially in the press.
He was angry, Ethan.
I sent our daughter to prison.
You refused to cover up a murder.
Olivia was responsible for what happened--
no one else.
Still, if the the situation
had been reversed,
I might've felt the same way as Henry.
Sorry if I'm interrupting, but I just talked
to Brian Hastings at CTU.
What's going on, Rob?
They have someone who
claims he's got information
about an assassination plot on Hassan.
How real is the threat?
Real enough to loop you in.
This informant came to
them through Jack Bauer.
I thought that
Jack was out of all of this.
How did he get involved?
As far as I can tell,
this informant came to him.
We'll know more once the
informant signs an immunity deal,
provided you authorize it.
How secure is the venue
for the press conference?
Very. And I just raised the alert level.
But we need to set up a call to
inform Hassan about the threat,
ideally before the conference gets started.
We can't tell Hassan.
Certainly not before the press
conference.
Why not?
Well, he might scuttle everything,
out of concern
for his own safety. Hassan's a big boy.
He's used to taking risks or he
wouldn't be here; you know that.
Plus, if Hassan finds out we knew
about this and didn't tell him,
then all the trust we've built up
over the last year goes out the window,
and then he'll pull out of talks.
And frankly, I wouldn't blame him.
I'll think about it.
Thank you both.
Madam President, I'm telling you,
holding this back from Hassan
could be disastrous.
I said I'd think about it, Rob.
Thank you.
Ethan...
Listen-- sorry if I went after
you a little hard in there.
Uh, I was just making my point.
No need to apologize, Rob.
I recommended you to the President
because you're not afraid
to speak up.
She needs that.
Yeah, well, still,
I know I can get carried away; I...
Don't worry, kid... I ain't dead yet.
I can handle mysf.
Even up against you.
Hey, sweetheart, it's me.
Hey, we're almost finished packing.
Are you on your way?
Something came up.
I'm gonna be a little late.
How late?
I think I should meet you at the airpo.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Kim, I promise everything's fine.
Well, Teri is so excited that
you're coming back with us.
Just, uh, let me know
when you're on your way.
Okay, thanks, sweetheart.
Keep your eyes open.
The precinct's two blocks away.
Let's cut through here. Come on.
The FAA's cleared a route and informed
all relevant agencies that
we will be in the air.
Good luck.
Aruz's file-- it was in
a proprietary database.
That's why it took so long.
Still, that shouldn't have thrown you-
you've been here a month.
Almost a month, and I've had
to relearn the interface
on every major system here;
everything's changed.
And you're having trouble adapting,
I understand.
But I don't think it's a
question of your intelligence.
Thanks.
I think it's ambivalence.
Ambivalence?!
I know the only reason
you only took this job
was because your husband was downsized.
Am I wrong? No!
I mean, yes.
Please, just give me a little more time
to get up to speed here.
Mr. Hastings, I need this job.
Fair enough.
But I'm all about efficiency, so if your
performance doesn't improve,
you may want to rethink working here.
Now, I trust this has been clarifying.
Sure.
If you really wanted to be more efficient,
why don't you just say
if I don't catch up soon,
I'm going to be fired?
Your flight path is a straight shot
southwest over the river,
and the 12th Precinct
has confirmed that their helipad is clear
and operational.
Comm net and satellite coverage
of your flight, both legs,
and full-time aerial from the drone--
Why are you looking at me like that?
Like what?
Look, I just want to make
sure nothing's wrong.
Nothing's wrong,
like I said.
Just be careful, okay?
I will be.
You ready?
Yeah.
You know, maybe she
should finally set a date.
She's getting cold feet.
How about you shut up
and just focus on your assignment?
Come on, Victor!
Victor? Victor!
Stay with me.
Victor, stay with me!
Stay with...
Damn it.
Stay with me!
We're going to need to recompress the wound.
TV REPORTER: If successful,
the agreement could be the beginning
of a real lasting peace in a lon
g-troubled region.
Presidents Taylor and Hassan
are scheduled to give their first joint
press conference in just
a few minutes, and we'll
carry that live.
In a moment, Christiane Doumany will have
a report on the history of
the many failed attempts
at a Mideast peace,
and why this accord may be different.
It's time to go.
Tell your father I'll be right there.
I'll wait until you're done.
He doesn't trust me to be on time.
Of course he trusts you.
When did you become such a good liar?
You don't have to defend your father, Dalia.
He can take care of himself.
You look beautiful, Dalia.
And you look handsome.
Let's not pretend any more than we have to.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
It's not your fault.
My dear Kayla.
We should go.
Yes.
Let her through.
Thank you.
I will tell you the same
thing that I told him.
Unless you want to destroy
everything that he's worked for,
stay away from him.
Excuse me, ma'am.
President Hassan is on his way.
You're not going to tell
him he's being targeted.
Madam President, I'm sorry.
You risk destroying in a
single day all the-- Rob,
you've made your point.
More than once.
And believe me, I don't like keeping this
from President Hassan any more than you do.
Then tell him.
Mr. President.
Ladies.
You've met my chief of staff?
Of course.
Hello, Mr. President.
I haven't had the chance to
thank you for compromising
on the verification issue.
It was the right thing to do.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to brief you both
on the format of the press conference.
The Secretary-General will be introducing
you both after some brief remarks.
The conference itself
shouldn't take any longer
than 25 minutes or so.
Put your hand on it.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
MAN: Don't move!
Got a call that you two are having
a problem down here. What's up?
Officer, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm transporting this man on behalf of CTU.
He's an informant vital
to national security.
Call it in. Listen to me.
The men that are trying to kill him
are monitoring all emergency channels.
Do not let him make that call.
Shut up and get against the Dumpster.
Now!
At least take us into the precinct.
We can verify everything there.
Get down, now!
Damn it!
I'm going to cover you.
Make a run for the door.
You ready? Go! Go!
I'm out of bullets.
Chloe, it's Jack.
How far out is the helicopter?
Two minutes. Jack, what's wrong?
We're under attack.
I need you to put me in touch
with whoever's in command of that unit.
Okay. It's Agent Ortiz.
He's the head of field ops.
Is there a problem? Yes.
Mr. Hastings, we have a
situation with the pickup.
Keep going to the roof. Now.
Don't stop for anything.
Keep going.
Agent Ortiz, you're on with
Jack Bauer. ORTIZ: Roger.
What's going on, Mr. Bauer?
We're being pursued by two shooters.
There's no way we're going
to make the precinct.
We're in a building on West 21st,
three doors in from Ninth Avenue.
We're heaWe're lookingposition
for an alternate pickup.ne.
Copy that.
Right there-- the roof of that
parking structure might work.
Can you zoom in closer?
The satellite's refreshing.
It'll take a minute.
I'm moving the drone there now.
There's a parking structure next
to the building you're in.
Roof looks clear to land.
DANA: Did you get that, Cole?
Yeah, I see it. Mr. Bauer,
looks like you can access that roof
from the eighth floor of
the building you're in.
How far out are you? 90 seconds.
Copy that.
Don't be late.
Victor... Victor, listen to me.
You got to tell me everything
you know about the hitter,
so I can call it in
in case we don't make it.
If I don't make it,
I don't care what happens.
Get me to CTU.
You always were a son of a bitch.
Come on.
Let's go.
Stay there.
Lock down access points to the roof!
Where are the hostiles? They're dead.
You need to get him out of here.
He's losing a lot of blood.
Cole Ortiz. It's an honor to meet you.
Thanks for doing this.
Look, Hastings wants to
debrief you back at CTU.
I'm not going back to CTU.
I delivered him, I'm done.
No, Mr. Bauer... I got a flight to catch.
That's it?
Get down!
Ortiz, report in.
CHLOE: Agent Ortiz?
Agent Ortiz, what's your status?
Agent Ortiz?
Jack, come in.
Jack, can you hear me?
Anyone, come in.
Victor.
Victor, Victor, come on.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Listen to me.
You don't want to die like this.
Do the right thing.
Tell me what you know.
The hitter has someone on the inside.
Close to Hassan.
Give me a name
Give me a name. Give me a name!
Victor...
Victor, who's on the inside?
Victor!
Come on.
Come on, come on.
No.
He's dead.
The brother revoked my clearance,
but I had Hassan reinstate it.
No, I know.
I know I'm behind schedule.
But it'll get done.
www.tvsubtitles.net