Can I assume there is no change
in the status
of President Hassan?
I'm afraid not.
Then he is still being
held by terrorists.
If Hassan dies,
there is no treaty.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were hoping
for that to happen.
Jack thinks that someone inside
of CTU is working
for the terrorists.
Jack recovered Tarin's
cell phone from the crash.
If someone did call
and tip him off,
we can get the number off
the memory.
It's Dana's phone.
I spoke to Hastings.
He cleared me through.
Stay where you are
and keep your hands
where I can...
She just entered
the parking garage.
The only reason you've got
any leverage right now is
because President Hassan
is alive.
So stop screwing with me!
They are gonna force him
to make a statement,
and then they're going
to kill him.
Just read the statement,
no more.
You will renounce
the peace agreement.
I will never do that.
He's stronger than we thought.
Bury him.
I will tell the world
of his crimes.
This man is not our president!
He's an arrogant...
Jack, looks like Samir's
grabbed him.
We need you to get in there
right now!
I have a visual on Hassan.
Ready to engage.
I'm sorry.
Yes?
Excuse me, ma'am.
I have Jack Bauer
on the line for you.
Put him through.
Jack...
Madam President,
I don't know what to say
except that I'm sorry.
I trust there was nothing
you and your team
could have done differently.
No, ma'am.
President Hassan was dead
before we even got there.
Then you don't owe me
an apology.
I failed you, ma'am.
It was Hassan's choice
to surrender himself
in order to save
American lives.
It was out of your hands.
Don't put this responsibility
on yourself.
Madam President, you need to
keep this peace agreement alive.
There can't be any agreement
when the IRK is
without a leader, Jack.
The hardliners there will take
advantage of the vacuum
and-and reverse all the progress
we made with Hassan.
I'm gonna have
to address the delegates
in a few minutes
and announce the dissolution
of the peace summit,
and, and formally release them.
Ma'am, if you give up,
it means they win.
I don't see another choice,
Jack.
I-I wish to God I did.
Good-bye, Jack.
What's his condition?
He took a round to the shoulder,
another through the abdomen,
but it exited clean.
BP looks steady.
Look, we need this guy for questioning.
Is he going to make it or not?
Doesn't look like
any vitals were hit.
He'll live. All right.
We'll transport him back to CTU.
Medical will take him for now.
Jack.
President Taylor is going
to formally announce
the end of the
peace conference.
Jack, you did everything
you could.
It wasn't enough.
We should get back to CTU.
Why?
The fuel rods
have been recovered.
The peace conference is over.
Everybody who was responsible
is either dead or in custody.
Cole.
What's the status on Samir?
He's still unconscious,
but the EMTs say he'll make it.
Okay, good.
I want you to stay with him.
I'm handing over
complete authority
and responsibility
for his transport to you.
Are you heading back to CTU?
No.
We're going home. We're done.
Hastings is still
probably going to want
to debrief both of you.
I'm sure he will.
He knows how to find me.
I'm sorry it ended up
like this, Jack.
Me, too.
You're a good agent, Cole.
I wouldn't be standing here
without you.
Thank you.
I hope everything works out.
I'll pack my kit up downstairs.
Madam President.
The delegates are assembled
in the lounge, as you requested.
Let's get this over with.
Discontinue the peace summit that was to be
a cornerstone
of her administration.
President Hassan apparently
had been kidnapped earlier,
and then taken to...
Jamot.
On behalf of my country,
you have our deepest sympathy
for this terrible tragedy.
Though, on a personal level,
I imagine you
have mixed feelings right now.
Beg your pardon?
Hassan had you arrested
without cause
during his purge
of suspected enemies.
Allowed you to be
brutally interrogated.
I would think you
have little love for the man.
President Hassan
was under tremendous duress,
and he lost his way,
but I never stopped believing
in what he stood for.
Of course.
I meant no offense.
I'm sure you didn't.
Excuse me.
While we have not learned
the identity
of the terrorist in the video...
President Taylor.
Minister Jamot.
If you can spare a few moments,
I need to speak with you.
I will be happy
to sit down with you
after I have addressed
the other delegations.
I know you're intending
to announce
the end of the peace summit,
but there may be a way
to prevent that from happening.
Before you do anything,
I need you to hear
what I have to say.
All right.
Ma'am, what about the delegates?
Just... just give me a moment.
Let's go in here.
Please.
Federal agents mounted
an operation
to rescue President Hassan
from the terrorists
that commenced
approximately 30 minutes ago.
Yes?
Samir's men were all dead,
thanks to the Americans.
Samir was the only one left,
but I took care of him.
So, there's no connection to us?
We're in the clear?
Maybe not.
There was a woman there
who might have recognized me.
What woman?
She may be CTU...
I'm not sure... but...
I've seen her face before.
Where?
Six years ago,
when we were using
that mobster,
Vladimir Laitanan,
to smuggle military weapons
out of the country,
she was with him.
Are you sure it was her?
I don't forget faces.
Where is she now?
In a taxicab,
just ahead of me,
with Jack Bauer.
Bauer?
Are they going to CTU?
I don't think so, no.
Then, it seems unlikely
she recognized you.
Better not to take the chance.
I'll take out Bauer, too,
while I'm at it.
The Americans believe the IRK
were solely behind
the recent attacks.
Killing Bauer and this woman
would only alert them
to the fact that others
were involved.
How long before they
discover that it was us?
It will take even less time
if this woman remembers me.
What are my orders?
Continue to follow them...
keep them in sight...
And I'll get back to you.
I don't have the words
to tell you and Kayla
how sorry I am.
I know you did everything
in your power.
Jamot, I wasn't aware
that you were here.
I only arrived a short time ago.
I want you to know that,
in our last few hours together,
Omar expressed
his regrets to me,
not the least of which
was his treatment of you.
I appreciate that.
Mrs. Hassan, I realize
our timing is intrusive,
but there's something we need
to discuss privately.
Did you find him,
President Taylor?
The man who killed my father?
Samir Mehran.
Yes.
He was badly wounded,
but he'll live to stand trial.
And, believe me, he will pay
dearly for what he's done.
Kayla, darling,
I need to speak
with President Taylor alone.
Give us a few minutes.
What is it that you wish
to talk to me about?
Mrs. Hassan, as you know,
for almost a year,
your husband and I
worked to make this
peace agreement a reality.
Now, in that time,
I saw the kind
of leader he was.
He managed
against difficult odds
to bring a fractious
and contentious
parliament together.
But, now that he's gone,
your country is going
to be thrown into turmoil.
I am aware of the challenges
that we are facing.
Why are you telling me this?
Clearly, someone needs
to take the reigns
of the IRK government.
Someone who believes
in the same ideals
and principles as Omar Hassan,
and who shares his strength.
Minister Jamot
believes that that person
should be you.
What?!
I'm not the only one
who believes it.
I've spoken to our delegation,
as well as
with the other members
of our cabinet back home.
You represent our best.
Our only real chance
to preserve our government
and your husband's agenda.
You are out of your mind!
I am no politician.
But you are a martyr's wife.
And history has proven that
to be something
far more powerful.
You have always been popular
with the people.
The vast majority
of them want peace.
They will rally around you.
The Council of Guardian
will have no choice
but to recognize you
as successor to the presidency.
But I have a choice.
You assume too much of me,
Jamot.
I realize that
this is a lot to consider,
especially now while
you're grieving,
but without a unifying figure
to hold your country together,
everything your husband
worked for will be for nothing.
President Taylor, my marriage
to Omar was far from perfect.
We had many problems
for a very long time.
I know only too well
how difficult it is
for a marriage
to survive a life in politics.
But through it all,
I never stopped loving him.
Or sharing his desire
for better relations
with the West.
If it is the will of my people
and of my government,
I will take my husband's place
at the peace conference.
It will be my honor
to stand with you.
We'll make the announcement
together
from the United Nations.
Mrs. Hassan,
thank you.
She's going to do it.
Oh, that's incredible
news, Madam President.
I want every delegate
contacted personally.
Tell them to cancel any plans
to leave the country.
We are returning to the UN.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll also call CTU
and implement those changes
we discussed
if I still have
your permission.
That's your decision.
Do what you think is best.
Yes, ma'am.
Where's Bauer?
Jack left the scene,
took Renee with him.
Hassan's death hit him
pretty hard.
Samir's been taken to Medical
to get patched up.
Is he conscious?
Barely.
You let me know the second
he's ready for questioning.
All right.
Put him through.
CTU. O'Brian.
This is Tim Woods
with Homeland Security.
Hold on. I'll put you through
to Mr. Hastings.
Oh, no. Actually, I'm calling
to speak with you, Ms. O'Brian.
Me? Are you sure?
I know this is
an unusual circumstance,
so I'll get straight
to the point.
President Taylor
and the foreign dignitaries
are returning to the UN shortly
where the president
will announce her intent
to move forward with the signing
of the peace agreement.
Well, excuse me,
but how can she do that
without President Hassan?
I'm not at liberty
to say just yet,
but our immediate concern
is whether CTU is capable
of handling security
for the rest of the process.
It's already been infiltrated
by an enemy agent,
compromised more
than once today.
We cannot have
any more mistakes.
Are you suggesting
I'm responsible
for those mistakes?
On the contrary.
I reviewed the hourly reports,
and from what I see,
you've made some astute calls,
and have proven
to be very resourceful
throughout this crisis.
Okay.
So why are you calling me?
I'm relieving Brian Hastings
of his post
effective immediately.
We're now in the process
of vetting suitable candidates
to replace him,
but until we find someone,
you'll have provisional command.
You're... You're putting me
in charge?
For the time being.
I know your record
at CTU's L.A. branch,
and how important you were
during the Sangala crisis.
There's nobody in that building
that has more experience
than you do.
Sir, you're making a mistake.
What happened
with President Hassan,
and everything else...
It wasn't Mr. Hastings' fault.
Chloe, I don't have time
to debate this with you.
Division feels
you are the most qualified
to step in, and I agree.
My decision's made.
Now accept it,
and let's move on.
Does Mr. Hastings know?
Division's informing him
as we speak.
Just try to make the transition
as quick and painless
as possible.
I'll be in touch
as soon as the president arrives
at the UN.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
Mr. Hastings?
It's okay, Chloe.
I just want you to know,
I don't think it's fair
what they're doing,
laying all the blame on you.
Everything that happens here
is my responsibility.
The successes and the failures.
I recruited Dana Walsh
into this agency,
so I let the snake
into the garden.
I need to review
protocols with you.
Let's not waste any time.
Did you live here long?
No. Just during my recovery.
You know, I still think
I got some coffee around here.
What's her name,
your granddaughter?
Teri.
Kim named her after her mom.
Jack, listen,
I know that we've said a lot
of things to each other,
and you've made promises
to me about...
I just
want you to know that I'm not
gonna hold you to them.
It's been
a terrible day, and I know
that we-we say things
in the moment, and I just...
I don't want you to...
Hello?
Somebody there?
Take my briefcase
to Marine One,
and tell the Secret Service
I'll be ready to leave shortly.
And send Mr. Novakovich in.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Novakovich.
Thank you for seeing
me, Madam President.
Not at all.
What can I do for you?
I just had a curious phone call
from Tim Woods
indicating that you are
intending to move forward
with the peace initiative
with the IRK.
That's correct.
May I ask
how you propose to do this,
considering
their leader is dead?
Well, I intended
to answer that question
during my address
to the Assembly,
but since you're asking...
Dalia Hassan will be signing
the agreement
in her husband's stead.
That's... an interesting idea,
Madam President,
but I don't see
how she would have the authority
to sign such a document.
She's getting it
from her government now.
Their parliament called
an emergency session
to ratify her
as provisional president.
The letter confirming that
is forthcoming.
Madam President,
I appreciate your optimism,
but I don't understand
how you can believe
that installing Hassan's widow
as some kind of figurehead
will alleviate our concerns
about the instability
of the IRK government.
With President Hassan dead,
the opposition
will only get stronger.
Hassan's death will galvanize
his supporters
and every advocate
of this peace process
to endorse her
as his successor.
You can't be certain of that.
Once again, Mr. Novakovich,
you're giving every indication
that Russia has no interest
in this peace accord.
I'm sorry that you feel
that way, Madam President,
but the fact remains
that we are no longer confident
that any meaningful progress
can be made.
Respectfully,
my country will be declining
to sign your peace document.
Excuse me.
Do I need to take this up
with President Suvarov myself?
If you like,
but I can assure you,
I have full authority
on this matter.
Any decision that I make
represents the formal position
of the Russian government.
Good day.
Agent Peters, I need
to see Secretary Kanin now.
Yes, Madam President.
Liberty's on the move.
We managed to clear a blockage in
one of your coronary arteries,
and the X-rays show
the heart muscle damage
to be less than we expected.
In other words,
I'm a tough son of a bitch.
You're a lucky man, I'll say
that for you, Mr. Secretary.
I guess that means
I can resume my duties.
Although the procedure
was noninvasive,
I'd prefer it if you
took it easy for a little while.
That isn't a no.
Hello, Ethan.
How are you feeling?
Well, uh, I've
seen better days.
Would you give us
a few moments, please?
Thank you.
You heard about Hassan?
Tim Woods told me.
He also filled me in
on the IRK plan
to install Dalia Hassan.
What do you think?
Her family's well
connected and powerful.
I think it's an inspired idea.
Well, the Russians don't.
Novakovich told me in no uncertain
terms they won't accept her.
They're using it as an excuse
to pull out of the signing.
Even if the IRK
has a new leader,
the peace agreement won't stand
without Moscow's endorsement.
I need your help, Ethan.
You got the Russians
to the table.
What can I do
to keep them there?
There may be someone
who can help us here.
But you're not gonna like it.
Who?
Charles Logan.
Logan?
Ethan, you can't be serious.
The man's a criminal.
I don't care if he was pardoned.
I didn't agree with President
Daniels' decision, either,
but the fact is he's left
several messages at my office
over the past hour.
Apparently, he's aware
of the Russians' reticence
in signing the agreement;
he's offered his assistance.
How could he possibly know about this?
Well, despite
his political downfall,
he's managed to maintain
a uniquely close relationship
with Moscow.
His messages indicated
he has information
which might prove useful
in keeping the
Russians at the table.
What information?
He didn't say.
Allison...
I don't trust this man
any more than you do,
but I'd be remiss
if I didn't urge you
to at least... hear him out.
Okay, listen up,
everyone, please.
I've never been very good
at good-byes.
But I want to tell you
what an honor it's been
for me to have served
with each and every one of you.
Division is now vetting names
to replace me.
In the meantime, Chloe O'Brian
will be in charge, and I'm sure
you will show her the same level
of loyalty and commitment
that you've all shown me.
Thank you.
Sir...
Aw, don't worry, Chloe,
you can do this.
I hope so.
I just want to say,
we had a rough start,
but I eventually
really enjoyed working for you.
Well, I'm happy to say
that I was wrong about you.
If I had listened to
you in the beginning,
maybe things would have
turned out differently.
I doubt it.
I'll be at Division debriefing.
But I'm available to you
if you have any questions.
Thank you, sir.
Good luck.
Mr. Hastings.
I have Agent Ortiz on the line.
They have a situation
in Medical.
This one's all yours, Chloe.
Ms. O'Brian.
Cole, it's Chloe.
Where's Hastings?
He's not here.
What happened?
Samir's just gone
into cardiac arrest.
What?
I need four
milligrams epinephrine
and 275 Lidocaine.
I'll be right there.
Clear!
Going again at 360.
What happened?
I thought his injuries
were not life-threatening.
So did I.
Where the hell is Hastings?
He's been removed by Division.
Who's in command?
I am... until they find
a replacement.
You were with Samir
the whole time?
All the way
from the scene, yeah.
What about at the scene?
He may have been out of
my sight for a few minutes.
Emergency personnel
were with him.
Look, we got to move his body
to the morgue for an autopsy.
Not yet... order
a preliminary toxicology panel.
But they'll run a full
panel during the autopsy.
I want it done now!
Chloe, he was barely conscious.
He couldn't have taken
something to off himself.
No, but somebody
could have given it to him.
Do what she says.
I'll be in Hastings' office...
my office.
Let me know when
you find something.
A few of the more conservative
members of our delegation
may continue to resist you,
but... we can...
we can persuade them.
Perhaps if I spoke
to them personally.
A very good idea.
Miss Kayla,
I didn't get a chance to tell
you how deeply sorry I am.
Thank you.
Well...
I will see you both
back at the U.N.
The U.N.?
I thought you were going home.
No, not yet.
There are new developments.
I'll explain them to you
on the way.
What is going on, Mother?
Why did President
Taylor and Jamot
want to speak with you alone?
They have asked me
to consider staying on...
to complete your father's work.
I don't understand...
what does that mean?
Our party wishes to appoint me
as the new president.
What was your answer?
You told them
you couldn't possibly accept,
not after what's happened.
Kayla!
Our country is
on the verge of a coup
by the people responsible
for the murder of your father.
Someone must lead.
You can't beat them,
don't you realize that by now?
I don't believe that; I won't.
And the greatest blow
I can strike against them
is to sign the peace agreement.
This will be
your father's legacy.
It will be
a death sentence for you!
You want peace to live,
but all these people want
is anarchy.
Oh, Mother, they'll kill you!
Enough!
You are not the only one
who has suffered today.
This was not
an easy decision for me,
but it was mine to make.
I do not need you
to remind me of the danger.
I need you to help me be strong.
Now, pull yourself together...
there is a car waiting for us.
Well, I'm sure the media does
want a response, but I'm not
ready to give them one
just yet.
They'll have to wait.
All right.
Thank you.
The press secretary says
the Russians are already
leaking to the news channels
their intention
to "reluctantly"
pull out of the talks.
They don't like wasting time.
Has my guest arrived?
Yes, ma'am.
I had Secret Service
bring him in
through the freight entrance
and then deliver him discreetly
to conference room number three,
as you asked.
Thank you, Tim.
Yes, ma'am.
Madam President,
let me convey my condolences
on the loss of President Hassan.
I know you worked
closely with him.
This must be very hard for you.
Thank you... for your
sympathy, Mr. President.
If you don't mind, I'd
like to talk to you alone.
This is my executive assistant,
Jason Pillar.
I assure you he can be trusted.
Well, forgive me
if I don't give much weight
to your endorsement.
He needs to leave.
Will you excuse us, Jason?
Let's get something straight.
I agreed to this meeting
only at the behest
of Secretary Kanin.
Now, I'm not sure you're
entirely aware of the situation.
My understanding is,
the Russians are
rejecting Dalia Hassan
as a legitimate successor,
and as a result, won't sign off
on the peace agreement.
You're well informed.
I have close friends in Moscow.
In some ways, people there
appreciate me more than
people in my own country.
It wasn't their constitution
you trampled.
The Russians
have been trying to back out
of this agreement from day one.
Do you honestly think
your relationships
can change their minds?
I'm certain I can.
How?
Let's just say
I'm going to be able
to exercise some leverage.
What kind of leverage?
If it gets the job done,
does it really matter?
It does to me.
I can promise you
no laws'll be broken,
nothing will tarnish you
or your presidency,
but the details really must stay
between me and the Russians.
You and President Hassan
created the framework
for the most significant peace
in a generation, and you got
the entire world behind it.
To let the Russians tear down
what should be the crown jewel
in your administration...
Don't play me.
This is about you
trying to repair
your reputation.
Is that so hard to understand?
You participated
in a conspiracy to cover up the
assassination of David Palmer.
I was trying
to protect the country
from an unnecessary trauma...
Don't! You were
doing what was best
for yourself.
Yes.
You're right, Madam President.
You're right.
I suppose I've spent
so many years
trying to justify my actions
that it's become difficult
for me...
to own up to the truth.
I made mistakes,
terrible mistakes, that stained
the office of the presidency...
and for which I will be paying
the rest of my life.
But I still can be
of value to my country.
I can still do some good.
Look, we both know you wouldn't
have called me unless
you were out of options,
so we can continue
to dwell on the past,
or you can let me pursue
the only chance you have
of resurrecting
the peace process.
Please.
Let me help you.
All right.
Thank you.
What do you intend to do first?
Arrange a meeting with
the Russian delegate Novakovich.
Uh, get a message
to him at his hotel.
Tell him that you are sending
over your official emissary
to have a talk with him.
What if he doesn't agree
to this meeting?
Make sure he knows it's me.
He'll agree to it.
God help you
if you make me regret this.
O'Brian.
You okay?
Perfect.
Promise?
Hmm.
I am so thirsty.
Me, too.
Do you want me to get you
something to drink?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Don't move.
Jack, your cell's ringing.
Don't worry about it, let it go.
Hello.
Jack's phone.
Renee, it's Chloe.
I need to talk to Jack.
What's wrong?
Samir Mehran is dead.
I think he was assassinated.
What do you mean, assassinated?
I ran a preliminary
toxicology report.
It showed traces
of an unidentified toxin
in his bloodstream.
Someone must have injected him
with it, probably at the scene.
There was,
there was an EMT there.
He looked familiar.
There was so much going on,
I-I didn't take much notice.
Familiar? From where?
I need you to get
my FBI case files.
Get me everything you have
on Red Square.
You think he was
from the Russian Mob?
He looked like somebody who
was with Vladimir Laitanan
during the time I was under.
That was six years ago.
Are you sure?
Honestly, no.
Just send me the case files,
all the surveillance photos
that were taken,
and I'll see if he's in there.
Okay.
Jack...
you need to hear this.
Samir...
Renee...
Renee!
Renee?
Come on. Come on.
Jack.
Renee, are you there?
Don't talk, I'm gonna
get you to a hospital.
Did something happen?
Who is this?
It's Chloe.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Renee's been hit by a sniper
through the window
of my apartment.
We're still taking fire.
I need a trauma team
at St. Andrew's now.
Hold on, stay with me.
Come on.
Let's go.
Keep everybody in the lobby.
There's a sniper outside.
Call 911.
Now!
Move!
She's been shot;
We need to get to the hospital...
St. Andrew's Hospital,
22nd and Ninth.
Come on, you can make it.
Wait... just wait...
We're gonna make it.
We're gonna make it, I promise.
Do whatever you have to!
We've got to get
to the hospital now!
Come on, come on.
I got you, I got you.
I got you.
You'll be all right.
We're almost there.
They're a few blocks
from your hospital
and should be there any minute.
Please make sure
she's given priority care.
Thank you.
Arlo,
pull up satellite.
Isolate the areas
between Eighth Avenue
and West 18th Street.
What's going on?
Renee Walker was just shot.
What?!
Just do what I asked.
Jack said the sniper
was positioned
at his apartment at 1145
West 18th Street.
Roll back the feed
three minutes.
Is she gonna be okay?
He's rushing her
to the hospital now.
I don't get it.
Why would anyone want
to kill Renee?
Help! She's been shot!
There's no exit wound!
We got a gunshot wound to
the chest... let's move.
What's her pulse?
110, respiratory
is still ragged.
Check her carotid.
BP is 80 over 50.
Right here.
What do we have?
Five is prepped.
We're gonna take care of you.
O.R. five, let's go.
How many gunshot wounds?
One in the chest.
Sir, you need to stay right here.
Is patient typing crossed?
No.
Call the blood bank, send up
four units of O-negative.
- Right away.
- Come on, come on, come on.
Yeah.
Jack, it's Chloe.
How is she?
Not good.
We rolled back satellite to
the area around your building.
The shots were fired
from an office
across the street.
PD reported finding a body
at the scene.
What about the shooter?
We don't have anything.
We lost him.
You were on the phone with her
right before she got shot.
What were you talking about?
It's not important right now.
Just...
be with her.
She's in surgery,
Chloe, I can't.
What were you talking about?
I told her what I'm
calling to tell you.
Samir Mehran was given a
lethal injection at the scene
of his capture, probably
to keep him from talking.
Renee thought she may have
recognized one of the EMTs.
She didn't say anything to me.
She wasn't sure.
She didn't think it meant
anything at the time.
Where did she say she
remembered him from?
From her days undercover
with the Russian Mob.
She asked me to get her
the Red Square file.
Did you pull up the file?
Yes.
Jack?
I gotta get back to you.
I'm sorry, she didn't make it.
There was just
too much arterial damage
and blood loss.
I'm very sorry.
Transcript By Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net