I have been looking
all over this
hospital for you.
All night? Because I've been
calling you all night.
I didn't get in
till 2:00 in the morning.
And I didn't
check my messages.
I... I was exhausted.
And now I have to get
you back to the airport.
I told you this
was a stupid idea.
Yeah. But you
didn't tell me
that Matt and Sarah were away.
I didn't know.
I assumed that you called them
before you called me
for a ticket.
Who's Carlos?
Who?
Carlos.
They guy you live with.
Oh.
Oh, all right. Okay.
Everyone else knows.
You might as well know, too.
Everyone knows?
I got married.
What?
I'll tell you about it
on the plane.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
What?
You're not...
I'm not what?
Nothing.
I'm ready to go.
Well, not ready.
But, considering
I have no choice,
I'm as ready as I'm going to be.
You know,
I'm actually
feeling a little better
since your news will actually
take the spotlight
off me for two minutes.
It's going to be okay, Simon.
No, it's not.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ When I see
their happy faces ♪
♪ Smiling back at me ♪
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ I know there's
no greater feeling ♪
♪ Than the love of family ♪
♪ Where can you go ♪
♪ When the world
don't treat you right? ♪
♪ The answer is home ♪
♪ That's the one place
that you'll find ♪
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ Mmm, 7th Heaven ♪
♪ 7th Heaven. ♪
(barks)
I'd better be going.
I'll be okay.
I know, I know.
You have to let go of me, Mom.
Next year,
you'll be in high school.
High school.
It's hard to believe.
And the boys will
be in kindergarten.
I bet they could use a hug.
And, next year,
Simon will be in college.
Unless, of course, allowing him
to transfer to another school
doesn't work out like
your father thinks it will.
He'll go to college.
He's Simon.
Maybe he'll even go this year.
I hope so.
I really do.
Simon is not going
to turn out like Mary,
if that's what
you're thinking.
That's what I was thinking.
Have you heard from him?
No. But Simon will
be on a plane with Mary,
and they'll be home tonight
for dinner.
Mary's coming home
tonight for dinner?
We haven't seen much of her
this summer. I miss her.
I wish she'd come back home.
I do, too, but I don't think
that's going to happen now.
Because she loves flying
so much.
I have to go.
That's not what
you were going to say.
I was just
simplifying it.
It's pretty much
what I was going to say.
And I've got school.
And I'm meeting with Peter
and... good-bye.
Wish me luck.
I have to get to class,
but I appreciate
your meeting me.
And I appreciate
everything you
said to me, Lucy,
but this is it.
Tonight's the night.
With or without Mary,
I'm telling your parents.
'Cause your family should know.
Mary told them that
she's coming home for dinner.
She's coming from the airport
with Simon.
She's my wife. We talk.
I know she's coming
from the airport with Simon.
But I also know
how many times
she planned
to come home
and have dinner at
your parents' house
and tell them,
only she never has.
And maybe she never will.
But I told her that
I was going to tell them
whether she showed up or not.
I want them to know.
Is there some reason
why it has to be now?
It should have been months ago.
But why now? Tonight?
Because it's now or never.
We need to talk.
I thought you
were on vacation.
Well, I decided
to work instead.
Why?
Because I need
to keep busy.
You've been doing
plenty of that.
What's wrong?
Did something happen
to your father?
No.
Did someone die?
No. No one died.
Chandler broke up with me.
Oh. Well, I'm
not surprised.
Why are you not surprised?
Because he loves you,
and wants to marry you,
and, for some reason, you
don't want to marry him,
even though I think
you love him.
Is that any reason
to break up with me?
Yeah, that's a reason.
If you don't want to get
married, and he does,
what'sa guy
supposed to do?
Just wait around until
you change your mind?
Maybe it's best if he
quits wasting his time
and gets over you
and moves on.
It isn't about
what you want
or don't want this time,
Roxanne.
It's about what he wants
and doesn't want.
Respect that.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
It's me.
I need to talk to you.
I need some time.
I don't.
Look, Roxanne, I love you,
but I don't think this
is going to work out.
Especially now that I know
that you don't want to marry me.
At any time in the near future.
Look, we agreed to spend some
time apart and think about this.
So that's what I want to do--
think.
I don't want to talk about it.
Sorry. I... I couldn't
help but overhear.
Did... What? Did
you and Roxanne...?
I don't want to talk to you
about it either, all right?
Please.
I can't stand to hear
"I told you so"
when my heart is breaking
into a million pieces.
I'm... I'm sorry, Chandler.
Look, I got
a really busy day.
I got to come up with another
high school for Simon to go to.
The family decided not
to go to trial,
but they're asking me
to get Simon out
of the same high school
their other son goes to.
For Simon's sake, and for his.
Since Simon desperately
wanted out,
well, I'm going
to do whatever I can,
as long as it's
to everyone's advantage.
Well, he could
test out of high school
if his SATs were
high enough last year.
If his grades are good enough.
He could work through the fall,
and go to college
in January or next fall.
And until then?
He can get some kind of job
until then.
Paid work to help with tuition,
or volunteer work.
The Youth Corps or something.
Hmm. No senior year?
I didn't have a senior year.
I got out the summer before,
and went to college.
I never regretted it.
I don't suppose I could get you
to come to my house for dinner.
Simon is supposed to be home
from New York by then,
and maybe you could talk to him,
you know, after I talk to Annie?
Sure, I'd love to.
It's not like I have any plans.
I hope Lucy's on
for our pizza night.
I can't wait to talk to someone
who's a little more sympathetic.
Is that tonight?
Yep. That's tonight.
I don't think she's
planning to go,
since you're supposed
to be at the beach.
Well, I 'm not at the beach,
so I want pizza night with Lucy.
We have a family dinner tonight.
Then I'll just have dinner
with her there,
and we'll talk afterward.
Tonight might not
be the best night.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the men's room,
okay?
Who are you calling?
Hello.
Hi. It's Roxanne.
Um...would it be all right if
I came over for dinner tonight?
Chandler and I just broke up,
and I really don't feel
like being alone,
and my dad is still
on his extended vacation,
and I really feel
like being with family,
and you're practically family,
and I need to speak with Lucy.
Of course you can come.
Thanks.
Um... can I bring anything?
No, just yourself.
See you around 7:00.
Is it my cooking?
Do you cook?
No. I'll see you at 7:00.
(ringing)
Hello.
Hi. It's me, Cecilia.
Is Simon still in New York?
Uh... well, he's...
he's on his way home.
He should be here
in time for dinner,
and Mary's coming with him.
Mrs. Camden, I've been trying
to talk Simon into coming back
to school.
Well, we all have.
But I think maybe
I was just being selfish.
Maybe he shouldn't
be here after all.
There's... a lot of talk.
Well, if you're talking
about the older brother,
and how upset he is, we heard
from the parents last night.
I didn't think
it would get this bad.
Well, we didn't either,
but Eric talked to Simon,
and they'll talk more
when he gets home.
Can I come over
and talk to him, too?
If you want, of course.
Are you angry with me for
driving Simon to the airport?
No, no.
It wasn't your decision.
We understand that.
But I know that Simon's
hurt your feelings,
and, you know,
I hope he didn't just use you
to get to the airport.
And I'd hate to have you come
over tonight
and have him be rude
to you again.
He has hurt my feelings.
But maybe because I've just
been pushing too hard.
Maybe I should just let go
and let him know that
I'm there if he needs me.
I think that's a good idea.
So, I'll see you for dinner.
And maybe Simon and I can
talk afterward. Bye.
Okay, bye.
What's for dinner?
Same thing we've been
eating all summer.
Trouble.
A big heaping bowl of trouble.
With a Mary on top.
Oh, I was hoping to
catch you in the shower.
Hmm, I could always
go back in.
Maybe later.
How was your day?
I got my schedule today.
It's not bad. No early
morning classes.
That's good news.
Oh, uh, I had coffee
with Carlos.
He's dropping by the
house tonight for dinner.
Hoping Mary will be there,
but even if she isn't--
Good. I hate keeping secrets.
You didn't ask Carlos if he
and Mary are pregnant did you?
No, but he didn't
say they aren't.
He didn't say Mary's
not pregnant.
I think you're wrong.
Not to change the subject, but
did you hear there's no trial
with the insurance companies?
When did that happen?
The kid's parents
decided against it.
But they want Simon
to stay out of school
so their older son doesn't
have to deal with him.
That's a shame,
because, sooner or later,
Simon and this guy will have
to deal with each other.
Mom and Dad just want
to give him some time.
Especially since
the parents asked
and Simon doesn't want to
face him right now anyway.
It might be good
for him to get away.
Give him a chance
to grow up a little.
I don't think he's going away.
He's just going
to another school.
Not to change the subject
because I do think
he'll end up going away,
But I have some
news for you, too.
Roxanne and Chandler broke up.
So that's why she's been
so anxious to see me.
(groans) And I haven't
even called her back.
I feel terrible.
(knocking on door)
ROXANNE:
Lucy?
Annie invited
me to dinner.
I'm so sorry.
I just heard.
What happened?
You really don't want
to get married?
I want to get married.
I just don't want to get married
right now.
And now that I've had
some time to think about it,
I don't think that I want
to be married to him.
That's the first time
I've said that out loud.
I just don't think
I'm cut out to be
a preacher's wife.
I mean, I'm not even good at
being a preacher's girlfriend.
The whole thing is
just so unnatural.
I don't know, I mean, I mean,
he's like this
holy man and I'm like...
I don't know, so unholy.
Um, are you staying for dinner?
Well, your mom invited me.
I thought maybe we could get
coffee and talk afterwards?
Do you think I'm unholy?
No, not exactly.
Not exactly?
What does that mean?
I-I don't know.
I don't know what unholy means.
Look, I really do
want to talk to you.
It's just that well,
tonight's dinner,
it might get
a little complicated.
Mary's coming home.
I know. She's bringing Simon
back from New York, right?
Is something going on with Mary?
Well...
Hi. I was wondering
the same thing.
Is something going on with Mary?
Annie invited me to dinner.
What's going on with Mary?
Without Simon,
I'm out of the loop.
Hi.
I guess you've heard.
I don't want to
talk about it.
Okay, but Roxanne is...
I don't want to talk about it.
...in our apartment
talking to Lucy.
(sighing)
You're staying?
I was invited so,
yes, I'm staying.
You know, Mary is
going to be here.
And?
And I know Eric wants
to discuss some things.
Family things, with Simon.
Oh, I know that.
That's how I got invited.
I'm supposed to talk to Simon
after Eric is finished
talking to Annie.
Well, there are some things
going on in Mary's life that...
may actually overshadow the
things going on in Simon's life.
At least just tonight.
What could possibly overshadow
what's going on in Simon's life?
You're here on a
historic night, you know.
I know. I'm a little nervous.
I am, too, but you know,
the flip side
of nervousness is excitement.
Believe me, I feel guilty
feeling anything but horrible
after that accident.
But, as of today,
life is starting
to move on for all of us.
And we need that.
So, we may as well
get excited about it.
What happens if your parents
don't take Mary's big news well?
What if they're not
at all excited about it?
And what if it's the straw
that breaks the Camden's back?
There is no such straw.
We're a family.
Everything will be fine.
Okay, everything may
not be fine tonight,
but eventually--
Are you sure she's
going to have a baby?
I'm not sure,
but Lucy and I think so.
What does Kevin think?
Kevin's a guy.
I'm a guy, too.
And I think you're
jumping to conclusions.
Want to bet?
I can't take
your money, sweetheart.
No.
What?
(doorbell ringing)
Can I do anything else?
Well, you can
get the door
and if it's anyone
else for dinner,
the inn is full.
(knocking on door)
Hi.
Um, I don't know
if you remember me.
At Christmas
a couple years back?
Mary met you at the shelter.
We sent you home
to your family.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, come in.
Come in.
Thank you.
How are you?
I'm fine.
It's Carlos.
Kevin, Chandler,
this is Carlos.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Excuse us.
So, it's been a long time.
How's your family?
Good, good, the family's good.
Getting bigger every day.
Our family, too, yeah.
Lucy got married last April.
You remember Lucy?
Yeah.
Carlos is in the living room.
I think Dad wants you
in the living room.
Why, who was at the door?
All:
Carlos!
ALL:
The homeless guy that Mary
brought home one Christmas?
ALL:
Carlos is in the living room.
LUCY, ROXANNE, CECILIA:
Now?
What's going on?
ALL:
Nothing.
What do you know
that I don't know?
So, are you working?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm working.
I've been very fortunate
that my father
brought me back
into the family business.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah. I can't tell you
how much it means to me
to be part of the family
and the family business.
And the family.
Yeah, yeah.
'Cause family is so important.
Maybe the most important
thing in life.
You're right.
And if you don't have a family,
th-then you can make a family.
But hopefully you have a family.
And sometimes
one person's family
and another person's family,
they come together
and they make
a very big, happy family.
Hey, Happy.
Hey, girl!
Excuse me.
Mary! Simon!
Oh, it's so good to see you!
We should talk.
But after I talk
to your mom.
Hi!
We've missed you.
Oh! Do you remember
Simon and Mary?
Oh, yeah.
Oh this is wonderful.
Hey, Mom.
Oh, Mary!
Simon, no more running away.
We want you home with us.
You scared me.
You remember Carlos,
don't you, honey?
Of course, Christmas.
A few years ago. Mary
brought him home. Hi.
Nice to see you.
MARY:
Hey, you guys, hi!
Well, actually, um,
Carlos and I...
We ran into each
other in New York.
When he was at the airport
picking up his brother.
Carlos:
Right. And, uh, we
remembered each other
from that very wonderful
Christmas I spent here.
MARY:
And so I went out
with him and his brother.
And then she went
out with just me.
And we went out
several times.
Oh! S-So
you're dating?!
Well, that's great,
you know? Good for you.
You can tell us all
about it over dinner.
Let's go.
Carlos:
Uh, we
were dating.
A lot.
And, well...
And... now you're not dating.
It's okay.
It happens.
Well, not exactly,
Reverend Camden.
Mrs. Camden,
I've been trying
to tell you this for
several months now, but--
But I wouldn't let him
because-because I got scared.
And I wanted to
change my mind.
But then all this
happened with the accident
and then this whole
crazy summer
and I changed my mind
about changing my mind.
And, uh... we're...
You're not...
you're not dating?
Are you two engaged?
You're engaged?
They're engaged.
Ah...
Please don't hate me.
We could never
hate you, ever.
No matter what,
we-we love you.
So let's eat.
Carlos and I got married
last April a week
after Lucy and Kevin.
I was going to have
the marriage annulled,
but-- not because
I don't love him,
because I was so
afraid to tell you.
And I thought
that, you know,
if I could undo what
we'd-- what we'd done,
then we could redo it.
And-and you guys could get used
to the idea for a little bit
and I could have time
to get used to the idea.
Annulled?
Well, I just
thought about it.
Well, you didn't
tell me about it.
Well, I couldn't because
I didn't really want to.
No, but you
thought about it?
I panicked!
Why?
Just because.
Can I have a few minutes
alone with, uh,
with my wife?
Please?
Don't leave.
No. There are things
I need to say to you
that I don't care to say
in front of your parents.
I know.
That's why I want them here.
Well, this is not about them.
It's about you and I.
So, you were saying?
An annulment?
(speaking Spanish)
Loca, loca...
I know what you're saying.
Not unless your Spanish
has improved greatly.
Something about a chicken?
I wasn't chicken.
I just didn't want to hurt them.
I didn't say anything
about a chicken.
Loco?
El Pollo Loco--
it's a chicken place.
El Pollo Loco means
"the crazy chicken."
And I said you were
crazy not chicken.
Why would people
eat crazy chickens?
So you think I'm crazy?
Yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
You're calling your wife
and the mother
of your future children crazy?
Yes.
(speaking Spanish)
I love you, too.
Hey, your Spanish
is getting better.
♪ ♪
So if Mary was, you know...
she would have told them.
No, she wouldn't have.
She would let them
get used to one idea
then spring it on them.
Where is everyone anyway?
No one's hungry.
Except for us.
We're very hungry.
Is Mary really married?
Yes, she is.
Why didn't they
have a wedding?
They had one,
but no one was there.
Not even them?
Mary and Carlos were there.
Just none of the Camdens
were there.
Why not?
Sometimes people don't want
their families at the wedding.
Why not?
Because sometimes families
can make it complicated.
And Mary and Carlos are
already pretty complicated.
What do you mean by that?
Yeah. What do you mean?
Well... they're from
different backgrounds,
different religions and--
And they might be...
No, they're not.
Are we doing
the right thing?
Taking a break?
I think maybe we are.
I'm sorry if I misled you.
What does that mean?
I can't marry you.
I can't be a preacher's wife.
I'm not a
preacher's wife type.
That's it?
That's all that's keeping
you from marrying me?
Honestly?
No.
I knew I didn't want to get
married from the beginning.
It was just really fun
to think of all this stuff.
The wedding, moving in together,
having babies.
Why do we have to get married?
Why do we ever have
to get married?
Believe me-- we don't.
Does this mean we
can still be friends?
Can I still come over here
and see your family
and call you on
the phone, and...
We were friends before we got
into this relationship Simon.
We can be friends.
Can't we?
Some day.
But not right now.
I can't be a friend
to anyone right now.
I'm sorry.
I just have
to focus on me
right now and I have
to get out of here.
I'm going to miss you
at school, Simon.
I'm going to miss
you everywhere.
Shouldn't you be inside
with Mom?
She wanted to lie down.
She needs some
time to think.
And you don't?
What's to think about?
Our little Mary is
married evidently.
And hopefully, it's not
just her first marriage.
Hopefully, she'll be
very happy and so will he
for the rest of
their stupid lives.
I knew you weren't happy.
I just didn't know
if it was them or me.
I haven't had a chance
to talk to your mom yet.
Well, actually I haven't had the
nerve to talk to your mom yet.
Here's the thing.
Instead of going
through the torture
of transferring--
as you put it--
it might be possible
to test out.
And instead go
to a community college.
I think the testing
part sounds great.
I think I could do a little more
than community college though.
I want to go to...
to a real college.
What do you mean
by a real college?
I mean I want to
go to a college,
far, far away from here.
I thought maybe you
would want to be
home with your family,
around people who
love and care about you.
I've been around people who love
and care about me all summer.
Look, I know everyone feels
badly about the accident.
The fact that anyone
feels bad for me
after what I did, it's--
Dad, it's making me crazy.
Simon...
It was an accident,
I don't care.
You know, I
couldn't feel worse
if I had done it--
if it had been intentional.
Dad, I've heard everything
you've said to me.
I know it's a process.
I... know it might be
a life-long process, Dad,
but this is a process that I
have to go through on my own.
Might be a little easier
with your friends and family,
maybe even your girlfriend?
I don't want dealing
with this to be easy.
I want it to be hard.
Besides, Cecilia... (sighs)
she's finally letting go...
for now.
Simon, don't keep
punishing yourself.
I-I swear I'm not
punishing myself, Dad.
I'm just, I'm trying
to find some meaning
in what happened, you know?
If there's no meaning,
then maybe there's something,
something that comes
from it, you know,
like a, a greater
understanding of life?
Dad, I don't know.
Something.
Maybe I could help you
if you'd let me.
Cecilia told me about the church
sign on the way to the airport.
(groans)
I was gonna tell you.
But you didn't.
Surgeons... shouldn't operate
on their own families, Dad.
And I'm in somewhat dire need
for a surgery
that, that you can't do for me.
So let me go away and get
my help somewhere else.
We were just talking about
letting you get out
of high school a year early.
And that was it.
I'm not ready
to let you go away, Simon,
and I know your mom's
not ready.
You're 17.
You're only 17.
I know... but I'm ready.
Oh, please, Dad?
Sooner or later, I'm gonna
have to talk to Justin.
Maybe not this week.
Maybe not this month,
and maybe not even this year.
But when we eventually find
ourselves face-to-face...
I'm gonna need to be ready
to hear how much he hates me.
And I'm gonna  need to be ready
to say something back to him.
Something more than
"I'm sorry" and "I understand."
And I don't think I can get
ready for that
just by hanging around
with my family,
waiting for that eventual
confrontation.
I have to
get away, Dad.
I have to confront myself.
I'm not even sure who I am.
But I am sure...
I'm sorry about that kid.
You know, Dad, I'm so,
I'm so horribly sorry.
(sighs)
Now I'm starving.
Me, too.
You want to go and see
if we can steal some dinner,
or do you want me
to go get us something?
Anything you want.
Kevin?
Lucy?
I don't want
to have a baby.
I know we've been talking
about it a lot.
and talking about
it's really fun,
but the reality of it,
well, that's something else.
Yeah, I know, but...
But when I graduate college
and when I've had time
to start my career
and when we're settled
into a place of our own
and when we've spent time
together, just the two of us,
and when we feel
that we can be responsible
for the life
of a new human being,
then I would love
to have a baby with you.
Whenever you're ready.
What changed your mind?
Was it something Roxanne said?
No, actually,
it was seeing Mary.
I still think
they've got a reason
for telling Mom and Dad
they're married.
I think they're pregnant
even if you don't.
And I was thinking
about how I want
to tell you when we're pregnant
and how we'd tell our families.
I want it to be a wonderful
moment, not a scary one.
Do you really think
they're pregnant?
Yes, and I bet she
hasn't told Carlos.
But I bet he already knows.
Oh, what happened to her?
Straight-A student
headed for college
with a basketball scholarship,
and then out of nowhere breaks
into the high school gymnasium.
The next thing you know,
she's an airline attendant
married to some guy
that we don't know.
What happened?
I don't know.
But maybe marriage
will be good for her.
It was
a rhetorical question.
Just the same,
you know,
it might be
good for her.
No, it won't.
Did the twins eat?
Yeah, they ate
with Ruthie and Peter.
What about Simon?
Not yet, but he will.
He's too thin.
I'll make sure
he eats something.
Just make sure
he doesn't leave home
and end up married
to someone we don't know.
And especially make sure
he doesn't leave home.
He's going nowhere
until he finishes college.
It-It's-It's gonna be
fine, Annie, I promise.
I know,
I... I know.
Just pray that Mary
isn't pregnant.
Pray that that's not the reason
she didn't get an annulment.
Pray that's not why she's
telling us she's married.
She's not ready to have a baby.
Who said anything
about having a baby?
Maybe they're waiting for us
to come to them.
No, they'll come
to us, believe me.
When they're ready,
they will find us and
they will talk to us.
We'll cry,
we'll laugh.
(both chuckle)
I hope so.
Okay, speaking
of laughs,
I have something
funny to tell you.
Go ahead.
I can't wait to hear it.
Okay, remember when I
was out here last May?
Right.
When you were out here
last May for...
for the annulment?
Okay, I told you.
I just thought it
would just be easier
if we backed up and
then got married.
Yes.
So you were out here
last May to get us backed up,
so that we can
get married again...
I scared myself, okay?
Okay, okay,
so you were out here last May.
This is not working out
like I planned.
First of all, you don't plan.
And secondly, what?
What's not working out?
Our marriage?
Because I love you.
I love being married to you.
I love being married
to you, too.
I-I meant that I had planned
to tell you something.
I rehearsed it.
And now I can't,
I can't seem to say it.
What, you rehearse
your conversations now?
How do you do it?
How do you know what the other
person's gonna say?
I make it up!
Mm-hmm, so you rehearsed
the conversation
about the annulment?
'Cause I'm dying to know
what I had to say about that.
I knew you weren't over it.
No, I, I am, I am.
I'm over it.
It's just, you know,
how does it work?
I mean, it must be really
difficult not knowing
what the other person's
gonna say, no?
I'm trying
to tell you something.
Okay, okay, fine, fine.
I am sorry.
Please, go ahead and tell me
whatever it is
you have to tell me.
Oh, no, just forget it.
I'll tell you later.
Are you sure?
Maybe you want to say it now
so you don't surprise me
in front
of your whole family again.
Do you know something?
Tell me.
Please tell me.
You know, don't you?!
All I know is that I love you.
How do you know?
Just say it!
I can't.
Why?
Because once I say it,
it'll be true.
And I want it to be true.
We're gonna have a baby.
Yes!
Oh, yes.
Oh...
Soy una gallina loca
embarazada.
(both laugh)
www.tvsubtitles.net