TWINS:
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Hi, guys.
(dog whines)
How you doing?
I'm okay. How are you?
Okay.
As okay as any of us.
Looks like it's going
to be a nice day today.
Where's Simon?
Please, it's the last day
of vacation.
Simon...
I don't want
to be on vacation.
I don't want to have
a picnic on the beach.
I'm gonna keep saying
this to you
until I get through to you:
it was an accident.
(sighs)
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ When I see
their happy faces ♪
♪ Smiling back at me ♪
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ I know there's
no greater feeling ♪
♪ Than the love of family ♪
♪ Where can you go ♪
♪ When the world
don't treat you right? ♪
♪ The answer is home ♪
♪ That's the one place
that you'll find ♪
♪ 7th Heaven ♪
♪ Mmm, 7th Heaven ♪
♪ 7th Heaven. ♪
(barks)
♪ ♪
(both laugh)
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's been a tough summer.
You know, ever
since you told me
you thought that you
might be pregnant,
I felt really happy,
not that you
weren't pregnant,
but because you
will be someday.
Someday, you and I will
have children together,
and I can't wait.
Well I'm afraid
you're gonna have to.
We're due downstairs
for some more family fun.
What do you think?
About?
About having children?
I still have two years
of school left.
I think we'd better wait
until I get out of school.
If that's what you want.
It's not what I want.
What I want is to have a baby.
I haven't been able to stop
thinking about it
ever since the scare either.
No, we can't.
We really can't.
I could baby-sit
while you go to class.
(chuckles)
No, I could.
Are you serious?
You want to have a baby?
I need something life-affirming.
We all do.
Do you have any kings?
N... no.
Yes, he does.
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
If you have a card
with a king on it,
you have to give it to Ruthie.
I'm sure.
Sorry this is the last day
of vacation.
It's been really fun.
This is the best
vacation I've ever had.
I'm really glad you came.
I'm really glad you invited me.
(boys making kissing sounds)
Why you guys want
to give me a hard time huh?
Because we love you.
We love you.
And you love Ruthie.
You love Ruthie.
(making kissing sounds)
(boys laughing)
I just wish I didn't feel so
guilty about having a good time.
I feel badly for Simon, too,
but I'm still having
a good time.
What are you doing here?
Uh, I was wondering
what you were
doing here.
We have the house until Sunday.
Uh, you had the house
till Saturday,
and it's, uh, late Saturday.
And we're here
because it's our turn.
We're not going home
until tomorrow.
What about church?
We'll be home in time
for church.
You said you wanted
to be home for the weekend.
Did I? Uh, I meant I wanted
to be home for Sunday.
Well, it's a very long drive.
We just can't turn around
and go back.
No, no, of course not.
Uh, come on in.
Oh, no, no,
I don't want
to spoil your last night here,
which was supposed
to be last night.
I wouldn't want to spoil
your first night here,
which is supposed
to be tomorrow night.
ROXANNE:
How are you doing?
How do you think I'm doing?
I was just making
polite conversation.
But if you want to, we can talk.
I've been worried
about you.
I wish everyone would stop
worrying about me.
It just makes it worse.
To have people care about you?
I don't want
anybody to care about me.
Not even Cecilia?
No, not even Cecilia.
Simon, don't do this
to yourself.
I killed someone.
And don't say it
was an accident...
Because it was an accident
that happened
when I was driving.
I'm responsible
for killing someone.
How's he doing?
Not so well.
When do you go to court?
Next week.
Unless our insurance company
settles,
and they don't want to settle.
Does Simon have to go?
He doesn't have to go.
but I think he should.
It was an accident.
Look, I almost forgot why
you were on this vacation.
Roxanne and I will get a hotel
and we'll come back tomorrow.
No, you should just stay here.
No, you spend your last night
with your family, all right?
I'm sorry about the mix-up.
No, there are plenty of rooms
here for everyone.
There's a room for you...
and a room for Roxanne.
Unless, of course,
you decide
to get married tonight.
Ah, we'll just leave
and come back.
Come back married?
I don't want to get
into this right now... again.
Okay. No judgment.
You don't know
that we're doing anything.
She's not sure if she wants
to get married right now.
Depends on whether or not
the fun lasts?
What time are you leaving
tomorrow?
No matter when we leave,
whether we're here or not,
God knows what you're doing.
God does, but none of you do.
We're hungry.
Yeah, we're hungry.
You just ate.
The beach makes me
hungry all the time.
When are we eating dinner?
In an hour
or so. How about a snack?
What's for dinner?
Whatever your mom wants to cook.
She's sleeping.
If she sleeps until tomorrow
morning, we won't have dinner.
Well, she won't do that.
She only did that once,
and we still ate, didn't we?
There's nothing wrong with
banana sandwiches for dinner.
We're at the beach.
We're on vacation.
Oh, I get it, you want me
to drive you somewhere
and get you something to eat.
Something good.
In case there's no dinner.
Okay, come on.
I'm taking
Sam and David to
Captain Crabby's
Crab House
for a snack. You want to go?
You hungry already?
No, but they're hungry.
I'll take 'em.
Forget it.
What?
Because I saw the look
on your face, Dad, that's why.
If it was just an accident,
then why are you so scared to
let Sam and David drive with me?
Why is everyone frightened every
time I get behind the wheel?
That's not true.
I wasn't going that fast, Dad.
I wasn't going any faster
than anyone else.
I didn't see him okay?
I didn't see him.
He came out of nowhere.
We heard Simon.
I'll go talk to him.
No, let me go this time.
I think
it's my turn.
No. it's not your turn.
You've had
too many turns.
This hasn't even been
a vacation for you.
BOTH:
I thought we were going
to Captain Crabby's.
I'll take 'em.
Kevin can talk to Simon,
and you should get a nap.
This is your last afternoon
to get a nap.
Come on, guys.
I hear they're giving away
free pirate hats.
Want to go?
All right, let's go!
I don't know how we're
gonna get him through this.
I don't know how
we're gonna get us
and the rest of our
family through this.
(sleepy murmuring)
It's okay. I-I, I
wasn't talking to her.
I was talking to You.
I'll be right here.
♪ ♪
My gosh. I'll get dinner.
We already had dinner.
Would you like something?
Uh...
Mom and I made vegetable
soup and cornbread,
and we saved
you a brownie.
Annie came down?
Then she went back up.
Well, that, that's good.
Then she hasn't been asleep for
the 12 hours I thought she had.
I'll get you some soup.
I got it.
What time
did the twins pass out?
PETER:
11:30.
More like 8:30.
Well, you know,
I'll take them upstairs.
I'll take them up.
Oh. Okay.
By the way,
Cecilia's here.
She just got here.
How's that going?
Not that well.
They took it down to
the beach, though.
If I wanted to talk to you,
I would have called you.
You shouldn't have driven
all the way down here.
I had to. I can't stand
knowing you're in so much pain
and not being able to be
with you and talk to you.
It's been three months.
How many times do
I have to say it?
I don't want
to talk to you.
I don't want to
talk to anyone.
Then fine, we won't talk,
but can't I just be with you?
No.
Look, just... just stay away.
Okay? Find a new boyfriend,
someone people don't hate.
People don't hate you.
It was an accident.
Everyone knows
it was an accident.
Doesn't matter.
School starts on Monday
and it's gonna be
a living hell for me.
Why make it
the same way for yourself?
You're better
off without me.
What?
You think I'm feeling
sorry for myself?
'Cause I'm not!
I'm feeling sorry
for the kid I ran over
and his brother and his parents.
I'm sure
Justin is grieving
for his brother, Simon,
but he's been in school
with you for four years.
He knows you're not a bad guy.
He knows you didn't
mean to do it.
Really?
Do you think he's
that understanding?
Do you think anyone's
Because if it
had been me
and some guy and his car had
come along and hit Ruthie,
you think I just would
have went up to him at school
and said, "It's okay, I know
you didn't mean to do it"?
(telephone ringing)
Hello?
Yes, this is Officer Kinkirk.
Is that you, Detective Michaels?
I'll let Eric know.
He can decide how he
wants to handle it.
Thanks for finding me.
Good night.
(sighs)
Okay, make it snappy.
Church starts
in one hour.
Come on, babes.
(clearing throat)
I'm just gonna help
Ruthie take her stuff up.
(telephone ringing)
Hello.
How'd it go?
We had it cleaned up by sunrise.
I don't think too
many people saw it.
Really?
Even if people did see it,
they wouldn't just, er... call
and tell Simon, do you think?
(sighs)
Well, I'll talk
to him after church.
I probably won't make it.
I'm gonna come home
and get some sleep.
I understand.
Thanks.
What?
We found out who painted
the church sign,
not that it was too
hard to figure out.
The kid's brother, Justin?
Yeah.
Have the Camdens considered
having Simon transfer
to another school?
Eric's been
working on it,
but Simon doesn't
want a transfer.
He doesn't want to
go to school, period.
When's the trial start?
Jury selection begins tomorrow.
Trial will probably start
Tuesday or Wednesday.
I can't understand why
the insurance company
doesn't just pay.
The family wants more
than they want to pay.
No matter how much they get,
it won't bring their son back.
I just wish it hadn't
have been Simon.
But it was, and nothing we
can do can change that.
How are we
gonna do that?
Why are you asking me?
Then I'm gonna take
the shower first?
Yes, and then
I'll shower.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I mean, we were just
discussing some things.
Showering and things.
I don't want to go
to church today.
I've gone
every Sunday
all summer.
I don't want to go today.
I want to stay home and I want
some time to myself.
I need some time to myself.
Okay.
Okay?
Its okay I don't go to church?
Is there a reason its okay
I don't go to church?
You just said you needed
some time to yourself.
But do you have a reason?
You know, fine.
I don't need a reason.
See ya.
Shouldn't you be
getting ready for church?
Yeah, I am as soon as
Annie's out of the shower.
Did you tell Simon?
No, I didn't
tell Simon.
Maybe you should
before someone else does.
After church.
I'll tell him after church.
What happens if
someone else tells
him at church?
Simon's not going to church.
Neither am I.
Kevin's been up all night
and I just want to be there
for him when he gets home.
You can't be there
for him after church?
What does that mean?
It means you got
the rest of your lives
and today is Sunday...
What if Simon needs
someone and no one's home?
It's been a tough summer
and Kevin and I need some
time to do something...
live-affirming.
Like?
You're not thinking of doing
something life-affirming
like, uh... having
a baby, are you?
What would make
you think that?
I just think that.
You have plenty
of time to have a baby
after you finish school.
It's been a hard summer
for all of us.
We all need something
life-affirming,
and I'm sure God
will provide in ways
other than... children
being born to mothers
who are still in college
and who want
to finish their degree
before starting a family.
All right, already.
I'll go.
We really could use a little...
uplifting distraction, You know.
Uh... Look, dealer's choice.
I'm going home now!
I'll see you
in church!
I'm surprised he doesn't keep
a change of clothes
in the house.
Call if you need a ride!
I need more of a
life-affirming distraction
than dealing with teen love.
Just...
Peter! You forgot your bag!
Uh!
Sorry.
I was just
trying to get up the nerve
to knock on the front door.
Don't I know you from somewhere?
Do you remember that Christmas
when your sister, Mary,
brought me home
from the shelter?
And then your family
helped me return to New York
to my own family?
Barely. So you're just
here to thank us?
Well, not exactly.
It's Carlos, isn't it?
Yes. Yes, and if I remember
correctly, you're Ruthie.
Only...
when I knew you then,
you were just a little girl
and now you're a young woman.
A young woman chasing
after a young man.
Sorry. Don't let me stop you.
This can wait.
It's waited all summer.
No. This bag can wait.
Please.
Sit down. Let's talk.
Oh.
And not necessarily
a distraction.
Maybe something real.
Something wonderful
that would lift us all.
Heal us all.
Maybe if I could rise above the
darkness that's fallen over us
for an entire season...
maybe I could do something
to help Simon.
Maybe I could help
that family in their grief.
Anything, I'll take anything.
Shower's free.
That's a start.
I love you and I want
to marry you.
And it's just not enough
just to be with you.
I want us to be
husband and wife.
I'm sorry about your dad.
Come on, Roxanne,
this has nothing to do
with my father dying.
It's about me and you.
I just can't help but
feel you want a family
because of what happened.
And I just can't help but feel
that you keep using
this as an excuse.
Knowing that I wanted
to marry you
before I even knew
my father was sick.
This is not about what anyone
thinks of me or thinks of you
or anything other
than that I love you,
and I want to marry you,
and I want to have babies
with you.
And-and-and...
And I want to keep doing this
for the rest of our lives.
I'll be here when
you get home.
Wake me up.
Definitely.
By the way,
who is that guy
I saw on the front porch
talking to Ruthie?
Ruthie's talking to a guy
on the front porch?
Tall guy, my age,
maybe younger--
I didn't get a good look.
Oh, you know,
it might have been
what's his name, Carlos.
So you've been keeping a
little secret from me, huh?
(clearing throat)
Oh yeah, nice sermon.
I'm just going to say
good-bye to Ruthie.
She was kind of quiet
in church.
That's the way
it's supposed to be.
It's a place of worship.
A lot of talk going
around just the same,
even though
it's a place of worship.
Someone painted
the church sign last night.
Simon know?
No, but I plan to tell him
so I hope no one else
will tell him first.
Not to worry.
I won't say anything.
Not even to Ruthie?
She already knows.
It wasn't me.
She overheard what I overheard.
What else are people saying?
They feel really badly
for that kid's family.
But they also feel badly
for Simon and your family.
What else?
Everyone thinks Chandler and
Roxanne should get married.
Or he should break up
with that hussy.
I'm quoting.
It was some older women talking.
They use words
like that-- hussy.
Are they calling Chandler
any names?
No, they seem to like him.
Anything else?
Well, they were talking
about Mary,
but they're always talking
about Mary.
I think she may be
the most popular person
on the church gossip circuit.
Yeah, so what's the gossip now?
They're just
wondering why
she hasn't been around
all summer.
You know with everything
happening to Simon and all.
Why do they think
she hasn't been around?
There are lots of theories.
My favorite is that she's a spy.
For?
France.
Yeah.
Makes as much sense
as anything else.
How is it that you hear all
this stuff and I don't?
Just always at the right place
at the right time I guess.
You know you can't
keep a secret.
Yes, I can.
I know stuff, okay?
What stuff?
If I told you I would be
proving your point,
and if I don't tell you,
I'll be proving my point.
How did you get him to tell you?
One, I'm me and two, he's
ready to tell the world.
Mary doesn't want
to be married.
She wants an annulment.
An annulment?
When's the last time
you talked to her?
Why?
Because maybe she
changed her mind.
Why would she change her mind?
Isn't it obvious?
(knocking)
Hey, we missed you
in church today.
You can come even
when Simon doesn't.
We're always happy
to have you there.
You okay?
I'm not sure.
I might have done something
really, really bad.
You want to tell
me about it?
Yes, that's why I'm here--
to tell you about it.
Is Simon upstairs?
Do you know where Simon is?
You know neither Annie nor I
are in a good place
right now emotionally.
We're both
rather exhausted.
But I'm in a better place
than she is
and I'd say she'll be down here
momentarily
to make lunch for everyone.
I took him to the airport.
The airport?
Why?
Because he asked me to
and I love him,
and I would do anything for him.
Do you happen to know
if he'll be back in time
for school tomorrow?
I don't think so.
He's going to New York
to see Matt.
Who is going to New York
to see Matt?
Simon.
I left my Bible.
Always in the right place
at the right time again?
It's a curse.
So what's the plan?
I'll let you know.
You'll let me know?
I don't think so.
I'll let you know
after I talk to Mary.
After I talk to Carlos.
He can't go to New York.
He's got school tomorrow.
Wait! Wait!
I want to talk to you!
What else do you know?
What else?
You overheard the conversation
about Simon going to New York.
Honest, I didn't mean to.
What else didn't
you mean to hear?
What do you mean?
I mean you found out something
when you were up
in the attic, didn't you?
Whoa, what do you have
like super powers?
Some days, yes.
Now what was it?
I can't, Reverend Camden.
Trust me, I can't.
It would mean the end of my
relationship with Ruthie
and that would mean the end
of my world as I know it.
Meeting Ruthie,
being with this family,
is the best thing
that's happened to me
since my dad left.
Please, please don't
ask me to tell you.
No, no, I won't ask you, Peter.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
It's okay.
You can go home now.
I didn't mean
to frighten you.
I apologize for even asking
you to tell me something
that obviously my daughter
or daughters--
don't want me to know.
Thanks, Reverend.
Oh.
and just so you know,
it's daughters.
You said daughter or daughters
don't want you to know.
Oh, so it's both of them.
It's all three of them?
You were saying Simon's
on his way to New York?
I just wanted to say good-bye
to Peter.
I'll call Matt.
What good is that going to do?
Well, Matt will make
him come home.
Who is he the Wizard of Oz?
Well, what do you
want me to do?
Well, I want you
to go and get him.
You want me to go
all the way to New York
when Matt can just
put Simon back on the plane?
One of us is going!
It's not going to be me!
Well, it's not going
to be me either.
We've been waiting all
summer long to have a fight
so why don't we
just have it now,
while Simon is
out of the house?
Oh, so that's what
you've been waiting for--
Simon to get out of the house.
Couldn't you have just asked
him to get out of the house
so you could say to me
whatever it is
you wanted to say
to me since May?
I know what you
want to say to me!
You want to say
it's my fault.
That if I had left with
the rest of the family
that I would have
been driving
and Paul Smith would
still be alive.
Isn't that what you want to say?
That you blame me for this?
What if I had left
with the family?
What if I had been driving?
What if I had
killed Paul Smith?
What if it were me
instead of Simon?
What if it never happened--
if I'd been driving
this never would
have happened, right?
Annie, we can't
afford to play what if.
We have to stay
with what is,
and what is, is our
son was driving
when he came around a curve
and Paul Smith wasn't
looking where he was going.
And now-- one life is changed
forever and one life is over.
We're the lucky ones, Annie.
We're the lucky ones.
Simon's life may be changed
forever, but he's still alive.
All I wanted to say was
why couldn't those
parents make sure
that their son was
wearing a helmet?
We have a problem.
Okay.
She knows.
RUTHIE:
Carlos is waiting
for me to call him
and tell him
when he can come over
and talk to Mom and Dad.
Okay.
Okay?
Don't you think it's
about time they knew?
Don't you think it should
be Mary who tells them?
I think she's not
going to tell them
and somebody is going
to have to tell them
before everyone knows but them.
Let Carlos tell them.
Then I should
at least warn them.
And how are you
going to do that?
KEVIN:
This is between
Carlos and Mary
and your mom and dad
and if Carlos wants to
tell them, let him tell them.
Then I think you
should be there
because they don't
need any more bad news.
KEVIN:
I don't think this is
necessarily bad news, is it?
Why do you think he's in
such a rush to tell them?
Yeah. Why now?
Why? Because it's been months
since they got married.
Don't you think you're
being a little naïve?
We think that
maybe they're--
Don't even say it.
That's ridiculous.
They're not pregnant.
Marry me.
You know I'm going
to marry you.
You've been saying that
you're going to marry me,
but I want to know for certain
that you're going to marry me.
I want to buy you a ring.
I want to set a date.
All right.
How's next May or June
or August or a
year from now?
How's next week
or next month
or the end of the year?
I'm just not in a hurry.
I mean, I like things
the way they are.
Things will be
the way they are
only we'll be married.
Nothing's going to change.
Is that what
you're afraid of?
Or is it, uh, that you
like that you can just
walk away from this, uh,
with things like they are?
I can't keep doing
this, Roxanne.
I love you, but I can't.
Let's get married, or...
Or?
(laughing):
Planning on moving in?
I'm looking for Matt Camden.
He's a medical student;
he works here, I think.
He's not here.
He and his wife went up to the
Berkshire's for a little R&R.
Oh.
That's an uh-oh?
Maybe I should have called.
Are you a friend or a Camden?
I'm a Camden.
I'm Matt's brother, Simon.
As in the Bank of Simon?
Oh, hon,
I know all about the Camdens.
There's Matt, Mary, Lucy,
you, Ruthie, Sam and David.
Matt and I are very close.
I'm the one who told your dad
he was going to be a grandpa.
When he wasn't.
Oh.
So, run away from home?
Not exactly.
Do your parents
know where you are?
Probably.
I don't know.
My ex-girlfriend Cecilia
was supposed to tell them.
You want to call them?
Not really, no.
Why don't you call
Mary and Carlos?
Maybe you can stay with them.
I'm sorry, Mary a-and who?
I never said anything.
She's living with a guy?
I know nothing.
Well, are they married?
I hope so.
Oh, got to go!
The phone's on the desk.
Help yourself, bye!
(doorbell ringing)
I'm-I'm-I'm very
surprised to see you.
Uh, please
come in.
Would you like
to sit down?
Well, I suppose you
came here for some reason.
Is there anything I can do?
Anything we can do for you?
We're going to accept the offer
from your insurance company.
We don't think that any amount
of money can replace our son.
And while we hoped to get
more because, in our anger,
we wanted to punish
your family and Simon,
we don't want to go to court.
Paul should've been
wearing a helmet.
We reminded him
always to wear a helmet,
but he didn't wear a helmet.
He never wore a helmet
when he rode his bike.
But wearing or not wearing
a helmet didn't seem important.
Not when we were dealing with
much bigger problems with Paul.
Y-You don't, you don't
have to tell me.
No, we want to tell the truth.
It's the right thing to do.
We hope that we can
do the right thing
so our other son
will do the right thing.
Justin.
Justin painted your church sign.
We'll pay to have
it repainted.
That's, uh, that's
not necessary.
I-It's been taken care of.
He had a problem with drugs.
Paul.
The autopsy shows that, um,
he was under the
influence of drugs.
So, while your son, Simon,
may have been guilty
of not paying attention,
our son, Paul, was guilty, too.
I had no idea.
It would have come out
in the trial,
but we'd rather
just let you know.
ERIC:
Still, you
didn't have to.
I didn't have to know the reason
why you decided
not to go to court.
ANNE:
I-It probably
won't help
Simon to know this, you know,
we want you to tell him, but...
No, he's still going
to be dealing with a lot.
And for more
than just a few years.
Maybe even for a lifetime.
But... that's just the thing,
he still has a lifetime.
DON:
Our other
son, Justin,
he's a good boy, a good
student, a good person.
But he had this thing about
trying to help his brother
with his drug problems and he
thought he was making progress
before the accident and, well,
now he's got a lot of anger
directed towards Simon
and he's out of control.
We have him in
grief counseling
with us as a family and private
sessions just for him as well,
but it's not going that well.
And we don't want
another tragedy on our hands.
We tried to talk him out
of going back to school,
but he won't
hear of it.
He could transfer,
but it's not going to happen.
So, what we're hoping is maybe,
if you and your wife and
your son would consider it,
maybe Simon could go
somewhere else this year.
Because frankly,
Reverend Camden,
we're afraid that Justin
will do something stupid.
I don't think that he would
physically hurt Simon,
but we really
can't be sure.
We'd just like to
remove the temptation,
hope that in time
the therapy works
and he can get through this.
We hope we can all get through
this, without any more trouble.
We can't take another
event in our lives.
We're exhausted.
Simon decided
to take off for New York
to see his brother,
our oldest son, Matt.
Simon doesn't want
to go to school.
My wife and I have been
trying to make him. So...
well, we'll stop
doing that right now.
And we'll figure out
some alternative.
It seems that's
the very least we can do.
(sighs) That's all
we really wanted.
Thanks.
Thank you for coming over here.
And thank you
for dropping
the court battle.
And thank you...
for trying to protect Simon.
God bless you.
And again, my
deepest sympathies.
I'm very sorry about your son.
Thank You.
Now, if you could just
help me find Simon?
www.tvsubtitles.net