So how did you get
this job, andrew?
I was a client.
I was just like
you once, charlotte-
Lost, lonely,
looking for love.
Clumsy, hapless, pathetic.
- Okay, I get it.
Sitting right
here was james -
Beautiful full
beard, devastating.
Oh, so james was
your soul mate.
At first, until he
shaved off his beard.
And I was like, "what'd you do
with my boyfriend, al roker?"
So was the beard the only
reason you and james broke up?
Well, that and his wife.
No more talk about me.
Let's move on to the
next question on the test.
Okay.
Tell me more about...Wayne?
That can't be
the next question.
I have the power
to change the test,
Because I have the pencil.
It's complicated.
Mike, jill, leslie,
and I were all friends,
And it was all
going along fine,
And then wayne comes along.
I smell passion.
Start from the beginning
and don't leave anything out.
Do you know tom
cruise is only 4'12"?
Isn't that actually 5 feet?
It's all camera angles.
And musical superstar prince?
Technically a dwarf.
Ah!
Did not know that.
It's going pretty well,
don't you think, charlotte?
I mean, usually
first dates are awful.
Yeah, awful...
Dreadfully awful.
No, no, this is good.
I've never done it with
an irish chick before.
I'm english.
Good luck with that.
Oh, you're feisty.
Just like the 4'6"
sarah jessica parker.
All right, hold your horses.
I'm gonna go
squeeze the lemon,
And then we'll go
back to your place.
He's a doll.
Sorry, were you talking to me?
Your date. He's actually
the size of a doll.
Oh, he's harmless.
What is it with girls like you
Wasting your time
with guys like that?
Girls like me?
You don't know me.
You don't know
anything about me.
I bet I know more
than you think.
I bet I don't care.
All right.
What do you think
you know about me?
Well, you're wearing
your hot -date dress.
You have long brown hair,
Pretty eyes.
You only date harmless
guys like short stack...
When you really should
be dating a guy like me.
Oh, right-
A cocky jackass who spends
his time scruffing up his hair
Just enough to make it
look like he doesn't care
So girls will fall
into bed with him.
So you're into me.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
Wayne!
Mike!
Oh!
Charlotte, this is wayne.
Have you guys already met?
Oh, we've met.
- Yeah.
In fact, charlotte and I were
about to go back to her place.
Not true.
Wayne and I have been best
buds since camp watahachie.
It was a rich kids' camp.
I worked there-
And I was rich there.
This is wayne wayne?
Mm-hmm.
Last time we spoke,
You were living
in "barthelona."
Yeah.
Man, I crashed
my cigarette boat
Off the coast of majorca.
Oh, ridiculous.
Yeah, it kind
of bummed me out,
So I came back here.
So you're back. You're
back in the city.
I am back in the city.
Charlotte, wayne
is back in the city,
And we are back in business.
He is gonna be hanging
out with us nonstop.
How great is that?
Oh, I can hardly stand it.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Well, why'd you even
go out with that guy
In the first place?
Well, I didn't
want to judge a book
By its tiny, little cover.
It's a nice place.
Do you mind?
No, not at all.
I can't believe you
two have never met.
Wayne, has it been four
years since you left?
Yeah, man. Traveled
all over the world.
Actually picked up
a little spanish,
A little french,
a little swedish,
And a hot little hungarian.
Charlotte, he was
talking about girls.
Yeah, I got that.
Are you sure that you
two don't want to catch up
In your apartment downstairs?
Are you kidding me?
I want you two to get
to know each other.
Well, I was gonna
make some tea.
I've developed the
most splitting headache.
Well, I will fix your tea.
I want you to sit down here.
So I'm guessing
from the accent,
You're not from around here.
Is it long island or...?
No, charlotte is
from london town.
And how do you know mike?
Well, we- - do you
remember leslie?
Charlotte and leslie
met at some lame job,
And then leslie
introduced her to us.
And, uh, here we are.
And how do you like it here?
Mike?
- She loves it.
She sometimes gets
lonely for london,
But we're like her
family, so she gets by.
Oh, my god,
charlotte, you're here.
Wayne!
Jill!
What are you
doing back in town?
Oh, I crashed my cigarette
boat off the coast of majorca.
Ridiculous.
- Right?
Charlotte, how much
do you love wayne?
Oh, she loves him.
Are you kidding me?
She absolutely loves him.
Oh, my god, I almost forgot.
I have really bad news.
- What?
Jeffrey is getting married.
who's jeffrey?
Leslie's ex.
- Oh, yeah, I hated that guy.
Yeah, he's a total tool.
And he's getting married
to somebody else tomorrow.
Okay. Leslie cannot find out.
It'll absolutely crush
her. So here's the plan.
When we see leslie,
no one says the words
"wedding," "jeffrey,"
or "married."
wedding...
Jeffrey... Married.
I think she knows.
Oh, leslie, it's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Were those words?
Did she say something?
She said, "how can you
do this to me, jeffrey?"
Kindergarten teachers speak
emotional meltdown fluently.
How did you find out
jeffrey was getting married?
She ran into another party
planner named roberta.
Sorry. Robin...
At the flower market,
and they got into a fight
Over the last acacias.
Azaleas.
And robin told her that
she needed the flowers
Because she's planning
jeffrey's wedding.
God, he knows we're
party planners.
Why didn't he use us?
Sorry. That was so
very wrong of me.
Oh, let it out.
Whatever we can do to
make you feel better-
Whatever you want,
we're here for you.
I want to crash the wedding
And make him see
he should marry me.
She wants to
crash the wedding -
We heard that one.
I have a better idea.
We don't go to the wedding.
We stay here, and we talk
about everything you're feeling.
We could always
play scattergories.
Weak!
What do you mean, "weak"?
She loves scattergories.
We need to get
her mind off this,
And in order to do
that, we gotta go big.
Wayne is the
king of going big.
When I got my heart broken
in 10th grade, 11th grade,
12th grade, and the
summer after 12th grade,
Wayne was right there for me,
Going big and
making me feel great.
If I were leslie,
I'd get dressed up
In something slutty and
party all night long,
Maybe get it on
with some stranger.
Oh, that's very healthy.
Not finished.
I'd have somebody
videotape the whole thing,
And then I'd send
it to this jeffrey
As a big "up yours."
Weak.
That is a terrible idea.
No, it's an awesome idea,
And you know what
rhymes with awesome?
Atlantic city.
And we could take a limo
there, couldn't we, wayne?
It's the only way to go.
A big limo with a
hot tub in the back.
Do they make any other kind?
We fill it with
the best champagne
And crab cocktails.
Is crab cocktail okay, wayne?
I could eat me some crab.
"I could eat me some crab."
You see why I love this guy?
I'm calling for the limo.
Knock yourself out.
- Yeah.
Okay, w -wait.
This is ridiculous.
We're not going
to atlantic city.
I think I know my friend
slightly better than you, wayne.
What she needs is
to be here with us
In a safe place where she
has time to process and heal.
She wants to go
to atlantic city.
Hey, guys, I'm naked.
Mike, please,
do us all a favor
And turn on the bubbles.
Hey, jeffrey, take a look
at what you're passing up.
Good. That's really good.
Um, tiny, little note-
You may want to squeeze your
knees together just a bit.
Come on, look at
her. She's having fun.
Yeah. I think she should
possibly have worn pants.
And I think you really
want to have fun,
But you're stopping yourself
Because it was
my awesome idea.
Are you always this confident,
Or is it some sort
of mental illness?
You are really into me.
Hey...
Wayne!
More champagne?
More champagne!
Hey, driver, more
bubbly, my good man.
If I'm stopping to
get more champagne,
Should I use the credit
card that I have on file?
No, no, no, no, no,
no. That's my card.
Wayne, give him the real card.
Use the black one.
Guys, like, 200
people in the country
Have this black credit card.
More like 199 now.
What does that mean?
Why don't we just
use your card?
Are you kidding me?
I can't afford this.
Well, neither can I.
What?
My dad kind of...
Cut me off.
I'm paying for this?
Hey, driver?
How much would it cost
If we stopped the limo
right now and got out?
$1,100.
- Stop the limo!
Everybody get out! Get
out of the limousine!
Go now! Now!
The meter's running!
Oh, I'm sorry none of us
grabbed your clothes...
Or your wallet...
Or your keys.
You were quite insistent on
leaving that limo, though.
How could you be poor?
What happened to your
cigarette boat in majorca?
I crashed it.
That was the last
straw for my dad.
That, and he
thinks I'm a loser.
How could you let
me order that limo?
It's not like I have thousands
of extra dollars lying around.
Well, you're a lawyer. I
thought lawyers had money.
I don't have
atlantic city money.
Can I just say something?
What?
This is the best shopping
cart I have ever used.
I mean, you really don't find
ones like this in the store.
Look, I can push
it with one finger
And still have
complete control.
I'm sorry, man.
I didn't want to
bring everybody down.
Great job with that.
Mike.
Mike!
All right, I'm out of here.
Wait, you're not gonna try
and sort things out with mike?
He doesn't want to talk to me.
Oh, right. So that's the
kind of person you are.
There's a problem,
you avoid it.
Leslie's sad, take
her to atlantic city.
I've hurt mike's feelings,
I'll just run away.
Have you ever heard
the expression,
"people who live
in glass mansions
Shouldn't throw diamonds"?
Oh, I can't say I have.
You act like you've
got it all figured out.
You take care of
everyone else's problems
To avoid your own.
What's that supposed to mean?
You have issues.
I mean, I have issues,
but you have issues too.
What issues?
Men issues, for one.
I feel like a fool.
Am I, jill? Am I a fool?
No, but you should know
You dropped your towel
abt 20 yards back.
What the-
Isn't this fun?
Oh, this is fun!
This is what we need.
Wayne doesn't know anything.
Leslie, do you
want me to feed you?
Thanks for the
clothes, charlotte.
Mike, what are you
doing for knickers?
Nothing.
Oh. You could keep those.
I can't believe wayne's
poor and that he's gone.
No, that's what he does.
One minute he's there,
turns his light on you,
And you know that
everything's gonna be okay.
And then in the next,
He disappears into the night.
Like batman.
Well, I think it was terrible
He didn't tell you the truth,
Leaving you to spend $1,100
And bare your behind
To all those poor
people on staten island.
I thought we were
gonna split the $1,100.
We just told you that
to get you on the bus.
Oh!
Do you think they're at
the rehearsal dinner now?
It doesn't matter.
I just know he's out there,
Wandering around aimlessly.
No friends, no family,
no black credit card.
I miss jeffrey!
I miss wayne!
Enough! Enough with jeffrey!
And enough with wayne!
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I'm not crazy about wayne.
Do you know what
he said to me?
He said I distract myself
with my friends' problems
So I don't have to
face my own-get this-
Man issues.
That's ridiculous.
- You? Absolutely not.
Do you want me to
have this or not?
Oh, it's you.
Hey.
Hello.
Uh, can you give that to mike?
It's just 23 bucks to go
toward covering the limo.
It's all the
money I had, so...
I'm sure he'd love to see you.
I think I'm the last
person mike wants to see.
He's been shouting
your name in his sleep.
I think you two are on some
sort of pirate adventure.
Charlotte.
- Hmm?
I can't find leslie anywhere.
She's right there.
- Oh.
That's a throw pillow
and a pair of socks.
What are you worried about?
What do you mean, what
am I worried about?
It's Saturday.
The wedding.
- The wedding.
Captain wayne, skeletons
on the starboard bow!
Right. Here it is.
Hey, this is really
the type of wedding
That you and leslie
should be planning,
Not those crappy bar mitzvahs.
Thank you, jill.
Right. We have to go inside.
I've never crashed
a wedding before.
I have.
Anyone asks, you're the
groom's second cousin,
In from phoenix.
Nobody wants to
hear about phoenix.
Right.
We'll wait out here.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
It's just that...
I was embarrassed.
Why?
You always talk about me
And act like I'm the
coolest guy you know,
And now...
You think I wouldn't like you
Because you don't have money?
It happens. Trust me.
Do you remember in 11th grade
When you dad
took us to greece?
The only think I
remember about that trip
Was the night that you and
I stayed awake all night
Writing that song
about spanakopita.
That was a great song.
- That was a bad song.
Lyrically it was weak,
but it was very melodic.
I don't care about
the money, wayne.
I do.
Well, tell you what.
If you want, you can
stay with me for a while
Till you figure out
what you're gonna do.
Really?
For the past 20 years,
Whenever I've been down,
you have picked me up.
In a private jet.
- Yeah.
I have a couch.
I'll take it.
All right.
She's not in there.
But they really pulled
out all the stops.
That is a gorgeous,
gorgeous wedding.
Yeah.
Well, if she's not in there
and she's not out here,
What should we do?
Maybe we should go up there.
She wouldn't-
Just go.
Leslie!
Are you okay?
This might be a
shot in the dark,
But I'm gonna go
ahead and say, "no."
I was going to
go to the wedding,
And I figured when he saw me,
He'd realize he was
making a mistake.
But I couldn't even go in.
Oh, leslie, I'm so sorry.
Why don't we just go home?
You don't need to see this.
Oh, here comes the bride.
And she's fat.
She's not fat.
She's not fat, she's huge.
Look at her.
Really? She's fat?
Sure.
- Like circus fat.
I don't see her.
That's because she probably
ran off to the buffet.
Give me the binoculars.
Oops.
Oh, and look, look.
I think jeffrey's
losing his hair.
Really?
- Yeah.
That is so awesome.
Hey, let's make a pact.
If we're not married
by the time we're 35,
We will come back
to this rooftop,
And we will hold hands,
And we will jump off
this building together,
Just like thelma and louise.
And mike.
Could we make it 37?
Sure.
I think we got off
on the wrong foot.
So you do want
to sleep with me.
Oh, my god.
I'm gonna throw
you off this roof.
Oh, feisty.
Just like the 4'6"
sarah jessica parker.
I'm sorry I said you
run away from problems.
That's okay. It's true.
I'm sorry I said
you had man issues.
Yeah, well, you should
be, 'cause it's not true.
Everyone knows it. I
have it all together.
What did we miss?
Ring bearer's
picking his nose.
This wedding has
gone downhill.
Well, it's over.
They're throwing the rice.
I'm sorry, leslie.
It's okay.
Congratulations!
Oh, my god!
- No!
Yeah, it's fine.
You sure it's not
too small for you?
'cause seriously, if you
want, you can have my bedroom.
Yeah, okay.
I'll take the
bedroom. Thanks, man.
O
- okay. Good.
Great. Yeah, uh...
I'll empty my bureau.
Dude, I'm kidding. I'm not
gonna take your bedroom.
I mean, the couch
is more than fine.
You're a good egg, mike poole.
So what's the
shampoo situation?
Better not be that
two-in-one crap.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net