You know, after
answering only a few
Of these soul mate questions,
I totally see why
they're so probing and complex.
Well, I think
You're making them harder
than they're supposed to be.
I mean, you didn't
exactly have to tell
A whole 30 minute story
when I asked you
If your billing address
Was the same as
your current address.
It was a brilliant story.
[phone ringing]
I'm not getting that.
Why?
It's my ex, renaldo.
He's crazy.
But he looks just like
a cocoa brown Daniel Craig.
He's a bad, bad,
delicious, bad man.
Oh. Mm.
I tried a renaldo once.
Really? I can't see you
with a bad boy.
His name was Luke,
and he was a biker.
Vroom, vroom!
- Mm-hmm.
Jill was dating his friend,
Which should've
been my first warning.
But there was
something about him.
With muscles, his leather...
Tattoos, sweat!
This might be the first story
of yours
I actually wanna hear.
Then I got this one
a few months ago.
It's the Japanese symbol
for strength.
Yes, it is.
And, um, what is this one for?
Well, that one there's
for my friend Rico.
He passed last year.
Man, I couldn't do anything.
Couldn't ride, couldn't drink,
Couldn't fight
for, like, six months.
It's hard when you lose
as many friends as we do.
Together: To Rico.
So you just leave
that there on the floor?
God, so rebellious.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
- Hey--whoa!
That is dangerous.
Someone should
put a cone over this.
Mike, Wayne,
this is Luke and Pete.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
See you later.
- Oh, we were gonna join--
- See you later.
- So we can't even--
Right.
Hey, Tony, the usual.
Hey, you know what
those guys remind me of?
- Who?
- Us.
Would not have been
my first guess.
I mean, they're biker brothers
And we're blood brothers.
Remember?
Camp Watahatchi, summer, 1989.
Oh, yeah.
The Watahatchi two.
I was the chief and
you were the medicine man.
Yeah.
My allergies were
out of control that summer.
That was still
an amazing six weeks.
I became blood brothers
with you
And I made out
with Sally Ann macintosh
Behind the mess hall.
Didn't she wear a back brace?
Not for long.
We're kind of done with
The public portion of our date.
Yeah, we're outta here.
Nice.
Um, so,
Do you have any scars
or battle wounds?
Well, I got my appendix
taken out when I was eight.
We had really bad insurance,
So the doctor
was kind of sloppy.
Wanna see it?
- Yes, please.
- All right.
Hold on.
Yep.
See, it's here.
And there's some over there.
So I'll cover this one
Till you get another
one of those signs, okay?
Whoa, whoa,
watch yourself, miss.
Very slippery.
♪ can I ask you
a question? ♪
♪ can I ask you a question ♪
♪ and 99 more? ♪
♪ all your fears and mysteries
♪ the love
you're searching for ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Boy, bikers sure do dress cool.
Yeah, I really
don't look at guys.
Yeah, whatever.
I got my own
blood brother right here,
Who needs to
look at other guys?
Blood brothers, yeah.
[chuckling]
What?
- I--it's nothing, nothing.
Well, you can't just do that.
[chuckling]
It's funny.
It's a funny story.
I wanna hear it.
All right, you know
the blood brothers thing?
Yeah.
So you cut your hand,
and you're crying and bleeding.
Oh, ho, ho!
I remember that!
Well, I actually
didn't cut myself.
I put tabasco sauce on my hand
and shook yours.
No, that's funny.
That's...
That's a funny story.
I mean, I remember
my hand was stinging.
But I thought that was from
The cosmic connection
being formed.
No. No.
It was from the tabasco sauce.
And then you know what he did?
He put tabasco sauce
on his hand.
20 years of friendship
based on a lie.
And he doesn't even care.
Oh, I'm sure he cares, Mike.
Well, he doesn't act like it.
I wish I could
talk about this now,
But Luke's
gonna be here any second.
[gasps]
you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna get new friends.
And then Wayne will realize
Just how valuable a friend
I am.
[knocking]
[whispers] you get that.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Hey, Luke.
- Hey, li'l Mike.
Hey, Luke, what are
you doing tomorrow night?
I don't know,
probably watching the fight.
A fight.
How about you
watch it at my place?
I got a big tv, I can
get some food, some beer.
Yeah, sounds good.
I'll bring the guys.
Great!
Downstairs,
apartment 2g, 8:00.
- Great.
- All right.
- It's a date.
- Not a date.
It's not a date.
[motorcycles revving]
See, I told you we could make
it downtown in ten minutes.
I really didn't know you could
take sidewalks on these things.
Eh, if the bike will fit,
That's the path we're taking.
You got a great scream.
[laughing]
No one's ever
noticed that before.
You're gonna love this bar.
Full of loud music,
cheap whiskey, and a bull.
A mechanical bull!
No. Come on.
Here you go.
Hey, it's really cool of you
to have us over for the fight.
Oh, yeah.
My roommate and I
had a kind of falling out.
See, back in camp Watahatchi,
I cut my--
- Are we gonna watch
the fight or what?
Yes, we are.
Wayne!
Oh, this is awkward.
I didn't realize
you'd be stopping by.
Uh, I live here.
That's my bed.
- Wayne.
- Hey, Luke, right?
Yeah, that's Luke.
He is officially
one of my new friends.
In fact, all of these guys
are my new friends.
Hey, mark,
the fight's about to start.
- Mark, mike--
doesn't matter to me.
It's how close we are.
One fight coming up.
Well, uh...
I'll get out of your way.
Yeah, you should
probably just go.
What are you talking about,
there's room here.
We can scootch, right guys?
Come on.
Oh, you don't wanna
scootch on a couch like this,
It's more of a three person--
- Oh, yeah, I love that.
Hey, mark...
If you're
heading to the fridge,
You mind hooking me up
with a beer?
So after the movie,
Luke took me to
this crazy place last night.
New Jersey?
Have you been?
It's fascinating.
No, Jill, it's not serious.
I'm just having fun for once.
It's a rather
nice change of pace.
[knocking] he's here.
Sorry I'm late, babe.
It's quite all right...
Babe.
You are cute as a button.
So what are
we gonna do tonight?
Movie, drag race, cock fight?
[laughing]
Actually, I got
a little surprise for you.
Oh, really?
Aw, you didn't have to do that.
Where is it?
Right here.
Um...Is that me?
Yep.
On your chest?
Yeah.
It's official now,
you are my old lady.
I didn't sign up for forever.
This was a romp.
This was a fun little fling.
I was dipping my toe
into the murky waters
Of the bad boy pool.
Well, it looks like
you fell in face first.
[sighs]
What did you say
when you saw it?
I didn't know what to say.
So I said,
"please don't slouch,
You're giving me
a double chin."
I'm jealous.
Pete never got a tattoo of me
And we've been dating
twice as long.
A girl tattooed
my name on herself once.
When I dumped her,
She put "smells" underneath it.
I'd say she won that battle.
Check out my new ride.
Now that I'm rolling
with my new best friends,
I decided to get myself a bike.
What'd you get, a harley?
Well, the harley of scooters.
Got a vespa.
- A vespa?
- Yep.
Just tell me you didn't
get a powder blue one.
For your information,
it's called Capri blue.
Guys, my face is plastered on
a very dangerous man's chest!
We get it, Charlotte.
Luke likes you
more than Pete likes me.
You have to dump this guy.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You can't break up with him.
Pete told me when Luke's last
girlfriend broke up with him,
He went crazy.
Like, crazy, crazy.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Be his old lady
for the rest of my life?
No, no, no, just
for the rest of his life.
- Oh, my God.
- Charlotte, calm down.
I got you into this mess,
I'm gonna get you out of it.
What are you gonna say?
Don't worry, I'm really
good at this kind of stuff.
I'll think of something.
Okay.
Mike is dead.
Li'l Mike?
Yeah.
How'd he die?
Charlotte?
An accident?
- On his new scooter?
- Yes!
Yes, that is exactly
how it happened.
Mike was cycling, right?
And he was hit by a giant...
Beer truck.
They found him,
like, 100 feet away.
With his arm still saying,
"may I go right?"
I can't believe it!
Li'l Mike!
Wow, you're
really taking this hard.
Anyway,
you know how close we were.
He was sort of like my Rico.
I just can't see myself
doing anything--
Going out, staying in,
Or us even talking for
at least six months to a year.
Sh, sh, sh, sh, sh.
As long as you need.
Thank you.
I really appreciate
your understanding.
Oh, you are an amazing man.
And I'm just lucky
to have known you.
Take care.
Wait...
When's the funeral?
No funeral.
Mike was...Alaskan.
You know how that goes.
Take care.
Well, he died on two wheels.
He was a brother, we should
at least pay our respects.
Well, we'll probably just
spill some things on the ground.
Well, we'll be there.
You guys are having a memorial
for him, aren't you?
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
When's that?
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
Why am I dead?
Why not Wayne?
Or Leslie?
In high school, she was voted
most likely to die young.
I was?
It wasn't my idea,
it was Jill's.
I thought
we were gonna tell him
I'd won a cruise
around the world.
You should've
gone with my idea.
I'm not telling someone
I have a venereal disease.
At least my plan
got you out of it.
Well, not yet.
Luke and the guys
are coming around
Tomorrow for your memorial.
I can't believe this!
I just made a bunch
of new friends.
Now I'm dead.
Mike, I know you're upset,
but I had to get out of this.
I'm so sorry.
All right.
[sigh]
- But it better be tasteful.
- Yes.
- With speeches.
And I wanna listen in
on speaker phone,
So you'd better make them good.
And only friends are invited.
Real friends.
Men of their word.
Men who do not base
an entire relationship
On a lie, Wayne!
Are you mad at me?
Yes, of course I'm mad at you.
It meant nothing to you, Wayne.
I cut open my hand
for the promise of
A lifelong friendship
And you poured a hot,
vinegar-based condiment on it.
Is this about the blood oath?
You know what, you're
not invited to the service.
Right, Charlotte?
Well, it is your funeral.
He had so much life
left to live.
You know he's not dead, right?
[phone ringing] Hello?
How's it going?
How many people showed up?
Did snakebite
wear his dress leathers?
Mike.
Well, I wanna hear it.
Put me on speaker phone.
God. Fine.
I would like
to welcome you all.
We are here to remember
our dear friend,
Michael poole.
And if you don't mind,
any drink pouring
Could be done on
the balcony or fire escape.
So is anyone gonna say
anything about li'l Mike?
Yes!
The speeches, of course.
I guess I will start.
Bah!
Yes, this was
Mike's scooter helmet.
We can take comfort
knowing his last moments
Were spent riding
his beloved vespa.
Riding like the wind
at 30 to 35 miles an hour.
Mike had so many
wonderful qualities.
Jill.
Well, that sucked.
Mike was an amazing bowler.
He once bowled, like,
I don't know, like, a 63.
2! 263!
[groans]
Leslie?
Hi.
Mike and I have been friends
since I was eight.
His was the first penis
I ever saw.
It popped out of his fly
during gym class,
But he waited till he finished
the whole obstacle course
To put it back.
That's the kind of guy he was.
People saw!
Um, thanks, Leslie,
that was lovely.
So thank you all for coming
On this sad, sad, sad occasion.
So if none of you have
anything else left to say--
- I do.
I have something to say.
[gasps] Wayne!
Mike poole was my best friend.
He gave me a home,
a weekly allowance,
And always let me
have the last beer.
I just want him to know
That even though
I didn't cut my hand,
It doesn't mean
that the bond we formed
In our 20 year friendship
wasn't real.
If I could go back,
I'd cut my hand open.
I didn't do it because...
I was just too chicken.
I'm sorry, bro.
[sniffs]
Now that's a speech.
[sobbing] that's a speech.
Yeah, we're gonna get going.
But before we do,
I just want you to know
That Mike really touched
all of us.
Boys.
"li'l Mike."
Holy crap.
Pete, are you kidding me?
You can't get
a tattoo with Jill,
But you run right out
and you get a Mike?
Hey, he's a fallen bro, babe.
Oh, and I suppose goofy
Taking a bong hit
is a fallen bro too?
You know what,
if I'm not important enough
For you to get a tattoo of me,
then you can just forget it.
Fine.
'cause you're suffocating me.
I get enough of
this crap from my wife.
You're married?
Yeah.
You know what?
After the Motorhead concert
this weekend, we're done.
So why did you all get tattoos?
Oh, they're for
the li'l Mike memorial ride.
Me and some of the boys
are gonna ride
From the West village
all the way to West Hollywood
In his honor.
He was gay, right?
[chokes]
Poor li'l gay Mike.
And once we get there,
our West coast brothers
Are also gonna get a "li'l mike"
tattoo with a rainbow--
- Fine, this has got to stop.
Luke, you can't go
on this ride.
Why, babe?
I feel terrible.
I didn't want to be
your "old lady,"
So I may have told a lie.
About what?
Mike.
He's not dead.
You made up a story
about your friend being dead?
- Yeah.
- What is wrong with you?
A fake memor--we got tattoos!
- I know!
I know, it all got out of hand.
Though, in my defense,
you biker types do really
Jump the gun when it comes
to getting tattoos.
Um, I will gladly
apologize to your friends.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no. No.
You will tell them nothing.
I have a reputation.
So here's how
she's gonna go down.
Either you keep your mouth shut
And nobody's
ever gonna know the truth,
Or we're gonna be having
a real memorial for li'l Mike.
I vote for keep my mouth shut.
Yeah, good.
You know, I thought
I wanted a good girl,
But you good girls are crazy!
Come on, boys.
Let's roll.
To li'l Mike.
Yeah.
How do I do it, every time?
I choose the worst men.
And I try so hard.
I keep looking and looking.
Well, I would stop looking
and I'd let him come to me.
What if he doesn't?
What if he does?
I guess I should cross
bad boys off my list.
Are you sure?
Why?
'cause I just got this bad boy.
What is that?
It's you.
But I felt creepy
drawing your boobs,
So I drew
a dragon body instead.
[laughing]
It's pretty awesome.
It's really rather flattering.
Oh...Too bad I crossed
bad boys off my list,
I could never date you now.
Yeah, that is too bad.
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Yeah. Hey, Mike.
Of course I heard my speech,
I said it.
Are you crying?
I-I--just hang in there,
I'll be right down.
I have to go.
Okay.
Tell Mike thanks
for being a good sport.
And he's not allowed to leave
the building till Tuesday.
That's when the li'l Mike
memorial ride begins.
Oh, and one more thing.
You know, this thing comes off
with soap and water, so.
Oh, good to know.
[door closes]
Dude, I'm not riding
on the back of this thing.
Well, only one of us
has a scooter license.
[sighs] eh, fine.
Just don't
beep your horn, okay?
I cannot promise anything.
Grab my waist.
Mike...
Mike!
What?
You been going to the gym?
No, not at all.
I know, I can tell.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net