Don't touch.
You already broke my zen rake.
I am so sorry.
I just needed to
see if it came apart.
I don't know why.
Aw, is that your husband?
You're assuming
a lot there, girl.
I'm sorry, boy.
Uh-uh. - I
won't do that.
I'm not gonna do that.
So you think a gay man
can't have male friends?
No, I didn't mean that.
That's my best friend...
With benefits.
Oh. Sounds like an
interesting friendship.
Sounds like I need to
ask you the next question.
Are you open-minded?
Well, to answer that I'm
gonna have to tell a story
About my friends,
without benefits.
Ain't nothing to
it but to do it.
Sorry. Does that mean "begin"?
Begin.
- Okay.
Well, it's been
a heck of a day.
Let's pack it in.
I get the feeling
you want me to leave.
No, not at all.
Nighty-night. Home safe.
Hello.
- Oh, boy.
Charlotte, you should
be happy to see me.
Why?
- Because I'm fun.
Ladies.
- wayne now.
I need milk for cereal.
Do you have any cereal?
Guys, really,
you need to leave.
I'm going out.
- I knew it.
Those are your
going-out lips.
Those lips do say,
"where's the party?"
Oh, do you have a date?
Hey, charlotte, are you ready?
Ew. Are you going
on a date with mike?
I mean, are you going
No, she's coming to
meet a girl I'm seeing.
Are you hiding another
girlfriend from us?
Yes, I am.
- Charlotte.
Well, you guys
weren't invited,
And I didn't want to
hurt your feelings.
oh, I, on the other hand,
Don't care about
your feelings.
charlotte, let's go.
Hey, that's not fair.
Even my kindergarteners
know when they have a party,
They have to invite everyone.
You want to know
what's not fair?
You and leslie pecking away
Until you find a
flaw with every girl
I've ever introduced you to.
Name one time we did that.
Kristy silva.
- Sarah taylor.
Jessica rosen.
- Okay.
Why can't I come?
Because I say to them,
"this is my friend
wayne," and then they say,
"mike, would you give
wayne and I some privacy?"
Name one time that happened.
Kristy silva.
- Sarah taylor.
Jessica rosen.
Look, guys, I
really like kate.
Kate?
See, that's why charlotte's
The only person who
gets to meet her.
Because she doesn't judge.
The way I don't
judge her trampy lips
And her weird vest.
Shall we?
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Is that her?
- No. No.
- No!
Is that... Wayne,
jill, and leslie?
Please, god, no.
Hey, buddy.
Did you follow us?
No.
- Yes.
Okay, listen, you
guys have to leave.
You have to leave right now.
is that her?
No, charlotte.
Yeah, that's her!
That's her. Okay. Um...
Um, you two can stay
long enough to say hi.
That's it. And you...
You have to turn
off the charm.
Like a computer. You got
to put it in sleep mode.
I can do that.
Activate sleep mode.
God, that is amazing.
Mike.
- Kate. Hey.
Um, kate, this is
jill and leslie.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for coming.
So your name is kate?
They have to leave
Because they're paramedics,
and they just got a call.
But it was really
nice to meet you.
A pleasure.
What was her problem?
This is wayne.
Hello.
And I'm charlotte. It's
wonderful to meet you.
Finally, the charlotte payne.
Mike goes on and on about you.
He goes on and
on about you too.
I'm an "on and on"
- er.
I go on and on. I tend to-
I'm doing it right
now. I just...
I don't know
when to- - stop.
Okay.
So what is this? Art?
Um, yes, I'm an artist.
I'll be the judge of that.
Um, kate, should we go
and get some champagne?
All right.
- Yeah.
Wayne.
- Yeah?
Do you think maybe you
could find a nice balance
Between turning off the
charm and just being rude?
Okay, if that's a
gamble you want to take,
But the charm is pretty
strong in me, buddy.
Damn it, it is.
Why would anyone look at art
When they could look at shoes?
Leslie, mike did look happy.
Maybe we should
give kate a chance.
No, we shouldn't.
Okay.
Look at these boots.
They're so beautiful.
They would look
really cute with jeans.
Or a dress. Or a skirt.
Or shorts.
I want them.
You need to have them.
You should buy them.
Buy them right now.
is that the price?
Or the number you have
to call to get the price?
That's the price. I
can't afford those.
Leslie, those boots would
make you a better person.
They'd fill that
hole in your soul
That jeffrey tore
open when he dumped you
And married that other woman.
You're hurting my feelings.
Because I want you
to have the boots.
I'm getting them.
You're not seriously
getting them, are you?
Okay.
I mean, I guess I initially
moved here to get away
From my family, who
can be a bit crazy.
Me too.
cheese puffs!
I love things with cheese.
- Me too.
I knew kate and charlotte
would like each other.
They're both so sophisticated.
I think I could kill
someone for cheese fries.
Well, that's the real reason
I had to leave England.
I can see why mike likes you.
I'm so happy you two met.
Yeah. Me too.
God, sleep mode
is so relaxing.
Guys don't want
to be my friend.
Girls aren't hovering.
Mike, your life
must be so easy.
And then kate said that
you said she was funny.
Well, she is.
and then kate said
That you both like
cheese and candy.
What are the odds of that?
Everyone loves
cheese and candy.
Oh, and wayne, you know
what kate said about you?
Nothing.
Sleep mode is a powerful tool.
Whoa, that's my sandwich.
I can't afford my own.
I'm saving for boots.
Good for you. I
mean, they're nice,
But they could
definitely be bigger.
Boots.
Boots with a "t."
Shoes.
Hello.
kate.
Kate!
- Oh, that sounds great.
That sounds great.
- What sounds great?
I'd love to.
- You'd love to what?
Okay. I'll see you there.
Bye.
- What?
Kate's invited me to
see a show with her.
This is so great.
You guys are gonna
be total buddies.
I love it! I love
it! I love it!
Jesus christ,
mike, get a grip.
Don't let them
ruin it for you.
He's a man in love.
Well, he sounds like a
seventh-grade girl in love.
You know, I don't really
miss london that much.
I've such great friends here.
And now I have a
new great friend.
You know, this was really fun.
Well, you're really fun.
No, you're really fun.
Okay. I'm really fun.
Night.
- Night.
Oh, charlotte, it looks
like you sat in something.
Oh.
- Let me.
Just...
Did you get it?
- Oh, I got it.
Night.
Charlotte, the only way
I can get these boots
Is if I spread them
over seven credit cards.
And two of them are yours.
Leslie, I have to
tell you something.
But you have to promise
not to tell anyone.
I love calls like this.
I think kate
could be a lesbian.
Why, because mike
looks like k.D. Lang
When he wears his jean jacket?
No, because tonight,
when I was with kate...
Kate said charlotte must
have sat in something...
And then kate brushed
off charlotte's butt...
And her hand lingered.
So my girlfriend's a lesbian?
Mike, I'm sorry, you
know I always support you,
But this time your
girlfriend could be a...
Lesbian.
Have you been wearing
your jean jacket again?
What? No. Charlotte.
Don't let yourself be
poisoned by these sirens.
They live to find flaws
with my girlfriends.
Whoa, being a lesbian
isn't a flaw, mike.
I think you're
being a homophobic.
Listen, kate is an artist.
Okay, artists are more open.
Their hands are
like their eyes.
Well, then it sounds
like kate has been staring
At charlotte's butt
for quite a while.
I guess it's possible
I misunderstood.
Let's see. Show
me what she did.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Okay.
Huh.
Do me.
I'm getting some of this.
Huh.
Was there any squeezing?
I'd say it was
more of a caress.
All: Oh.
That's-stop it!
Stop it. Stop it!
You see, this is because you
people have nothing to do.
Nothing?
Did you not just
see this ass train?
I know how we can tell
if kate's a lesbian.
Throw a softball at her
and see if she catches it.
That would work.
No.
Don't. God.
If anybody's gonna be throwing
balls at my girlfriend,
It's gonna be me.
You know what I mean.
Oh, I feel so bad.
I should never
have said anything.
I really want this
to work out for mike.
Let's just leave
them alone. All right?
Yeah, definitely.
- Of course.
Of course.
Are we seriously
gonna leave this alone?
Of course not.
Whatever we do,
it should involve
Another ass train, though.
I'm so glad you're here.
Sorry that mike had to work
and charlotte couldn't make it.
I just texted charlotte.
She's on her way.
Uh-oh.
What's going on?
Jill is putting
bait on the hook,
Trying to catch a lesbian.
Uh, I love this song.
There's no music playing.
You don't feel that beat?
No.
Can you excuse me?
What are you doing?
She's straight.
- Really?
Total hetero.
I don't buy it.
Ah, I should have
brought my softball.
All right, there's
only one way to find out
Which way kate swings,
but we're gonna have
To bring out the big guns.
Deactivate sleep mode.
What's up, kate?
Uh, hi, wayne.
So...
Excuse me.
Yeah, full-on lesbian.
Shame on all of us.
This is ridiculous.
If she's going out with
mike, then she's straight.
I'm gonna go over there
And smooth
everything over, okay?
Oh, hey, charlotte.
Hey, kate. Sorry
if those guys-
Oh, you have some
chips on your shirt.
Oh.
Charlotte, has it
ever occurred to you
That perhaps you're
just a messy person
Who needs a lot of wiping off?
Oh, mike, I'm sorry,
But this time I'm sure.
She likes girls.
doesn't the fact
That kate is dating me
Make anybody sure
about her sexuality?
Not 100%, no.
You people are crazy.
Hey, if the shoe fits...
That's it. I'm
getting the boots.
You know, charlotte,
I used to be able
to count on you
When it came to my
girlfriends, but not anymore.
Hang on a sec.
So you're saying I made up
The whole
boob-butt-touching thing
Just to ruin
your relationship?
Maybe.
So you're calling me a liar?
He's saying maybe, but
I think he means yes.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe I might
just call kate,
Invite her over here,
And get everything
cleared up right now.
She's saying maybe,
But I think she's
gonna call her.
Whoa, has my hair
been in sleep mode
This entire time?
Was anybody gonna tell me?
Excuse me.
There was a pair of boots
over there, deep gray,
Hand-stitched, made for me.
I need them in a seven.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just sold our last pair.
And they were a size seven.
How about this shirt?
Are you even wearing a bra?
Yes. What is it to you?
Well, I don't want
you jiggling around,
Leading the witness.
- Oh.
Come on.
Now you've all got to leave.
Kate will be here any minute.
They're gone.
Somebody bought the last pair!
oh, I'm so sorry.
But you all have to
go right now, okay?
Come on.
This is ridiculous.
We should be able to stay.
No. You have to leave.
No, no, no, no, jiggles.
We got to make sure that
you don't accidentally sit
In something or spill
something on yourself
Before kate gets here.
She's here. Hide.
Hide! Hide!
Hey, charlotte.
Oh, kate, mwah.
I'm glad you called. I
really need to talk to you.
Yes, why don't we
go somewhere else?
Somewhere quieter.
Here's fine.
Mm, cute boots.
Oh, thanks, I just got them
At this great store
next to the art gallery.
They're hand-stitched.
Can I ask you something?
- Mm.
Do you think wayne and jill
were hitting on me tonight?
Well, first let
me ask you this-
If you weren't with mike,
Who would you more
likely go out with,
Wayne or jill?
Keeping in mind wayne is
a boy and jill is a girl.
Wayne's not my type.
First, he's rude.
Then he's all over me.
Real chicks like that.
And with jill, I
mean, she's cute,
But where's the challenge?
What challenge?
Why would anybody
want a challenge?
Kate, I have to
be honest with you.
They were hitting on you.
But only because I thought
you've been hitting on me.
I thought you'd never notice.
You're a lesbian.
Mike.
- Oh, kate.
Didn't I tell
you? Mike's here.
What are you doing?
Finding out for myself
That you and I
both like girls.
Mike, I'm not a lesbian.
How can you say that?
- I'm open-minded.
I like you, and
I like charlotte.
Open-minded?
So you're saying
you want to like me
And you want to like
charlotte at the same time?
Maybe in the same bed.
- Mike!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Um, kate, I am not
open-minded at all.
I'm open-minded.
Oh, yes, wayne is here.
But I'm not open-minded
if mike's involved.
Who else is back there?
No one.
Other than jill and leslie.
Just so you know,
you wouldn't be
My first lesbian
choice either.
It would be ellen
because she makes me laugh
And she likes to dance.
I can't believe you were
all in there spying on us.
Mike, your friends are crazy.
We're not crazy.
We care about him.
We're caring people.
If you give me those boots,
I'll give you charlotte.
Crazy it is.
Well, kate and I are over.
Oh, no, what happened?
Oh, mike, I'm sorry.
I really am.
Why do you guys
only mess with me?
Jeffrey was
terrible for leslie,
And we did nothing.
Wayne dates idiots,
charlotte dates maniacs,
Jill dates everybody...
And still we do nothing.
Hey, belinda wasn't an idiot.
You can't be an idiot and be
An arena football cheerleader.
Mike, you're the guy who
protects everyone else.
You were like a big
brother to leslie and jill
When they were growing up.
You take care of wayne now,
You even work as
a public defender.
And you're the only
man I've ever been able
To count on my whole life.
So that's how you
show your support?
By meddling?
No, it's just
sometimes we worry
That you're not gonna take
the time to protect yourself.
Really?
I'm so sorry.
Well, there is one thing
You could do to
make it up to me.
Anything.
Kate seemed really open to
the idea of the three of us-
Mike!
- Sorry.
A threesome.
I could have had a threesome
If charlotte
wasn't so selfish.
That's number two
on my bucket list.
Oh, what was number one?
Killing a shark
with a shotgun.
You know what wouldn't
be on my bucket list?
What?
- Watching the bucket list.
What would be on your list?
Eh, I knocked out my bucket
list by the time I was 21.
Oh, come on,
There's got to be
something that you would do.
Mm, all right, a fivesome.
Why not just a threesome?
Because a bucket list
Is about doing things
you haven't done.
A foursome?
I repeat, a bucket list
is about doing things
You haven't done.
All right.
You really got to
teach me some stuff.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net