- Welcome to soul mate
specialists, inc.
Make yourself comfortable.
But not on the couch.
As I said, I'm andrew,
your soul mate specialist.
- I'm charlotte,
your soul mate searcher,
Searching for-
- Please hold your comments
until I'm done.
Sorry.
Let me start by saying
Congratulations,
miss payne.
You're about to take
the most comprehensive
Personality test
in the industry.
- Sounds fun.
- Fun?
You go to a carnival
for fun.
I don't like carnivals.
- The point is, this is science,
miss payne.
100 scientifically
formulated questions
Answered face-to-face
To ensure the client
is honest, thorough,
And at least within 15 pounds
of what they say they weigh.
- You might just want
to change-
I already did.
Once you've answered these
questions,
We will know exactly
who you are.
Then we can find
your soul mate.
- The thing is, I'm not sure
I believe in soul mates.
Why not?
- Well, when your dad has four
ex-soul mates
And your mom has three,
It does make you question
the whole concept.
If you don't believe in it,
Then why are you taking
this test?
'cause I want to believe.
- Well,
let's get started then.
Question #1:
What brought you here?
- I guess it was a really
bad date.
- It always is, girl.
It always is.
- My friends and I went
to a yankees game
With this guy I was dating...
Rick.
- Oh, my god.
Look at the third baseman.
I don't care if steroids
shrunk his junk.
I would totally sleep
with him.
- And that makes
the entire infield.
- You know,
you should take steroids.
I'm a lawyer.
- Yeah, but you could be
a super lawyer.
- You're a wonderful girl,
charlotte payne.
Thanks, rick.
- I really enjoy spending time
with you and your friends.
You guys are great.
I feel like since I've started
dating charlotte,
You guys have become
my friends.
Like we're this...
Big group of friends.
That guy is not my friend.
Hey.
You wearing space pants?
'cause your ass
is out of this world.
Yeah. No.
I think you're looking for
someone with lower standards.
Hi, I'm jill.
- Charlotte, I need
to talk to you.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
please remain seated
As we have a very special
announcement.
Um, why are you standing?
Um, why do you have
a microphone?
Um, why are we
on the jumbotron?
Oh.
- Dude, we're totally on tv
right now.
Ha.
- Can I have your attention,
folks?
Charlotte payne,
The last three months
have been the sweetest
Of my life.
That is all because of you.
Bro.
Charlotte payne.
Will you marry me?
- Wh-rick, I don't know
what to say.
um...
I just don't feel that way
about you.
Oh-oh!
Oh, god, I'm so sorry.
I hope we can still be
friends...
Friends...Friends...
Friends...
We really shouldn't have
carpooled with them.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
I can't believe it.
People throw food at us
and we get thrown out.
- Is all the popcorn
out of my hair?
- You know, there's some hot dog
in there too.
You should really take
a shower.
- Rick cried for 45 minutes
straight.
I timed it.
It was 45 minutes.
Was it really that bad?
- When you said you hoped
you could still be friends,
My testicles actually hurt.
Like, physically hurt.
Why would he propose?
We've been dating
for three months.
Why would someone propose
after only three months?
- I'll bet it's the accent.
- It's not the accent.
- Then you must be wicked
in the sack.
- I am not wicked
That's disappointing.
- Um, so what do I do?
Do I call him?
Do I go over there?
- No. Uh-uh.
You are not going over there.
That is crazy.
The last person
rick wants to see is you.
Think about it.
Are there any other gestures
I can make with this finger?
- God, I regret buying you
that thing.
- "meet me for a drink
tomorrow at 5:00"?
Who is this texting me?
- It's the painted guy
from the game.
I slipped him your number
when security escorted us out.
When?
- Right before that tray
of nachos
Hit you in the face.
Come on, leslie.
Just go on one date with him.
- No. It's too soon.
- It's been a year.
Jeffrey has moved on.
- You can't be sure of that.
- We watched him get married
through binoculars.
- Well,
he didn't look happy.
- It'll be good for you
to get out and date again.
For all of us, really.
- Fine. I'll go out
with the creepy painted guy.
Yay.
- But if I end up dead
in a ditch, it's your fault.
- Yay.
- This is a bad idea.
That guy had the worst
pick-up line
I've ever heard in my life.
- The space pants?
It was cute.
Oh.
I can come up with a better
pick-up line than that
Off the top of my head.
Okay, let's hear it.
Okay. Fine.
Um, what's a n-
Hold on a second.
Are you an-are those win-
are you an angel?
Appalling.
- I thought lawyers
could speak good.
- Oh, yeah, I thought
kindergarten teachers
Were supposed to be able
to talk-to speak-
Forget it.
- There, I did it.
I'm gonna meet him for a drink.
Not a date.
Just a drink.
So everybody just calm down.
- Okay, I cannot just sit here.
I'm going to call rick.
- Yeah. I want to see
if he's still crying.
- Oh, god. He can't still
be crying.
- Uh, he's crying
if he's watching this.
What is it?
- It's a video of you breaking
a grown man's heart.
It's all over the internet.
And they're calling you
the, uh...
Yankee bitch.
- I hope we can still be
friends...
Friends...Friends...Friends...
- Oh, there it is again. Oh.
- Forget it.
I can't call rick.
I can never ever, ever
face him again.
The ring is still on my finger,
isn't it?
Everybody's staring at me.
- No, they're not.
They're staring at me.
And I like it.
No, wait, they are staring
at you.
- Oh, hi.
My name's charl-
- Mr. Preston, the yankee bitch
is here to see you.
- Rick. Hi.
I'm so sorry to bother you.
It's just I left you messages
and I didn't hear back.
And I didn't know if it was
'cause you didn't get them
Or if you didn't want
to see me-
- I didn't want
to see you.
Now I know.
Yes. And I wanted
to give you back the ring.
There. There.
I'm so sorry, rick, about
the way everything happened.
If I could just
turn back time-
- Where's the ring?
- It's not there?
- You lost
my grandmother's ring?
- It was your grandmother's.
It was his grandmother's!
- All right, calm down.
Uh, let's retrace our steps.
Yes.
- Last night
after you humiliated rick-
Well, I wouldn't say-
We went back to your place,
You discovered the ring
was still on your finger.
Right.
- Then it got stuck
on wayne's finger.
- Wayne put it on?
- For, like, two seconds.
- Then he ran around the room
pretending he was gollum
From lord of the rings.
my precious.
- Oh, that was gollum.
I thought he was doing yoda.
Yeah.
- And then mike did
that magic trick
Where he swallowed it,
but it reappeared at the bottom
Of leslie's wine glass.
no way.
oh!
- That is crazy!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- That was awesome.
- Yeah.
- That ring has been
in our family for 70 years.
- I'm so sorry.
I will find it. I promise.
- Can you tell me
which of these men is single
And makes six figures?
- It's not here. We're never
gonna find this ring.
- Charlotte.
- Yes!
- I just found a big-ass check
made out to you and leslie
From max goldberg.
Who's max goldberg?
- We planned his son's
bar mitzvah.
Leslie sent a collection agency
after him.
- What should I do
with the check?
- Put it back in the couch.
You never saw it.
- I got it.
- Yes, the ring!
- Nope.
The best pick-up line.
Wayne and I are having
a competition.
You ready?
Do you have a sunburn
or are you always this hot?
- Ugh.
- Ugh. Blugh.
- My turn.
- Disgusting.
Do you have a sunburn
or are you always this hot?
- Aw.
- Hi.
Ah! That's my line.
- I told you, it's not
about the line,
It's about the delivery.
- Well, you were supposed to say
something that you wrote.
I didn't write anything.
- What were you doing
this whole time?
I was drawing a ninja.
God, this is awful.
First I embarrass him-
- humiliate!
- Humiliate him
at yankee stadium
And then I lose his ring.
His grandmother's ring.
- Thank you very,
very much.
- So I go to meet
the body painter.
I walk in, scan the room,
And then I realize
I have no idea
What this guy
actually looks like
Without his body paint.
And then...
- Leslie?
- Well?
- Albino.
All: Albino?
- What-what did you do?
Did you run?
Did you just run out of there?
- No.
- I would've run.
I would've just run
out of there.
I didn't know what to do.
I just made up the first excuse
that came into my head.
I'm engaged.
Ah, the ring!
I know. I'm sorry.
It was on my finger from when
mike and I did the mock wedding.
What mock wedding?
- You fell asleep.
It was beautiful.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait,
what did he say?
- He didn't buy it.
He said "you're not engaged.
That's the ring that guy gave
the yankee bitch."
- I think that nickname's
gonna stick.
- So what did you do?
Did you leave?
- Actually, no.
We started chatting.
And then we ordered a drink.
And it turns out...
You like the albino.
I like the albino.
I told him to meet us
at the bar later.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No. I'm sorry.
I do not think
I can handle that.
No. This is perfect.
I'm gonna call rick,
have him meet us at the bar,
Give him back the ring,
And then I will be done
with this. Yes.
one ring to rule them all.
- I think
that's the cookie monster.
I wish rick would get here.
I want to get this over with.
- I got something to take
your mind off the whole thing.
Did I just feel
an earthquake
Or did you just
rock my world?
- Ew.
- Please.
- Come on, mike,
it's getting old.
How about this?
Did I just feel an earthquake
Or did you just rock
my world?
- Aw.
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on, I just said
the same exact thing!
I will bet you 100 bucks
I can pick up any girl
in this bar
With any line you write.
anything I write.
- Yeah.
It's all in the delivery.
You are on.
There is no way a man
could garner a woman's interest
By saying these words.
- Okay,
that's just disturbing.
- Any girl, right?
- Yeah.
Her.
Candy from a baby.
In 1775,
cancer of the scrotum
Was a common disease
among chimney sweeps.
- What's your name?
- Oh!
Come on!
- Face it, mike,
there's nothing you can write
That wayne can't sell.
- Yes, there is.
- Oh, god.
You gonna write another fun fact
about scrotum cancer?
- No. I'm gonna write
the one thing
That wayne will never say
to a woman.
- Which is?
- Hello, charlotte.
- Rick! Hello.
- Where's my grandma's ring?
- Um, rick,
could we please talk?
Go ahead. Talk.
Well, not in front
Of all these people.
Suddenly you want privacy.
- Mike, I believe, uh,
you owe me some money.
- Care to go double
or nothing?
Yeah. You got a line?
What is this?
- The truth.
Ha. I think I'll pass.
- Did you see
the internet thing?
I did.
- They already did
a techno remix.
I know.
60,000 hits, though.
It's terrible.
People are terrible.
- Man. Rick looks
really mad.
- I wish I knew
what they were saying.
Does anybody read lips?
- I'm pretty good
at charades.
- I think it's a movie.
- Five words. Sounds like...?
Children of a lesser god!
- Guys, they're not actually
playing charades.
- No, it's something
with bruce willis.
- Die hard.
- No.
- Die hard 2.
- No, no.
- What's the one
where the little kid,
He sees all the ghosts?
- Hi, leslie.
- Aaah!
- Ah-ah.
- Oh.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I- I'm sorry.
You startled him.
He has this thing about-
- I thought you were a ghost.
No. No, no!
You were stupid.
- Rick, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Well, you did.
- And I never guessed
in a million years
That after only three months
of dating,
You'd propose
at yankee stadium.
Well, I did.
- There'll be someone out there
that says yes.
- So what is it, you're just
not the marrying kind?
- No, rick, it's not that,
it's just-
- It's just you don't want
to marry me.
I'm sorry, rick.
Well, just for the record,
My grandma
would not have liked you.
- Oh, rick, please
don't be like this!
- Keep it down, yankee bitch!
- God.
I am not a bitch!
Technically,
I'm not even a yankee.
- Leslie, I'm sorry I yelled
at your albino friend.
- You didn't yell,
you shrieked...Like a girl.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
Wayne, did I shriek?
Like a tiny, tiny girl.
- Charlotte, you're really
eating a lot.
You told me to always
tell you.
Well, I'm upset.
- Well, you got to tell us
when you're upset
So we know to order
more food.
This whole rick thing,
It's made me realize
that for the first time
In my entire life,
I want somebody.
I want somebody forever.
Wh-what if I don't
find that person?
What if the right guy
never proposes?
- I'm telling you,
guys are gonna propose
Simply because
of that accent.
I've known you six years,
I've almost proposed
like 14 times.
- You had a mary poppins thing
when you were a kid.
Who didn't?
She's a dirty little nanny.
- Hey, guys,
I'm not up for
The mary poppins discussion
tonight, just so you know.
- I've got
your spoon full of sugar
Right here, mary.
Right. That's it.
The yankee bitch
is throwing you out.
Everyone out.
- I bet if you got
a couple drinks in mary,
She'd be supercalifragilistic-
expiali-delicious.
- You want us to stay?
- I'll be fine.
forgot my foam finger.
Helps when I want
to hail a cab.
- What was written
on that napkin mike gave you?
- Uh, the one thing
I wouldn't say to a girl
I was trying to impress.
- Oh, yeah?
Which was?
Eh...
My name
is wayne rutherford.
My father is a billionaire.
18 months ago, he cut me off.
I've never held a job
and I have no money.
I sleep on my friend's couch
and have no idea
What I'm gonna do
with the rest of my life.
Now would that line work
on you?
- Um, you're right.
That would never work.
- There's a guy out there
for you.
He's gonna turn up.
And he's gonna ask you
to marry him.
And it won't be because
of your accent.
you're wicked in the sack.
There's only one reason
he'll want you to be his wife.
- What?
- You don't know?
It's 'cause you're
charlotte payne.
What are you writing?
This isn't the type of answer
People normally give,
is it?
Hell, no. Not at all.
But I think I can help you.
- Oh, great.
Who is my soul mate?
- Ted merman. He's an accountant
on long island.
- Really?
- No, that's my joke.
- You've only answered
one question.
We've got a long way
to go.
Now, question #2...
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net