Andrew, can I ask
How close are we
to finding my soul mate?
A long, long way.
Right.
But when you do
find the perfect match,
When people finish the test
and they meet,
Is it just like in the movies?
Is it magical?
Are they over the moon?
Not over the moon so much
as a safe public place
Agreed upon by both parties.
If said parties continue
to explore their "soulmance,"
Soul mate specialists
Is not liable for
any communicable diseases,
Mental breakdowns,
Or sudden weight gain
of said soul mate.
It sounded so much
more romantic in the brochure.
That's how they get you.
Right.
But I'm on to you.
You're a romantic.
Oh, I am.
I'm the most hopeless romantic
you will ever meet.
I guess you could say I'm--
I'm guided by my heart.
And it always ends up
biting me in the ass.
We're not liable
for that either.
Right.
So then after dinner we will
open up the dance floor
And the band will play
your parents' wedding song.
Oh, that would be great.
Uh, their song is
it had to be you.
Because it had to be them.
Hmm.
Anyway,
looks like we're done.
- Okay.
- Oh, wait.
Um, we haven't discussed
how your parents met.
When we plan
an anniversary party,
We like to have the full story.
Don't we, Leslie?
I guess.
Leslie, why don't you
take the calculator
And go and add things up
in the kitchen?
Fine.
- So your parents.
- Right.
So they're both in D.C.
Protesting the Vietnam war,
And they literally bump
into each other
Outside a donut shop.
Donuts, fascinating.
My mom spills her coffee.
My dad helps her clean it up.
That night they drive
to the Jersey shore,
Run out of gas near the beach,
and sleep in the car.
And they've been together
ever since.
That is
such a romantic story.
Oh, God, I'd love
something like that.
I know.
Me too.
You know, I always have
this weird thing
Where I think that maybe
My ex-wife and I
would still be together
If we had
had some big romantic moment
Like my folks did, you know?
Anyway, I should go.
Oh.
And if there's anything
at all I can do,
Please don't hesitate
to give me a call.
Okay, bye.
My, God.
Is it me, or is he the most
romantic, wonderful man
You've ever met?
It's you.
I'm kind of mad about him.
Yeah, I watched you
do this...
A hundred times.
And the first time he was here,
You kept licking your lips
like a dog in a hot car.
He didn't seem to pick up
on any of it.
'cause you have
terrible signals.
I have brilliant signals.
You wanna see a signal?
This is a signal.
Okay, that's actually
very good.
He's been here twice.
Why don't you just ask him out?
No.
Didn't you hear him?
He's a romantic just like me.
We can't just go out.
It's gotta be much more
difficult
And exciting than that.
Like something out of
a Sandra bullock movie.
You're nothing like
Sandra bullock.
- J lo?
- No.
- Kate Hudson?
- I'm Kate Hudson.
So I'm just
a Hugh Grant with boobs.
- That I buy.
- Thanks.
♪ can I ask you
a question? ♪
♪ can I ask you a question ♪
♪ and 99 more? ♪
♪ all your fears and mysteries
♪ the love
you're searching for ♪
♪ hey, la la la la ♪
♪ can I ask you a question? ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Okay, does anyone have
any romantic movie moments
For me and Tim?
I've got one.
Tim's a vampire, and he
wants to suck your blood
Because you're a virgin.
I don't think that's gonna
work for a lot of reasons.
I got one.
Super romantic.
All right, it's world war ii.
Thanks.
Oh, Wayne, I almost forgot.
Can you wake up early tomorrow?
- How early?
- 9:00.
Which 9:00?
Sunshine 9:00.
I had a dad drop out
for career day,
And I need you to fill in.
The kids wanna meet
a real fireman.
So I need you to pretend
to be a real fireman.
I can be a fireman.
Um, firemen need to be able
to lift, like, 100 pounds.
All at once?
Oh, Charlotte, that's
something romantic you could do.
Set your apartment on fire.
That's how I met Shawn.
I need a glass of water.
These Thai taco poppers
aren't sitting very well.
Okay, how about this?
It's raining.
We have a minor fender bender.
We both get out of the car,
our eyes meet, and we--
- Share insurance information.
Assess the damages.
Move the cars to a safe place
on the side of the road.
Fine. Ugh.
- So anyway, Wayne,
sunshine 9:00--
You, lie, fireman, kids.
Got it?
Done.
Let me get the address
for you.
Oh, look, hunter tried
to scare the girls
With this rubber spider today.
Did it work?
This thing wouldn't work
on anybody.
Wanna bet?
Ahh!
I have to tell hunter
that it worked.
You've been scared
of your own shadow
Since you were a kid.
Well, I have
a very scary shadow.
My hair often makes horns.
- That rubber spider didn't
scare a five-year-old girl.
Yes, it did.
Mike's been trying to scare
her since the third grade,
But he never has.
And he never will.
We Koreans are a brave people.
Yeah, well, so are we Irish,
With some polish.
Face it, Mike, you're never
gonna scare her.
Oh, yeah?
I'm older now.
I'm smarter now.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna sneak
into her apartment
And I'm gonna pop out
when she least expects it.
I will not rest until
that double-jointed Korean
Pees her pants.
Okay, I've got it.
Tim said he jogs at lunch
At the park around the corner.
I'll go,
I'll bring a book--
Pride and prejudice,
The most romantic book
of all time.
I'll pretend I'm reading,
and I'll bump into him.
I'll drop the book.
He'll help me pick it up.
He'll realize it's me.
He'll brush a strand of hair
out of my eyes.
Eh, I don't know, Charlotte.
I don't think
that's gonna scare him.
Wait, what were
we talking about?
Oh!
What are you doing?
Why is your grandmother here?
She always showers here
after pilates.
Hello, Michael.
Hi, grandma.
Oh.
It's so nice to see you.
So how it works
Is a bad guy
sets something on fire.
The Mayor calls us.
We hop in our truck
And zoom over there
as fast as we want.
We also save things
from trees--
Cats, Frisbees, whatever.
My uncle's a fireman.
Congratulations.
What ladder number are you?
12.
How many firemen
fit in your truck?
Ten.
How many fire hoses?
Ten, obviously.
Okay, class,
Let's say good-bye
to Mr. Fireman.
No, it's okay, I got this.
What's your last name?
Smith.
It says "Jones" on the back
of your jacket.
Well, I'm borrowing
Jones' jacket,
If it's any of your business.
You're not a fireman.
Are you gonna let him
talk to me like that?
You're a "liarman"!
Okay, okay, you got me.
I'm not a fireman.
All right, big deal.
What does your dad do
that's so great?
He sells copy machines.
Oh, I'd kill myself.
Wayne!
So what is your job?
No, I don't have a job.
Oh.
Are you okay?
He didn't even notice me.
Pride and prejudice,
One of my favorites.
Yeah, whatever,
it's a classic.
Wayne has finished his snack,
So I think it's time
for him to go.
But miss Jill,
if he doesn't have a job,
Where does he live?
Well, he lives
on his friend's couch,
But it's only
a temporary situation.
Mike said I could stay
as long as I want.
You get to sleep on a couch?
Yeah, right in front
of the TV.
- Cool.
- Mm-hmm.
So what do you do all day?
Well, when he's not
looking for a job,
He reads and practices
writing his numbers.
Don't you think we've lied
enough to these kids?
I watch TV,
I play video games,
And then I go to happy hour.
Happy hour sounds fun.
Oh, it's very fun.
All right, well,
this big guy needs a nap,
So I'm gonna hit the road.
That would be great.
So what did we learn today?
You don't need a job.
Only you can prevent
forest fires.
Spay and neuter your pets.
Jill, am I forgetting anything?
- No, just go.
- All right, cool.
I'm gonna rock a couple
of these juice boxes for later.
How do I look?
Do you have a shorter towel?
No.
- Then you look fine.
- Right.
So Tim's coming over
to get some paperwork.
It appears as if he's caught me
just out of the shower.
"oh, how unexpected,
"how intimate,
How Julia Roberts."
It's perfect.
At what point do you drop
the towel?
No, I don't drop the towel.
I just want him to see me
in a more intimate light.
Then you should drop
the towel.
He's here. He's early.
You have to leave.
That's fine.
I'll just hang
from the fire escape
And drop onto the dumpster.
You would do that for me?
Wouldn't you do that for me?
Yeah, of course.
- Okay, bye.
- Mwah.
Wait, you just got out
of the shower.
Oh, yeah, mmm, good.
Mmm, yummy.
Is that lemonade?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
I got a package
for Charlotte Payne.
Oh, I see what this is.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Oh, lady, I've been
in this job for six years.
I know what this means.
They moved the dumpster.
Are you Tim?
I can be whoever
you want me to be.
- Tim.
- Hi.
Oh, come on in, fella.
I've been with dudes before.
It's cool.
I'll come back another time.
No, no, no.
I can explain.
I've been shot.
Whoa!
I got shot.
Is Leslie even here right now?
She's supposed to be here.
I think I am gonna go.
Mike!
So are we gonna get
this party started or what?
What do you think Mike's
gonna do to try to scare you?
I don't know.
He just texted me
And told me to wait here
for him.
Hmm.
What do you think he's gonna
show up with,
A bear or a clown?
Or a bear clown?
That would be scary.
What?
I saw one once.
It was horrifying.
Ever since you told me
about your parents
And how they met,
I have been trying to have
A romantic moment with you,
because I like you.
And I feel like such an idiot.
No, no, no, I'm the idiot.
I can't believe I didn't
pick up on any of it.
Well, in fairness to you,
Some of them weren't
so much romantic moments
As crazy moments.
Still, here's this
beautiful woman
Trying to get my attention,
and I don't see any of it?
Do you see it now?
I do.
I'm sorry.
I've just been so preoccupied
with my own stuff,
Between my ex-wife and
my parents' anniversary I just--
- I think I could be
persuaded to forgive you.
- I've got an idea.
- What?
- We'd need a car.
- I can get one.
Let's get in it and drive,
Just the two of us.
Just go down to the shore
and run out of gas
Just like your parents.
Give me one second.
Leslie, I need to borrow
your car.
- Why?
- We're doing it.
We're just gonna drive,
Just like Tim's parents.
Yay!
Shush.
yay.
Fine, but no eating,
no drinking, no sexing.
Did you just say "sexing"?
Just respect my car.
Okay. Bye.
Ladies.
Hey, thanks a lot.
After a morning with you,
my kids have all decided
To pursue nothing.
Glad I could help.
Guys, five minutes
till happy hour's over.
I'm gonna go get
as much as I can carry.
Wayne, this is serious.
Hunter used to want
to be a doctor.
Now he wants to live
on Patrick's couch.
- Is Patrick a stand-up guy?
Look, you have to come back
to the classroom
And show them that you
can do something, anything.
Anything that could be
a career.
What did you want to do
when you were growing up?
Be a ninja.
Okay, what else?
Uh, drive a dune buggy
on the moon.
Come on, Wayne, think.
This is important.
There's got to be something
that you love to do,
Back when you did stuff.
I like to draw.
Eh, mostly nudes.
That's it.
That's perfect.
Come back to class,
Draw a picture for the kids--
with clothes--
And we'll tell them that you're
pursuing art as a career.
Will there be
any juice boxes?
Yes.
All right,
I'll draw them something.
Great, let's go right now.
I want it to be there when
the kids show up in the morning.
All right, fine.
Here we go.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
We're leaving.
Wayne's gonna draw a picture
for my students.
We'll be back though.
What am I gonna do with
13 sour patch Martinis?
Uh, just keep drinking
till you see the bear clown.
These things set me back
four dollars.
Well, that is it.
We are out of gas.
Whoops.
Tim?
- Sorry.
It's--sorry.
- Tim, someone's coming.
- Keep kissing me.
Is that you, Timothy?
- Who's that?
- Nobody.
Tim, what's going on?
Do you see this, Vicki?
I'm making out
with a beautiful woman.
What do you think of that?
Wait, you know this woman?
- I'm his ex-wife.
Oh, hi.
You're not supposed
to be here.
I'm calling the cops.
Oh, I'm not supposed
to be here?
This is my house.
Call the freakin' cops.
I dare you.
Dear God.
What's going on, Vick?
- It's my ex-husband.
Oh, is that son of a bitch
sleeping in my house?
You better not be sleeping
in my bed, dude.
You better step off, bro.
Oh, don't call me bro, dude.
I have the worst taste
in men.
Yeah, what's your problem?
Charlotte, it's me.
It's Mike. It's me, Mike.
My God, Mike?
What are you doing?
I was waiting for Leslie
to leave the bar
So I could scare her,
and then you two showed up.
Oh, what are we gonna do?
All right,
we got to get out of here.
How?
We're out of gas.
Charlotte, you honestly think
this guy ran out of gas
In front of his
ex-wife's house?
What are we gonna do
about Tim?
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God.
Uh, he'll be fine.
Thank you for doing this.
Oh, it's kinda fun.
It's not bad, is it?
It's great.
Maybe I could pursue art.
You know, when I was in college
My art classes were the only
ones I always made it to.
I even had a professor that
told me I had promise.
Wish my dad could see this.
Oh, Wayne.
And that little kid, hunter.
They can both suck it.
It was such a disaster.
For a romantic, that guy Tim
could really fight.
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
I really thought he was
gonna be something.
I never liked him.
You never met him.
Still, I know these things.
I'm an artist.
Hey, I'm an artist.
You want to get out of here?
Yeah, I do.
Cool.
See you later, guys.
Is Mook here yet?
I mean, is meek here?
Milk.
Mulch.
Moo, monk.
Does she mean me?
How much did she drink?
At least
13 sour patch Martinis.
She's not gonna remember
anything in the morning.
What are you doing here?
You were pretty drunk
last night.
We didn't.
We did.
Big time.
It's not a dream.
My work here is done.
Leslie,
I know you're in here,
And I am not scared.
Hey, man.
What'd you find,
a gray hair or a mouse?
Thought you were Leslie
trying to scare me,
Which is not gonna work.
You're ridiculous.
Well, she is not
in the toilet tank.
How small do you think
she is?
Trust me,
this girl is nimble.
Her grandmother spent 34 years
with the Korean circus.
She was an acrobat?
- No, she sold CDs
and t-shirts.
Oh.
Ow!
Koreans.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net