Okay, next question.
Well, that's a big no.
Wait, that's not fair.
What's the question?
It doesn't matter.
I'm trying to
save us some time.
There's a spin class
I want to get to
That starts at 6:00.
I want to hear the question.
Fine, fine.
Have you ever had
a one-night stand?
Actually- -
oh, my goodness!
Charlotte payne's
had a one-night stand.
Well, actually-
- oh, my goodness.
Charlotte payne's never
had a one-night and.
Oh, it was a wager of sorts,
And I'm not usually a
gambling type of person.
But this really
snowballed into-
Yeah, I'm definitely not
gonna make that spin class.
No.
Is it that time of year again?
Yep. Fashion week.
And our little
neighborhood bar
Has been overrun by a
flock of supermodels.
The swallows have
returned to capistrano.
Hey, guys.
Both depressed: Hey.
Look at our couch.
Yeah, five of them
fit into a space
That normally
holds three of us.
You know what?
I would much rather
date one of you guys
Than one of them
skinny, gorgeous models.
You guys have substance, a
little meat on your bones.
All: Shut up!
I don't believe it.
Ariel's here.
Ariel who?
Ariel goodman,
French-israeli supermodel.
I saw her in monte
carlo three years ago.
A prince was doing jell-o
shots off her stomach.
Wanted her ever since.
Yeah.
Well, I do not date models.
No, it's a rule of mine.
They are too much drama.
She is all yours. Go get her.
Ariel goodman,
Here comes the wayne train.
Wayne, you are a pig.
Well, pigs are the
smartest mammal,
So thank you, charlotte.
This one's on mike.
Whoa, sorry.
I don't date models!
Think you're a little low.
Wayne rutherford?
Ariel goodman?
I didn't even know
it was you. How crazy.
This is crazy.
Last time I saw you
was monte carlo, right?
Was it? I don't even remember.
Well, if you're
around this week,
We should totally hang out.
Totally.
Oh, look, that
model's on fire.
Whoa!
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
See?
The five of us can
easily fit on this couch.
Can't do it!
- My neck is hurting.
See, that is one
of the main reasons
I do not date models.
They're crybabies.
Flammable crybabies.
You guys, I have to
make a confession.
Right before she
caught on fire,
I wished for something
bad to happen to her.
Do you think I have some
kind of witch powers?
Well, not unless you wished
for her to catch on fire.
Oh, my god, I
have witch powers!
All right.
I have a confession
to make as well.
Remember how I told you
that I do not date models?
Well, the truth is
They don't date me.
Are you kidding?
- No.
Yeah, it's true, it's true.
Whenever I get around a model,
I get nervous, and
I get tongue-tied,
And I can't be myself.
Dude, the key to
models is confidence.
You got to be cocky.
You got to not
think and just talk.
You need to- - be
more like wayne.
Be more like wayne, man.
Excuse me, folks,
Anyone here see how
the fire started?
Me. I did.
Would you mind
filling out a report?
I'll fill out a report.
Mike, get your own report.
This one's mine.
What's with her?
You don't recognize that guy?
That is mr. November
From the new york
fire fighters calendar.
Yeah, mike, I'm surprised
you don't recognize him.
Well, do you think
charlotte knows that?
Oh, she knows.
Oh.
He is unbelievably,
spectacularly, crazy hot.
Ew, ugh, you're a
pig, charlotte payne.
Oh, please, it's different.
You are acting just
like when I saw ariel.
No, I'm not.
Didn't say I wanted to give
him a ride on the payne train.
That's because you can't
have a one-night stand.
You're not capable.
I've had plenty of
one-night stands.
With who? Name one.
And even if I haven't,
Everybody has to
start somewhere.
Mr. November. His
name is cade rollins.
Born June 15, 1977.
He is a gemini.
He enjoys skiing and sailing,
And he's a vegan.
I guarantee that
you will not have sex
With a vegan fireman
named cade rollins.
Is that a challenge?
All: Ooh.
It's a bet.
All:
Oh-oh-oh.
I can certainly make love-
Sex.
- Ooh.
Oh, we're not
gonna do that one?
Fine, I guarantee
I can make s-sex with cade
Before you get into
ariel's tiny little pants.
It is on.
I think that charlotte
should have some sort
Of a head start, because
she hasn't had sex in, like-
Doesn't matter.
Are you guys ready to order?
We're waiting for a
vegan fire fighter.
We heard he eats
here all the time.
Oh, you mean cade.
- Yeah.
We have a dish
named after him.
The five alarm tofu chili?
No, the cade wrap.
Oh.
I'll check back.
There he is.
Oh, brilliant.
Got to get his attention.
Cade!
Oh, hey.
Charlotte, right?
Yeah, hi.
So you guys are vegans?
I am.
Yeah, veggies,
veggies, veggies.
I do all that healthy stuff.
Do you do yoga?
Do I do yoga? Do I do yoga?
Jill, he's asking
me if I do yoga.
Do you do yoga?
Um, yeah.
Only, like, five days a week.
Right after I recycle
and rescue animals
And donate blood to them.
There's a great yoga
studio across the street.
You should come take a class.
When?
Noon tomorrow.
Ugh, noon tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Great. See you then.
Yeah.
- All right.
Wayne is going down.
You guys ready to order?
No, we're not
eating this crap.
Thanks.
So I guess I should
get this out of the way.
I'm not a billionaire anymore.
Oh, it still
hurts saying that.
So what are you going to do?
Well, I'm watching
a lot of tv,
Mastering call of duty.
No, about me.
Now that you've lost
your superpowers,
How will you get the girl?
Well, we're gonna have
to go back to your hotel,
'cause I got a
bit of a situation.
It's not going
to be that easy.
I'm gonna make
you work for it.
All right, fine.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to woo
me, wayne, hmm?
The good old-fashioned way.
Wooing.
I can totally do that.
You'll see, I'll be all like,
"woo! Woo!"
Yeah, don't do that.
Yeah, sorry, that was bad.
Where you going?
Oh, don't worry
about where I'm going.
You've got work to do. Hmm?
Oh, yeah, yeah, the wooing.
Yeah, I'm on it.
How'd it go with ariel?
Not very well.
She wants me to-
Who the hell are
you supposed to be?
You.
Told me to be more like
you. I'm being more like you.
And don johnson. It's
a bit of a hybrid.
Check it out.
Hi.
What do you say
we get outta here?
you get outta here?
Okay.
Now this is food.
Vegans think that
non-vegans hate animals.
I love animals.
I'm loving every
animal on this pizza.
Hey.
What's with your hair?
He's trying to be like me.
So wayne, how'd
it go with ariel?
It went great.
No, it didn't.
She wants you to woo her
the old fashioned way.
Mike, a little support.
It went great.
No big deal.
I got this.
- Really?
'cause it looks like what
you thought was a dunk slam
Isn't.
The term is slam dunk.
Don't be coming over
here to our country
And screwing up
our catch phrases.
You're just mad 'cause ariel's
Not falling for your
big, dumb brown eyes.
Well, your eyes are big
and dumb and brown too.
Yeah, well, cade thinks
they're beautiful.
Boom!
Yeah, well, ariel is
a super hot supermodel.
Super boom!
- We're out.
Worked pretty good.
"super boom" just
came into my head.
You did really good.
Hey.
Ah.
I'm so glad you could make it.
You are gonna love this class.
It's the perfect balance
between ashtanga and hatha.
Oh, good.
'cause if it wasn't,
I'd be like, "grr,
get me out of here."
It's a shame to put all
this limberness to waste.
I'm very flexible.
I'm very gay.
Cool.
Okay, everyone.
Let's start with
an easy trikonasana.
Ooh, trikonasana.
I think I broke my ass-ena.
What should I do
with my powers?
Should I feed hungry people?
Should I stop wars?
Should I break up brangelina?
You are not a witch.
Yet, you're also
not a masseuse.
My neck is worse.
Well, hey, guys.
Just popping in, checking
to see how everyone's doing.
I heard there was a terrible
accident in yoga class.
I'm fine.
Well, that is it. It is over.
You slept with her.
No, but it's just a
formality at this point.
I got a plan.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna woo her brains out.
Well, you better woo her soon.
'cause I'll have you know
cade is on his way over here.
You can't even move your neck.
The way I have sex, I
don't have to move anything.
I'm not sure cade's
gonna enjoy that.
See you later.
I've got to win this bet.
And I've got to win it now.
When cade gets here,
We're giving new
meaning to the phrase
"the british are coming."
So are you ready to be wooed?
Yes, I am.
What are those?
Two round trip
tickets to romance.
I wouldn't normally say
something that stupid,
I just thought it was
something a wooer would do.
You still think money is
the way to a woman's heart.
You think taking me to
paris is going to woo me?
No, it's not paris.
- Where is it?
It's anywhere in the
continental United States.
To be used anytime we want.
Except weekends, holidays,
And any other blackout
date shown on this calendar.
Oh, yeah, and when
we get to the airport,
My name is michael poole.
Wayne, I wanted
something from your heart.
Yeah, I don't know
what that means.
Well, figure it out because
you've got one more shot.
They say wisconsin is
beautiful in the fall.
I know it's not,
who am I kidding?
Oh, cade, I forgot you
were going to drop by.
How nice to see you.
Mm, that was tasty.
Have you been eating carrots?
Yep. Nature's candy.
Would you like one?
- Never turn down a carrot.
Cade...
Would you like to see
the tv in my bedroom?
Do you wanna go have sex?
Yes, please.
- Cool.
Ew!
So gross!
I am so sorry.
Did you touch it?
You saw me touch it.
Why would you have
a leather headboard?
Sh, let's just forget it.
It's the only thing
in the entire apartment
That's made from
animal product.
Then what about those boots?
- Um...
And that purse?
There's down in these pillows.
- Mm.
Charlotte, this place
is a killing field!
I had no idea.
You said you were a vegan.
Well, vegans don't lie.
I'm outta here.
W- w-wait,
let's stay!
Let's have some more carrots!
Broccoli?
sex?
From my heart. From my heart.
What can I give her
that's from my heart?
You could write her something.
A book?
We don't have time
to write a book.
Be practical, mike.
No, I was thinking you
could write her a poem.
You know, in her
native tongue.
Huh.
She's french-israeli, so
what's her native tongue?
Hm.
I once heard her talk
in a wacky language.
Okay, was it pretty?
No.
- That is hebrew.
Okay.
All right, a poem.
Okay, here it goes.
Get this down.
- Got it.
Arielle...
I wanna have sex with you.
Yeah, how's that?
Inspired.
Um, I was thinking something
more along the lines
Of "arielle, my desire
for you has never waned.
My heart has never forgotten."
So what's that in hebrew?
Um...
Hebrew...
That's really beautiful, yeah.
I was just trying to have a
one night stand before I die.
I hope you don't mind me
talking to you like this.
I'm waiting for my
friends to get here.
I'm not even listening to you.
Did you know vegans don't lie?
They lie every time they put
A piece of tofurkey
in their mouths
And say, "yum."
And if leslie could
break up brangelina,
I would encourage
her to do it.
Because they are
very annoying.
So what do you got?
And I hope it's
from your heart.
I can't believe you're
making me go through all this
'cause I don't have any money.
That's not why.
I'm doing this to get back
at you because you hurt me.
Oh, good, I thought it was
'cause I didn't have any money.
So what did I do?
You really don't remember?
Monte carlo?
We had plans to
meet at the casino,
And you never showed up.
I waited nearly ten minutes.
Sorry.
Well, anyway...
I wrote you a poem
in your native tongue.
You wrote me a poem?
Oh, wayne, that's exactly
what I wanted to hear.
Really?
Let's go get in the
tub at my hotel room,
And maybe you can,
uh, read it to me.
That sounds good.
Charlotte?
Oh, there he is.
Winner, winner,
chicken dinner.
Wayne...Let's go.
My apartment.
How'd I get here?
Awkwardly. I had to carry you.
What happened to your french
- israeli super duper model?
Well, maybe some things
Are more important
than supermodels.
Really?
- No, not really.
No, I don't know.
Don't make me think about it.
I can't do it, wayne.
I can't have a
one night stand.
Well, you're too good for
one night stands, anyway.
Wayne?
Yeah?
So are you.
Good night, char.
Where is charlotte?
She's supposed to be here.
I think that's arielle.
Excuse me?
Where's wayne?
Hmm, he rejected me
for the second time.
Can you believe it?
He told me he'd have
to take a rain check.
And just left with
this drunk girl
With a fake accent.
Oh...I'm sorry.
I know how much
he was into you.
The guy's gotta be
a pretty big fool
To leave a girl like you.
Really?
That's nice of you to say.
I should probably tell you
I don't normally date models.
See that? That's all me.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net