Previously On: "10 Things i
Hate About You"...
Stop seeing that dee
p-voiced man-boy.
Dad, you don't even know him.
You're right.
Invite him over for dinner.
You break up with him,
and I'll give you your life back.
If you don't come over,
he says we can't hang out.
You are nowhere near qualified
to see my daughter. Get out.
Get out.
Dad, we made all of that up.
You've been punked.
This past week with
you has been amazing.
You're not choosing me?
I broke up with Joey so
we could stay friends,
and then I got back
with him a second later,
because I realized real friends
would never make me choose
between them and my totally hot,
wonderful new boyfriend.
You said yourself,
you don't even know this guy.
If I learn he's bad news,
he's gone.
So there's no actual
meat in this meatloaf?
No, just lentils.
- -
- Please be a pizza.
Oh, it's Joey.
Watch this and learn.
I'm sorry, young man,
but if you'd like to see Bianca,
visiting hours are from 3:
30 to 5:00 on Tuesdays.
I've actually come to see you, sir.
It is my hope...
That you'll grant me permission
to date your daughter.
Here's my driving record,
vaccination card,
and a list of references.
They can't be-- Friends,
family or fake. I know, sir.
Did you put him up to this?
Good girl.
Let's go to my study
and make some calls.
If they all check out, I'll
need an itinerary for your date.
Is your phone GPS-enabled?
Wasn't that so romantic?
So romantic. Maybe they'll
negotiate your dowry while they're
at it.
How many camels do you
think you're worth?
You're just jealous. I'm nauseous.
It's the "Meatloaf". At least
Joey asked me out on a real date.
Has Patrick ever asked you?
Look, if I wanted to go on a date
with him, I'd ask him myself.
Feminism, ever heard of it?
isn't that the thing
that killed romance?
English Version By
ISUBS.COIL.US.TO Team Sync By
YesCool - ADDIC7ED.COM Team!
Thank God it's Friday.
Or, if you're an atheist, thank
the spinning rotation of the Earth.
I'm sorry, did I offend you again?
It's all right, I'm used to it.
Don't get me started on the pledge
of allegiance.
Big plans this weekend?
I think I'll check out
this new documentary
on the private life of plants.
Sounds kind of scandalous.
You are one weird chick.
Have an educational weekend.
Maybe we can hang out.
Well, I am really busy, so if you
want to hang out, maybe we should
set a time.
Are you asking me on a date?
I'm just saying, if you give me a
time frame, maybe I can fit you in.
- How about tonight?
- A more specific time frame.
Does 7 work, or will you be
watching your plant movie?
7's fine. It's a-- Deal.
Oh, hey, Hacksaw Manor 4 opens
tonight. You want to go?
Sorry, dude, it's the Sabbath.
No electricity allowed.
You never observe the Sabbath.
Nana's visiting.
Got to jet. Mom's making
me pick up the challah.
So where are you taking me tonight?
I'll give you a hint.
These are knives.
We're going to see Hacksaw
Manor?
No, Benihana.
He's taking her to Benihana?
That's where he took
me on our first date.
Okay, Joey's pathetic.
He totally lacks imagination.
I'm bored with this topic. Hey, do
you want to go see Hacksaw Manor 4
tonight?
As much as I would love to see
aristocrats torn to shreds,
I have a date tonight.
Fine. I know Janelle
wants to see it.
She hates aristocrats
because her family's poor.
Um, Janelle and her boyfriend
are busy tonight, too.
We're sort of going
on a double date,
but you could totally come, too.
And be the fifth wheel? No,
thank you.
I was invited to, like,
four different parties tonight,
and one of them is at
a celebrity's house.
I wish I could tell you who, but
the church of Scientology might
get upset.
Totes. All right, I'll see you.
Okay.
Mark this day in your calendar,
Bianca. I am asking you for advice.
- Burn them.
- I'm serious.
So am I. You can't wear
those on your date,
and you can't wear
that ponytail, either.
Guys only find those
sexy on cheerleaders.
A, what? And B, it's not a date.
At least, I don't think so.
You don't know? Would you
just help me pick the shoes?
Well, did you ask him
or did he ask you?
That part's a little unclear.
See, this is what you
really needed advice about.
Here's how you know
if it's a date--
If he's made a plan,
and if he pays.
I'm sorry, did I just stumble into
Mad Men?
Trust me, those women knew
when they were on a date.
I got your 911 text.
What's the emergency?
I can't decide between
these two earrings.
A true crisis.
- Daring or distracting?
- Way distracting.
That's what I thought.
Thank God you're here.
Come on, let's lip gloss.
Are you so excited?
Joey is such a catch.
And Chastity always
said he's amazi in bed.
Athletic, sensual and hygienic.
Oh, my God. Do you think
he expects sex tonight?
I doubt it. I mean,
it's the first date.
This may be California,
but we still have some standards.
Did you do it on your
first date with Mr. Ross?
Crap.
Joey still thinks I had
sex with my teacher.
Because you did.
Oh. You still think I did, too.
Um, look, Dawn...
Don't hate me, but I lied to you.
I'm still a virgin.
I was just trying to fit in.
Oh. Yeah, that makes more sense.
Oh, my God. That's Joey.
I should just tell him, right?
No. If you're honest now,
it might turn him off.
What if he tries to
have sex with me?
Don't panic. Just make out with
him like you normally would,
and if he tries to go further,
make up excuses.
Ouch, I think I pulled
my groin during Pilates.
Ooh, I think I'm
getting a cold sore.
Exactly. High school
boys are so stupid,
they'll believe anything.
And by the time you
tell him the truth,
he'll be so in love with you,
he won't even care.
Oh, my God, I love this plan.
And this is the baby crowning.
Wow. You never really think
about it, but it's a baby.
A whole baby that just
grows in there from scrah,
like a brownie.
A brownie that costs $250,
000 to raise.
And that's just in
the first 18 years.
If that brownie goes to college,
which it better,
you can tack on at
least $100,000 more.
My brownies will get
sports scholarships.
- You're missing the point.
- Hi, Joey.
Wow, you look amaze-balls.
I'm sorry, what?
Don't worry, Daddy,
it's a compliment.
Have her back by 10:00.
Remember what I said
about the brownies.
Don't get near her oven.
Hi, Patrick.
Have fun on your date, or whatever.
Hello, son.
If I come in, do I have to
watch the slide show again?
Yes, but we'll go
through it faster.
Okay, I have a last minute
surprise for you, Five-o.
Oh, goodie. I love surprises.
Should I close my eyes?
Sure. Just put this
blindfold on first.
So where should we head
for tonight's adventure?
I don't care.
I figured you'd have a plan.
Well, I'm hungry.
Let's go eat. Cool.
How about Hal's Steak House?
I'm dying for a rib eye.
You know I don't eat
anything with a face.
They usually cut that part off
before they serve it to you. You
don't say.
How about Vegan Nirvana?
No, thanks. I'll just chew
on a tree and save 20 bucks.
You know what? I'll just drive.
We'll find something.
#  The boy meets the girl # <i
># Somewhere in a crowd #
This doesn't look like Benihana.
Because it's my house. Voila.
I set the table myself.
I even cooked a dish I
invented for myself.
I call it chicken a la Joey.
And it's only 300
calories per serving.
Wow. Joey, this is so thoughtful.
Well, I really wanted
tonight to be special.
Don't move. I'm going to
get us the hors d'oeuvres.
Oh, I almost forgot the best part--
My parents are out of town.
We have the place all to ourselves.
Want to go somewhere
more comfortable?
Uh, sure, but do you think I could
have another piece of pie first?
Sorry, babe, you finished it.
Let's move to the couch.
Um, okay. You're so tense.
Really? I don't know why.
I couldn't be looser.
I don't mean that I'm loose.
I just... I'll give you a massage.
Look, 20/20.
Man, I miss Ted Koppel.
I'll record it. Just relax.
Did you feel something?
I think there was an earthquake.
Nope, didn't feel a thing.
Baby, what's wrong?
Do you have any aspirin?
I have a splitting virgin.
Finally. I'm starving.
We would have been eating
an hour ago if you ate fish.
Nothing with a face.
- This place is expensive.
- We're not going anywhere else.
Hi, my name is Winston. I'm going
to be your waiter. Can I take your
order?
Actually, we haven't finished--
Look, in 45 minutes, I got to
kick you out of this table.
We got some VIPs coming in.
So more time with the menu,
less time eating.
I'll have the chicken.
The passion fruit poisson
or the fricassee?
The first one.
And for the lady?
I'll just have the side salad.
And please don't call me lady.
- And for your entr?©e?
- That is my entr?©e.
Look, I'm just letting you know
that the side salads are side
salads.
They're quite small.
That's why they call
them side salads.
Get whatever you want. I got it.
You sure? Don't worry about it.
I'll have the ginger chipotle tofu,
but without the chipotle.
Okay, just so you know,
that's not the way
the award-winning chef designed it.
And for your water,
sparkling or still?
Tap. Of course.
Actually, I'd like
sewer water, please.
I'm going to get you for that.
You know, Hacksaw Manor 1,
there wasn't enough blood.
Hacksaw Manor 2,
way too much blood.
Hacksaw Manor 3,
too many babies died.
Chastity Church?
What are you doing here?
Are you by yourself?
Of course not. I am on a date.
Okay, I can't really tolerate a
man screaming during a movie.
It is so unsexy.
So I told him to sit in the back.
Oh, that sounds exactly like you.
I'm going to get some popcorn.
Will you save my seat?
Oh, could you get me a hot dog?
Yeah, sure.
And some licorice.
Black. I hate the red.
And maybe some nachos.
But only if they
have nachos supreme,
but not if the nachos
supreme have sour cream.
Could I just-- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Is that all?
- And a diet soda.
And hurry back. You don't
want to miss the previews.
Okay.
Here you are, safe and sound.
And two hours before curfew.
Thanks for walking
me to my door, Joey.
Tonight was...
Great.
Dinner was amazing.
I'll e-mail you the recipes.
Up top, Five-o. Awesome night.
Joey, wait.
Are you sure you're okay
with me being a virgin?
Totally. No problemo.
Everyone's a virgin at some point.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Then can I have a kiss good night?
Sure. Good night.
I know the drummer
from Orchid Breeder.
Shut up. How?
This guy I know met him in rehab.
This guy I kvow. Was it you?
You got me. I'm a sex addict.
Oh, my God. I thought I
recognized you from group.
You were the guy
wearing the hoodie.
You should have seen what
I was wearing underneath.
Nothing.
If you hand me your card now,
it'll save time.
I'd like to review the check first.
Thanks, Patrick.
I'll totally get the next one.
Cool. But this time...
Run. Come on.
I can't believe you did that.
What were you thinking?
We have to go back
and pay that bill.
Excuse you.
This is not funny. That was wrong.
What's wrong are those prices.
Who pays that much?
All the other people
in the restaurant.
Lighten up. That waiter was a jerk.
What's the big deal?
The big deal is that I don't want
to commit a crime on our first
date.
Oh, I didn't realize
this was a date.
Neither did I,
until you offered to pay.
- Ah, but I didn't pay.
- Ah, yes, I remember.
Fine, this isn't a date.
What's your problem?
I thought you were cool with this.
With what?
With going on dates and
not calling them dates?
What's so terrible about a date?³
Because a date comes with all
these expectations on me,
and I didn't sign up for--
Are you okay?
Is something wrong?
It's not fair.
I know. They're just aristocrats
whose carriage broke
down in the wrong manor.
No, you idiot. My life.
My life isn't fair.
I dumped Joey, and now he's
on a date on a Friday night,
and I'm here alone.
I'm here, Chastity.
Exactly.
Oh, my life is such a mess.
Why is this happening to me?
I don't know.
Can it happen somewhere else?
We're trying to watch a movie.
Hey, hey, give her a break.
She's been through a lot.
Please tell me what
Joey did to you.
Can you just leave me in peace
with my ice cream and my Sex and
the City marathon, please?
Did he try to have
sex in your city?
I don't want to talk
about it right now, Dad.
Why didn't they make
you with an off switch?
Fine. Then I'm going
to call and ask him.
- I'll just get his folder.
- Nothing happened, Dad.
You really want to
know what happened?
At the end of our date,
he gave me a high five.
Are you happy?
Ecstatic.
- That was scary.
- So scary.
Who knew there were so many ways
to kill people with one hand tool?
Yeah. And if anyone
finds out about tonight,
I'll find one more.
Hey, Dr. Stratford.
I missed you, too. Is Bianca home?
She's in her room.
Just leave the door open-- And I
know you will, because you're a
good egg.
Look, Joey, I didn't mean to
overdo it with the slideshow.
You may kiss her good night.
- Chastely.
- Is that with or without tongue?
- Without.
- Okay.
- You okay?
- I'm never eating tofu again.
Promise? Hey,
look on theright side...
Our first date was memorable.
But I'm not giving you
a good night kiss.
Your breath is seriously nasty.
- Oh, my god. Is she drunk?
- No, food poisoning.
Okay. Come on inside.
We'll get you some Gatorade.
Maybe pump your stomach, huh?
- Patrick, about the check...
- Oh, my God. Are you kidding?
- I'll take care of it somehow.
- Do not pay for the tofu.
Joey, what are you doing here?
I came to apologize.
I freaked out on you.
No, I'm sorry.
I should have been honest.
It's just-- I was expecting our
relationship to be an R-rated
movie.
Actually, I thought we
might even be NC-17,
since you slept with your teacher.
And then I found out we were PG,
and I uldn't remember
when my last PG movie was.
And then I was driving home,
and I remembered.
Transformers 2.
That's the last PG movie I saw.
And Megan Fox was so hot in it,
- And she didn't even flash a boob.
- Okay.
What I'm saying is is that
no matter what kind
of movie we are,
if we're going to be PG,
then you're my Megan Fox.
That is so sweet.
And over time, we can eventually
build up to being R-rated.
Cool. That works for me.
When you say eventually,
do you mean weeks or months?
English Version By iSubs.Coil.Us.To Team
sync By YesCool... Addic7eD.com Team
www.tvsubtitles.net