Hate About You...
We did not get a chance
to officially meet.
- Kat Stratford.
- William Blankenship.
So it's theoretically possible
that you could be interested
in someone besides me?
Yes, if she wasn't
just a theoretical person.
Your mother was the love of my life,
and after she died,
I never thought I'd want
to meet someone again,
but just that little spark
of anticipation
made me realize life goes on.
You betrayed me.
It's not personal,
it's just politics.
One day, Brangelina
will be obsolete,
and all of your diligent
studying will have been
for naught.
That's a fancy word
for nothing.
You're welcome.
Thanks. For transferring
out of the school?
I have two tickets
I can't use
for the Andrecorso's
art opening tonight,
Mad Cow Fire.
It was denied federal funding
for being--
Too controversial.
I'm dying to see it.
Wait. I don't like you.
You can't still be upset
about meatless Mondays.
That was two weeks ago.
What if I reluctantly,
yet sincerely, begged
for your forgiveness?
Mm, sorry. I'm not charmed
by the Masterpiece Theater act.
Jack the Ripper had
a British accent, too.
You honestly find me
that awful?
I think you should
be deported,
and if I didn't have
such strong reservations
about the INS,
I would report you.
All rightie then.
Pleasure as-- Well, never.
Fine.
I'll take them
off your hands.
Thanks.
You can go.
Hey.
Hey back.
Do you want to see
this cool modern art show
tonight?
Let me think for a second.
Spend a night
staring at blobs of paint,
pretending they don't
look like bird crap.
Ah, but this is different.
Some of his paintings
are made with bird droppings.
He believes in using
everyday materials--
Oh, never mind.
Fivehead, I just got us tickets
to the French club's
movie night.
I think it's Saturday at 7,
but I'm not sure,
'cause the dude
selling the tickets
only spoke French.
What does--
[speaks gibberish French]
...mean?
That's not
even close to French.
Let me see the tickets.
Tres Jolie?
Man, I'd love to see that
on the big screen.
So allez avec nous.
Oh, come on,
you guys are a couple.
I don't want to, you know,
get all up in that.
No, you do not.
Dawn just broke up witMax.
We can all go together,
and if the movie's lame,
we can leave together.
Sweet.
A bientôt, mes amis.
[speaks gibberish French]
Not French.
Tickets.
Are you sure Dawn's
going to be into this?
Why wouldn't she be?
It's just a movie.
It's a make-out movie.
Translate By Mumy [iSubs.coil.us.to]
Sync By YesCool! [Addic7ed.com]
Gross. I'm not going
to a make-out movie
with you and Joey.
No, not like that. Ew.
Cameron's going,
so it'll be me and Joey
and a couple people
hanging out together in, like,
a casual group thing.
Sounds like a fix-up.
Sorry, Bianca.
I only have 126 Saturday nights
left before college,
and I promised my dad I'd start
taking school seriously.
I can't waste one
on a nork.
Please? I already
told him you'd go.
Plus, what else
are you going to do?
All that's on TV are shows
about people who want to dance
or can't dance or do dance
with overly tan celebrities.
That's true.
But what if Cameron
thinks this is a date
and falls in love with me?
Just watching you
go through that
was so annoying.
He won't. I'll make sure of it.
Just don't look
too gorgeous.
Okay. But if I get bored,
I'm peeling you off
Joey's face
and making you
hang out with us.
Yay.
You don't have to pretend
you're not trying to fix us up.
I know you.
You can't help yourself.
What? No. Yes, I can.
She and Max broke up.
I'm available. Well done.
You should see
her baby pics on Facebook.
And she's a Leo. I'm an Aries.
The universe is smiling down
on this union.
No, the universe
is freaking out right now
because you're already
off the rails.
Look, Bianca, I know
I thought I loved you
and Stacy
and that girl in homeroom
who said hi to me,
but this thing with Dawn
has real potential.
Cameron, there is no thing.
You've got to stop
falling in love like this
if you want any chance
at a normal life.
But not falling in love
is hard.
Don't worry.
I'll coach you.
Whenever you feel like
you're falling for Dawn,
just recite this mantra.
Look me in the eyes.
These are not
feelings of love.
Okay. These are not
Now own it.
[both]
These are not
feelings of love.
[both]
These are not
feelings of love.
[both]
These are not
feelings of love.
Ooh, that would go perfect
in our living room.
First, I have a taser
in my purse,
and second,
I have your ticket,
so why are you here?
I gave you my extra tickets.
And you're welcome.
Thank you. Now please let me
enjoy the exhibit in peace.
Materials-- Human blood
and elephant dung.
I hope he didn't
finger paint this.
There it is.
I knew I could make you smile.
Oh, that wasn't a smile.
It was a wince.
Really?
Your humor causes me
physical pain.
Right.
[Dr. Statford]
Hi, sweetie.
Guess what?
That nice Ms. Tharpe
from your fake intervention
left me a voice mail asking
if I wanted to chaperone
your movie night,
to which I will reply,
"Sign me up."
Sorry, Dad,
but you're too late.
Those chaperone slots
are like hot donuts.
They go fast.
Darn it. I'm sure
they could have used
my expertise.
All these squishy parents
nowadays want to be
friends with their kids.
Kids don't need more friends.
They need old, scary people
to intimidate them.
Well, Dad,
you'll really be missed.
That was close.
Could you imagine my dad
chaperoning a make-out movie?
What? What did you say?
A make-out movie?
Dawn's expecting me
to kiss her?
I've never kissed
a human girl.
No, no, no, no.
There will be no kissing.
Dawn's still hung up
on Max Morita.
Now eat your apple sauce.
Poor Dawn.
I've been there.
Bet she could use a hug.
Mantra.
[both]
These are not
feelings of love.
Well, that was bloody awful.
You seriously think
a show like that deserves
government funding?
Just because we thought
it was crappy, pun intended,
doesn't mean it shouldn't
be supported.
Maybe he's ahead of his time,
like Van Gogh.
Oh, it's Van Gogh.
But if art is subjective,
then it should be driven
by the marketplace.
So based on that logic,
last year's best film
was, what, The Hangover?
Oh, it's up there.
Come on, the naked guy
in the trunk? Amazing.
Tonight was fun, right?
Yeah, shockingly.
How about a proper date?
What?
I'll pick you up.
You'll wear your good jeans.
I'll offend you
by opening the door,
you'll lecture me
on women's rights,
so I'll let you
pick up the check.
As enticing as that sounds,
I can't.
I'm seeing someone.
The motorcycle chap?
He's your boyfriend?
We don't feel the need
to label everything.
So does that mean that
you and your non-boyfriend
can see other people?
No, I think.
Look, I just can't
go a date with you, okay?
It's complicated.
Well, if it ever gets
uncomplicated, let me know.
So I'm prepping for
our make-out-a-thon.
I've been eating
eucalyptus leaves, parsley,
and last night, my mom made
garlic toast, my fave,
and all I did was smell it.
Joey, that's so sweet.
I can't wait to make out
with you for three hours.
I know. Me too.
And fingers crossed,
we'll be able to reach
a legendary kissers' high.
What's that?
Oh, Bianca.
When you're kissing that long,
you're breathing in
each other's air
and your brain goes into
this sparkly Zen place
and you feel like
you're floating above
and looking down at yourself.
Joey, are you sure
that's not astral projecting?
No, that's when you have
a sexy dream.
Hey, Bianca,
the mantra is working.
Last night, I had the urge
to call Dawn, but I didn't.
At least not on a real phone.
Nice self-control.
And then she sat
next to me in study hall.
Don't worry, coach.
Every time I almost said
"I want to live in your hair
"and vacation on the tippy tip
of your cute little nose,"
I did my mantra in my head--
These are not
feelings of love--
And then said normal stuff.
Yay. Go us.
Yeah.
Hi, guys.
Cameron, wear blue tomorrow.
It'll make your eyes
jump off your face.
And try to style your hair
like Jake Gyllenhaal,
with that swoosh thing.
Sure, if I got time.
Why don't I do it for you?
Let me see what I'm
working with.
Down.
You need product.
Come on. Got some mousse
in my locker.
These are not feelings of love.
Hey, Patrick.
How lame was the art show?
Not lame at all, actually.
His work has
this savagery to it
that's really primal.
Sounds kinky.
Blank was there.
Blank. Stupid name.
What, his parents were too lazy
to come up with, like, Bob?
It's a nickname.
His name is William.
Still lame.
It was a weird night.
In addition to the bloody limbs
and severed dolls' heads,
he asked me out.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
So what did you say?
What do you think I said?
I don't know.
I wasn't there.
Are you going to go?
Why would I do that?
Why wouldn't you?
So you'd have no problem
with me going on a date
with him?
Why would I?
This is a free country.
You remind me of that
all the time.
If you want to go, go.
Okay, I will.
Have a nice time.
I plan on it.
May I present
the winning look.
Why are you going through
all this trouble for Cameron?
You said he was a nork.
That was before
I got to know him.
That was two days ago.
It feels like forever.
He's so bumbly and funny
and such a good listener.
Every time I talk, he stops
to process what I've said.
Think how cute
our kids would be--
Half-Asian
and the perfect height.
Kids? Dawn, you're not
supposed to like Cameron.
You're supposed
to tolerate him, remember?
Yeah, but I could use
a nice boyfriend,
especially one who can
pick me up and carry me around.
Just think,
when we go to a concert,
I could finally see
what's going on.
Back up, back way up.
You can't do this to Cameron.
He's fragile and innocent
and vulnerable.
Aw, like a sweet
little baby lamb.
No, not like a lamb,
like a boy who will
fall in love with you
and be devastated
when in 24 to 48 hours,
you fall in love
with someone else.
You're right, you're right.
I bet he's never even
kissed a girl.
He hasn't.
Clay Aiken has more experience
with women than he does.
So I'll just have to kiss him
and see if he's the one.
Yeah, I'm just about to watch
some riveting television
about people dancing.
Dad, Ms. Tharpe just called.
A chaperone just cancelled.
You're off the wait list.
I'll grab my kit.
♪ [French music]
♪ [singing in French] ♪
[Kat]
I can't believe
this many Padua students
are willing to read subtitles.
There's not loads
of dialogue in the film.
I mean, has anybody
actually spoken yet?
Shh, Jolie is about to speak.
[speaks in French]
Do you find Jolie
to be too whimsical,
or not whimsical enough?
A tad too whimsical,
especially the way she walks
with one foot on the curb
and one foot in the street.
She's going to get
whimsically hit by a bus.
Hands where I can see them.
Bianca, why is your dad here?
[Dr. Stratford]
All body parts on top
of the blankets.
Oh, I have no clue.
Great, now no one can make out.
[mutters]
Not feelings of love.
These are not
feelings of love.
Hey, Daddy, over here.
Hi, honey.
Hi, kids.
Hey!
Warning shot.
Dr. Stratford, I'm so glad
you could make it.
I didn't think
you were interested.
Are you kidding?
I live to keep teenagers
from having fun.
Wow.
Um, we're low on soda
at the concession stand.
Would you help me restock?
I'd do it myself,
but I just have these
tiny little bird wrists.
I'm not being sexist,
just stating a fact.
I'm on it.
Just follow me, this way.
[whimpers]
Oh, boy.
Look, Dawn. Paris.
It's so beautiful.
We should
go backpacking there.
Dawn, look.
The Eiffel Tower.
Okay, I'm going in.
I'll see you in three hours.
We should have known.
That this would be
a Roman orgy?
Come on, people.
You're in public.
Well, if we can't
beat these hedonists,
I say we--
Join them? No, thank you.
This has swine flu
written all over it.
I was going to say
ignore them.
Mmm, this is good.
And messy.
You've got a little, uh--
Chocolate on your--
Thanks.
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
I know, I know.
It's complicated.
Which is ironic, because
Leather Jacket Man
is so simple.
What do you mean by that?
I'm just guessing here,
but I can't see e two of you
sitting around debatin
off-shore drilling.
Look, we debate lots of stuff.
Just stop talking about him
fore you--
Before what?
Before I tell you
what you already know?
That you're too good for him?
I can't believe you just
said that out loud.
You are such an elitist.
You can't tell me the thought
hasn't crossed yr mind.
I don't know who I find
more annoying, you or Jolie.
This date is over.
You have to come
to my parents' house
in Laguna this summer.
Oh, I just got accepted
into space camp,
but I can bail.
It's just space.
Oh, Dawn.
I don't remember my life
before we kissed.
[coughs]
Mantra.
I'll be right back.
These are not
feelings of love.
Female incomin
the re of high school   or you'd
daydreaming about living
in some girl's hai
Thmantra's not worng.
And you want to know why?
Because these are
feelings of love.
Da's into me.
She invited me to Laguna.
Th's what she es.
She falls in love
every other day,
just like you,
except she'll be
over it morrow
and you won't.
Well, this feels real  me,
so I'd appreciate it
if you would butt out.
She asked me to proofread
this e-mail she wrote
to Max Morita.
Hey, Max, it would be
so awesome if you could
hang at my parents' house
in Laguna this summer.
She wrote that three days ago.
There's a typo.
Laguna has one "g,"
just so you know.
I'm sorry.
I just don't want to see you
get your heart broken.
Thanks.
Wow. Walter,
what a heart-breaking story.
Thank you for sharing
your truth with me.
I'm afraid I've over-shared.
Maybe it's the couch,
or just that
you're so easy to talk to.
I just feel for you.
Raising two teenage girls
by yourself--
It just seems really lonely.
I've lost people too, Walter.
My first fiancée,
he fell overboard
on a booze cruise
in Cozumel.
I'm so sorry.
I thought he was dead,
for many years.
Then I found him on Facebook.
Well, man like that's
bound to fall off
something else.
Where do you think
you're going?
Patrick?
We're going home.
Well, I guess
congratulations are in order.
You're walking on two legs.
Okay--
Why don't you get
on your broom stick
and fly back to whatever
Harry Potter movie
you came from?
Stop it.
I don't want to hurt you.
That's weird, 'cause I want
to hurt you a lot.
Let's go.
Are you kidding me?
All right, sorry, guys.
Whoever beats the crap
out of each other
does not win me!
Stay away from my girlfriend.
Okay, I do have a problem
with you seeing other guys.
Good. So we're exclusive.
No, I'm going to see
other people.
I just don't want you to.
You guys just missed Jolie
dancing in a rain puddle.
Uh, I feel like
watching the movie now.
Yeah, but I want
to make out.
Why don't you make out
with Max Morita?
What?
Hope the beach house
is big enough for
all the guys you invited.
Bianca, you showed him
my Max e-mail?
I didn't even send that.
I was trying to protect him.
I asked you to back off,
and you wouldn't.
You know what your problem is?
You are too meddling
in Cameron's love life.
I am not.
Yes, you are.
You kind of are.
For your "informash,"
I'm crazy about this guy.
I like him for the reasons
you like him as a friend.
I don't care if you believe it.
It's happening.
Cameron, we're moving.
Pick me up.
[Twice]
Okay.
What's going on
with you, Fivesies?
Why are you obsessing
over them?
It's just weird.
They're my best friends.
It's like sixth grade
all over again,
when Jojo Riverton
and Amy Gardella
went to Wild Water Kingd
without me.
I know it's not the same,
but I'll go
to Wild Water Kingdom with you.
I mean, for real.
It sounds awesome.
[Playing Franch Song]
Sync By YesCool
[Addic7ed.com], [iSubs.coil.us.to]
www.tvsubtitles.net