-I think we should give it a shot.
-I do, too. -Is that what this is?
Your master plan to get me to sleep with you?
-I love you, Bianca. -Oh, my God. I love you, too.
Just because I want to have sex
doesn't mean I should.
I've been fooled by guys
like you before,
but not his time.
I'm on The Biggest Poser.
I leave for New York tomorrow.
-I miss my boyfriend.
-Joey left two days ago.
I can still smell his body spray.
-That's because I'm wearing it.
To remember him.- He's not dead. He's just on
a reality TV show, which is probably worse.
-At least there's dignity in death.
-Could you show a little compassion?
This is his locker.
We shared so many kisses here.
Here's a novel idea,
why don't you call him?
Then he can listen to this
instead of me.
I can't. He's sequestered in the model house,
and they only have one phone.
Last night, some girl
told Joey to hang up
or she'd scratch his face.
I'd give anything to hear
the sound of his voice.
The Buddha says, "Desire is
the root of all suffering."
Thanks, fortune cookie.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
The fact that you want Joey to call
is creating the pain you're feeling right now.
So what? I shouldn't
want him to call me?
Exactly.
So you're not dying to talk to Patrick
about the other night?
If I wanted to talk
to him about it,
I'd call him.
He's not in a model house.
I'm walking my path,
and he's walking his.
I wish him well.
You're so deluded.
Whoa, wait a second.
Why is Dad talking
to Miss Tharp?
Maybe he worried you're an android.
Oh, my God, they're dating.
♪ Hey, hey ♪
Bianca, calm down. Try and imagine we're bamboo
gently bending in the wind.
And hurricane Tharp
is about to rip us to shreds.
We don't know they're dating.
Maybe they were reminiscing
about your fake intervention.
I am an expert on fliy dy language.
She did the hair flip/arm squeeze
which means they've been on two dates
and they've made out with tongue.
What are we going to do
about this unholy union?
We support Dad.
We've been wanting him
to date for years, remember?
Someone age-appropriate
who workat the hospital,
not the crazy lady from school
with zero boundaries.
Dad's coming.
-If you say anything, I will hurt you.
-I thought Buddhists were nonviolent.
-I'm a beginner. -Hi, girls.
-Hi, Daddy. -Hi, Dad.
-How was your day?
-Uneventful. -Yep.
They ran this guy's shorts
up the flagpole at lunch.
That was funny.
And then we saw you
flirting with Miss Tharp.
Bianca.
She thinks you two are dating.
What? That's absurd.
Alright, I'm not going
to lie to you.
We've been on two dates.
Told you.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner,
but I wanted to wait till I
knew it was something special.
See, Bianca?
It's nothing special.
Actually, it is.
Or it could be.
I don't know.
She's funny
and surprising and--
20 years ynger than you
and our guidance counselor
and a weirdo.
She's different,
and like her.
And when I'm around her,
I feel alive again.
You know how, like,
when your foot goes asleep
and you shake it
and it gets tingly?
[chuckles]
Ew, now you're bringing
feet into this?
Girls, you know yore
the mo important things
in my life.
I won't date Miss Tharp
if you tell me not to.
Okay, then don't.
All right.
I'llust be really sad.
But that's okay
because your happiness
is more important than mine.
Dad, we would never dream
doing something so selfish.
Would we, Bianca?
[sighs]
Why don't you invite her over for dinner
so that we can get to know her better?
-Really?
- [phone rings]
It's Darlene. Should Iet it ring one more time
and not be too eager?
Or what if she hangs up?
Darlene, are you there?
Oh, hi. Nothing.
[gong]
And breathe... in through theight nostril
and out through the left.
[gong]
Everyone, slowly return
from nothingness.
Now, I know
our meditation collective
has no official leader,
but I have a few announcements.
First of all, welcome, Kat Stratford.
Kat, we're excited to be
a part of your journey.
Namaste.
-Namaste.
Second, there are still a few spots open
on our study abroad trip to Nepal.
Anyone else like to join us?
-I'm in.
Wonderful. I'll get you
the paperwork.
[phone rings]
- Oh, my God, Joey, I miss you so much.
- I miss you more than my mom.
I can't wait to hear about
all your modeling adventures,
but first, I have to tell you
about the insanity I'm dealing with.
My dad is dating Miss Tharp. No way.
Nice job, Dr. Stratford.
Joey, this is not good news.
Old people settle down fast
so that they won't die alone.
What if she becomes
my stepmom?
Calm down, Bianca.
Here's what you should do.
I have to call my baby girl
before bedtime.
Joey?
Joey, are you there?
Why do they only have
one phone?
Okay, come on. You can do it.
Swim upstream, little salmon.
Is there any way I can
persuade you to keep moving?
I think we both
know the answer to that.
What's this?
It's an invite
to my little sister's
birthday party.
Princess theme. She asked me to...
All right, it's a love poem for Dawn, okay?
[laughs]
Did you write it in calligraphy?
So what if I did? Look, last night
on the phone without thinking,
I said, "I got to get some Z's, Dawn,"
but I don't know if she was done talking.
Now I feel horrible.
So I wrote her a poem
to apologize.
For saying good night?
Nice backbone.
Well, better to tell Dawn
how I feel
than let her get away.
That's the moral
of every romantic comedy.
There. Now she'll know
how I feel in iambic pentameter.
Sorry.
What a lovely home.
Thank you.
It's so inviting.
It's like I'm
on the set of Friends.
[both laugh]
Jennifer.
Bianca, you love Friends.
Why don't you discuss this shared interest
while I check the lasagna?
[both chuckle]
Hey, did you hear
Friends got canceled?
Yes, but people love it
in reruns. And you know why I think that is?
Urban tribes are now
a substitute
for traditional families.
Yeah, plus it's funny.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I was meditating.
Dad, can I talk to you
about an amazing opportunity?
Kat, I have no interest
in a timeshare right now,
especially
when we have a guest.
Oh, hi, Miss Tharp.
Namaste.
Namaste, Kat.
Dad, I want to go to Nepal.
And I'm sure someday you will.
How about next week?
Huh?
There's
a school sanction program
where I'd spend three months
in a remote village
in the Himalayas
helping them build a school.
Plus, the trip is led
by university faculty members
who'll teach courses
in East Asian history.
And the best part--
daily mediation at a monastery
with real Buddhist monks.
That sounds like the perfect trip
for someone else's daughter.
Let her go. I'll turn
her room into a gym.
I know that program, Walter.
It's very well run.
Not only do the students achieve
a higher level of consciousness,
but it looks great
on a college application.
Don't say no yet.
Just think about it.
I will.
After dinner. Would you
take a seat, please?
[Bianca]
So, Miss Tharp,
have you ever been married?
Bianca, what kind of a question is that?
No, it's okay, Walter.
I want this to be an open forum
where we can all
share our truths.
Great. So have you?
I have been engaged three times--
four if you count
this one night in Vegas.
But I haven't actually
quite made it down the aisle.
Oh, why not?
Bianca.
Well, it's a question
I am currently trying
to figure out in therapy.
Enough questions.
This is a family dinner, not a deposition.
Dad, I'm just trying to hear
Miss Tharp's truth.
- So have you ever been arrested?
- Biance!
[Walter and Kat]
Bianca!
What?
Yes, but I was young and naive.
Girls, please learn
from my mistake.
If a cute man asks you to carry
a package over the border,
don't do it.
Don't ever do
what cute men want,
unless it's me.
- Oh, my God, Joey?
- Babe, I've been missing...
Give that back, Dad.
Bianca, we have
a dinner guest.
You can talk to Joey later.
No, I can't.
You just sit there and be
polite or go to your room.
[phone rings]
I've been waiting for him
to call all day.
You're ruining my life.
Darlene, I'm sorry.
Bianca can be a bit over-dramatic.
A bit? It's like she's living in a telenovela.
[laughs]
Let's not let it ruin our meal.
[knock on door]
May I come in?
I don't mean to be rude,
but I don't want to share my truth
or do mirror work
or do any of that crap.
I just want to be alone.
I can tell how much you miss him.
I love him.
And he's gone.
And who knows
when the model phone
will be free again.
Oh, I remember what it
feels like to be your age
and in love.
His name was Diego.
When he got deported,
I thought my life was over.
And the worst part about it--
nobody took my pain seriously.
They're so insensitive.
I'm sure they're doing their best,
but not everybody's equipped
to give us what we need.
I'm here.
I'm a good listener.
Thanks, Miss Tharp.
Oh, please call me Darlene.
So how long have you guys
been together?
We've been together
for about two months.
Okay, Darlene, here I come.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, my God, I can't believe
we're wearing the same thing.
You look so cute.
So do you.
Here. I made you
some Nepalese tea.
Or chaia,
as the Sherpas say.
Katarina, I'm not going
to give you my blessing
to go halfway
around the world--
Correction.
Only 12,130 kilometers,
give or take a few.
Oh, is that all?
I didn't realize you could
come home on weekends.
I know it's far,
but this is an amazing opportunity.
And I'll be going off
to college in 18 months.
Consider this a dress rehearsal.
For a play I don't want to see.
I'm ready for this.
Please don't keep me from
going because you're scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm terrified.
Of what?
Of what? You're going to a place
without indoor plumbing or telephones
or parental supervision.
It's dangerous.
Some warlord's going to pay
seven goats for you.
Seven goats?
Yes.
Dad, you can just say no.
You don't have to insult me.
Please let me go.
Let you?
I've never let you do anything in your life.
It's always been one of my favorite things about you.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
Please don't celebrate
till you're alone in your room.
All right.
Thanks, Dad.
And don't come back
with one of those rings
through your nose.
[phone vibrates]
Hey Joey, I'm in my new class.
-Hey, Good news
I made it to four
out of my six "go sees."
Oh, that's so-- Oh, goody,
a bejeweled cell phone.
Just what I always wanted.
But, Mr. Meanly,
it's a matter of life or death.
[chuckles]
[snoring]
- Hey. -Hey back.
-That's a really good look for you.
Thanks. I got it for my trip to Nepal.
I leave next week.
For three months.
It's this fascinating study
abroad program. Cool. Have fun.
You, too.
Your poem is the most romantic thing
any guy's ever done for me.
Even that time Chris Yuscratched my name
on his guitar.
I just wanted you to know
I couldn't live without you.
Aw, recite it to me again.
Hark, my Dawn.
You are the sweetest treat in the candy store.
I've tasted your sugar, and I want some more.
You're so hot
you melt my heart.
Lips, sweet and delicious,
like a mixed fruit tart.
You're cuter than Bambi,
an adorable baby fawn.
You light up my days,
my very own Dawn.
Check out all that natural beauty.
Eyeball exploding, right?
You guys are in for the journey of a lifetime.
Maybe even a few lifetimes.
[all laugh]
That's a little Buddhist humor.
Sindu, that is too funny.
I find your spirit infectious.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Do you know our host families?
I'd like to start practicing
pronouncing their names.
The families live
in one-room huts.
It's a little crowded,
so we'll be sleeping in tents.
But it'll be spring,
so you know what that means.
It won't be too cold? Avalanche season.
But don't worry.
You'll each have a GPS tracker.
I haven't lost a student yet.
Just a toe.
Now, let's talk vaccinations.
You'll need hepatitis A and B,
typhoid, and tetanus,
but good news,
because of the new well
we dug last quarter,
you'll no longer need the
Japanese encephalitis booster.
One thing we can't vaccinate
against is dysentery.
[sighs]
I really wish we could, though.
But we can't. Questions?
It's a non-invasive process
that will really help you access your,
I hate to interrupt,
but this is an emergency.
Oh, okay, just give me a sec, Tanya,
and then we'll start the hypnosis.
Hey, what is going on, honey?
Joey called
during math class,
and Mr. Meanly took my phone away.
Darlene, please help me get it back.
Bianca, honey, in this office,
I'm not Darlene.
I'm Miss Tharp.
And Miss Tharp has
to support Mr. Meanly.
You should not be talking
on the phone during class.
But you know how hard it's been
for me to not talk to Joey.
Yesterday you called us
star-crossed lovers.
And Darlene was serious about that.
Really?
Because it sounds like
she was just sucking up to me
so she could date my dad.
-No, she would never do that.
In fact, if you want to process this tonight
over a pint of ice cream and a Katherine Heigl movie,
Darlene will be there.
Tell Darlene I said
"Thanks for nothing."
Bianca, be reasonable.
I am being reasonable, Dad.
She's the one with
multiple personality disorder.
Darlene said you were just upset
because she wouldn't give you your phone back.
I'd hardly call that
a severe mental illness.
This isn't about my phone.
It's the fact that she's
my guidance counselor and your girlfriend.
It's too confusing.
All right, why don't we
just invite her over?
And we'll share our truths.
After all , if there can be
a lasting peace in Northern Ireland
I'm sure we can work this out.
Dad, you don't get it.
I don't want to work this out.
Now, please just leave me
to my homework.
Bianca, wha-- It's too strange.
You said if we didn't want you
to date her, you'd stop.
So stop.
Okay, fine.
See you in our
next class, okay?
Siena, hey.
Hi.
Listen, I haven't been able to find
quick-drying snow pants anywhere.
Where did you get yours?
Oh, Kat, I didn't tell you?
I'm not going to Nepal.
You're not?
I realized
I don't like hiking,
which means I'll probably hate trekking.
But have fun. Take pictures.
Hey.
Hey back.
I'm glad I caught you
before you left for Nepal.
Really? Why?
Keith found this in the back of his van.
I know how much you like it.
Thanks.
I was wondering where it was.
In Keith's van.
Yeah, you said that.
I guess I'll see you around.
Have a safe trip.
Joey, I miss you so much.
I miss you more.
Co Liviette just fainted during our photo shoot,
so we have the phone until she revives.
Then she's going to want
to call her baby.
Goody, I hope she's out for a while.
We have so much to catch up on.
Tomorrow's makeover day. I'm so nervous.
What if they shave my head?
I don't know
how to work my skull.
Joey, there's something
I have to do right now.
Call me back later, okay?
But-- Love you. Bye.
[sighs]
[Man on TV]
I'm on the other end.
Yo, Tom, I thought
you brought it.
You've got style.
You were sexy.
Looks good. Can I have some?
Don't choke on it.
Look. I'm sorry I freaked out
about Darlene.
I was being selfish.
Was?
You mean you're not being
selfish anymore?
Listen, I know how it feel to want to talk
to someone so badly it hurts.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. Can I call her?
-Yeah, but...
I'm switching to the other
guidance counselor.
Deal. |Joey
Don't worry about your makeover.
I told you she'd come around.
Listen, are you free to see
a movie this weekend?
I have seen you model enough
to know you're a chameleon.
What are you doing out here?
The program recommends
we try out all our equipment
before the trip.
Can I ask you something weird?
Where will you go to the bathroom up there?
Oh, God. You're so brave, Kat.
I could never go to someplace
halfway around the world
where I didn't know a soul
or speak the language
or have any idea what I'm eating,
but it all sounds so exciting and exotic.
I don't want to go.
I like indoor plumbing.
I don't want to forage for roots
or wear snow pants.
And-- And what?
And he didn't try to stop me.
I'm stopping you.
I need you here.
Dad is still dating
our guidance counselor,
and based on their body language,
they're three dates away from having sex.
- Sync By YesCool [Addic7ed.com] -
www.tvsubtitles.net