- Previously On "10 Things i Hate About You"...
- it's first day of school, so
Remember the most important thing,
don't get pregnant. Bye, dad. -You
*** at school.
I'm Chasity. this is my boyfriend,
Joey Donner.
Who is Captain Intensity over there?
Patrick Verona. People say he
knows the taste of human flesh.
Please. My name's Cameron.
I'm so lucky to have met you.
You're my first GBF.
- What...  A GBF?
- Gay best friend.
People are not scared of me.
Sure they are. That's why
I find you interesting.
Maybe I'm a really bad boyfriend.
You're, like, the perfect boyfriend.
All this time we've been friends,
you've liked me?
I've loved you. I don't feel the same way.
You have no right to do that. Bam.
They're making us wear uniforms.
So you don't give a damn that
we no longer have the rights
that are guaranteed to
us in the Bill of Rights?
What's the point?
It's not like we can change it.
Be quiet, please.
Shut up and listen to her.
Joey and I broke up. I cut him loose.
Come back here with that,
or you're suspended, too.
Then I guess I'm suspended.
You sure about this? No.
But I'm doing it.
Hey, Kat. It's your sister calling
from a deserted parking lot.
Oh, hello, creepy man in a van.
I don't need a ride.
My sister's picking me up.
Thanks. Call me.
Hey, Fivehead. Do you need a ride home?
Joey, we can't be seen together.
Chastity has vowed to dismember
the girl who kissed you,
and our make-out sessions won't be
nearly as fun if I have no arms.
This sucks.
I just want to shout from the rooftops-
I'm dating Bianca Stratford!
That is so sweet,
but could you just mouth it?
Okay, I have a simple two-step plan
to get us through this.
Step 1, we date in secret. Joey.
Oh. Doing them now.
Step 2, we track down the surveillance tape
of our make-out session
before Chastity sees it.
Cool. We could watch it together.
So we can erase it.
That's good, too. No bad ideas.
Oh, God. Get down. Hi, Chastity.
Hop in, B. I'll give you a ride.
We can play a game. It's called
Top 10 Ways to Torture the
Skank Who Kissed Joey.
I'll go first. Waterboarding, duh.
TP her locker? Lame.
Put semi-permanent green
dye in her sham-- Mm-mm.
Throw her in the ocean in
a meat bikini. I love it.
I can't believe I just did that!
I can't believe I just walked out of school!
It was so exciting. I wonder
if Gandhi ever felt like this,
so alive, so inspired, so-- Hot.
We took a stand. Uh-huh.
We told the establishment to stick it.
Yeah, yeah, we're heroes.
Let's go in. Hell, no.
And I thought you were a tough guy.
I'm suspended. My dad is going to kill me.
Sync By YesCool
www.isubs.coil.us/addic7ed.com
I am so stressed out about
this Chastity thing,
I can't even enjoy the fact
that Dad is going to kill you.
Hi. Dad, I'm so glad you're home.
Relax. I just got here. Hi, honey.
Hi, Daddy. So I heard some good news today.
I heard someone got suspended.
Who was it again?
Oh, that's right. It was you.
What are you doing? Don't you know
it goes on your permanent record?
I thought you were going to drop this.
I was going to, but-- But what?
What happened in between me
ordering you back into school
and you walking out of it?
I had to stand up for my principles.
They were hassling some guy.
Guy? There's a guy now?
Do you know this guy? What guy? Some guy.
Some-- Some poor kid.
Oh, a kid. They were going
to search his backpack.
Someone had to intervene before they
performed a full-body cavity search.
This is America, not Xinjiang.
Do you notice that this isn't
China or Tibet or Cambodia?
But there is an emperor here, and it's me.
Who, incidentally,
taught me to think for myself.
Oh, no. You can't blame me for this.
You broke the rules. You're going to
have to deal with the consequences.
I know. I'm suspended tomorrow.
No, these consequences.
You're painting the living room tomorrow.
Just in case you don't get into a college,
now you'll have a skill to make a living.
Okay, does the back of this girl's head
look like the back of mine?
No. She doesn't have enough-
What do you call them?
Natural highlights. Natural, sure.
What are you doing?
All that Chastity knows
about Joey's mystery girl
is she's blonde and thin,
so I'm assembling a list of suspects.
Once Chastity sees how huge it is,
she'll be overwhelmed and give up.
Thank God we live in California.
Here's a thought.
If you didn't do anything wrong,
why not just tell the
Satanic Smurfette the truth?
Like you did? i did?
Dad, they were totally going to search
some poor kid's bag,
so I had to stand up for his rights
and ride off into the sunset with him
on the back of his bitchen motorcycle.
Bianca, I was standing up for
our constitutional protections.
Oh, my God. Shut up.
You're like a live feed from CNN.
So I told Bianca I need time to get over her,
then I turned and walked
away without looking back.
Yes, yes, I was hoping
you wouldn't look back.
Good for you, bro. You finally told her off.
When you say it like that, it sounds harsh.
Now I feel bad. Maybe I should apologize.
After all, it's not her fault
she doesn't love me back.
Dude, if you really want to get over Bianca,
stop making excuses and get angry.
Did you learn anything
from your parents' divorce?
I'm not angry. I'm just
hurt and disappointed,
and for some reason,
I can't listen to the radio.
Bianca rejected you, okay?
You gave her your heart,
and she riverdanced over it,
then made out with the
quarterback of the football team.
And you want to apologize?
Not that much anymore.
Oh. Hey, Cameron.
How are you? Very well, thank you.
Yeah, buddy. Yes! Hey, bestie.
I found out where they keep
the surveillance tapes.
You did? Oh, goodie.
They're locked in the AV closet.
I tried to bribe the janitor to open it,
but he's afraid he'll lose his job.
Like there aren't a million other
bathrooms to clean out there.
Well, darn it. I guess we'll
never get the tape, then.
Well, that's what I thought,
until I remebered
that that tall nerd person friend of yours
is king of the AV club.
Get the key from him, okay?
I'd do it myself, but I don't
want to look petty and vindictive.
You cannot come in.
If my dad sees you here,
his head will explode,
and then I'll have to repaint.
Your dad's at work. How's he
going to see me? Hidden cameras?
Yes. Come on. I'll help you paint.
It's the least I can do.
After all, you did get suspended for me.
Don't flatter yourself.
I got suspended for my principles.
I just fled the scene with you.
Really? Because I think...
I'm not kidding. I can't mess around.
You don't get the point
of being suspended at all.
Day off, no school. It's like a vacation.
This is not a vacation.
After I paint this entire room,
I have to study for an English
test I was supposed to take.
If you get suspended on a test day,
you get a zero.
Dem's da rules.
A zero? No. They'll just
have to make an exception.
I don't think they do that.
Not that I've ever tried.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I can't get a zero.
That'll bring down my whole GPA,
and on top of the suspension--
Why did I do something so stupid? I have
ruined my entire life, my whole future.
I won't get into Brown.
I won't be able to protect civil liberties
and crusade against injustice.
And I can't even be a house
painter because I suck at it.
Don't you think you're overreacting?
It's your first day as a painter.
You'll get better.
I'm just kidding.
If this test is that important,
then just break into school and take it.
How am I going to do that? With my help.
I'm not so sure about this.
What if somebody recognizes me?
Don't worry. With that hood and glasses,
they'll just think you're a celebrity.
Whoa, check it out, dudes.
It's Patrick Verona.
And he brought our favorite
freedom fighter, the Dalai Mama.
Really? Me, your favorite?
Because of you getting
your protesting back out,
we got to empty our lockers,
all full to brimming with sweet hydro.
That's exactly what I was fighting for--
Your stash. Could you guys get in
and grab the wheel, please,
before the BKWs catch us?
We need passage.
The southwest hall is clear. How do you know?
There's an app for that.
Bianca. Joey. Bianca, I got your text.
How'd you get out of class?
I told the teacher I was itching.
God, you're pretty.
Thanks, but that's not why
I need to talk to you.
We have an emergency. Step 2 of our plan
is about to go off the rails. Step 2.
Destroying the security tape.
Are we done with step 1?
No. Step 1 is like the Olympic torch-
It's always going.
Now listen-- I need you to
get into Cameron's pants.
He's gay. It shouldn't be that hard.
To steal his keys. That's what I thought.
He has gym next period.
Steal his keys. Get them to me.
I'll get the tape, erase it,
then you slip his keys back into his pants
before the class ends.
Do I need to write this down?
I don't mean to diss on your plan,
because it's really complicated and awesome,
but why can't you just ask him for the keys?
Because he's mad at me. Long story. Strange.
But listen, we need to act fast.
If we don't, Chastity will,
and then we'll have to move to Bolivia.
Calm down, Five-o. No one's moving to Africa.
I'll get you those keys. Oh, Joey. Bianca.
School police. I need to see that hall pass.
This watermark looks like
it was made with diet soda.
Do I look like an idiot to you?
You Out from yurs class to
make out with your boyfriend?
Just the last ten minutes. Besides, it's
history. I already know how it ends.
Everyone dies.
Aren't you supposed to be
painting the living room?
I have to take an English test.
You broke into school to take a test?
You are so weird.
Hi, I'm Joey, Bianca's boyfriend.
We should double sometime.
Joey, we're dating in secret.
Bianca, I think they know.
I was never here.
You Stratford sisters are a strange breed.
Kat? Aren't you suspended?
Would I be here if I were suspended? No.
I'd be home watching Oprah.
Did you know I was once an
audience member on her show?
You don't say.
They gave us all a pair of these tennis shoes
that firm your butt just by wearing them.
That Oprah deserves the Nobel prize.
She is a saint.
Are you trying to steal my keys?
No, no, I was just
admiring them from a-close.
Okay, look. Bianca told me that
you guys are kind of in a fight.
Yeah, well, I don't want to talk about it--
Especially with you, Joey Donner.
I'm sorry. I understand.
Well, not really, but Bianca needs your help.
Does she, now? Yep.
See, there's this security tape,
and I'm supposed to get your key, so--
Wait a minute. Let me check my notes.
Keys out of pants. Get the keys to Bianca,
who destroys tape, then go--
Are you done? I have a rope to climb.
Okay, man to man.
Me and Bianca, we're making out
on a tape that's locked in the AV closet.
We need to get the said tape
before Chastity sees it
and bad things happen.
So I'm just a part of her master plan?
Yeah, but you're not supposed to know.
Oh, and don't tell anybody that we're dating.
I always forget step 1.
So you're dating now? Well, congratulations.
Thanks! Hey, thought--
How about you snag the tape for us?
That makes it so much easier.
Sure, bro. I'll get you the tape.
And then I'll even sweeten it up,
with a little Jay-Z and some cool effects.
And then I'll wrap it in a heart-shaped box,
filled with rose petals and wishes.
Don't bother. We're just going to erase it.
But thanks. Up top.
Academic catastrophe averted.
I took the test. Actually, I aced the test.
Incense, my ass.
I know my incense. I got five different
types of incense in my bathroom.
I got sandalwood, old school musk...
You've been wanting to do that all day.
Let's get out of here.
I still have to finish painting the
living room before my dad gets home.
Someone's coming. Shut up. Let's go.
Hey, you.
Motorcycle man. You shouldn't be here.
Today was fun.
You want to run? Okay. I got you.
Oh!
You.
- You Tell Cemron that we dating?
- I had to call an audible.
- No.
- He must be so upset.
Not at all.
In fact, he wanted to do this
whole soundtrack thingie.
Uh-oh. Chastity's at 6:00. Now 7. She's at 8.
I can't tell time this fast.
Hang up the phone.
Great news, B. Your nerd boy?
He got me the tape.
He gave it to you?
You don't want to watch this.
Uh, yeah, I do. I do.
It's already cued up. I wish we had popcorn.
No, I don't want to wait the three minutes.
Chastity, listen, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
It's not that big of a deal. There she is.
I will never forget those roots. Ugh.
Listen, Chastity, I want you to know
that this shouldn't affect
our friendship in any way,
because what you're going
to see is not-- Damn it.
Security system's crap. Stupid public school.
I guess we'll never know who she is.
It'll just remain one of life's
mysteries, like Fergie's age.
I can't be the only person who saw them.
I mean, you know what?
We'll start interrogating people.
Eventually, some nut will crack.
Chastity, can you just explain
to me one teeny, tiny thing?
You dumped Joey.
Why do you care who he kissed?
Because-- Because...
it's humiliating.
It didn't even take him a day to get over me.
When he kissed that sloor,
he probably still had the taste
of my strawberry ultimate shine
lip quencher on his mouth.
Whoever that girl is,
she can't compare to you.
You are the most popular girl at this school.
You're the youngest head cheerleader
in the history of Padua High.
You are Chastity freaking Church.
You're right.
You're right. I'm me, and she is nothing.
A nobody. A nasty, mangy piece of garbage.
Okay.
Thank you for reminding me how amazing I am.
I am so glad we're besties. Air hug.
Oh, and give that back to nerd boy.
What's your deal? Is someone
paying you to ruin my life,
or is something clinically wrong with you?
Dad, I had to-- Not another word.
What did she do now?
Today's stunt was breaking into school.
To take an English test. Hush.
They were going to give me a zero. I said--
Wait, what? You broke into
school to take a test?
I know. It's weird.
And it's going to cost you another mark
on your permanent record.
So let me get this straight.
You're going to punish my daughter
for trying to get a good grade?
Well, I'm sure as hell
not going to reward her
for breaching our costly,
yet apparently crap, security system.
Come on.
If this is the way you treat a good student,
what do you do with the bad ones?
Chain them up to break rocks during recess?
Just because she's a good student
doesn't mean she's good.
She's in my office more than
that boy that randomly bites
other kids' necks. Damn this vampire craze.
Look, Kat is many things-
Stubborn, intractable,
relentless-- Annoying, trouble-making.
Pardon me, Principal Holland,
but if anyone's going to insult my daughter,
it's going to be me.
This girl is a great kid.
She's smart and soulful,
generous and good-hearted.
She's determined to make a difference
in the world, and she will.
I'm sure of it.
Yesterday, when she walked out,
yes, she broke the rules,
but it was 100% the right thing to do.
She was just defending a poor kid
against authority figures who prefer
to scare kids into submission,
rather than inspire them to greatness.
I got the other one.
Man, he's fast. Well, well, well.
Here's that poor kid now.
That poor, defenseless kid.
Cameron, thanks for erasing the tape.
Consider that your last favor.
Look, I'm so, so, so sorry.
I wanted to tell you about Joey,
but you weren't speaking to me.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I thought you were this sweet,
innocent girl from Ohio,
who thinks about puppies as she falls asleep.
But now I see you're this ruthless vixen
who will step on anyone
to get what she wants.
In fact, I bet you hate puppies.
I love puppies. Not falling for that again.
Hey, B. You want some fro-yo?
I got a huge one because I
feel like celebrating me.
Mm, whoever invented sprinkles
deserves a gold star. Mm.
Chastity, I have something to tell you.
I'm so glad we've become friends,
real friends, which makes
this so much harder to say,
but I have to be honest with you,
no matter what happens.
Uh, well, consider the suspense built.
I'm the one who kissed Joey.
So that went well.
The test grade counts,
the suspension's been lifted,
and Principal Holland admitted
that she didn't have a concussion
in front of witnesses.
Thanks to you, I'm still
an Ivy League candidate.
You're also a liar. What?
This whole time, you've been telling
me this is about your principles.
You forgot to mention your
principles drive a motorcycle.
So it was Patrick's bag.
That's not why I left.
The school violated several
Constitutional amendments.
Dad! Kat!
Just get in the car and drive.
What is going on?
Why are you covered in sprinkles?
Just drive.
Go, go, go. Chastity is coming.
Oh, I will see you at school tomorrow!
www.tvsubtitles.net