It's important to stay
as low as possible...
because heat rises.
Heat rises.
Did you know that?
No, but maybe if he goes over it
another ten times, it'll sink in.
Pay attention.
Don't touch that doorknob...
until you've checked
to see if it's hot first.
What do you know? Look at that.
Room temperature. You can escape now, Dad.
Don't wanna be late for the conference.
The other gynecologists will ice you out.
- Time to go, Dad.
- Bye, Dad.
- Kat, you're in charge.
- Mm-hmm.
- That means you're responsible for Bianca.
- Cool. I get to order you around.
You know what?
Maybe I'll just skip the conference.
What else can I learn? The last time I heard,
babies still come out of the same place.
Dad, it's healthy for us to spend time apart
so we don't get sick of each other.
I could never be sick
of my little girls.
- Okay. Time to go.
- Well, all right.
- Oh, thank you. Thanks.
- Bye. Love you.
- I'm gonna miss you. Oh, I left--
- Love you so much, Dad.
Have a good time.
Bye-bye.
It's finally happening.
An entire weekend
without Dad.
- See you Monday.
- Yep.
:::   Timecodes  -  gius   :::
Oh, do not sell any
of our furniture on craigslist.
I'm just taking
"before" pictures.
Before what?
I'm having a few friends over...
and I just wanna make sure
I can replicate the "after".
This is so cliché.
Dad goes out of town,
you throw a wild party...
someone breaks
our Fabergé egg, and...
then we have to turn this place
into a brothel to pay for it.
Sounds like an awesome weekend.
Come in.
Hey, Bianca.
We are here for karaoke.
Ohh.
I know what you're up to.
I've seen those crappy teen movies.
Oh, me, too.
Aren't you supposed to show up
much later wearing a hockey mask?
And you'll be the first to go.
Come on.
This is just karaoke.
Let me guess. Some football drones
with beer and a spiked watermelon.
* Five, four, three, two, one *
It is only 9:30. This party
should totally suck right now.
This is going
better than planned.
If this party turns epic,
I could be a legend at Padua High.
Shane DeMarco graduated four years ago,
and people are still talking about his party.
Hey, blonde girl,
is this your party?
- Uh, yeah, it is.
- Not bad.
Strong hot-guy ratio,
and some are in college.
- Hey, what's up?
- So what's your name?
Bianca Stratford.
Tell all your friends.
Okay.
- Oh, my God! College guys!
- Shane DeMarco can eat it!
Bianca, no more people,
or I'm shutting this place down.
Did you even think
about putting out trash cans?
Move!
Come on!
Put your back into it.
Whoo!
Okay, when my back
wants to touch your front...
I'll tell you.
Joey, sweetie...
- I'm thirsty.
- Me, too.
- Oh, I'm on it.
- Thanks, honey. Love you. Bye.
Ughh. He's like a puppy
who hasn't been housebroken.
Ooh.
Who are those boys?
Or should I say men?
Wow.
Apparently they go to college.
Well, I hope they find someone interesting
to talk to so they don't get bored.
All right.
I'll do it.
Ooh. If Joey comes back,
cover for me.
What?
I'm curious about college.
- Seriously...
- Kat, will you let those people in?
As soon as three people leave.
We are at capacity.
Will you lighten up?
Our house is hotter...
than the swag room
at a Golden Globe party.
Dad left me in charge, which means
I'm responsible for this party.
- Have you even organized designated drivers?
- No. I'm busy hosting.
Bianca, if Padua students
are drinking here...
which, by the way, is illegal, you're obligated
to make sure they're taken care of.
Don't you remember the moral
of Dad's field trip to the morgue?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Drinking, bad.
I'm not drinking, am I?
Designated drivers wear these.
- "Save the naked mole rats"?
- Left over from that walkathon.
Apparently people only care
about cute endangered species.
- Stupid pandas.
- Please let them in.
We can make them
the designated drivers.
- Ah, congratulations!
- All right!
You've been chosen
to be designated drivers.
- What?
- If I see any of you drinking...
- I will neuter you.
- Oh.
Bummer.
Heard about your party.
Did my invite get lost?
- Speaking of getting lost.
- Come on. I just wanna talk to you.
- So talk.
- Privately.
Have you seen Chastity?
The ice in her drink is melting.
She's over there in the corner
talking to some guy.
- What guy?
- He's a missionary.
Don't go over there
unless you wanna be saved.
Come dance with us.
Whoo!
Yeah!
Oh, I see. When you said,
"Wait here" at the dance...
you really meant
for, like, six days.
If you ever returned a phone call, you'd know
I didn't bail on you. I got arrested.
Oh, and here I thought you were just a jerk.
Turns out you're also a criminal.
I didn't even do anything.
The charges were dropped.
So let it go.
Don't.
- Then what do you want from me?
- Nothing.
I've seen red flags from you
ever since I met you.
In fact, you look
like Communist China.
What the hell am I doing here?
It's like talking to a brick wall.
You make up your mind,
and that's that.
Don't turn this around on me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Oh, of course not.
You're perfect.
I am not.
Have fun up here
in your perfect world...
all by your perfect self.
Thanks. I will.
Say hello to your parole officer!
What is that?
Get out! Get--
No! No! Hello!
Get out of there!
That is my closet!
It looks like Bianca's
in a great mood.
Maybe now
she'll accept my apology.
Be careful.
She's happy, not drunk.
What's the difference?
Drunk girls do things
they normally wouldn't do...
like forgive people
or skinny-dip.
I'm gonna go wait in the pool.
Some of these chicks are bound
to come around sooner or later.
I'm gonna talk to Bianca.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
All right.
- Tasty watermelon!
- All right!
Right after I have a snack.
Oh, my God, guys.
Don't drop me.
Thank God I wore
my good underwear tonight.
Thank God
I wore underwear!
- What are you doing?
- Shutting down this party.
I don't think so.
You know, if you weren't my sister,
I'd actually feel bad for you.
You're incapable of having fun.
I am not gonna be responsible
for your party.
Then I will be.
You? You've never been responsible
for anything in your entire life.
You remember your hamster?
Of course I do.
But Britney Spears was one hamster.
- I didn't know she had to eat twice a day.
- What about Gumdrop?
Fish are easy to forget.
You know how quiet they are.
Exactly.
There's always an excuse.
So I make mistakes.
I never claim to be
Little Miss Perfect like you.
Ooh! I am not perfect!
- Why does everyone keep saying that?
- Because you act like you are!
Fine.
You wanna be in charge
of this party? Have at it.
Now I'm gonna have some fun.
Little Miss Perfect
has just relinquished her crown.
Oh-ho-ho!
It's all you!
Drink up!
- Whoo!
- Ahh!
- Nice! All right!
- Yeah!
* I'll make you mine *
So before a game, I spray a tiny bit
of hair spray on my butt...
so my leotard won't ride up.
Unless we're trying
to distract the other team...
and then we skip the hair spray.
I thought cheerleaders
were just vapid cretins...
but you're actually
master strategists.
Totally.
- Kat, what are you doing?
- I'm just hangin'.
You know, girl-talking
about butts and stuff.
Look at you.
Maybe you should change your shirt.
Maybe you should
change your face.
Your sister's cool.
Bianca, do you or do you not
have any energy drinks?
Yeah.
No big D, guys, but could you shut
the fridge when you're done?
I need to get amped up,
'cause things are about to go down.
Wait! What? No, nothing
and no one should be going down.
Chastity's not flirting with a missionary,
she's flirting with a college dude.
- Hey, that's my girl, man.
- Oh.
Excuse us. So sorry.
Sorry. Okay.
Okay, what has gotten into you?
This is a social function,
not Maury Povitch.
Me? You're the one flirting with
a college dude right in front of my face!
Well, maybe I wanted
to have a conversation...
that didn't start with,
"Um, do I, like, look fat in this?"
Hey, as a model, I have to be the boss
of my body, and that's a full-time job.
You think it's easy for me
to sit next to you at the movies...
while you're grubbing on Red Vines
and popcorn and gummi worms?
Joey, sweetie...
in an effort to support
your modeling career...
I'm gonna let you practice
your stupid little runway walk...
all the way home.
- Ohh!
- Excuse me.
Don't think I won't!
Loser!
Uh, okay, everybody.
Halftime show is over.
Let's get back to the party.
Whoo!
* Lost *
* In a dream *
* I don't know which *
* Way to go *
* You are all that you seem *
* Way too slow *
Ha-ha!
* I've been a fool before *
* My love caught
in a slammin' door *
* How about some
information, please *
Yes! Now, everybody
put your hands together!
Right? I wanna give a shout-out
to the naked mole rats.
Naked mole rats!
- Who we gonna save?
- Naked mole rats!
Naked mole rats!
Kat, you are out of control.
We should sing one of the songs with the
two people-- when they do it together.
- A duet?
- Oh...
I don't say this often enough, Bianca,
but you're so smart and prettiful.
I love you, Bianca!
I hope we stay sisters--
* Forever *
I think you should go outside
and get some fresh air.
* Save the naked mole rats *
Hey, weren't you in my car once?
You're Bianca's sister.
- You're scary.
- No, don't say that.
Okay.
I'm fun, right?
You'd tell me if I wasn't fun?
Come on. You're, like,
the funnest person in the world.
- I feel fun!
- I love watermelon!
Hey.
I hate myself.
I'm sure everything
with Chastity will be fine.
You know she can be
a bit dramatic.
No. These-- These had to be
at least 1,850 calories...
plus all that sodium...
I already feel bloated.
So you'll do an extra hour
of cardio tomorrow.
It's just so hard
to be with her sometimes.
Or-- Or maybe it's me.
- Maybe I'm a really bad boyfriend.
- Are you kidding me?
You're kind and sweet,
and you look great in photos.
You're like...
the perfect boyfriend.
Wow. Bianca...
what you just said to me filled me up
more than this bag of Cheeseritos.
Bianca, come upstairs.
Something freaky's going on in the toilet.
I'll be right back.
Don't eat.
- No more alcohol.
- It's just watermelon.
I don't drink.
I'm above the influence.
You're the guy who gets wasted
because he's too dumb to know...
that the watermelon was spiked.
Maybe those teen movies
really are set in reality.
I'm drunk?
Oh, I thought it was just
'cause I was depressed...
'cause Bianca's mad at me,
and...
- you're her sister.
- Mm-hmm.
How do I get her to forgive me?
Buy her something that sparkles.
Oh, a sparkler!
It doesn't matter anyway.
Bianca's all, like...
"Stay out of my life!"
Yell, yell, yell!
She won't even let me explain.
That's not nice.
I didn't mean
to hurt her feelings.
She probably knows that
deep down.
I bet she wishes she could
make out with you right now.
Really?
How do you know?
I just know things in my mind.
Do you think I should
apologize first?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You should-- You should do that.
I have to make a phone call.
- Yeah!
- Whoo! Whoo!
- Yeah! Here, dude!
- Put the duck down!
Whoo!
What are you doing
in my uniform?
This party is so awesome,
I heard about it at the North Pole.
I think
I'm gonna be sick.
Oh! Take it off!
Bianca,
I have to talk to you.
- Cameron, when did you get here?
- In time increments?
Uh, three watermelons ago.
Your sister is trashed,
by the way.
She's not the only one.
You need to go home.
No.
I've been waiting all night to do this,
and you have to listen to me.
I'm sorry I ruined your date with Beau,
but he was not a good person.
I know, but that doesn't excuse
what you did. Stay out of my life.
I can't.
I'm in love with you.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am!
- But you're gay!
- I'm not gay... at all!
In fact, you're gayer than I am
because you kissed a girl.
That was for money.
See, I could never kiss a guy for money,
except for Johnny Depp.
So all this time we've been friends,
you've liked me?
No. I've loved you.
Bianca, I wanna spend
the rest of my life with you...
and if it turns out we have afterlives,
I wanna spend those together, too.
Cameron--
Think about it. We could have a really
cool moniker, like Biameron or Camianca.
You pick.
I-- I don't know how to tell you this,
but I don't feel the same way.
I'm so sorry.
Maybe we should talk about this
when you're sober.
Um, how about we never
talk about this again?
Will you please take him home?
No, no, no. Come over
so I can tell you something.
Kat, I need you to help.
Because I need to do it in person.
Because I just do. Just do it.
Kat!
I am on the phone!
You have got to be kidding me.
What do you expect me to do, woman?
The toilet's jacked.
That is it!
The party is over!
Over! Okay, everybody,
it's time to leave right now!
Right now!
Come on! Leave!
Please? Please? Please?
It's time to go... away!
Five-head, look what I found.
Someone barfed in it.
Hey, it's okay. We can get it out.
Do you have a Shop-Vac?
Joey, I think I'm going to have
a nervous breakdown.
This party is out of control.
I'm a victim of my own success.
- How did Shane DeMarco do it?
- Tell me how I can help.
Whatever you want me to do,
I'll do it.
- I just want this party to be over.
- Well, then, let's get her done.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
Uh, can you guys get up for a sec?
Apparently somebody
who was in here has crabs.
Oh, my God!
They're everywhere!
Oh, they're everywhere!
It worked.
Everyone's gone.
I know. That was amazing.
Up top.
- That didn't happen.
- I know.
But... if it did,
it was amazing.
Too bad it didn't.
Has anybody seen my clothes?
You'd never know there was
a raging party here last night...
except for in my head.
Oh, God, the pain.
I was up all night.
I even steam-cleaned the carpets,
no thanks to you!
Inside voices.
Here.
Drink this.
Thank you.
"I heart Patrick"?
- Some jerk wrote on me.
- Don't look at me.
You're the one who called him last night
and begged him to come over.
- Oh, my God, what did I say?
- Why don't you ask him?
I was busy playing the role of the girl
who learns to be responsible.
Guess who played the girl who gets drunk
and makes an ass of herself?
No.
It's Dad. Uh, go upstairs
and take a shower.
Yeah. Okay. Go.
Shower time.
- I am never drinking again.
- Uh-huh.
Thanks for indulging me
with this movie night.
I missed you girls
this weekend, and...
I just wanted a nice
Sunday night together.
We missed you, too, Dad.
All we did was sit around
and ponder how much.
- That's why my brain hurts.
- Aw.
So, what movie
are we gonna watch?
It's called House Party...
and it was shot by this hip new
director named Mr. Duck.
Now, everybody put
your hands together!
Right? I wanna
give a shout-out to--
Settle in, girls.
We've got four hours
ahead of us.
- What are we gonna save?
- Naked mole rats!
www.tvsubtitles.net