- Hi, Dad.
- Hi honeys.
Sorry I wasn't there this morning
to make pancakes for you, but...
you never know when Mr. Stork
is gonna pay a visit.
You realize we know where
babies come from, right ?
Do you realize where they come out ?
Trust me. Not pretty.
It's the first day of school,
remember the most important thing :
Don't get pregnant !
I'm just saying. Boys want to put
a baby in you. Are we clear, Bianca ?
Well, they'd have to do it in vitro,
since I can't date until Kat does.
Then we're clear on the rules.
I only make them because you
girls mean so much to me.
Your mother...
predicted what smart, beautiful,
young women...
you'd grow into, and how right she was.
She'd want you to know that.
- Thanks, dad.
- She'd also want you to know...
syphillis, gonorrhea and genital
herpes are on the rise...
- among American teenagers.
- Bye, Dad !
Push.
We're heading to high school,
not the Academy Awards.
You never get a second chance
to make a first impression.
We're talking about teenagers.
They're impressed by shiny objects
Thus, my earrings.
You could just try being yourself.
Spoken like a true unpopular person.
That never works.
Using exhaustive Facebook, I've identified
the most popular girl at school.
I've then deconstructed her
profile and used that data...
to carefully plot out
our first encounter...
so as to easily befriend
and beguile her.
Beguile ? Big word, Shakespeare.
Pull over here.
I want to make an entrance.
Your door is stuck.
Your Highness.
How do I look ?
- Shallow.
- Thank you !
You're the one speeding
in a school zone.
Do you mind ?
This is my spot.
- I was told spots aren't assigned.
- No. They are assigned.
By Charles Darwin.
So, why don't you
and your dinosaur head to the back...
with the rest of
the extinct species.
Oh, my God.
My car !
My dinosaur wanted to
jurassic park here.
- Hey, sophomore.
- What are you wearing ?
It's the new look for the new Michael.
Goodbye, Mikey.
Hello, Michael.
Emo, hipster musician.
You played piccolo
in the marching band.
High school is how you spin it.
Even the biggest dorks can be cool.
As long as they play
their cards right.
- Look at Shia LaBeouf.
- I don't care about cool.
I just want a girlfriend.
every girl here remembers
that tornado drill
in 4 grade when I wet my pants.
Can I press pause on
this lifetime TV movie ?
This is our year, man.
Change is in the air. I can feel it.
Hey, Mikey.
What are you doing out of your locker ?
Hey, Big-A.
Back here on the senior year, I see.
Hear the new Fallout Boy yet ?
It slays.
It's really good, man. You should
check it out, they're a great band.
My locker hates me.
I could help you.
17, 13, 11.
Great combo,
you'll never forget this.
- Descending prime numbers.
- Yay, math.
You're new here ?
Yep, my family just
moved here from Ohio.
Well,...
if you need any directions,
class advice or,
or CPR, I am certified.
- My name's Cameron.
- Bianca.
Thanks a lot.
Love you.
This is a very serious matter.
Girls, tell me what happenned.
What happenned is this...
girl,
mauled
- my Mini Cooper.
- No,
I asserted my right to park.
Those spaces are communal proper...
Chastity, are you okay ?
Does anything hurt ?
My neck is a little bit sore.
Probably from
flipping your hair too much.
You should go see
the nurse right now.
After all, we can't risk our head
cheerleader having an injury just
days before the first pep rally.
Go, Penguins !
So, get out of here.
And have a wonderful first day.
What you did was dangerous.
Very, very, very dangerous.
I was going two miles an hour.
Not exactly The Fast And The Furious.
Listen, Carol... Karen... Katherine.
I can tell from your transcripts
you're gonna be a very effective...
activist someday.
I'm sure you'll really
stick it to the man.
But here at Padua High, the man...
is Chastity.
The daughter of the school
board superintendent.
This is a public school,
where every student deserves to be
treated with dignity and respect.
No. That's private school.
Here we keep Chastity happy,
so that we keep our funding.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to kiss some ass.
Mr. Verona, what a surprise !
Come in.
Without the sharp object.
Personal space. Ever heard of it ?
What's she doing now ?
Other than looking beautiful,
of course.
She's taking off her shirt
Man, I figure they're a B-cup, tops.
I don't have much time before
her social status is determined.
It's like she's about to reach
into the sorting hat at Hogwarts.
Well, then get over there Harry
Pooper and pull out your wand.
What do I say first ?
Careful.
Go slow, all right ?
Sorry.
So brave.
Watch out.
I wouldn't want you
to fall in those...
fierce shoes.
- Marc Jacobs ?
- Betsey Johnson.
Besides, as my grandma used to say :
"I can't be caught dead
without my mascara"
My grandma used to say that.
No way.
My favorite ban it's Coldplay,
I love scrabulous.
And my dream car is a metallic
blue convertible Mini Cooper.
I'm Chastity.
Walk with me and tell
me your life story.
- Well, we just moved here from Ohio...
- Wow, great story !
You should try for cheerleading.
Too late. Voldemort's got her.
Not so fast.
All we need is a plan.
- Your mom is at Wine Club tonight.
- It's scary you know that.
She gets a little flirty after...
But, tonight, when they're gone,
- we're gonna throw a party.
- The last party we went to
was a Bar Mitzvah. Yours.
If we throw the first rage of
the year we will be legends.
And Bianca will be able
to talk to you in public.
- My mom will be home at midnight.
- We call the cops at eleven...
they break up the party
and make it even more epic.
Come on. Picture...
greeting Bianca as she walks
into this raging party...
at your house.
- At my house.
- Yeah.
We're not exactly Clooney and Pitt.
How do we get people to come ?
Trust me.
I do.
Don't worry, I won't bust you.
Just had to get out of the lunch room.
Apparently, it's no longer socially acceptable
that you eat with your mouth closed.
What's your name ?
When you're a big time artist, I want to be
able to say I knew you back in high school.
Provided you're not
in jail for vandalism.
Mandella.
Who is Captain Intensity over there ?
Patrick Verona. People say
he knows the taste of human flesh.
Please.
He's trying to act mysterious
so he can get laid.
Watch.
Maybe we should stand somewhere else,
somewhere out of state.
There. Do you work
in any other mediums ?
- Favorite dog ?
- Labradoodle.
- Efron or Timberlake ?
- No contest. Timberlake.
- Project Runway ?
- Love it.
Want Tim Gunn to
officiate my wedding.
Well, we are so alike, it's scary.
Hold this.
Bianca...
this is Joey Donner, my boyfriend.
And Padua's starting quarterback.
Babe. I told you I don't know if
I'm gonna be starting this Friday.
Well, let's hope so,
because I don't date second...
I'll see you at tryouts.
I really hope that you don't suck.
She's a sprit fire ?
I can see why you love her.
Yep. She's the best.
- So I'm late for Chemistry.
- Well, I'm late for Chemistry.
After you.
Tabitha, go !
I'm Tabitha Cook,
student council secretary.
A new school year is upon us.
And you can just feel
the excitement in the air.
In order to get everyone excited,
we'll be holding...
Attention,
Padua High School students.
Is the end of summer
bringing out your dark side ?
Well, nothing cures the back
to school blues better...
than a kick-ass intergalactic party.
Right, Chewie ?
If you like to party, and you want
to do it tonight... text 555-0127.
Luke, I am your father.
Hurry ! If we get caught in here,
I'll get kicked out of the A/V club.
You're one of two members.
It's highly unlikely.
- You think it worked ?
- Yeah. It worked.
- Nice wookie, by the way.
- Thanks.
Megan ! Enough.
You all did really great
at try-outs today...
give yourselves a round of applause.
The reason
that we called today try-outs...
is because not everyone can make it.
If everyone could make it,...
well, they instead would
be called sign-ups.
And that means that some...
No,
Most of you won't make the squad.
Those of you who don't may
beat yourselves up about it.
Heck, some of you may regret
it for the rest of your lives.
You'll think back on, tomorrow,
when I post the list,
as the moment...
when it all went
wrong.
So, good luck.
Great speech.
Very inspiring.
But no one cried.
Sorry.
I'm expelling their loser energy.
After all, you and I, are winners.
There's Road Rage girl again.
Of the ten things I hated about today,
she is number one...
number five, and number eight.
Christ, will they allow
anyone into public school.
You're right. Dad's going to
kill us if we're not home for dinner.
Quit the charades
and get in the car.
See you tomorrow.
By the way, you look...
amazing in this light.
Amazing !
She hates you.
I'm touched.
You've ruined my chances
at being popular.
I'm sorry, but that girl sucks.
She's a teenage Kim Jong-il.
Speak English, you show-off.
Kim Jong-il,
the dictator of North Korea. Dad !
North Korea ? So, what ?
I'm talking about our high school...
where I'm going to become unpopular.
My life is unworth living.
Yes. It's way worse than having
bound feet or wearing a burka.
- English !
- Enough !
Bianca, honey, look.
I know you're upset, but Kat's right.
Sometimes you get obsessed with popularity,
keep things in perspective, that's all.
- May I be excused ?
- Already ? That's like a record.
I don't need to carbo load.
I'm not running a marathon tomorrow.
- Thank you, dad.
- For what ?
For agreeing with me that popularty is
a shallow, superficial thing to pursue.
I don't agree with you.
What ?
What's wrong with being popular ?
I loved it.
I loved being
captain of the football team...
president of the student council.
Any girl I wanted.
That was uncle Jimmy.
So, what ?
Look, the problem is,
it's the popular girls...
and the popular boys,
when they have S-E-X.
Could you get the parmesan, please ?
How much longer do I have to
use this thing in the house ?
Until you learn
that a car is not a toy.
- Today's actions could have much worse.
- Told you. It wasn't an accident.
Dad !
You bit me.
That's the first thing you learn
in my victims no more class.
Where are your car keys ? I have to go
to tell Chastity that you're adopted.
You are not taking the car.
You haven't even had Driver's Ed.
It's a big go-kart,
how hard can it be ?
Fine.
You drive me.
No way, Miss Daisy.
I'll tell dad you're not a virgin.
You have one hour.
See, I didn't realize the person
who throws the party
is also supposed
to supply the alcohol.
But I have a surprise !
Keg's here.
Courtesy of me.
Mike Bernstein, sophomore,
musician and legend.
Enjoy, everybody.
How did you get a keg ?
- It's non-alcoholic beer.
- My God. They're going to know.
By the time they figure out they're not
drunk the cops will have busted up the party.
- Yeah ?
- She's here.
- Welcome to my home.
- Thanks, Cameron.
- It's nice.
- I can't take credit.
I have an gay uncle
who dabbles at decorating.
This theme was Suburban Rainforest.
How fascinating.
Listen, do you know
if Chastity is here ?
I don't.
But I could help you look.
Enough.
All right, Hannibal Lecter.
Let's cut to the chase.
You want some of this ?
No ? Now, how about some of this ?
What do you want ?
What do you mean ?
I mean :
Do you want to deal me drugs ?
Or, steal my car ?
Or, harvest my organs ?
Why are people scared of you ?
- People are not scared of me.
- Sure they are.
That's why I find you interesting.
Tell me more about liking Ohio.
Well, they have a good outlet mall.
Oh, fascinating. What stores ?
A little closet time ?
Is it true ?
I swear I never showed anybody
our video.
No ! Is it true that Tommy is starting
in Friday's game ?
Coach said I needed to work
on my three-step drop.
Which is what
you should have been doing all summer
instead of taking
those stupid modeling classes.
Maybe this is a sign
that modeling is my future.
Joey...
I am the youngest head cheerleader
in the history
of Padua high school.
My future is dating the quarterback.
Not a catalog model.
- Look, I could be high fashion.
- OK.
Bianca ?
I thought that you were Chastity.
She thinks it's dumb that I want to be
a male model, but check this out.
You're really smiling
with your eyes.
Modelling is hard work.
I mean, I'm making it look easy.
People think it just happens.
I know how you feel.
You want to be a model too ?
- No.
- I mean, I think you could.
- You've got a great bone structure.
- Why aren't you chasing after me ?
- How dare you ?
- It's not what you think.
We have Chemistry together.
The class, not the other thing.
We match.
Get out.
Hey, how's the party ?
Right, buddy ?
Let's do this.
We're the world's last superpower
and yet we don't have universal
health care.
Are you talking to me,
or the Democrats in your head ?
Dad, have you seen
that box of old piano sheet music ?
No, honey. Why ?
Since I'm not going to be popular,
I guess I'll join the show choir.
Closeted gay guys are fun.
- She doesn't seem like herself.
- I know, isn't it great ?
Come on. Dad, she's obsessed
with what other people think.
Mom would not approve.
You know,
your mother saw Bianca's ability
to fearlessly dive into any social
situation as one of her best traits.
- She did ?
- She did.
She also loved your respect for others,
and your sense of fairness,
which is why I find it strange that someone
so passionate about universal health care
could lack any compassion
for her own sister.
You're good.
You're the one who played the dead
mom card. I just served it back.
Oh, my God, I love this part.
Seeing all their crushed, sad,
little faces makes me realize
how lucky we are.
And we should never forget it.
I'll meet you girls outside.
I'm gonna do a second coat.
Build the suspense.
See ya.
- I love this part.
- I knew it.
I don't want to be a part
of any lesbian locker room fantasy.
- I'm here to talk about my sister.
- Oh, what a coincidence !
I was just about to send her
to social Siberia.
Look, Bianca and I are
completely different people.
I wanna be somebody,
and she wants to be... you.
Big deal, every girl on this school
wants to be me.
And the guys in show choir.
- Put her on the squad.
- Not a chance.
- Move it, Elphaba.
- Bring it on, skinny bitch.
What are you doing ?
Stop. I wasn't ready. It's morning.
I signed up
to be yearbook photo editor.
I'm sure that'll look really good
on your community college application.
Which means I'm in charge
of all the photos that go in it.
Put her on the squad,
or in every page
you'll be sporting a double chin,
a muffin top or cankles.
Freaky friends forever.
Bianca ! Hey.
Listen,
I think I was a little bit hard
on you.
After all, you can't help who...
or what
or what your sister is.
And Joey told me about his confusion.
He's confused. A lot.
And I guess buying the same blouse
does show that you have good taste.
I asked a hundred people in Times Square
who wore it best.
You won.
I am prepared to give you
a second chance.
I'm a cheerleader ?
Not quite.
But, you can be the mascot.
Percival the Penguin.
- The mascot.
- Well, you'll be on the squad.
One of us. Only covered in fur.
Which means you don't have to worry
about fixing you hair color.
So, what do you say ?
Poor Percival.
You know he had two kids ?
No, I didn't.
But I do know the inside of his head
smells like a field of armpits.
Hey, at least
I made the cheerleading squad.
You did.
Happy day.
Now I can focus on passing French.
It's way beyond what I had in Ohio.
I could tutor you.
I mean, if you want.
You would do that ?
See ? I didn't get any of that.
You're a lifesaver.
See you tomorrow.
Adiós.
I mean, Ciao.
I've gotta learn French.
You guys could really be wearing
helmets.
Safety first.
Let's go before someone sees me
in this piece of crap.
Tough talk from the girl
carrying the giant penguin head.
I made the squad.
That's what counts.
It turns out, Chastity is a real sweet,
forgiving person.
Nothing like that Long Duck Dong.
- Kim Jong-il ?
- Whatever.
No more NPR.
It's giving me a menopause.
What was that sound ?
Justice.
You have got to be kidding me !
www.tvsubtitles.net