I don't want to go in there.
What are you talking about?
You love it in there.
Hey, free the naked mole rats.
Ripping.
I was the "girl gone wild"
this past weekend.
All you did was throw
an awesome pretty.
If I tell you something,
do you promise not to be judgy?
Thanks for the buzz!
Whoo!
Apparently I shaved that guy's head,
so I'm in no position to be judgy.
After Chastity left,
Joey and I...
kind of made out for,
like, two seconds.
- Way to go, Sienna Miller.
- Judgy.
This is why I don't want to go in there.
The guilt is killing me. What do I do?
Either live with the guilt
or tell Chastity.
I would, but I prefer to keep
my intestines inside my body.
Ugh! At least you know
what to feel guilty about.
Five-head!
It's me, Joey.
Just pretend I'm a guy
reading the newspaper.
I don't want Chastity
to see us talking.
It's okay. She doesn't know
anything happened between us.
And she never will
once we get our stories straight.
That is our story.
Nothing happened.
Oh, gotcha.
Bianca.
Good news, baby.
The war in "Azerbijackistan" is over.
Okay, his behavior's
becoming so erratic.
He's like my grandma
before we put her on meds.
Seemed fine to me.
Whatever. I'm not here for that.
I'm here to spread joy.
You know how I've been dying
to make you a cheerleader for months?
Oh-- No.
Of course I have.
You're my best friend.
Anyway, Janelle has mono so bad
she has to eat through a tube.
Oh, my God.
Is she going to be okay?
She'll be fine. It's her own fault.
She'll kiss anything.
And this comes on the heels
of that fainting spell...
and her stupid Achilles,
and I am done.
This is cheerleading,
not Grey's Anatomy.
- You're taking her spot.
- I'm a cheerleader?
Yay! I love it
when dreams come true.
Here, try to sound sincere
when you sign her "get well" card.
Just so you know, I was really drunk
Saturday night, like Mel Gibson drunk.
You don't remember
what you said, do you?
I'm like one of those
soap opera actors with amnesia.
Whatever I said, I was joking.
Oh, trust me,
you were dead serious.
- Please, just tell me.
- Nah, I want to save this.
People, just think of this
as airport security.
Only instead of going to Hawaii
so you can sip on mai tais...
you're going to school so you can
drink up a little bit of knowledge.
Excuse me, little lady. I'm going
to have to inspect this carry-on here.
- You have no right to do that.
- Oh, I do now. Bam!
School board enacted it's own
little Patriot Act last night...
and I am the new Dick Cheney.
Uh-oh. I'm going
to have to confiscate this.
Well, Dick, you better pray
I don't get cramps.
Got my eye on you.
:::   Timecodes  -  gius   :::
"End fascism now"?
Is this because I blocked Showtime?
You don't need to make a poster.
- We can just talk about it.
- No.
The administration has instituted these
completely unconstitutional new rules.
Look at these.
It's like going to high school in Cuba.
More than 10 students
need permission to assemble.
School has the right to search lockers.
No drugs or weapons.
Oh, my God! Do you mean to tell me the students
have to leave their Uzis and heroin at home?
- Dad, this isn't a joke.
- How about knives and crack?
They're trampling our civil rights.
This time they've gone too far.
Even the mindless mouth-breathers at Padua High
will be marching to the tune of justice.
Why do I get the feeling
this isn't going to end well?
Daddy, look.
My little cheerleader!
Did you ever think
today would come?
Finally, one of your daughters
makes something of herself.
I'm never taking this off.
Sounds like someone hasn't read
the new security policy.
Are you going on about Cuba again?
[speaks Spanish] to that.
Ah.
They're making us wear uniforms.
What? No!
No, no! I finally clawed
my way to the top...
so that I could have the honor
of wearing this cute little outfit to school.
They can't take that
away from me!
This is inhumane.
I can't believe she thinks it's okay
to say these things out loud.
Well, it is
her First Amendment right.
Funny.
Ugh! I can't believe
this is happening to me.
These uniforms-- I know. How are we supposed
to express ourselves through fashion?
No, Joey and I broke up.
You did?
- Why?
- Guys are such pigs.
Did he tell you he was studying for trig
when he was really studying Kelly Morris?
Do you think he would cheat
on this test?
- No.
- Uh-uh.
Never. Not even if it
were multiple choice.
But why did you guys break up?
Well, you know that college boy
that was hitting on me at your party?
- Who could blame him?
- I know.
Well, then, Joey turned
into this possessive freak.
I thought actors were bad,
but models are so much worse.
So I couldn't lose.
Oh. When I told him,
he started sobbing.
I hate it when guys cry.
It's like--
Fine. Be sensitive, but don't,
like, slobber all over me.
I'm the one that wants to cry.
I finally get back into circulation...
and now I have to wear
this stupid uniform.
Amen.
- It's un-American.
- Mm-hmm.
These are our civil rights, people.
Yes, you, too.
You, too.
Throwing another party?
Woman, you are an animal!
We have to ban together and fight.
- Who we gonna save?
- Naked mole rats!
Screw the stupid mole rats!
This is about our freedom!
I don't think half these kids
can spell "freedom".
- Wanna help hand out flyers?
- Yeah-- No.
But I was thinking after school
we could head to the beach.
At your party,
you said you wanted to go.
- I did?
- No.
Can you please just
hand these out in auto shop?
I'll put them on the table,
but I'm not passing them out.
- Gee, thanks. That's so supportive.
- This is your thing, not mine.
So you don't give a damn that
we no longer have the rights...
that are guaranteed to us
in the Bill of Rights?
Must be nice
not to care about anything.
Well, what's the point?
It's not like we can change it.
I'll tell you what. Come to the beach,
and I'll tell you what you said.
What's the point?
It's not like I can change it.
Cameron, we have to talk.
I love you,
but you don't feel the same way.
- What more is there to say?
- Cameron, wait.
I'm so sorry. The last thing
I'd ever want to do is hurt you.
You're my best friend.
You're smart and funny...
and you're the only person
who knows I like to watch 60 Minutes.
And I miss you...
so much.
I miss you more.
Do you think we could
go back to being friends?
I don't know.
I guess we could try.
Yay! So I'll see you
at French tutoring.
Au revoir, mon ami.
"You're my best friend"?
First, you already got
a best friend.
And second, she's just
not that into you.
Hey, she's still transitioning into
seeing me as a viable heterosexual.
Are you hearing the words
that are coming out of your mouth?
Despite everything, I still feel that Bianca
and I are meant to be together.
Haven't you ever known something
deep in your heart?
I'm 15.
I know things deep in my pants.
That's why I don't waste my time
on chicks that aren't into me.
Michael, a foundation of friendship
is the best gift you can give a relationship.
See? This is what happens when
you don't have a strong father figure.
I did not approve this flyer, Kat.
Although I love your font choice.
The only approval I need
is the First Amendment.
- In fact, I--
- Yeah, yeah. Kumbaya.
- Just don't do it again.
- I will do it again.
And again and again
until you change this policy.
I'm an Energizer Bunny for liberty.
Do you think I like this?
Look at all this new paperwork.
Duplicates, triplicates, quad--
I'm so swamped,
I had to cancel my foot massage...
which I depend on to keep me
from screaming at you people...
to leave me the hell alone!
Then lift the policy.
You can make all of this go away.
I'm just a cog in the machine...
a tool of the man.
Hey, I think that's my ibuprofen.
The bottom line is...
the superintendent enacted this.
We follow it, or we don't get funding,
and I get fired. So we're both stuck.
Unless you can convince her
to change it.
"Her"? I thought
the superintendent is a man.
He is. I was talking about
his daughter, Chastity.
And what Chastity wants,
Chastity gets.
- Yes, but Chastity hates me.
- Oh, no.
This revolution stuff is hard.
Waah!
There's Joey. Hope he doesn't do
that sobbing thing again.
- Hey, five-head, can we talk?
- Bye.
So I heard you and Chastity broke up.
Are you okay?
I'm more than okay.
I'm the maximum okayness there is.
In fact, you wanna go out
on Saturday?
You, me, out, together.
Yummy. Dinner.
I'm buying.
Joey, I would love
to go out with you.
But it's too soon.
You and Chastity just broke up.
We shouldn't even be seen
talking together.
Hey, she broke up with me.
I don't even know if she ever loved me.
Not the real me.
I was just this gorgeous status accessory,
like Paris Hilton's poodle.
Girls like Chastity don't like other girls
playing with their poodles...
even if they've given
their poodles away.
And Chastity
can be really mean.
That's why I'm ready to be
with someone really sweet, like you.
Take you, for example.
No. I can't do this.
I just became a cheerleader.
Yeah, I mean
I just got tired of him.
Sure, he's good-looking and all,
but I've got that covered.
- Chastity, can we talk?
- Nope.
It's first period. I only deal
with unpleasant things after third.
I'm on a mission of peace.
I need your help.
I know you do, but I only give
one makeover a year...
and I already helped Tori.
Mmm! Boy, was that hard.
This is important.
Doesn't it bother you that we're all
being treated like suspected criminals?
Hmm.
No, not really.
Fine. Doesn't it bother you that
you have to wear that outfit again?
Oh, that bothers me so much.
We should do something about it.
Can you get me
a meeting with your dad?
It's pointless.
I already asked him, and he said no.
I even cried real tears.
Then we'll stage a walkout.
We'll refuse to go back inside
until they lift the regulations.
It'll work
if the whole school does it.
And the only person who can get
the whole school to do something is you.
That's true.
But it all sounds
really exhausting.
Free these kids from their uniforms,
and you'll be a legend.
I'm thinking fourth period.
Great idea.
- Great idea.
- Thanks.
Everyone, can I have
your attention?
Shh!
Guys, this is a walkout,
not recess.
Shh! Shh.
Guys, come on!
Be quiet, please!
Shut up and listen to her!
We are here today
because our Constitutional rights...
do not start the day
we graduate from this hellhole.
We deserve dignity
and respect now.
After all, we're not just
stupid teenagers.
We are citizens
of the United States of America.
When I say "uniforms",
you say "suck"!
- Uniforms!
- Suck!
Infringement on civil liberties!
- Huh?
- What?
Suck!
Don't confuse them.
- Uniforms!
- Suck!
* My country, 'tis of thee *
- Sing louder, people! Louder!
* Sweet land of liberty *
* Of thee I sing *
* Land where my fathers died *
Five-head!
- You're as light as a balloon.
- What are you doing?
I couldn't stay away.
I need a kiss to get me through the day.
But I thought we agreed
we were going to sneak around.
No one's gonna see us.
They're all singing gospel.
Come on, five-o.
Just one smooch...
and I'll never ask you
for another favor again.
* Let freedom ring *
- Everyone, shut up!
Yeah.
Shut up!
Chastity, your--
your father's on the phone.
Be strong.
Daddy?
No, you listen to me.
Okay? I'm at school
and in this uniform.
Everyone looks the same.
No, I'm not being a brat.
Okay, you wanna go there?
We'll go there.
Ditch these stupid uniforms,
or I'll tell Mommy how I found out...
that your executive assistant
doesn't wear a bra.
Whoo!
S-- I- I understand.
Yes, sir. I--
Back to class.
No more uniforms.
Yeah!
Whoa. Whoa. Wait!
Our struggle has just begun.
Call your dad back. What about our
First and Fourth Amendment rights?
They can still search our lockers!
I don't have time for this crap.
I got my own problem.
Yeah! Whoo!
Hey Chastity, great rally.
Listen, I wanna talk
to you about Joey.
I know. I saw him kissing
that blonde slut, too!
I cannot believe that he would
do this to me! Ugh!
- You saw him kissing someone?
- Some... thing.
She looked like a--
a toothpick with hair.
I couldn't make out her face.
It was probably hideous.
But I thought you said
you were over him.
Thank God they installed
those security cameras.
- Security cameras?
- Yeah.
All we have to do is review the footage,
and then we'll know who she is.
Then you'll help me
destroy her, right?
Sure.
We'll get her.
Thanks, B.
I don't normally do this, but...
You're the best friend
I've ever had.
What would I do
without you? Mm!
* Until we're free *
So, should we sing something else?
How about "Blowin' in the Wind"?
Maybe we'll just sing in our heads.
Can't.
Plastic water bottle.
- I could pour it in my hand.
- I'd do that, I'm so thirsty.
Eh, we'll recycle 'em.
Dad, I know why you're here.
It's okay. Unchain yourself.
We need to talk. Now, Norma Rae.
Be right back.
Did that deep-voiced man-boy
put you up to this?
No. I'm just fighting
for what I believe in.
Principal Holland threatened to suspend you
if you don't stop this right now.
It would go on
your permanent record.
That's just an urban myth to scare
smart kids into submission.
I don't get this, Kat. You always wanted
to go to an Ivy League school.
They'll appreciate
my social conscience.
No. They'll label you
a problem student.
You know how competitive it is.
They'll look for some reason to reject you.
It's like enlisting in the army and
writing down, "Oh, by the way, I'm gay."
- Oh, I'm against that, too.
- I'm just saying, pick your moments.
I can't just give up. That's not
what Mom would have wanted.
Oh, no.
You learned that one from me.
Besides, Mom would've wanted you
to see the big picture...
and not be an idiot.
Look, you have you whole life
to save the world. Right now...
don't give up your dream
of going to Brown.
This is not fair.
- I shouldn't have to make this choice.
- Then let me make it for you.
You made your point.
Go back to class.
Got it?
Got it.
Great job, guys.
No more uniforms.
The school came together.
I think we can call this a win.
Now we should get back to class.
You're kidding, right?
We can regroup
and figure out the next step.
After all, none of us
wants to get suspended.
Wow.
I guess everyone has their price.
- Why is he so mad?
- He's not mad. He's disappointed.
It's going around.
Cameron! Oh, God,
I really need your advice.
I just had the most awful thing
happen with Chastity.
You're gonna have to tell your problems
to someone else. I can't do this.
Do what?
Be your friend, especially while
you're wearing that perfume.
- Then I won't wear it.
- Don't you get it?
I need time to get over you.
I didn't sell out.
I'm just thinking big picture.
I wanna go to a first-rate college...
so I can get a degree in social policy
and change the world.
- The real world, not high school.
- You sound like one of them already.
- What the hell?
- Nice bag.
Verona, hand it over.
- Keep it.
- What's going on?
Young man, where do you
think you're going?
You walk out of here,
you're suspended.
Did you hear what I said?
I wish we could spank them.
- Hard.
- Search this.
Then can I keep it?
You said I could keep it.
You have no right
to go through this.
Kat, come back here with that,
or you're suspended, too.
Then I guess I'm suspended.
Fight the power.
* Hey! *
* Owww! *
This is yours.
* I want you *
- You sure about this?
* To want me *
- No.
* I need you to need me *
- But I'm doing it.
* I'd love you to love me *
- "Hold my hair."
Excuse me?
That's what you said to me
at your party right before you hurled.
* I want you to want me *
- Nice.
* I said *
- Helmet.
* I want you to want me
Yeah *
Hey! *
* I said I want you
* Whooaa! *
* Owww! *
www.tvsubtitles.net