(gasping)
Madam President,
we have your husband,
but he sustained
a gunshot wound to the chest.
TAYLOR:
Is my husband going to be okay?
We're not going to know anything
until the doctors see him.
Since your husband was the only
leverage that Dubaku had left,
it's safe to say that he's
trying to leave the country now.
Whatever we're going
to do to find him,
we're going to have
to do it fast.
Whatever it takes,
I want that
son of a bitch found!
Have someone
find my daughter, Olivia,
and bring her to me.
What is it
that's so important
for my mother to steal
me away while I'm trying
to do business?
It's your father.
He's been shot.
My, God, I...
Do you think I'm a fool,
Mr. Burnett?
If anything should happen to me
on my way out
of the country,
a data file with all the names
and bank transactions
of all those involved will be
sent to the Justice Department.
You told me that once
Dubaku served his purpose,
you'd take him out.
Why are we still helping him?
He's threatening to expose us
using a database he's kept
with names and accounts
of everyone involved.
Including mine?
We don't know
where the file is,
so you just better pray
that he gets away.
I'm begging you,
Marika...
FBI! Don't move!
Get on your knees!
Now!
Where is Dubaku?
Who?
RENEE:
Don't play games with me!
Ike Dubaku!
JACK:
You know this man?
She was going to meet him.
When the car arrives,
we would like you
to go with the driver,
so that we could follow you
back to Dubaku.
You want her to go to him
and face him?
It's the   only chance we have
of finding him before he
disappears forever.
I'll do it.
You keep her safe,
you hear me?
We will.
You're less than a mile
behind the target car.
I got Metro PDs trying to build
a roadblock around us.
(siren wailing, tires screech)
RENEE:
We can't afford
to lose them, Jack!
I gave this woman my word
we'd protect her.
(tires screeching)
Get out of the
car, right now!
(cops clamoring)
Federal agent!
On the ground!
She's a federal agent!
(panting)
BURNETT:
Your girlfriend's
been turned by the FBI.
If you let her come to you,
you're risking
your chances of escape.
I'll call my driver,
have him take care of her.
No. I'll take care of her.
Sean,
I need to talk to you.
Is it important?
You tell me.
Did you issue
a federal warrant
on this vehicle?
What?
I found a digital footprint
on server four's backup
partition.
It originated from your station.
I'd like to know
what the hell is going on!
Keep your voice down.
You want to get us caught?
I sent out the warrant,
to sideline Bauer and Renee.
They were
closing in on Dubaku.
I thought you said
Dubaku's on his way
out of the country?
He is, but his girlfriend's
talking to FBI.
They used her
to track him.
Oh, my God.
Don't worry, I
took care of it.
Bauer and Renee are
in police custody.
By the time
they're released,
Dubaku will be long gone.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
Why didn't you just tell me
what was happening?
'Cause I knew
you'd react like this.
The last thing I need right now
is one of your meltdowns.
Now, listen,
I got you into this,
and I'm going to get
you out of it,
but not if you start panicking.
You've got
to keep it together.
I'm just really scared,
you know?
I know. I am, too.
I'm just a little better
at hiding it than you are.
I've got everything covered.
I ran a bounce-tap
into the conference room
speakerphone that
they'll never find,
and I can hear
everything they're saying.
Now, sit at your station.
Try and act normal.
Let me worry about
Bauer and Renee.
Okay?
The man that we were tracking
is responsible
for today's terrorist attack.
If you don't let us go,
he's going to get away.
Look, my Captain's on the phone
with your superior.
You're making a mistake!
You've got to let us go!
That warrant had
to be sent out by one
of Dubaku's operatives.
I know.
Then Dubaku knows that
Marika is working with us.
He will kill her, Jack.
We should not have
used her like this.
We didn't have a choice.
She was our best asset.
She's not an asset, Jack.
She's a human being.
Colonel.
The FBI is still
looking for us, sir.
I'll do this quickly.
Wait there for me.
Samuel.
What? What is it?
Sweetheart, what's wrong?
Give me your cell phone.
My cell phone?
I know you've been
talking to the FBI.
You've been working
for them, Marika.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
What are you doing?
What? What are
you doing?
(cell phone smashes)
No!
(grunts)
I trusted you!
How could you do this to me?!
The FBI told me
who you really are.
About the terrible
things you've done.
And you believed them?
They showed me proof!
They showed you lies
created by my enemies!
You don't know me.
And you don't
know my country.
I brought peace to Sangala.
(crying softly)
No. Shh, shh!
Don't be afraid, huh?
It's just...
when I heard what
you had done,
it was like you had
driven a dagger
through my heart.
I'm a forgiving man, Marika.
I still want
you to come with me.
I want to give you
the life that I promised.
I can't go with you.
I don't know who you are.
You do.
You do. If you look
past your fear,
you'll see that
I am still the man that you
fell in love with.
I won't leave
without you, Marika.
All right.
You won't be disappointed.
Come.
The FBI may be close.
Your story
was verified by FBI.
I'm sorry about
the misunderstanding.
Did FBI find
Marika Donoso?
I don't know.
You can ask them yourself.
Agent Moss wants
to talk to you.
Larry, where are they?
Where's Marika?
We lost her cell phone signal.
What do you mean?
What happened?
Don't know.
Just went dead
about three minutes ago.
Where?
CHLOE:
In an alley
on the Northeast corner
of N and 10th Street.
I'm looking through
traffic cams now.
All right, we're going
to comm. Standby.
They lost Marika's signal.
That's it.
There. Jack?
We got a make on the car.
It's a dark gray
Jeep Grand Cherokee,
turned south on 11th Street
about two minutes ago.
Copy that.
Moving to intercept.
Did you see Marika?
Yes. She got in the car
with Dubaku.
Chloe, stay on those
traffic cams.
I'm on it.
We're ten minutes
from the airfield.
Is my plane ready?
Fueled and waiting.
Did you take care
of the problem?
She's had a change of heart.
She's coming with me.
Colonel, she was working
with the FBI.
You were almost arrested
because of her.
She's not your concern.
You just worry about
getting me out of the country.
Who was that?
It was a government official.
He's been
working for me.
A very corrupt man.
I look forward to no longer
dealing with people like him.
I want to spend time
with people I really care about.
CHLOE:
They're still on 11th.
They just crossed over
to New York Avenue.
Copy that.
Come on!
Jack, they're
turning left.
Hold on.
(tires screeching)
Colonel!
FBI. Go! Go!
Hold on!
Ah!
Get on top of the car! See if
you can maintain a visual.
Ow!
Marika!
(grunting)
Jack, they crashed!
Go!
Get back in your car!
JACK:
Larry, Dubaku's vehicle's
been involved in an accident.
We need an
ambulance, now!
Copy.
Back away!
Stay on your knees!
Get on the ground, now!
Now!
(gunshots)
I got Dubaku.
(grunting)
Agent Walker,
the car is on fire.
Get out of there!
I gave her my word, so back off
or help me.
RENEE:
It's her leg-- it's pinned.
Hold on.
(grunting)
Pull... pull!
Jack.
Go!
You all right?
RENEE:
Come on.
Larry, where is my ambulance?
Dubaku's badly injured.
He's unconscious.
I need that ambulance now.
They're on their way, Jack.
(breathing heavily)
ETHAN:
Admiral Smith estimates
we'll have the capitol of
Sangala secured within the hour.
He's surprised
how little resistance
our troops
have encountered.
And you'll be happy to know
we have liberated
the refugee camp
in Kasanga Province.
2,000 civilians are safe
from Juma's forces.
Madam President?
I'm sorry, Ethan.
Oh, my God, Kasanga Province.
That's... That's very good news.
Uh, maybe we should
finish this
another time.
Can I get you anything,
Madam President?
No, thank you.
Would you like to talk about it?
What happened to Henry
was my fault, Ethan.
He never believed
our son committed suicide.
He was right.
And I didn't listen to him.
And if I had, we wouldn't
be here
right now.
Henry wouldn't be
fighting for his life,
and we might have exposed
this conspiracy.
Our government
wouldn't be paralyzed.
I didn't believe Henry, either.
No one did.
But I'm his wife.
He deserved my trust.
BUCHANAN:
Madam President?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's all
right, Bill.
Go ahead.
I just spoke
to Larry Moss at FBI.
We captured Dubaku.
He was seriously injured
in a car crash
during the
pursuit.
How bad?
Critical, nonresponsive.
Jack Bauer and Agent Walker
are with him.
They'll be there
to question him
should he regain
consciousness.
So, you're saying
that if Dubaku dies, our chances
of uncovering this
conspiracy die with him.
He could be the only one
who knows
the names of everyone
in the government
he's corrupted-- yes.
Madam President,
given this latest news,
I don't think
it's safe
for you to remain here.
I strongly urge you
to return
to the White House.
I'd prefer to stay
with my husband.
You're too exposed.
I can't effectively
protect you.
Am I any safer
at the White House?
My administration
has been
corrupted, Bill,
and now you're telling me we're
about to lose our only lead.
Madam President,
I assure you I've taken
every precaution
to secure the White House.
It's the safest place
for you to be right now.
Henry will be in surgery
for several hours,
Madam President.
There's nothing more
we can do here.
You are needed
in the Oval Office.
All right.
I'll have the cars
brought around.
I'll also redirect
your daughter's escorts
to the
White House.
Thank you, Bill.
What are we going to do, Ethan?
How can we possibly
run this government
when we don't know
who we can trust?
We'll just have
to pray Jack Bauer
can get those names
from Dubaku.
You got him stabilized?
Yes, sir.
We're transporting
him right now.
Bring him around.
I need to talk to him.
Sir, he's in
no condition
to speak
right now.
This man has information vital
to national security--
bring him around now.
Now!
One milligram epinephrine.
I know you can hear me.
You're in federal custody.
These paramedics are trying
to save your life.
You want them to continue,
you're gonna
tell me what I want to know.
I want the names
of everyone in the United States
government that you've
been working with.
Come on.
You and I
both know the game.
It's over
for you now.
There's no sense in trying
to protect them.
You and I, we're both soldiers.
I know you don't care
about your own life,
but you got a family.
I know where your son is
in Sangala.
I know where he lives,
and I swear to you,
I will track him down,
and I will make him suffer,
and I will make sure
that he knows
his father
was responsible.
All you got to do to make me
stop is give me the names.
Just give me
the names.
Don't hurt my family.
I have a list... list.
Where is the list?
His BP's spiking.
Give me the list.
Where is the list?!
He's going into
cardiac arrest.
Bring him back!
Get the paddles.
Start at 200 joules.
(machine whirring)
Clear.
No response--
there's a glitch.
Once more.
(whirring)
Clear.
There it is again.
Electronic
interference.
This could be it--
feels like
a metal plate
or something.
All right.
Amping up to 300.
(whirring)
Clear.
Where's the plate?
All right.
He's stabilized--
let's get him boarded.
Where's the plate?
It's below
his rib cage.
Open him up.
Sir, we don't
have time.
I have to ask you
to step aside.
You open him up now.
Do it.
Sir, this man will die
if we don't get him
to the hospital.
Get him out of here.
Patch me through to Agent Moss.
This is Moss.
Larry, it's Jack.
Go ahead, Jack.
I found some
kind of digital
storage device implanted
under Dubaku's skin.
What is it?
In an effort to
protect his family,
he said he would
provide me
with a list of all
of his U.S. government contacts.
He said it was on him;
he meant, in him.
Larry, this is his
insurance policy.
I'm sure of it.
Jack, we need that data
as soon as possible.
Can you upload
the files to FBI?
I don't think so.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Hold on one second.
Officer.
My name
is Jack Bauer.
I'm working
with the FBI.
I need you to get this device
to regional headquarters.
I want you to give it
to an Agent Larry Moss.
You put this in his
hands, his hands only.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Do it.
Larry, you got a chopper
coming your way.
You should have the drive
in five minutes.
We're gonna stay with Dubaku.
Get back to us as soon
as you got anything.
Copy that.
Sean.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Just listen to me,
and try not to overreact.
Okay, we have
a situation,
but I think I have
a way to handle it.
What situation?
You told me you had
everything
under control.
I do...
but they have Dubaku's database.
What?
Sean, our names
are on that list.
You told me that you
were taking care
of this,
and now you're telling me
that they
have our names?
No, they don't
have our names yet,
so here's the plan.
Sean, we have to get out
of here.
We have to get out
of here right now!
I'm not going
to jail, Sean!
Do you hear me?
Nobody's going
to jail.
I promise.
I'm sick
of your promises.
You promised me
that this
is all taken care of.
You promised me
you're leaving your wife.
You make all these promises,
but you never
keep any of them!
Stop talking,
and just listen to me--
now, I told you I have a way
out of this, but I need your
help, do you understand that?
Now, listen... okay?
As soon as O'Brian
downloads those files,
we're gonna crash
the entire system,
every single server
on this floor.
That's crazy.
No, it's not crazy.
We're gonna go up
to the mainframe room...
initiate a system-wide reformat.
We'll wipe
everything clean,
and they won't be
able to stop it.
We're gonna have to bypass a lot
of safety protocols, okay?
But nobody's
better at dealing
with those servers than you are.
Isn't that true?
I need your help.
I can't do this
without you.
Hmm?
Erika?
Yeah.
Okay.
Um...
we're gonna have to...
tie the main servers together.
I need an
AVI motherboard,
but you're gonna have
to reconfigure it
for a macro uplink.
Okay, and we
have to hurry.
The drive is gonna
be here any minute.
Go up to the mainframe room
and get started.
I'm gonna prep the motherboard.
I'll meet you up there.
Okay.
Hey.
We're gonna
be fine.
Huh?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
(indistinct chatter)
These are Marika Donoso's
personal effects.
Thank you.
Copy that.
Get back to me.
That was Larry.
They got the drive.
Chloe's gonna be
working on them.
They should have something
in the next few minutes.
That's all that matters,
right, Jack?
I don't like
what happened to Marika
any more
than you do.
We did what
was necessary.
You better figure out
a way to live with it.
How, Jack? Pretend
that it never happened?
Is it that easy for you?
I'll let you know when
Chloe's got
something.
Here it is.
(sighs):
This is a PX-1-7 drive.
It's got an
auto-erase function.
We've only got one download.
(computer clinks and chirps)
Where have you been?
Just took a little
longer than I thought.
(computer beeps)
What are you doing?
Checking surveillance.
Got to keep an eye
on Larry and O'Brian.
Once we do this,
they're gonna
realize someone's up here
in a few seconds.
We'll have to
make a clean exit.
How much longer is this going
to take?
I just have
to bypass safety protocols.
(phone ringing)
Once they're down,
I'll start the reformat.
Go ahead.
Dubaku hasn't arrived
at the airfield,
and he's not answering
his cell phone.
BURNETT:
What's going on?
FBI got him.
What?!
How long have you
known about this?
They're not going
to get anything out of him.
He's unconscious
in the hospital.
There was a crash
during a chase.
Listen, the FBI recovered
that database
you told me about,
the list of names.
I'm in the process
of deleting it.
I'm going to erase
every trace of it.
I don't have to tell
you what will happen
if they get that list.
They won't. I'm gonna
take care of the database.
You need to take care
of Dubaku.
Don't worry about him.
You just make sure...
ERIKA:
Damn it!
I got to go.
What's wrong?
It-It isn't working.
What do you mean,
it isn't working?
All the inputs are active,
the servers are aligned,
but the reformat won't start.
It doesn't make any sense.
Okay, well, just-just
think it through, Erika.
Right? You
can do this.
Would you just shut up?
Okay?
Okay.
Has to be server three.
(beep)
All right,
server three was upgraded
last week.
Which means they restored
the partitions to the
system default settings.
How could I be so stupid?
I just have
to configure the parameters.
Okay.
(trilling)
Okay? Is that it?
I think so.
Program's running.
(computer trilling)
What? What's happening?
What's going on?
The hard drive's
reformatting.
What?
The files are being erased.
We're losing everything.
Well, make it stop.
I don't have
the access.
Get the PX-1-7 out.
It's too late.
It's erased.
(indistinct, lively chatter)
CHLOE:
This is deliberate.
It's not a glitch.
Someone's trying
to crash the system.
Where's your mainframe room?
Come on.
Here they come.
We got to get out of here.
Almost there.
Erika...
It's done.
Are you sure?
Yeah. It'll take a few minutes
for the reformat to be complete,
but there's no stopping it.
Oh, baby.
Mm.
I knew you
could do it.
Yeah. We gonna be okay?
We're gonna be fine.
(gunshot)
(Erika gasps)
(panting)
(groaning)
(gasping)
(sighs)
Sorry.
(gunshot, groaning)
(groans)
(groaning)
(door opening)
Get on the floor!
It wasn't me!
(groaning)
(Sean groaning)
Larry, it wasn't me.
Chloe!
SEAN:
Larry, I followed her up here.
She was trying
to crash the system.
She shot me!
I went for the weapon,
and it went off.
Security, this is Agent Moss.
I need a team to lock down
the mainframe room.
And get a medic up here! Chloe,
can you recover the files?
I don't know yet.
What files?!
What the hell is happening?!
You tell me what the hell
is happening, Sean!
You were shutting me out, Larry,
so I looked around on my own.
I found out that Erika was
rerouting the sub-cam channel!
What the hell was she doing?
She sent out a-a warrant
on a vehicle with two suspects.
I knew something was wrong.
That's not part of her job.
I asked her about it,
and she tried to deny it.
She was acting
very strangely.
Why didn't you say anything?
I don't know
what the hell it meant,
so I hacked into
her hard drive,
and I found schematics
for the main server.
Bypass codes
for the safety protocols.
I followed her up here
to see what she was up to.
The second I realized
she was trying to crash
the system, I-I confronted her.
She shot me.
I went for the gun.
Larry, I didn't mean
to kill her.
Halt! Halt!
Larry, it's too late.
The system's fried.
Dubaku's
files are gone.
Are you sure?
Can you recover anything?
The server's wiped clean.
She got everything.
Is this everything you got?
No, it's not.
I didn't have time
to print out every single
message that came
through Erika's workstation.
That's everything she was doing
for the past three days.
Look, Larry,
I told you what happened.
I feel like
you owe me an explanation.
What the hell is going on here?
(sighs)
The government's been
compromised by Dubaku.
FBI, Secret Service.
God knows who else.
That's why I shut you out,
brought in Chloe O'Brian.
We were in the middle
of decrypting a file
that had the names of
everyone on Dubaku's payroll.
Erika erased it when
she wiped the server.
That was our only lead.
You should have told me
about this.
You should have trusted me.
Sean, I didn't know
who to trust.
You all right?
How's your arm?
It hurts like hell. It's fine.
Oh. When you're up for
it, I'm gonna need you
to write a statement.
Okay.
And keep your mouth shut.
(phone ringing)
We don't know who else
in this building
might be working
for Dubaku. Yeah.
Larry, don't ask me how,
but I did it.
You did what?
I recovered Dubaku's files.
What?
I was running a mirror file
on an outside server.
I always do that
when I'm dealing
with sensitive materials.
Erika's parameters
were too narrow to catch it.
How soon can you
have it decrypted?
It's decrypted. It's been
decrypting this entire time.
Dubaku kept
detailed evidence
on everyone.
Phone logs, financial records--
it's all here.
Listen, I'm gonna need you to
cross-check with FBI personnel.
Sean said Erika was
working by herself,
but I got to
be 100% sure.
Okay. Hold on.
Yeah.
Chloe recovered
the files.
That's great.
I should get to that statement.
Yeah.
Sean?
When you're
done there,
I want you to go downstairs
and see Dr. Weber.
You shot a fellow agent.
You're gonna want
to talk to somebody.
Yes, sir.
JANIS:
Hey, do you
have any idea
what's going on
with the servers?
Not a clue.
The whole system's down.
I tried to get
into the mainframe room,
and security has
got it locked off.
Ask Larry about it, Janis.
Where are you going?
I got to run an errand.
Now?
All right, all right.
Hold off.
(grunts)
You better start
talking to me right now!
I'd like to speak
with my attorney.
Put him in holding.
(breathing heavily)
Get me Bill Buchanan
at the White House.
(indistinct chatter)
Where is my sister?
Where's Marika?
There was an accident.
What happened?
Marika didn't make it.
What-What do you mean?
There was a crash.
Uh, it happened
during the pursuit.
Marika was killed.
I don't understand.
You said that you'd protect her.
You said she'd be okay.
We wouldn't have caught
Dubaku without Marika's help.
She was very,
very brave, Rosa.
What is this?
This is supposed
to make everything okay?
Marika was all I had!
I trusted you with her life,
and you let her die?!
I'm so sorry.
(gasps)
(crying):
Don't touch me!
(crying)
You killed my sister!
You didn't care how you did it
or who got hurt!
JACK:
Agent Walker?
Excuse me.
I just got off the
phone with Larry.
Dubaku wasn't lying.
On the drive was a list
of everyone he was working
with in the government.
They're getting ready
to make arrests.
It's over.
It's not over for Rosa.
What happened to Marika
was a tragedy.
But I'm not going
to stand here
and tell you what
we did was wrong,
because we weren't.
She made a choice,
a brave one,
to get involved,
but she made it.
God, listen
to yourself, Jack.
You don't even
sound human.
Don't you feel
anything?
We had a job to do!
To protect the hundreds if not
thousands of
innocent lives
that would not have
had a choice
if we let a terrorist
attack take place.
What we did wasn't wrong.
It was necessary.
I read your file.
When your wife was killed,
did you feel that
or did you just tell yourself
that that was necessary?
What do you want from me?
What do you want from me?!
I just want to know
that you feel something!
I want to know that you feel
the same kind of pain that I do!
Do you feel that?!
(crying)
It's all right.
You're going to be all right.
It's going to take a while.
But you will learn
to live with it.
What if I don't want to learn
to live with it?
Then quit.
And by the way,
that stunt you pulled
by the car...
...you ever pull your weapon
on my again,
you better intend to use it.
I did.
(door opens)
Olivia.
What's going on?
How's Dad?
He's still in surgery.
We're waiting for word.
Is he going to
be all right?
He was seriously injured.
The bullet
went through his lung.
Livy.
The doctors are doing
everything they can.
Who did this?
It's complicated.
I want to know
who shot my father!
Your father found out
about a conspiracy
inside the
government.
The people behind it
tried to kill him.
Who are these people?
We're trying to find
out right now.
That's all I
can tell you.
Okay, I want to go
to the hospital.
I want to be there
when he wakes up.
I can't let you do that.
The people who shot your father
are still out there.
It's not safe.
I don't care, I want to see Dad!
This is not a debate.
I'm not going to risk anything
happening to you.
You're staying
in the White House,
and that's
the end of it.
AIDE (intercom beeps):
Madam President,
Bill Buchanan is here
to see you.
I'll be right out.
There's a lot we need
to talk about, Olivia.
We've been ignoring things
for far too long.
It took Dad getting shot for you
to finally want to talk?
Let's not go down this path.
Not again.
Not today.
We'll talk later.
One of the guards will take you
up to the residence.
All right, Bill.
What is it?
I have very good news.
Jack Bauer just
recovered a database
hidden on Dubaku.
It contains the names
of everyone
in the government who
was working with him.
How many?
Close to a hundred people,
across all agencies.
Some at very
high levels.
My God.
Dubaku kept detailed
files on every person.
This is exactly
what we've been working toward,
Madam President.
We can finally put an end
to this conspiracy.
I assume you've already
begun acting on this
information.
Yes.
As a matter of fact, Larry
Moss just identified
two more individuals
working within FBI who
were on the list.
He's confident the
Bureau is secure.
What's the next step?
I'm working with FBI to
coordinate an interagency sweep.
We should start making arrests
within the hour.
Bill, I don't
know what to say
to thank you.
What you have done
here today
puts all of us
in your debt.
I appreciate that,
Madam President,
but there are a lot
of people to thank,
including Jack Bauer.
He's scheduled
to resume his testimony
before the Senate Committee
tomorrow morning.
I'm aware of that.
Madam President,
forgive me
if I'm out of line,
but I feel
Senator Mayer is on
a personal crusade
against Jack.
He's already taken
his pound of flesh.
He dismantled CTU,
attacked the reputations
of people
who've served this
country with honor.
Now he wants to make
an example of Jack.
It isn't right,
Madam President,
especially after today.
What are you asking me to do,
Bill?
I'm asking you to speak
to Senator Mayer.
Jack Bauer helped save
this country.
He doesn't deserve to spend
the rest of his life in prison.
I appreciate your sentiments,
Bill,
but I'm going to have to think
about this.
That's all I'm  asking,
Madam President.
Thank you.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I need to talk
with you.
About what?
I told you I was going
to follow up on a lead.
No, you said you were going
to turn yourself in
as soon as this
was over.
And I will.
But this ain't over yet.
There's going to be
another attack.
Here in D.C.
Dubaku is in custody.
He's already provided us
with a list of everyone
in the government
that was working
with him.
It's not Dubaku.
It's his boss, Juma.
He knows he's about to lose
control of his country.
So he's going to try and
rally his people behind him
by striking back
at the U.S.
How do you know this?
I tracked down
a source.
What source?
He was one of the men I worked
with on Emerson's crew.
He had a direct line
of communication
with the Juma regime in Sangala.
It wasn't easy getting
the information out of him,
but I'm convinced
it's accurate.
Then you should hand it
over to FBI.
No.
My source tells me
that the window opens
at 1900 hours.
By the time the FBI
wades through their
procedures and red tape,
it's going to
be too late.
What's the target?
He doesn't know
the exact target,
but it's definitely going to be
of high value
and high impact.
He gave me the name
of somebody
who's been involved
in the planning.
Who?
Ryan Burnett.
Senator Mayer's Chief of Staff.
That's right.
He's been involved from
the very beginning.
What about Mayer?
No.
He's not involved.
You're sure about that?
Yeah.
You better not be lying to me,
Tony.
This is real, Jack.
Burnett will be
on Dubaku's list.
As soon as he finds out
that Dubaku's in custody,
he'll start running.
You don't have a lot of time.
I've already got
a tail on him.
(sighs)
Listen, Jack,
if you're with me,
meet me at the corner of
First and Constitution.
I need your help.
MOSS:
Thank you for your patience.
As I'm sure some of
you already know,
our government and its
ancillary agencies,
including this office,
have been infiltrated
by operatives
in league with
Ike Dubaku.
(phone rings)
Yes, Senator?
MAYER:
Ryan, can you step in here?
Yes, sir.
(knocks on door)
I'm going
to the White House.
Sir?
President Taylor wants
to speak to me
regarding Jack Bauer.
Bauer?
What about him?
I don't know,
but we'll find out
soon enough.
It's odd, though.
What is, sir?
Bauer was pulled away
from the Senate hearings
this morning
to help the FBI
with an investigation.
And now the president
wants to talk to me
about him.
I don't like
the timing of this.
Grab your laptop, Ryan.
I want you there with me.
Yes, sir.
(phone beeps)
www.tvsubtitles.net