[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 7:;00 a.m. And 8:;00 a.m.
Tell me if you need more people on this,
and I will get them for you.
We don't need people. We need to get lucky.
The transmitter node on the laptop
is encrypted with multiple relays.
Can you source the transmission or not?
I'm trying to come up with a work-around.
- Call me as soon as you have something.
- I will.
- They still can't source the transmission?
- They're working on it.
Chloe and Janis are doing
everything they can.
Is there no other lead,
no other way to fiind my father?
This is a good lead, Kim.
The only reason we have it is 'cause of you.
Yeah, except my father is dying,
and we don't know how much time he has left.
[Shouts]
[Panting]
[Gunshots]
[Whirring]
[Loud Thud]
[Engine Revving]
No!
[Grunts]
[Knocking]
- Come in.
- [Door Opens]
What are you still doing here?
Just fiinishing up
the conversation we started.
Aaron, I told you
to escort Ethan to the gate.
Now take him out of my offiice and off
the White House grounds.
No, ma'am. I am not gonna do that.
I'm calling security.
[Collier On Speaker] Having me dig up dirt
on Noah Daniels is one thing.
This is a whole different animal.
[Olivia On Speaker]
I'm aware of that, Martin.
- I want this to happen. I want
this person taken care of.
- [Collier] Mm-hmm.
[Olivia On Speaker]
It's Jonas Hodges.
The digital card you confiiscated
from me was blank.
I gave the real one to Agent Pierce.
How long have you known, Aaron?
I had my suspicions, ma'am...
but I was hoping I was wrong.
I'll wait outside, sir.
Ethan, this doesn't tell the whole story.
Sounds pretty clear to me.
Hodges is dead. You're responsible.
I know, but I tried
to stop it from happening.
Oh, save it, Olivia.
You can't talk your way
out of this situation. Not this time.
All right, Ethan.
You win.
I'll resign. Come up with some excuse.
You could have your job again.
Everything will go-
This isn't about getting my job back!
It's about the truth.
The truth could
destroy my mother's administration.
I am fully aware of the implications
if this goes public.
You don't have to spell them out for me.
Then what do you want?
[Sighs]
For the president to take the next step.
Whether she decides to prosecute this
or bury it, that's her call.
But she needs to know the truth.
I'll let you tell her yourself.
I can't believe you're doing this.
You're betraying everything
that you've ever worked for.
I know you think this country failed you...
and I don't care what kind of ideology
you believe in now.
This is no way to fiight for it. What you're doing
is wrong. This is wrong, and you know it!
Damn it, Tony. Look at me.
Please...
as someone who was once your friend...
let me die in peace.
Don't let them use me
to kill innocent people.
I have no intention of letting them use you
as a pathogen, Jack.
- I never did.
- I overheard you.
This was your idea. You sold it to them.
It was just a play.
- A play?
- To get the man who's coming here right now.
Took me three years to fiind him.
Took me another year
to get him to meet me face-to-face.
I had to prove myself to him
by taking down Jonas Hodges.
I had to convince him
that I was a true believer in his cause.
What the hell are you talking about?
His name is Alan Wilson.
He was the man behind Charles Logan.
He's the one who ordered
the hit on David Palmer.
And he had Michelle killed
to cover his tracks.
This is the man who murdered my wife, Jack.
Everything that you've done
today is for personal revenge?
It's about justice.
Justice?
You killed innocent people, Tony!
Ten times as many people would have died
if it hadn't have been for me.
The deeper I dug to fiind the person
responsible for Michelle's death...
the more I kept running into men
likeJonas Hodges.
They're the ones with the crazy ideology,
Jack, not me.
I'm the one who had
a plan to bring them down.
I'd enlisted Bill and Chloe to help me track
all the elements of this group.
And when I fiinally got what I wanted...
they would turn 'em in and shut 'em down.
But you screwed that all up,
didn't you, Jack?
You see...
I'm the one who saved lives today, Jack,
not you.
I'm the one who helped you recover
the C.I.P. Device.
I'm the one who warned you
about the White House attacks!
I'm the one who stopped Jonas Hodges from
launching those missiles!
You tell yourself whatever you want.
You launched a biological attack
on Washington Center Station...
and if we hadn't gotten there in time, thousands
of innocent people would have been killed!
I did what I had to do
to get Alan Wilson there.
And now...
he's gonna die.
You kill him, and no one will ever know...
the full extent of this conspiracy.
I'm not gonna kill him, Jack.
You are.
Damn you, Tony. Damn you.
I'm sorry that it has to be you.
But the truth is, they wouldn't let me
within 50 feet of the guy.
You're the one he's coming for.
You're not honoring Michelle's life.
You are reveling in her death,
and she would despise you for this.
[Electronic Twitter]
[Grunts]
[Beeping]
[Jack Grunts]
We're clear.
- When's Wilson coming?
- Soon.
- He wants to see Bauer's medical record.
- It's right over there.
[Jack Breathing Heavily]
[Beeping]
Wilson doesn't know about us.
And it's best to keep it that way,
at least for now.
Sure.
I understand.
[Electronic Twitter]
He's here.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
[Train Horn Blows
In Distance]
Put your hands behind your head.
We're all clear, sir.
[Man]
Go ahead.
That's far enough for you.
Hello...
Cara.
This is Tony Almeida.
- Been looking forward to this, sir.
- Yes, I know.
Where's Bauer?
Right inside, second door on the right.
- [Keys Clink]
- You'll need this.
[Door Opens]
So, Cara...
thinks you should be
playing a larger role in our organization.
- You've been an asset.
- Thank you, sir...
but I believe there's
a lot more I can bring to the table.
But fiirst I want to see
Bauer's pathology report.
I have it right here.
[Renee]
This is the F.B.I. You're surrounded.
- Lay down your weapons.
- Fire at will!
Tony!
[Sirens Wailing]
[Tires Screech]
[Groans]
[Machine Gun Fire]
Set us down.
[Man Shouts]
[Groans]
I need you to get me to that green vehicle.
- [Engine Starts]
- [Tires Squealing]
- [Grunting]
- Jack.
Stay away from me.
I'm wired with C-4. Tony's got the detonator.
- Stay away!
- Wait. I know this trigger mechanism.
- I can disarm it.
- [Beeping]
- Where's Kim?
- She's safe.
She was the reason we were able to fiind you.
Tony's been playing both sides all along.
You need to stop him.
He's trying to kill the man who's behind
this conspiracy. His name is Alan Wilson.
He was responsible for killing Tony's wife,
Michelle. That's why he's doing this.
You want to end this for good,
you need to stop Tony from killing him...
otherwise you're gonna lose
any chance of exposing the others.
- [Beeping]
- Okay. You're clear.
Let's go.
It's the Woodside Industrial Complex.
We're in the southeast quadrant,
on our way to the perimeter.
Call me when you have an exfiiltration point.
How did this happen? Huh?
- How did they track us?
- I don't know.
[Scraping]
Tony!
[Exhales Sharply]
Thank God you're okay.
The extraction team will be here soon,
but we gotta move.
[Gunshot]
[Thuds]
It took me a long time to fiind you...
to peel back all the layers
of people you hide behind.
But I stayed patient.
'Cause ever since the day
you had her killed...
the only thing that kept me alive...
was this moment right here.
Hmm. You sound like you were involved
in some kind of a tragedy...
but I had nothing to do with it.
[Whispers]
Oh, no, no, no. No.
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
See, Michelle and me...
had gotten out of all this.
We made it out together.
And we were gonna start a whole new life...
until you came along...
and took it all away...
in a split second.
[Groans]
[Breathing Heavily]
It wasn't just my wife you murdered.
She was carrying my son.
You killed my son! My son!
And now...
I'm gonna kill you.
[Gunshot]
[Groaning]
Tony, don't move.
Tony, don't move!
[Groans]
[Groaning]
- Get him out of here.
- [Groans]
[Groans]
These people think they can take everything
away from us, Jack!
Somebody had to stop 'em.
And what did you do, huh?
You ran away!
That's right! You ran away, Jack!
You're one of them now!
Congratulations!
How would Teri feel
about that, huh, Jack? Huh?
[Tony Shouts]
[Tony Shouts, Faint]
[Handcuffs Clicking]
[Beeping]
[Siren Wailing]
- [Car Engine Starts]
- [Chattering]
[Chattering Continues]
A lot of people died today because of you...
including someone close to me.
You will be charged with treason...
and conspiracy to launch
terrorist attacks against this country.
The only way that I see you
avoiding the death penalty is by cooperating.
Tell me who else is involved
in this conspiracy...
and I will make sure that your cooperation
is taken into account by the grand jury.
Hmm.
How can I cooperate if I have no idea
what you're talking about?
That's not gonna work, Wilson.
Whatever this conspiracy is
that you think that I'm a part of...
I guarantee you won't fiind a shred of
material evidence connecting me to it.
In the eyes of the law, I'm an innocent man.
You son of a bitch.
Anything else you need to say,
you can say to my attorneys.
Ma'am, they're almost ready to take Bauer
to the hospital. You wanted a heads-up.
Hmm. Hmm.
I'm giving you hydromorphone to make
the ride to the hospital easier.
It'll make you a little sleepy,
but it will break the pain cycle.
No. Not yet. Please.
Jack.
Could you give us a moment?
Dr. Macer wants you at the hospital.
It's all right. She can wait.
Thank you.
What happened?
He's denying everything.
Claims that we don't have a case against him.
Is he right?
Maybe-which means
he has absolutely no reason...
to tell us who else is involved
in this with him.
But I can make him talk.
If we don't fiind these people,
one day they will launch another attack...
and I don't see how I can live with myself...
knowing that there was
something I could have done to stop it.
I don't know what to do.
I can't tell you what to do.
I've been wrestling
with this one my whole life.
L- I see 15 people held hostage on a bus,
and everything else goes out the window.
I will do whatever it takes
to save them- and I mean whatever it takes.
I guess maybe I thought...
if I save them...
I could save myself.
[Chuckles]
Do you regret anything that you did today?
No.
But then again, I don't work for the F.B.I.
I don't understand.
You took an oath.
You made a promise to uphold the law.
When you cross that line,
it always starts off with a small step.
Before you know it, you're running as fast
as you can in the wrong direction...
just to justify what
you started in the fiirst place.
These laws were written
by much smarter men than me.
And in the end, I know that these laws...
have to be more important
than the 15 people on the bus.
I know that's right. In my mind...
I know that's right.
L-I just don't think
my heart could ever have lived with that.
I guess the only advice I can give you is...
try to make choices that you can live with.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything at all.
Mr. Bauer, we really need to go.
[Beeping]
Henry! What are you doing out of bed?
- What's going on?
- Olivia wouldn't say until you got here.
You'll understand when I tell you.
It's gonna be hard enough to say once.
I'm listening, Livy. What's this about?
Jonas Hodges.
He's dead because of me.
Oh, Livy.
Don't tell me you were the one
who leaked the information.
It's worse than that.
Olivia...
talk to us.
He killed Roger.
Hodges killed my brother...
and then you agreed
to put him into witness protection.
And the thought ofhim
getting away was too much for me.
So I called Martin Collier.
He had once told me he knew someone...
who could do this kind of thing.
You're saying Collier
hired someone to killJonas Hodges?
No.
I did.
I tried calling it off, but it was too late,
and everything was happening so fast.
Olivia, who else knows about this?
Ethan.
He has a recording
of my conversation with Martin.
He's agreed not to turn it over
to the Attorney General.
He says he'll respect whatever you decide
to do with the evidence.
- Mom, say something.
- How could you do this, Olivia?
How could you do something so stupid?
I'm sorry.
I tried to call it off. I swear.
[Taylor]
It doesn't matter, darling. It happened.
For God's sake, Allison. Stop yelling at her.
- Hodges killed our son.
- I know what he did.
Then you know,
if anyone deserves to die, it's him.
All you should be thinking about now is how
to protect our daughter.
Protect her? How?
Destroy that recording.
And cover up a murder?
Henry, I can't just disregard the law.
Allison, spare me your sanctimony.
You're Olivia's mother.
I'm also the president of the United States.
And our family's already
paid a steep enough price for that.
What are you saying, Henry?
You know exactly what I'm saying.
Your job cost our son his life.
That is a cruel thing to say.
I couldn't have done anything
to prevent Roger's death.
But you can do something about this.
For God's sakes, Allison.
We've already lost one child.
[Knocking]
I'm sorry to interrupt,
Madam President, but there's some news...
from the Bureau you need to hear.
Uh, good news.
[Clears Throat]
I'll be down in a moment, Tim.
Yes, ma'am.
[Door Closes]
[Henry]
Go, Allison.
But so help me...
destroy that recording...
and save what's left of this family.
Go.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
Dad, what did I do?
We're going to fiigure this out.
I'm sorry.
We'll fiigure it out.
He's a high-value suspect.
Make sure you restrict access until I get there.
[Janis On Phone]
Agent Walker's bringing him back now.
- What's their E.T. A?
- About 10 minutes.
I'll be there in 20.
Have Wilson's transfer papers in order by then.
- Yes, sir.
- [Beeps]
Excuse me. Chloe.
I've gotta work on
Wilson's transfer papers...
so we're gonna have to
schedule debriefiing for later.
- I can come back later, or tomorrow.
- You staying in town?
I want to be here forJack.
I'd like to thank you
for all the help you gave me today.
Yeah. It was interesting.
Given what you have to work with, uh, you're
doing a pretty good job.
I'll take that as a compliment. Thank you.
Good. That's what it was meant to be.
Because the pathogen was weaponized,
the disease is at an advanced stage.
I'm sorry, Mr. Bauer.
All I can do is administer morphine...
which will induce a coma.
- But you won't feel any pain.
- No morphine. Not yet, please.
Excuse me, Dr. Macer.
Mr. Bauer has a visitor.
Yeah. It's all right.
[Monitor Beeping]
He'll see you now.
I'll be outside.
Thank you for coming.
I was surprised to get your call.
I'm dying.
I know.
[Breathing Erratically]
I made so many mistakes.
A-And I always thought
that I would have the time to correct them.
You have the time. Right now.
You don't know what I've done.
We live in complex times, Mr. Bauer.
Nothing is black-and-white.
But I do know this:
I see before me a man...
with all his flaws...
and all his goodness.
Simply a man.
[Breathing Erratically]
Let us both forgive ourselves
for all the wrongs that we have done.
Thank you.
It's time.
[Beeping]
Olivia, come and sit down.
No, I can't.
[Door Opens]
I never imagined that this job would-
would be so hard on both of you.
I had no idea of the price
this family would pay.
And for that, I am so sorry.
But I have a sworn duty...
to enforce the Constitution.
Failing to honor that oath...
would be the worst kind ofhypocrisy.
Olivia, I love you
more than anything in this world...
and I will do everything
I can to help you through this...
but as president,
this is what I have to do...
no matter how much it breaks my heart.
Agent Pierce will remand you
to federal custody.
Ma'am, I'm escorting you
to theJustice Department...
where you'll be held until formal charges...
have been issued.
I'm sorry, honey.
Henry.
[Door Closes]
[Exhales Deeply]
Allison.
Um...
- if you'd like to talk later-
- No.
As much as I wanted to cover this up, l-
I couldn't.
You don't have to explain yourself to me,
Madam President.
- I understand completely.
- Henry doesn't.
He'll come around.
In time.
I don't think he will, Ethan.
I really don't.
I've lost my family.
I've lost everyone.
Not everyone.
Then you'll take back
your letter of resignation?
If you want me to.
I do.
I need your help, Ethan.
And I need it now.
[Sniffles]
The F.B.I. Has taken a man into custody.
His name is Alan Wilson.
[Chatter On Police Radio]
[Door Closes]
Woods is on his way to pick up Wilson.
You need to sign the transfer documents.
What's wrong?
- What's going on?
- [Electronic Twitter]
- Get out of here, Janis.
- Excuse me?
- I said get out of here.
- What are you doing?
Get out!
No. Absolutely not. I'm staying right here
until Wilson is transferred.
- Fine.
- What are you-
Renee, what are you doing?
- Put your hands over your head.
- [Scoffs]
I said do it now, Janis!
Secure your hands to that pole.
- Now!
- Okay, okay, okay. Just-Just
calm down, all right? Just-
Renee, please don't do this.
Please don't do this.
You've done yourjob. You arrested him.
Let the courts take it from here.
Stop this now, before it's too late.
Don't throw away your career.
This is absolutely insane.
Larry would not have wanted this.
Don't dishonor his death like this.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
Daddy.
I'm too late.
No, he's still
alive, Kim.
We induced a
coma to help
ease him through the
harsher symptoms.
My name is Gohar.
I'm a friend.
A friend?
We spent the last
few minutes talking
and I can tell you he's
accepted what is happening.
Maybe he has.
But I haven't.
The stem cell treatment
that you told me about.
Can we still do it?
As I told you,
it's experimental
and the odds of
success are very low.
Just tell me
if it's too late to try.
No.
Then I want to do it.
- The risks--
- I understand the risks.
and I know my father didn't
want me to take that chance,
but it's my choice now
and I made up my mind.
This is Sunny Macer.
I need immediate access
to a surgical suite.
Have Dr. Rosen
call me right away.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
But I'm not ready
to let you go.
www.tvsubtitles.net