Ken Dellao, CNB.
I'm wondering if you can
confirm some information.
I'm gonna be reporting in
this evening's broadcast
that a rogue ex-federal
agent named Jack Bauer
is the prime suspect in
the murder of Ryan Burnett.
You leaked this story of Burnett's
murder and my involvement to the press.
So another one of your errors in
judgment bites you on the ass.
You've gone too far this time.
Renee, it's Jack.
Don't hang up the phone, please.
Whatever they told you,
I did not kill Burnett.
I sent you a photo
of the man who did.
All I want you to
do is make an ID.
John Quinn,
Black Ops combat vet.
He works for Starkwood.
Starkwood work with Juma?
If they did,
it wasn't on the books.
You know, if anyone knows,
it's Senator Mayer.
Renee, where's Bauer?
I don't know.
Don't you lie to me.
We know you accessed a
classified government database
and sent someone's name
and address to Bauer.
Tell me where he is.
I can't.
Put her in holding.
Mirandize her.
If Bauer connects us to Juma, it
could seriously impede this operation.
Yes, it could.
Is the shipment on time?
Yes. Due into port
in the next hour.
Once the weapons are deployed,
then it doesn't matter what Mr. Bauer
or anyone else knows.
I didn't kill Burnett.
This man did.
His name is John Quinn.
He works for Starkwood.
And what does Starkwood
have to do with this?
Your informant claims
that Starkwood was trying
to acquire a bioweapon,
and that's your connection to Juma.
You've been trying to dismantle
Starkwood for the last six months.
If they have a weapon like this, you
better believe they intend to use it.
No!
Just tell me where the
weapons are coming in.
You're too late.
They're already here.
(sighs) Sir?
Preliminary sweep of the
immediate area's done.
There's no sign of Bauer.
All right, widen the grid.
And run down security cameras
around the perimeter, witnesses.
Somebody must have seen him.
Yes, sir.
Yes?
Mr. Kanin, it's Larry Moss.
Agent Moss, please tell me you
have Jack Bauer in custody.
I wish that were the case, Mr.
Kanin, but the truth is...
Sir, it's Senator Mayer.
He's dead.
What?!
He was murdered at his house.
We only found out that Bauer was on
his way over here a short time ago.
Unfortunately, we
got here too late.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me that Jack Bauer
just killed a United States Senator?
That's the assumption that
we're working under, yes, sir.
How could you have
let this happen?!
He had us all fooled, sir.
I released Jack Bauer
into your custody!
I ordered you to keep
him on a short leash!
No, no. Mr. Kanin, you are not
gonna lay this one at my feet.
It was your decision to give
Bauer access to Burnett.
I advised you against it.
Mr. Kanin?
I'm sorry.
Uh, what did you say?
I said,
I advised you against it.
Yes, you did.
Sir, I have teams
sweeping the area.
Just find him, Agent Moss.
Yeah, I will.
Starkwood was involved with
everything that happened today.
They were the ones that
helped Juma and his men
bring down those planes
and attack the White House.
In exchange, they were allowed to
develop and manufacture a WMD
in Sangala.
It's a bioweapon.
Apparently, it's
already here in the US.
Who else knows about this?
No one. Senator Mayer and I were
piecing together the information
right before he was killed.
You said the weapon's
already here.
Are they in possession of it?
I don't think so.
The text message I got
off their agent's cell phone said,
"Port of Alexandria, Lot C, 10:15 p.m."
Why don't we just call the FBI
and lock the whole place down?
Because we're fugitives, Tony.
No one's going to believe us.
We need to know exactly where that
weapon is before we call anyone else in.
Tony, I need to know if
you're with me on this.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Okay. Meet me at the
north end of the port.
There's an access road right
before the main entrance.
All right, I'll be there.
It's over.
Dubaku and Juma are dead.
Everyone responsible for
the terrorist attacks...
responsible for Roger.
Thank God for that.
And there's...
there's something else.
Something good that's
come out of all of this.
Olivia is here at
the White House.
Olivia?
She's come home, Henry.
The crisis--
it brought us together.
I've asked her to stay on as Special
Advisor, and-and she's agreed.
Ally...
I can't begin to tell you
how happy that makes me.
Me, too.
Sweetheart, I know
that you're tired.
You should get some rest.
Olivia and I will come to the
hospital just as soon as we can.
When you can.
I'm not going anywhere.
Give Olivia my love.
Love you.
We love you, too.
The doctors expect him
to make a full recovery.
Henry's a lot tougher
than anyone thought.
Oh, maybe, maybe, maybe, just maybe,
this day will end on a positive note.
What is it, Ethan?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry to have to tell you this,
Madam President, but Senator Mayer
is dead.
What happened?
All evidence points to the fact
that he was murdered by Jack Bauer.
Bauer?
It's hard to believe, I know.
It-It doesn't make any sense.
After everything
he has done today,
why on earth would he do this?
We'll know more
when we find him.
My God.
Madam President,
in light of what's happened,
and for the sake of
your administration,
I'm afraid I have no choice but
to resign as your Chief of Staff.
Ethan!
Madam President, please,
you need to hear this.
Inevitably, it'll come to light that I
sanctioned Bauer's release from custody.
Unless I step down immediately, the
damage to your office, and
you personally,
will be extensive.
Ethan, Olivia has already
killed this story once today.
We can control the damage.
No.
No, not even Olivia
can control it now.
Not after the senator's murder.
The truth is, Madam President,
I didn't do enough to protect you.
The truth is, I failed you.
And I should shoulder the
blame for what's happened.
Ethan, really, you're...
you're taking this too far.
Am I?
I'm not so sure.
As your daughter has made abundantly
clear, I have a lot to answer for.
You have done nothing but be
an invaluable advisor to me
and an even better friend.
I appreciate you saying that,
Madam President, but Olivia's right.
The political
knives will be out.
Every decision I've made
will be scrutinized.
There will be calls for
a special prosecutor.
You're a great woman, Allison.
You have great work yet to do.
I'm a liability to you now.
Don't let me compromise your
next three years in office.
Don't let me sink your agenda.
Our agenda, Ethan.
Yes.
Our agenda.
Trust me, Madam President,
it's the right thing to do.
Accept my resignation.
I'll have a letter on
your desk in the morning.
They're gonna be
here any minute.
We need to narrow
down the search.
If they offloaded it today,
it should still be on the storage dock.
That's still a needle
in a haystack, Jack.
There must be over a thousand
containers in there.
We need to access
the yard's manifest.
What's the security?
I've spotted one Port Authority officer.
That's it?
That's it.
There's got to be more.
Come on, let's go.
Honey, it'll be fine.
I get relieved in a few hours.
Carl, you know I don't like
you working double shifts.
Well, it was my choice.
And we could use the overtime.
How are the girls?
Kicking like a
chorus line tonight.
They miss their daddy.
What'd the doctor say?
That I'm lucky
it's not triplets.
Honey, let me call you back.
Don't even think about
going for your weapon.
I need the port's manifest.
Where is it?
I'm just a PA cop.
Customs House.
That way.
Let's go.
We on schedule?
STOKES (on phone):
We're at the staging area
near the port, sir,
but we're still waiting on Quinn.
He should have
been there by now.
Have you heard from him?
We've tried his cell,
but he's not answering.
If Bauer took out Quinn, he might
have knowledge of the operation.
Mightn't he?
Should we stand down, sir?
No. Give Quinn five more minutes,
then go in.
Do so with extreme caution
then contact me the minute
that you've secured
the container.
Yes, sir.
SEATON: Everybody on
the board is here, sir.
You have a worried look, Greg.
It's very tense in there, sir.
They're six-year-olds, Greg.
And they need to
eat their carrots.
It's been a rough day for
the United States of America.
The White House under siege,
the President taken hostage...
It's especially painful because
we know this didn't have to be.
Fact: the United States military
is strained to the breaking point.
Fact: reinstatement of the draft is
off the table for political reasons.
Fact: the people in this room,
you all control
the largest private army
in the Western hemisphere.
Now, could we have
been of help today?
You bet your ass we
could've been of help!
But they didn't call us,
did they?
No. Instead, we sit here,
our contracts are canceled,
our soldiers vilified,
our corporate sovereignty
is threatened by
congressional fiat.
Doug, you brokered the
deal with this government.
You were short-sighted and they
don't understand that the global war
on terror can only be
won by forces like ours.
So as of this minute,
we sit for no more depositions.
We volunteer no more documents.
I don't even want us to take any phone
calls. Is that what this is about?
With the security of our country,
Is that what this is about?
we cannot afford to
let them take us down.
Is that what this
is about then?
You came here to ask the board
to risk a federal indictment?
It won't work, Jonas.
We got a deal.
It's a good deal and
we're lucky to have it.
With an administration
that wants to destroy us.
Wants to take us
out of business.
No, it's all different now.
Today was a game-changer.
No, institutionally,
we are in compliance with the subpoena.
Documents have been filed,
depositions taken.
Not anymore.
Jonas, we have to stay engaged with this
administration. No, we don't, Doug.
So look,
you and I can talk this out.
If you guys have any questions,
any further questions, Greg, you will
stick around and
you'll answer them.
Thank you for coming everyone.
Thank you.
Your way was a mistake, Doug.
You have to acknowledge that.
Maybe. But you and I both know
that Starkwood cannot survive
an all-out war against
the subcommittee.
Let me worry about that.
No, you should worry
about Senator Mayer.
He's not going to
let go of this.
He's got his teeth in it.
Senator Mayer's dead.
He was killed by a rogue federal
agent not one hour ago, tragically.
Jonas.
Tell me you had nothing
to do with this.
Are you accusing me of complicity
in the murder of Senator Mayer?
I want a personal assurance.
Starkwood is not in the business
of political assassination, Doug.
Though maybe we
should look into it.
I hear it's a growth market.
Jack, you finding anything?
12 ships were unloaded here today.
Any from Sangala? There's no deepwater
port in that area of West Africa.
If the weapon
originated from there,
it would've had to overland
into Pointe-Noire.
Where...
two of the 12 ships acquired cargo from
that port within the last four weeks.
Come on.
Come on. Damn it!
What is it? I can't access
their manifests;
their database is password protected.
What's your name, officer?
Gadsen.
Carl Gadsen.
I don't have any information
about a password.
Carl, I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
The same terrorists who took
down two planes earlier today
and attacked the White House are trying
to acquire a weapon of mass destruction.
They're coming here to
pick up that weapon.
It's somewhere out there in your
yard in one of those canisters.
Look, I understand
this might be hard
for you to believe.
No, actually, it's not.
You don't have a lot of time.
What do you mean?
They are coming.
In fact,
they should be here already.
Keep talking, Carl.
They told me they were smuggling
in electronics from South Korea.
I swear.
I had no idea they
were terrorists.
What'd you agree
to do for them?
Open the front gate.
Look the other way.
Is that it?
Disable the security cameras.
A yard this size should
have more police officers.
Where are they?
I'm the supervisor.
I do the shift schedules.
I made sure I'd be
the only one here.
That's enough
confirmation for me.
I'm making the call. Untie him.
Who's he calling?
The FBI.
Now that we're confident
the weapon's here,
we're calling in the authorities.
Tony? My cell is down,
so is the landline.
Someone's jamming
communications.
It's them.
They gave me that radio;
told me they'd be
contacting me. Answer the call.
Just play along.
Answer the call.
Hello?
Where are you?
I didn't think you were coming.
You're late.
Well, we're here now and we're waiting.
Okay.
They're at the front gate.
Put your belt back on.
I want you to resume your post.
Pretend like
everything's normal.
Just let them in.
And then what?
We're going to follow them
as soon as they pick up
their container;
once we're past
the jamming grid, we'll make our call.
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
You're a part of this, Carl,
whether you want to be or not.
You became a part of it this the second
you said "yes" to these people. Jack!
What do you got?
I got three vehicles.
Eight hostiles, heavily armed; got to
assume there's more inside the trucks.
Carl, if you don't open that gate,
they're going
to come in here looking you,
you understand me?
Let me put it to you this way.
These men have killed
over 300 people today.
If they get ahold
of that weapon,
they're going to make that
look like child's play.
You've only got
one choice here.
I just open the gate
and let them in.
That's all you've got to do.
And you guys got my back,
right? Yeah.
Promise me.
I promise you.
Okay.
Tony, get the
surveillance package.
Don't worry.
It's just so we can
hear what's going on.
Turn around.
I need to put this
on your back.
Listen, the money--
it wasn't about greed or anything.
It's my wife, Linda.
She's having twins.
They say it's the most natural
thing in the world, right?
Getting pregnant?
Well, it took us three years,
cost an arm and a leg.
No excuses,
but insurance doesn't cover a dime.
I just always wanted
to have a family.
You know what I mean?
Put this in your pocket.
You got him?
Yeah.
Remember, it's just
another day at the office.
You're going to be fine.
Let's go.
What took you so long, Carl?
You got the routing documents?
Sure.
I need to see them in order
to locate the container.
Relax, Carl.
They're right here.
Okay.
Center section.
Row 36, Q-block.
It's that fourth
stack on your left.
I know where the
container is, Carl.
Did you disable the
security cameras?
They've been off since 10:00,
just like you said.
How's your wife?
She's fine.
You didn't tell her anything about this,
did you?
No, of course not.
Did you tell anybody else?
No, no, why would I?
You tell me, Carl.
Why are you so nervous?
Okay, um, you want to know the truth,
Mr. Stokes?
Uh... I was expecting a simple pickup,
but you show up
with a small army here, and, um...
And what?
It's just...
not w-what I was expecting, that's all.
I just don't want
to get caught.
Nobody's gonna
get caught, Carl.
Let's go, we're moving.
You too, Carl, take a ride.
I told you,
it's the fourth stack on your left.
Q-block, row 36.
I'd feel better
if you showed us.
I really should stay here,
Mr. Stokes.
I got to finish my patrol.
Why, Carl?
You expecting somebody?
No. Then get in.
Okay.
Damn it.
Forget about him, Jack.
He was dead the minute he
stepped out that door.
You and I both know that.
Ethan, I just came to
say how sorry I am.
Well, I appreciate the
courtesy if not the sincerity.
As much as I may feel this is what's
best for my mother, on a personal level
I'm sorry you have to
go through this...
and for some of the harsher
things I said to you in anger.
Well, I suppose I owe you an apology,
too, for accusing you
of leaking my role in this
Bauer fiasco to the press.
I really believed you were
trying to blindside me.
Considering the impression I gave you,
I'm not surprised.
Olivia, as someone who's
known you most of your life,
I'd like to offer some advice.
Of course.
Ambition can be a valuable
quality here in Washington
as well as in life, but unchecked,
it can be unhealthy, if not dangerous.
What I'm trying to say is...
you got yourself a seat
at the president's table.
She listens to you.
But running a country is
not like running a campaign.
It's not about doing
whatever it takes to win.
It's about doing what's right
for the American people.
Sometimes those things
aren't mutually exclusive.
Well...
good-bye, Olivia.
Good-bye.
MAN: Hello.
It's Olivia.
You can go with that story now,
Ken, and it just got better.
Tell me.
Ethan Kanin's resigning.
What happened?
I thought the plan was to let him
twist in the wind for a while.
His hand was forced. Thank you.
It seems Jack Bauer just
murdered Senator Mayer.
(whispering): What?
You're kidding me.
Anybody else have this yet?
Not yet,
it's all yours in time for the 11:00.
Told you I'd take care of you,
didn't I?
You are too good to me, Olivia.
You just hold up your end.
Make sure Kanin's the fall guy.
My mother is nowhere
near this, understand?
No problem.
She really doesn't have any
idea that you're the leak?
No, and it'd better
stay that way.
She won't hear it from me.
When are we having that
dinner you promised?
Maybe next week.
It's always next week.
You'd better get to work if you're
going to make that broadcast.
So these files on the computer--
presumably Senator Mayer was looking
at 'em before he was killed?
Someone was, sir.
They were opened and viewed
within the last hour.
So if the sen...
if the senator was
killed point-blank
in the entry hall,
how are we explaining the slugs
in the door frame
and the railing?
I don't know, sir.
Get the crime lab guys on it.
Yes, sir.
Agent Walker,
it's Larry Moss for you.
Hello.
Senator Mayer is dead.
Where's Jack?
Don't know; we don't have him.
Okay, but what,
you think that he did this, Larry?
First Burnett and now Mayer?
Well...
it looks that way.
What do you mean
"looks that way"?
Well, that's why I'm calling.
Senator Mayer
was killed with a UMP
40 submachine gun.
If Bauer was on the run, where'd he
get ahold of a weapon like that?
Also, there's evidence to
suggest that the, uh--
there was a third
party in the house
when the senator was killed.
What kind of evidence?
Unexplained slugs...
...a broken set of French doors,
a chair where it doesn't belong.
Okay, so are you saying that
this third party killed Mayer?
Well, you know, Renee, I might be
saying that if I knew what the hell
Bauer was doing here
in the first place.
All right, Renee, listen.
I want to meet you halfway, I do,
but if you expect me to even entertain
Bauer's innocence,
you have got to help me here.
I can't, Larry.
If Jack is still underground,
he is underground for a reason.
There were files open
on Mayer's computer--
documents relating to his
investigation into Starkwood.
All right, so just tell me that,
tell me that.
Did Starkwood ever come up in
your conversation with Bauer?
Renee.
Look, maybe, maybe I should
have trusted you before, okay,
but you have got
to trust me now.
What role does Starkwood
play in all this?
The man who framed Jack
for Burnett's murder was John Quinn,
a Starkwood contractor.
Jack believes that they were behind Juma
and all of the terrorist attacks today.
He went to Mayer to get
the evidence to prove it.
I have to assume that
Quinn followed him there.
That's all that I know,
Larry, I swear.
Okay, I believe you.
Thank you.
Just sit tight,
I'll be in touch soon.
Well, let me help, Larry.
I mean,
Jack could still be out there.
He may be in trouble.
No, no, I can't release you,
not yet.
Reese, what's the status?
Just getting the chassis on,
sir, I'll be a minute.
Hurry it up.
Hold up, hold up,
I don't have my truck.
Put it down there,
I want it there.
Mitch, get up there.
Let's run a diagnostic now.
I want to be ready to roll as soon as
Reese gets here with that flatbed.
Yes, sir.
All right, there's the package.
We should get back to the car.
We want to be in position to follow
that container once they move out.
Jack.
Just give me one second.
Cooper.
Now's as good a time as
any to settle up with Carl.
COOPER: Yes, sir.
Thanks, Carl.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Where we going?
Your money's in my truck,
just one aisle over.
Jack, we should get going.
No.
What are you doing?
I thought you said the
money was in the truck.
What the hell's going on?
Just keep moving.
Listen, I don't know what Stokes
told you, but I didn't tell a soul.
Damn it, Jack,
what the hell are you doing?
Don't do it.
You're gonna turn a surveillance
job into a firefight.
It'll be two against ten.
Two against nine.
Right, and we lose our best
chance at getting this weapon.
Don't break your own rules.
You may save one man,
but what about the thousands of people
who could die in a
biological attack?
Is this about you,
Jack, or about them?
You want to prevent another disaster
or ensure that it's going to happen?
That's far enough.
Turn around.
You're going to kill me, you're
going to have to look me in the eye.
Okay.
Damn it.
Thank you, thank you.
We've got about 30 seconds before
they figure out what happened.
Okay, what's our fallback?
Steal the truck. Strong?
I'll make the direct assault,
you cover the east flank.
All we need is a big enough firefight
to get one of us behind the wheel.
You ready? Yeah.
Go.
How do we look?
Diagnostics check out, sir.
The package is stable.
Good.
All right,
let's get her on the chassis!
Cooper, come on.
Let's roll.
Cooper, do you copy?
Dolen.
Check the next aisle over.
Find Cooper.
Hold your position.
Wait for my signal.
Cooper's down, Cooper's down.
Go red, go red!
Let's move out... Greer.
Engage... engage.
Reese, get the truck
out of here now!
Go, go, go!
Tony!
The truck-- I'm going after it.
Cover me now!
Two shooters--
fan out and find them.
??
Tony, this is Jack--
do you copy?
Drop it.
Tony?
I know you.
You're on Emerson's crew.
You're Almeida, right?
I know Bauer's with you.
Now, where is he?
(phone ringing) Larry Moss.
Larry, it's Jack.
Jack, where the hell have you been?
I need you to scramble
multiple teams
to a weigh station on Highway 236,
exit 29.
I'm in a big rig
about ten miles south.
What's going on?
You also need to send
a CDC recovery unit.
Why?
I'm in possession of a biological weapon
interdicted at the Port of Alexandria.
A biological weapon?
Larry, just listen to me.
I don't care if you arrest me.
I don't care if you shoot me.
Just get your teams out here.
I fully expect to be
pursued by hostiles.
Starkwood?
How do you know
about Starkwood?
I talked to Renee.
And I saw what was
on Mayer's computer.
Larry, they're coming
after this weapon.
You can count on it.
Now, be advised, I believe that
Tony Almeida is being held hostage.
All right,
I'll call out an interagency alert.
We'll secure both locations.
Larry, hurry.
Damn it!
Sir, this is Stokes.
What's your status?
The package is secure--
we're inbound.
What about Bauer?
He's at the scene, sir,
but he sought cover nearby.
Well, we have to assume that
he contacted the authorities,
so we better be on an
accelerated timetable.
Get over here.
It will be there
in ten minutes.
We're right behind.
Good.
I've got teams on the ground
prepping for your arrival.
Larry Moss.
Larry, it's Jack.
I'm still on Route 236, but I had
to stop approximately seven miles
before the weigh station.
Jack, I got two units
moving to you right now.
Yeah, well,
you're gonna have to redirect them.
Why?
Starkwood reacquired
the bioweapon.
They managed to access one of
the dock's freight helicopters.
While they had me pinned down, they
airlifted the freight right out of here.
They were headed due west
from my current position.
West... they got a large
military facility in that area.
Okay, good--
redirect the teams there.
Jack, I can't assault a private
compound unless I have proof
that a weapon exists.
Okay, where's the CDC?
They're scrambling
a team right now.
Send them to me.
You'll have all
the proof you need.
Jack, what happened?
One of the canisters was breached
during the interdiction.
Some of the bio-agent
was released.
I...
I was exposed.
Okay.
Jack, just sit right.
CDC's on the way.
They're going to be there soon.
www.tvsubtitles.net