[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
Jack? We need a medic!
Bio-agent is more virulent than we thought.
- All we're doing here
is just masking the symptoms.
- I understand.
- [Macer] There's something
you may want to consider.
- What's that?
Apossible treatment using stem cells
from a genetically compatible donor.
I saw your file. It says you have a daughter.
I don't want my daughter involved in this.
Daddy.
Agent Walker told me that there's a chance-
a small chance that I could help you...
and you don't want me to.
I'm dying, and whatever small chance
there is to stop that from happening...
it is not worth the pain...
for me to let you sit there and watch me die.
Jack, Hodges has 13 Python missiles
armed with the bioweapons.
He demanded that I recall the planes,
or he would launch.
Tony Almeida is still inside Starkwood.
He believes he can gain access to the fuel depot
and lay a series of explosive charges...
and take the missiles out.
- What do you think you're doin'?
- You're gonna take me down to the fuel tanks.
- [Alarm Blaring]
- You're too late. [Grunts]
[Beeps]
Jonas, we've taken out your missiles.
It's over, and you're under arrest.
You can't even begin to imagine
what you're up against.
- What are you talking about?
- You'll find out.
Agent Moss, this is Davis at auxiliary gate six.
I have a Starkwood op in custody.
He was carrying a canister of the bioweapon.
- Are you sure?
- I'm looking at it right now.
One of the Starkwood ops.
He's got a canister of the bioweapon.
So I need you to close down all access roads...
and alert perimeter units and Metro Police.
- Janis, get me D.C. Metro.
- I'm gonna pursue from the air.
Let's go!
Come on!
[Groans]
I'm okay. Tony. Tony!
Oh, God. Tony.
[Muffled Grunting]
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 2:00 a.m. And 3:00 a.m.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Yeah.
- Tricia? Matt. I just got off
the phone with Secret Service.
You're cleared with White House security
at the south entrance.
- How soon do you think you can get there?
- Within the half hour.
- Do you have any more information
why Hodges was arrested?
- They didn't give me a lot.
Apparently, Jonas was in some kind
of a policy meeting with the president...
and things got out of hand.
And that's when he requested
his favorite attorney.
[Chuckles] I'm flattered.
I'll call you after I've spoken to him.
Thanks a lot.
[Gasping]
[Gasping Continues]
Hurry it up.
[Chimes]
[Rapid Beeping]
[Beeps]
Janis. We just got an I.D. On the suspect.
One of Starkwood's security cameras
picked him up leaving the compound.
He was carrying a backpack.
Robert Galvez, two-year Starkwood employee.
Former Special Forces.
Relay that information to Larry.
He needs to know who he's tracking.
I've been trying.
He's not answering his comm.
- How far away is backup?
- They're still a few minutes out.
But Agent Park's teams
have secured a four-block perimeter.
The bioweapons canister
is secured within the cordon.
Get Galvez's picture and description out
to Tactical and distribute department-wide.
- Got it.
- And keep trying Larry.
[Janis On Radio] All units,
I'm uploading a photo of the suspect...
to all agents'P.D.A.'s.
His name is Robert Galvez.
Be advised he has advanced military training,
so proceed with caution.
[Shouts, Screams]
[Groans]
[Cell Phone Ringing]
[Rings]
[Galvez]
Almeida. Almeida, are you there?
Are you in a secure location?
I'm holed up in a storage yard
near the projects on Jefferson.
- I just spotted a patrol.
I think I better keep moving.
- No, don't!
The F.B.I. Has got the entire perimeter
locked down, and they know who you are.
- How?
- They have a picture.
Which means the search teams
can I.D. You on sight.
Just stay put until I can get a read on their
search protocols, and I'll guide you out.
I should have never
let you talk me into helping you.
I promise you, that canister
you stole for me...
is worth a lot of money
to the people I'm working for.
Hell of a lot of good
that money's gonna do me in prison.
Just shut up and do what I tell you to do!
Guard the canister, stay put and wait for my call!
- [Panting]
- [Beeps]
We've got agents down.
Get a med team out here now.
Almeida. Almeida, can you hear me?
What happened? Where's the suspect?
- He ambushed us.
- Did you see where he went?
I don't know.
Renee, I just got confirmation
the tac team has arrived at the scene.
- Do we have a 20 on Larry?
- Not yet.
Excuse me, Agent Walker.
I know you're busy.
- Kim.
- I just came to say good-bye.
- Good-bye? Where are you going?
- Back to L.A.
Uh, I don't understand.
You're not going through
with the treatment to help your father?
- I mean, it's his only chance for a cure.
- I know that, and so does he.
But it's a slim one,
and he believes it's not worth taking.
So if he's gonna die,
he wants it to be on his terms.
Yes, but can't you change his mind?
I would think you'd know by now that no one
can change my father's mind when it's made up.
I'm- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I put you in this position.
No, don't be.
I'm grateful to you, Agent Walker.
My father and I
got to say a lot of things to each other.
I wish I could have said more,
but I don't want to cause him any more pain.
Renee, Agent Park is on the phone for you.
- I need to take this.
- I understand.
Good luck.
- This is Walker.
- It's Park. Agent Moss is dead.
- What?
- Apparently, he was killed
in an ambush by the suspect.
The chopper pilot too.
Tony Almeida's been shot, but he's alive.
I've got medical personnel
working on him now.
Agent Walker?
Do we have any lead on Galvez?
No, but the area's been cordoned off.
Couldn't have gotten far.
We're setting up an operations base here
on the scene to coordinate the manhunt.
- How do you want to proceed?
- Me?
You're the ranking agent in charge now.
Maintain the perimeter.
Begin a south-north sweep.
I'll chopper out a team
and meet you there as soon as I can.
Agent Walker,
I have more than enough personnel.
- You don't need to be involved in the search.
- Yes, I do.
- Keep me posted if you hear anything.
- Yes, ma'am.
- [Beeps]
- Larry?
- He was killed in a shoot-out with the suspect.
- Oh, God.
I need you to brief the White House
on what's happened.
Call Dr. Macer. Have her deploy
a hazmat team to the perimeter line.
Assemble a team to chopper out with me.
I'm so sorry.
Someone's gonna need
to notify Larry's ex-wife.
Probably shouldn't be me.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
- [Panting]
- All right.
We've debriefed on hours 8:00 a.m.
To 3:00 p. M...
pertaining to the C.I.P. Recovery
and capture of Iké Dubaku.
Now- Mr. Bauer,
maybe you'd like to take a break.
No. We need to finish this
while I still can. Let's go.
Now, according to your earlier statement,
it was about this time...
it was this time you received intel regarding
the imminent attack on the White House.
Tony Almeida provided me with the intel...
but we did not know
the White House was the target.
And who was Mr. Almeida's source?
He was interrogating a mercenary.
- Did Almeida give you a name?
- Um-
Yeah. Sorry.
Car- Cardiff.
He said his name was Vincent Cardiff.
Did you, yourself, question this source?
No. He didn't survive Tony's interrogation.
But he was the one who provided us
with the intel on the upcoming attack.
But we did not know that the White House
was the intended target at that time.
- We did not know the White House
was the intended target-
- Mr. Bauer.
You sure you don't
wanna take that break?
I'm repeating myself again. I'm sorry.
[Knocking]
Here's the data files you asked for, sir.
Agent Walker's got our assignments, all right?
- Excuse me.
- [Chattering]
[Renee] We are not gonna lose control
of this situation.
I know that most of you are tired,
working double shifts...
but I need each and every one of you
focused and alert...
if we are gonna locate the suspect and secure
the bioweapon canister that he's carrying.
While I'm out in the field,
you will pass all pertinent information...
out of this office through Janis.
Let's get to work.
Adams, you and your men are with me.
- Renee. Renee.
- I'll meet you at the helipad.
- The bioweapon's still out there?
- We have it contained.
Wait a second. Wait a second!
Just tell me what the hell is going on.
A Starkwood operative by the name of Robert
Galvez got away with a canister of the pathogen.
We have him trapped inside a perimeter
a mile or so from Starkwood's compound.
- Is Larry in command of the perimeter?
- He was killed in a firefight.
- What?
- Tony was injured. He's at the scene
with the advance team.
- Larry's dead?
- We have two agents down, yes. I have to go.
You're lucky. An inch to the left,
the bullet might have nicked the splenic artery.
- You need to get yourself checked out
at the hospital, sir.
- I can't do that right now.
- [Groans]
- Let me get you something for the pain.
No. I need to keep my head clear.
Sweep Nine, this is Mobile Command.
What's your status?
[Man On Radio]
Mobile Command, this is Sweep Nine.
Southeast grid 211 clear.
Moving on.
[Park]
Copy that, Sweep Nine.
- Sweep Seven, what's your position?
- Clearing 214. Nothing so far.
- No sign of him?
- Don't worry. We'll find him.
You should get some rest.
Thanks.
[Rapid Beeping]
- [Line Ringing]
- [Galvez] Yeah.
They're sweeping north, clearing grids.
You got a clear path on Jefferson,
all the way up to 12th and 13th Street.
That should be the last sector
they're searching.
Judging by their progress,
it'll give you about 30 minutes.
- Should be plenty of time.
- Time for what?
- You still got that C-4 I gave you?
- Yeah. I got it.
All right. I want you to find a structure.
A store or warehouse- something big enough
where they have to enter and search.
We need to draw as many of them into
the building as possible... and then blow it.
- You want me to blow up
a couple of dozen F.B.I. Agents?
- You got a problem with that?
They're still gonna have
the perimeter locked down.
- I don't see how this is gonna
get me out with the canister.
- Yeah. I got that worked out.
Ready to go when you're ready.
Watch your step.
- Jack, what the hell are you doing?
- I'm going with you.
- You're ill.
- If my condition interferes with your operation...
- I will stand down, I give you my word.
- Jack.
You want to keep arguing about this,
waste more time, fine. I'm not getting out.
[Beeping]
Ma'am.
- Good morning.
- [Radio Chatter]
- Ms. Eames. You'reJonas Hodges's attorney.
That's right.
They told us to expect you. I just need you
to place your thumb against the glass.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Beeps]
Okay. Sergeant Cadden
will escort you to the holding area.
- Thank you.
- [Door Opens]
How could this man have gotten out of Starkwood
with a canister of the bioweapon?
No one's sure,
but he's already murdered four people...
including Larry Moss.
The F.B.I. Has tracked him
to a nearby residential district.
They've sealed off the area
and are conducting a thorough search.
Mom, this man Galvez is a Starkwood
operative. Clearly, Hodges is behind this.
- Maybe.
- What do you mean, "maybe"?
As Hodges was taken away,
he said it wasn't over.
He alluded to others.
Called himself a small cog in a very large
machine that I wouldn't be able to stop.
- He was ranting.
- That doesn't mean he wasn't telling the truth.
We need to find out
what Hodges knows about this.
I want him taken to the F.B.I.
For interrogation.
He's a sociopath, Mom.
He's not going to talk.
He's going to want to make some kind of deal
in exchange for his cooperation.
- Mom, you're not considering that.
- Olivia-
You know what this man is,
what he did to Roger.
Just get him to F.B.I.
[Buzzer Sounds]
Mr. Hodges,
your attorney's here to see you.
Well, it's about damn time.
[Clears Throat]
We're going to need some privacy.
You're a little taller than her,
but it's a good look for you.
- Hello, Jonas.
- I'm not gonna ask how you got in.
But I'm definitely interested
in how you're gonna get me out.
Jonas, you're in a very difficult position...
and your actions today have put everyone else
in a very difficult position.
Oh, I see. I've upset the cart, have I?
Everyone's bent out of shape.
Where the hell were they when
the government came after my company...
when Senator Mayer
and his subpoena-waving goon squad...
were trying to ruin me
and everything I built?
You would have been protected, Jonas.
You and Starkwood.
But you jeopardized the plan.
That bioweapon that you developed for us
was not intended for personal use.
The consensus is
that you've had some sort of...
psychotic break.
Well, the consensus is wrong.
Coming from you right now,
that's not much comfort.
I wanna talk to them.
Get some form of communication between us.
I think it's a little late for that, Jonas.
You've brought undue attention
by showing your hand, exposing yourself.
And I'm sure
you could understand their concern...
that you may, in fact,
expose the others as well.
- How can I do that? I don't know who they are.
- You know enough.
And they need to be certain.
I think we can agree that there's no reason...
for your family to pay for your... mistakes.
Is that why you're here?
To threaten my family?
On the contrary...
I came to guarantee your family's safety-
if you do the right thing.
It'll induce a cardiac arrest
and leave no trace in your system.
A natural, dignified death.
Without you to prosecute, the case against you
and your company will be difficult...
likely impossible...
preserving at least some small part
of Starkwood's legacy...
of patriotic service.
Which I know is very important to you.
[Buzzer Sounds]
Party's over, counselor.
We're moving him to the Bureau.
My client has invoked
his right to silence and to counsel.
No one speaks to him unless in my presence.
Is that understood?
In some countries,
they'd have shot him by now.
- Process him out.
- Yes, ma'am.
Step outside, sir.
- Hands.
- [Handcuffs Clicking]
[Rapid Beeping]
- [Ringing]
- Yes.
- I met with him.
- And?
I'm quite certain
he understands our terms.
- They're transferring him
to the F.B.I. For interrogation.
- Will that be a problem?
Hopefully it'll just pressure him to resolve
the situation sooner rather than later.
I'll be happy when this is behind us.
Have you heard from Almeida?
- He called in before I met with Hodges.
- Mm-hmm.
- Has he secured the canister?
- Soon.
He's your guy.
He better not screw this up.
Tony's been the one bright spot
in an otherwise dreary day.
I have faith he'll come through.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- Yeah.
I found a place to set up.
It's an abandoned apartment building
just shy of the north perimeter line.
1297 Rincon, corner of 12th.
Yeah, I see it.
Sweep teams are just entering
three sectors to the south.
- You got less than 20 minutes.
- That doesn't give me much time.
No, it doesn't. Maybe you should get off
the phone and get to it.
[Phone Beeps]
I lost two partners in a row.
Early on.
I couldn't handle it.
I guess that's why, over the last 10 years,
I've pretty much worked alone.
It's all right for you to be feeling
what you're feeling.
But if you can't do this tonight,
that's all right too.
Just don't try to pretend
like you're not feeling anything.
- That's how you make a mistake.
- Please, Jack.
Don't tell me what to feel
and don't tell me how to feel it.
Come on! Let's go!
Right over there.
- Jack!
- Where is he?
- Around the S.U.V.
- You okay?
Yeah, I got lucky.
The bullet went right straight through.
- I didn't think I'd see you out here.
- I'm only here for observation.
You do not have to do this.
Show me.
Cover him up.
I'm sorry about Larry.
- How the hell did this happen?
- It all went down pretty fast. I mean-
We were ambushed
before we got out of the helicopter.
The chopper pilot was hit first...
and I was unarmed,
so Larry laid down cover so I could get clear.
I don't remember a lot,
but I definitely heard auto fire.
Once I was tagged, Larry came over
to help me out, and that's when he was hit.
I blacked out after that,
but I'm pretty sure Larry saved my life.
Larry was hit with heavy ordnance-
shotgun rounds, armor-piercing.
You obviously were hit
with something smaller-jacketed.
I treated Mr. A lmeida. His wound
was consistent with a nine-millimeter.
- You sure it wasn't a.45?
- Not likely. The entry was too small. Why?
Because you have
spent.45 casings in evidence.
Galvez had access to the weapons inside
the F.B.I. Vehicle he stole.
He probably switched
in the middle of the fight.
That many weapons? In the time frame
that you described the ambush?
- Doesn't add up.
- Okay. So what are you saying?
Someone was with him.
Like I said, it all happened pretty fast, but-
I mean, I didn't think so.
I guess it makes sense.
One man didn't do this alone. He had help.
I'll tell Park to alert the field.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Good.
[Beeping]
[Cell Phone Rings]
- Hello.
- Did I wake you?
No. Who could sleep
after what happened today?
How'd it go with your father?
- [Sniffling]
- Sweetheart?
What is it? What happened?
- He's dying, Stephen.
- What?
He was exposed to something,
like a biological agent.
It had something to do with the attacks
that took place earlier today.
Kim, honey, I'm so sorry.
Um, isn't there anything that they can do?
No.
- I'm coming back home.
- Don't you wanna stay?
Don't you wanna be with him
as long as you can?
My presence, with what he's going through
right now, will only make things worse.
- Did you at least, uh-
- [Coos]
Did you tell him about his granddaughter?
Hi, honey.
- [Sighs]
- Kim.
I couldn't, Stephen.
I couldn't bring myself to tell him
I wasn't the only person he was leaving behind.
Telling him about Teri
would have only made it worse.
I'm gonna try and get on the 6:10.
- If I do, I'll be back in L.A. By 9:00.
- Okay.
You can always leave later,
if you change your mind.
I won't.
I love you both.
We love you too. Bye.
[Beeps]
[Man On Radio] Mobile Command,
this is Sweep Nine. 221 is clear.
- Copy, Nine. Proceed to 224.
- Copy that.
Why has that area of the grid
not been cleared?
Sweep Three, why have you
not cleared 219?
Mobile Command, we're encountering some
resistance from the neighborhood residents.
They're not happy about their homes being
searched without a warrant at 2:30 in the morning.
I'm concerned about their safety,
not their happiness.
Whoever was helping Galvez may be
providing him shelter in one of those houses.
If those civilians are interfering
in that sweep, arrest them.
- But get that area cleared. Do you understand?
- Copy that.
- Jack.
- Excuse me.
[Man]
Westbound is his point.
[Gasping]
[Grunting]
It's my anti-seizure medicine.
I should have used it earlier.
Jack, what are you doing out here?
Why don't you go back to F.B.I. Medical
and let them treat you?
- There is no treatment. There's no cure.
- Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Yeah.
Why are you in the field?
Agent Walker just lost her partner, Tony.
Thought I could help.
I owe her that much.
Agent Stoller to Mobile Command.
Code yellow.
Go ahead, Agent Stoller. This is Mobile
Command. Are you reporting a code yellow?
Affirmative. I have a confirmed visual
on the target suspect with the canister.
- [Static]
- Repeat: Confirmed visual of suspect and canister.
Agent Park, may I?
Agent Stoller, this is Jack Bauer.
Is Galvez with someone? Agent Stoller?
[Galvez]
Negative. He's alone.
Repeat. He is alone.
- Copy that.
- [Renee] What's his 20?
Entering an abandoned apartment building
on the south side of Rincon and 12th.
- I am in pursuit.
- Try to maintain a visual and wait for backup.
- Do not engage until we get there.
- Copy that.
[Park On Radio] All primary units
respond to 12th and Rincon.
Suspect sighted
entering building with canister.
- Code yellow.
- [Renee] Agent Park.
I want a secure net around the building.
Agents at all exits.
- I want sharpshooters
covering all four exposures.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Jack.
- [Engine Starts]
I can't.
It's all right. I'll be fine.
I'll stay back. I'll watch operations.
You be careful out there.
I still think Galvez has a partner.
You watch your back.
[Siren Wailing]
[Beeping]
Thank you.
[Man]
All right. Let's go.
Hellfire.
You served with the 27 th in Pakistan.
Two tours, sir.
Did you, by any chance,
encounter any Starkwood units?
- [Grunts]
- There was a force protection team
attached by my C.O.
- They fought with you.
- Yes, sir. Side by side.
Soldier.
How would you rate their professionalism,
their performance under fire?
They were good men, sir. Well trained.
Thank you, son. You just made my day.
[Engine Starts]
Let's go.
Our orders are to deliver the prisoner
to the rear entrance at F.B.I.
White House wants to keep this low-key.
[Grunts]
[Gasping]
Sarge.
This is Sergeant Cadden!
Prisoner's in severe cardiac
and respiratory distress!
We are rerouting
to West Arlington Hospital.
Need emergency medical team standing by!
Go, go!
[Sirens Wailing]
[Siren Stops]
- Assemble the teams.
- Got it.
Agent Stoller, this is Agent Walker.
Do you copy?
- I copy you, Agent Walker.
- What is your position?
East of stairwell,
between the first and second floor.
Suspect with canister
has moved to the top floor.
- Do you have any indication that he's not alone?
- Negative. Not at this time.
All right. Stand by. We're coming to you.
Agent Stoller puts the suspect
somewhere on the second floor.
However, there's no guarantee
that he's the only hostile in the building.
Therefore, we stick to S.O.P.
Clearing room by room.
Agent Park and I will lead two teams, east
and west. Check your weapons and headsets.
- We move in 60 seconds.
- [Park] You guys are with me.
You guys are with Agent Walker.
- Mobile Command. This is Walker.
- Go ahead, Agent Walker.
We're about to enter the building.
Have hazmat teams on alert
in case the canister gets breached.
- How you holdin' up?
- Better, thanks.
- [Man #1] Move!
- [Man #2] Go!
[Man]
We're movin'in!
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- Excuse me.
- This is Bauer.
- Mr. Bauer, this is Agent Mizelli.
Sorry to bother you with this, but I need to
follow up on something from our debrief.
- Agent, this isn't a good time.
- Some new information has come to light...
- and I need to clear up a discrepancy.
- What discrepancy?
You told me Tony Almeida's source
on the White House attack...
- was a man identified to you as Vincent Cardiff.
- Yeah, that's right.
Is there a possibility
you misremembered the name?
- No, I don't think so.
- Are you sure?
You, yourself, had voiced some concern
about your own acuity.
Hold on. What is this here?
Agent Mizelli,
I'm gonna have to get back to you.
- Locator codes for all units'radio transponders.
- Are they in real time?
- Yes, sir.
- Can you do a map overlay?
- It'll take a minute.
- Get it done.
- What's going on, Jack?
- I'm not sure yet.
[Chattering]
- [Door Crashes]
- Second level.
Clear.
- [Beeping]
- We can go through it.
Let's see the next room.
Bring it back.
Clear. Heading to the third floor.
To the third level.
[Rapid Beeping]
Here's the all clear!
Let's go! Let's go!
[Beeping]
Right there. There's Stoller's transponder.
He's not even in the building.
Agent Walker, this is Jack.
Get your men out of the building.
- It's a trap.
- Jack, what?
Stoller's not even in there.
Get your men out now!
- Code blue! Repeat, code blue!
- [Phone Beeps]
- Cold blue! Move 'em out!
- Move, move!
[Screaming]
Keep back!
Agent Walker! Agent Park!
Get us a vehicle. Now!
All perimeter teams, this is Park. Agents
are down at corner of 12th and Rincon.
- We need assistance.
- Negative, negative. Disregard that order.
Maintain your positions.
I repeat, maintain your positions.
- What the hell are you doin'?
- They are trying to pull you off the line.
You leave a hole in that perimeter,
we are gonna lose the canister.
Tell your men to stand fast. Medevac
is on its way. Get them in the air now!
[Beeping]
- [Chattering, Shouting]
- I got you.
Set up a triage!
[Man Shouting]
Up, up.
[Siren Wailing]
Jack, I'm goin' in!
Agent Park! Agent Park!
- How many men are unaccounted for?
- Still assessing.
There were at least 30 of us
in the building when it went up.
- And Agent Walker?
- I don't know.
Renee, this is Jack. Do you copy?
[Men Shouting]
Almeida.
- You have the canister?
- Yeah.
Let me see.
Hurry up. We need to get moving.
Renee!
- Renee!
- Jack!
Jack!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. But he's not breathing.
We need a medic!
They've got him. I want to get you out of here.
Come on. Let's go now!
- How'd you know it was a trap?
- Stoller's transponder was outside of the building.
They were trying to thin our ranks,
create a diversion.
- Has the cordon been breached?
- No. I told the men to maintain their positions.
- The perimeter's secure.
- It's almost like they knew, Jack.
They would've needed time
to wire this building with explosives.
This is the last sector
we were due to search.
- You think they knew your sweep patterns?
- They must have.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it, Jack?
I'll meet you back at your vehicle.
- Hey, you want me to take him?
- No, I got him. They need your help inside.
- [On Phone] Agent Mizelli.
- This is Bauer.
You said you wanted to talk to me
about Tony's suspect, Vincent Cardiff?
Yes, yes. Thanks for gettin' back to me.
Listen, you told me that he expired during
the course ofTony Almeida's interrogation?
- Yeah, that's what Tony told me.
- Well, it can't be him.
What are you talking about?
Vincent Cardiff was picked up
over an hour ago by Customs...
- trying to cross the border into Canada.
- Are you sure?
Look, I'm positive. I've got his
arrest report right here. Cardiff's alive.
Were there any signs from his interrogation?
Physical violence, abuse.
- Anything at all.
- Nothing's indicated on the report.
That's why I was asking if maybe you had
mistaken the name that Almeida gave you.
- Okay. I got him.
- Thanks.
Tony!
- Tony!
- Yeah?
[Siren Wailing]
- We need to talk.
- Sure.
[Tony]
What's goin' on?
I told you earlier today,
if you were lying to me, I'd kill you myself.
What the hell you talkin' about?
Cardiff. Vincent Cardiff! You said
he was killed during his interrogation.
- Yeah. So?
- He's alive and well, in custody.
And he's showing no signs of physical abuse.
Explain that.
All right, look, Jack. I'm sorry.
Cardiff knew that by spilling that intel,
he was gonna get himself killed.
So I cut a deal with him.
I told him I'd let the F.B.I. Think he was dead
so he could walk away and disappear.
I thought it was just a meaningless lie.
You and I have been doing this
long enough to know...
that there is no such thing
as a meaningless lie.
- How are you involved in this?
- You're not making any sense, Jack.
That intel was good.
Without it, you'd have never been
in the White House to save the president.
What is your involvement?
- You're not thinkin' straight.
- How were you shot?
Does Galvez even have a second man,
or was itjust you?
Just stop and listen to what you're sayin'.
It's insane.
It's paranoia.
Now, why don't you put the gun down?
Don't you move!
The toxin's starting to affect your judgment.
That's what's happening.
You can see that, right?
[Grunting]
Is this what you're lookin' for?
I never wanted to hurt you, Jack.
I told you to stay out of it,
but you wouldn't listen, would you?
Can we get some help here?
This man's havin' a seizure.
Stand back, please.
Go get my bag, and call Dr. Macer, stat.
You're gonna be all right, sir.
Just try to breathe.
Relax. It's gonna be okay.
[Chattering]
[Siren Blares, Wailing]
I don't see anything.
The wound must be posterior.
Sir, I need to turn you on your side.
Put it down. Keep driving. Now!
[Beeping]
[Crickets Chirping]
www.tvsubtitles.net