[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
- No!
- Sir, it's Senator Mayer.
He's dead.
Are you telling me thatJack Bauer
just killed a United States senator?
How could you have let this happen?
Mr. Kanin, you are not gonna
lay this one at my feet.
What is it, Ethan? What's wrong?
Madam President, I'm afraid I have no choice
but to resign as your chief of staff
You're taking this too far.
Where's Jack?
[Larry]
We don't have him.
The man who framed Jack
for Burnett's murder...
was John Quinn, a Starkwood contractor.
Jack went to Mayer
to get the evidence to prove it.
Starkwood was involved
with everything that's happened today.
They helped Juma and his men bring down
those planes and attack the White House.
In exchange, they were allowed
to develop and manufacture a W.M.D. In Sangala.
The text message I got
off their agent's cell phone...
said " Port of Alexandria,
Lot C, 10:15 p.m."
- Go red! Go red!
- Engage. Engage!
- [Stokes] Get that truck outta here, now!
- Tony! The truck-
I'm going after it! Cover me now!
I'm in possession of a biological weapon
interdicted at the Port of Alexandria.
[Beeping]
[Hissing]
[Machine Gun Fire]
What's your status?
The package is secure. We're inbound.
- What about Bauer?
- He's at the scene, sir, but he sought cover nearby.
We have to assume that
he contacted the authorities...
so we better be on
an accelerated timetable.
- Get over here.
- Starkwood reacquired the bioweapon.
They airlifted the freight right outta here. They
were headed due west from my current position.
Jack, I can't assault a private compound
unless I have proof that a weapon exists.
- Where's the C.D.C.
- They're scrambling a team right now.
Send 'em to me.
You'll have all the proof you need.
- Jack, what happened?
- I was exposed.
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 11:00 p.m. And 12:00 a.m.
[Helicopter Passes Overhead]
We're ready for, you, sir.
Come with me.
[Sirens Wailing]
Mr. Bauer, Dr. Macer, C.D.C.
We need you to get undressed.
You're the one that talked
to Agent Moss?
He brought me up to speed. Said you had
some information about the bioweapon.
All I know is that
it was developed in Sangala.
According to rumors from the village
that it was tested on...
all the victims suffered
from dementia and paralysis.
Check neurological vectors and pathogens.
How much was released?
I'm not exactly sure.
The weapon was stored
in a pressurized canister.
It was breached for maybe two minutes
before I could seal it off.
This is not a reaction.
I've had these scars.
This is a full-spectrum antibiotic. It should
counteract a wide range of known pathogens.
[Injector Hisses]
[Man]
Step inside, sir.
Raise your arms, close your eyes.
- Janis, where are we?
- Metro closed down a six-mile
stretch of Highway 236.
The C.D.C. First responders are on site.
What the hell's going on?
One of the bioweapon
canisters was breached.
- Jack may have been exposed.
- Oh, my God.
Starkwood took the canisters.
They're probably flying 'em
back to their main compound in Virginia...
- along with Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
He was working with Jack. We think he might
have been taken captive. Hang on one second.
I need you to put together
a briefing packet on Starkwood.
I want every division caught up to speed
on what we might be dealing with.
Planning to move on Starkwood? That place
is enormous. It's practically a military base.
We're not gonna do anything until we have
concrete evidence on the bioweapon from C.D.C.
Then I'll inform the president,
and she'll decide how to proceed.
[Man Shouting]
Wait till I say!
Easy! Easy!
Almeida's not going to talk.
He's not the type.
He's the brave type.
"Know the psychology of your subject."
That's in our manual.
Here we go.
Mr. Hodges.
We isolated the damaged canister.
We got lucky.
They know we have the weapons.
That's not so lucky.
How fast can you have them ready?
- It's gonna take me at least two hours.
- Too long, Tom.
- Sir, we don't know what the government knows.
- They're coming.
And they'll be coming
with everything they've got.
And the only thing that's gonna stop them
is getting these weapons ready to deploy.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
I know you will.
[Whistles]
Okay, let's go!
- [Shouts]
- [Groans]
What does the F.B.I. Know?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
- [Shouts]
- [Coughing]
[Hodges]
Okay.
You're a good man, Tony.
I know your profile.
You've had some hard breaks.
I don't want to see you hurt.
So you just tell me what the F.B.I. Knows...
about what we're doin' here.
And I can't say
you'll walk away smiling.
That would be unrealistic.
But you'll be alive.
You hear me?
But I don't know anything, Mr. Hodges.
I'm giving you a way out, Tony.
Sir. May I speak to you for a moment?
- Not now, Greg.
- Please, sir. Just for a moment.
[Exhales]
What is it?
This was supposed to be a covert operation.
That is not the case anymore.
The government knows
that we have these weapons...
and they're not just gonna
sit on that information.
What are you suggesting, Greg?
Maybe we should destroy the evidence
while we still have some time.
I can't believe that
I'm hearing this from you.
I'm just trying to help, sir. I care about
this company as much as you do.
Oh, I doubt that.
We've invested a lot of blood
and treasure to get these weapons...
and I'm not gonna give them up.
Think about what you're
risking, sir- everything.
Everything you built.
You say you're trying to help.
You know what I think?
I think you're worried about your own ass.
Get him out of here and do what you have to do.
Think about what I said, young man.
You're a little nervous, Greg.
We'll, I've got a news flash. We're all nervous.
Keep your doubts to yourself.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
We're gonna need more blood and saliva samples,
and I'd like to collect a spinal fluid specimen.
Until we know what we're dealing with,
we need to keep you under quarantine.
How long till you know whether
or not I've been infected?
We should have the preliminary results
in the next 15 minutes.
- Okay.
- Dr. Macer.
- Yeah?
- We've detected trace amounts
of an airborne pathogen.
It's concentrated near the truck.
We're also picking it up from the surrounding
environments in much lower concentrations.
- Can you identify it?
- No. But we're analyzing a sample now.
These levels shouldn't present any danger
to the nearby population...
but I still want
atmospheric monitors set up.
It's a good thing you sealed off the canister,
Mr. Bauer. You saved a lot of lives.
You're gonna have
to transport me back to F.B.I.
I'm still material evidence
in an ongoing terrorist threat.
- Those were our orders.
We can run our tests from there.
- Okay.
BobJustman's been associate counsel
for the past three years.
He and Ethan worked
very closely together.
He's certainly qualified
to be chief of staff.
But?
After what's happened today, I think you
should be looking outside your administration.
An insider has a leg up.
Chief of staff has a steep learning curve.
I think you're underestimating
the value of a fresh perspective.
You have someone in mind.
I do. Rick Berman.
Would Rick even consider
leaving the private sector?
He's made his fortune. I think he'd jump
at the chance to serve his country.
- Let's sit down with him.
- Great.
But keep Bob on the list.
I still have a good feeling about him.
I'll start to set up meetings tomorrow.
Livy, it could take weeks
to find Ethan's replacement.
In the meantime, I'm going to
need a provisional chief of staff.
I'd like that to be you.
- Um-
- [Intercom Beeps]
- [Woman] Madam President?
- Yes?
Tim Woods is here to see you.
- Just give me a minute, please,
and then send him in.
- Yes, ma'am.
Livy, I need someone I can trust...
especially after everything
that's happened today.
You're not going to say no
to your mother, are you?
Of- Of course not.
- Good.
- [Knocking]
Madam President,
I have Larry Moss at F.B.I. Calling for you.
- What's this about?
- I don't know the specifics...
but he says it involves
an imminent homeland threat.
Put him through.
It's all right, Tim.
I've made Olivia acting chief of staff.
Agent Moss, you're on with the president.
Madam President,
we have a situation developing.
First of all, you need
to know thatJack Bauer...
did not kill Ryan Burnett
nor Senator Blaine Mayer.
- He was framed for their murders.
- I knew it. Who framed him?
Our operational theory is that
he was set up by Starkwood.
I don't understand.
Why would Starkwood frameJack?
To cover up the fact that they helped
Juma stage the terrorist attacks today.
- What?
- Ma'am, we have evidence
that Starkwood provided Juma...
with technological support
and intelligence.
In return, Juma allowed Starkwood
to use Sangala...
as a base to operate without having
to worry about any oversight.
- A base for what?
- To manufacture weapons of mass destruction.
Specifically, biological weapons.
What kind of bioweapons
are you talking about?
We're not sure, but it could be
some kind of neurological pathogen.
C.D.C. Obtained a sample.
They're analyzing it now.
Agent Moss, you said there
was an imminent threat?
Yes. A large shipment of bioweapons
was delivered to Starkwood.
We believe they're
in possession of them now.
Are you saying these weapons
are on U.S. Soil?
We suspect they're at the Starkwood
headquarters in Virginia.
You're not suggesting Starkwood intends to use
those weapons to attack this country?
We don't know.
But given their actions today...
we need to move on
Starkwood immediately.
Madam President?
Assemble the cabinet
and theJoint Chiefs.
Yes, ma'am.
[Beeping]
Jack was right about Starkwood.
You find evidence that
they've been supporting Juma?
Yeah.
Did you find out why?
What could Starkwood possibly get from Juma?
The infrastructure to develop
and test biological weapons.
We think they're holding 'em somewhere
on the Starkwood compound.
Okay. Where's Jack?
He's... on his way over here.
What, Larry? Larry?
He managed to secure the weapons...
but then, uh, Starkwood got 'em back.
And when that happened, um...
Jack was exposed.
He may have been infected.
He's being placed under quarantine.
Listen, he's on his way here,
and we need to find out...
everything that he learned
about these weapons...
and I think you should be
the one who debriefs him.
And I owe you an apology.
I was wrong not to trust you.
L-I let my prejudice
about Bauer get in the way.
But, Renee, you should have
kept me in the loop.
You should have trusted me.
I know.
I should have.
When are we moving on Starkwood?
Aaron. Uh-
I'll check in with you guys later, okay?
Thank you.
- May I speak with you for a moment?
- Of course.
I heard you finished your debrief
and were on your way out.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Well, I need you to stay.
- Ma'am?
- I've been appointed acting chief of staff.
The Secret Service is going to assign
an agent to handle my security detail.
I'd like that to be you.
Well, I'm truly flattered, ma'am,
but as you know, I'm retired.
I can have you reinstated.
There are plenty of fine agents
on the roster.
But I don't want them. I want you.
I can't go into the details now,
but the threat to this country isn't over.
We're in the middle of a crisis,
and I need people around me I can trust.
[Sighs]
I trust you, Aaron.
I can't say that
about a lot of people.
I'm running into a meeting
with the president.
I'll assume your answer is yes.
[Chattering]
- Gentlemen, ladies, please take your seats.
- Yes, ma'am.
Here's the packet.
Now those of you who haven't had a chance to
finish your briefing packets, please keep reading.
As we've all just learned,
this day is not over.
Our national security
is still being threatened...
and we are here
to consider our options.
Mr. Woods.
Your briefing materials
include F.B.I. Intelligence...
about a cache of biological weapons
on Starkwood's main compound
in Northern Virginia.
This is a recent satellite
view of the compound.
Over three square miles, 259 structures.
The weapons could be hidden
anywhere on the facility.
What kind ofbioweapons
are we talking about?
This is Ben Landry.
He's director of C.D.C.
He's here to answer any questions you
may have in regards to the pathogen. Ben?
I've just received a preliminary report
from our agents in the field.
They've identified the pathogen as
a prion variant indigenous to the East Congo.
It's a form of Creutzfeldt-Jacob disease.
It attacks the brain and the nervous system...
causes dementia, physical deterioration...
ultimately death.
Now, standard C.J.D. Kills within several months,
but this strain kills more quickly.
- How long?
- A day. Maybe two.
There's no treatment
for this disease. There's no cure.
If dispersed over a populated area,
the results would be catastrophic.
But it goes without saying we cannot allow
a private military force, these killers...
to possess weapons
of mass destruction.
We need to find these weapons
and arrest those bastards in Starkwood...
who are responsible
for bringing 'em here.
Uh, Madam President.
Given the size of the compound, it would take
a considerable force to locate these weapons.
Not to mention the fact that there are
1,500 highly trained mercenaries on that base.
God forbid they decide to resist.
We could have a small war
in our own backyard.
I share those concerns, Madam President.
We also have to consider...
the possibility that Starkwood might use
these biological weapons against our own forces.
What about an air strike?
A facility that large would
require multiple bombing runs.
We'd be looking at massive casualties
on the Starkwood base...
with no guarantee
of destroying the bioweapons.
For all we know, they've been buried
underground or in fortified facilities.
There's also a risk
that hitting these weapons...
with insufficient force could release
the bio-agent into the atmosphere.
We can'tjust ignore the law here.
All these scenarios...
would be in violation
of the Posse Comitatus Act.
I mean, we can't deploy military personnel
in a law enforcement capacity...
not without congressional approval.
Now, what I'm hearing
is that there are no good options.
I don't accept that.
Until we find a way
to contain this threat...
we are risking another attack
on this country...
and that is an option
I won't consider.
[Door Clatters]
Mr. Hodges wants to know
if you've given any thought to his offer.
[Clicks Tongue]
Why this loyalty to a government
that screwed you over?
I don't get it. Just tell us what
the F.B.I. Knows, and you can walk.
For the record, I bet Mr. Hodges
a pair of Redskin tickets...
you wouldn't talk.
Looks like I'm gonna be
sitting on the 50-yard line.
[Silenced Gunshots]
Hey.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
- I need your help.
- My help?
We need to stop this. It's gone too far.
Look, I'm not goin' anywhere
till you tell me why you're doin' this.
[Handcuffs Clicking]
I'm not spending the rest of my life in prison
becauseJonas Hodges has lost his mind.
- You know where the weapons are?
- Yes.
- Then you better tell me right now.
- I want immunity.
I can't promise you anything.
We can call the F.B.I.
And negotiate a deal.
Immunity in exchange for your help in recovering
the weapons. That's the best I can do.
I can set up a secure landline in my office.
Okay. Let's go.
[Sirens Wailing]
We're pulling up to F.B.I.
We have to put you in an isolation suit
to transfer you to the quarantine area.
- I understand.
- How are you feeling?
No different.
- We have the results of Mr. Bauer's blood work.
- Thank you.
Open it.
[Exhales]
Thank you.
[Beeping]
Excuse me. Larry wanted me to tell you
that C.D.C. Arrived with Jack Bauer.
- I'll meet them down in quarantine.
- He's not in quarantine.
- I don't understand.
- That's all I know.
They just cleared security.
He's on his way up.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
[Elevator Doors Open]
Jack. Are you okay?
My blood work came in positive.
I'm infected.
[Man] Mr. Bauer,
there's a room for you to change in.
Thank you.
It's fine.
But he's not in quarantine.
We've learned the disease isn't contagious.
It was engineered that way to prevent
blowback on the people deploying it.
Okay, but there has to be something
that you can do to help him.
There's no cure.
But he's patient zero.
Whatever we learn from the pathogen
will come from the tests we still need to run.
[Cell Phone Rings]
Excuse me.
- [Cell Phone Beeps]
- This is Macer.
He's stable for the moment.
- [Knocking]
- Yeah?
Jack, um-
I don't know what to say.
You can tell me that Agent Moss
followed up on Starkwood.
Sorry.
Larry debriefed the White House...
and we're waiting on the president
to decide on a course of action.
Good. Any word on Tony?
Sorry. We don't know anything yet.
I need to debrief you
on the canisters that you saw.
- You okay with that?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I've read the statement
from the port authority cop.
He said that you risked the mission
to save his life.
You did the right thing.
Thanks.
[Door Closes]
[Men Chattering]
[Beeping]
[Phone Ringing]
Uh, it's the lab.
It's probably Hodges.
I should talk to him.
Put it on speaker.
Seaton.
Where the hell have you been?
I've been trying to reach you.
I was, uh, checking on Almeida.
- Did Stokes get him to talk?
- He's still working on that, sir.
I told him to put Almeida down
if he didn't start talking.
I think we should give him
a few more minutes, sir.
We're busting our asses to get these weapons
ready before the government makes their move.
I want all hands on deck.
- We'll be there soon, sir.
- See that you are, Greg.
Call F.B.I.
I need to set up the secure landline,
make sure nobody's listening.
- All right. Well, do it.
- [Keyboard Clacking]
I never thoughtJonas
would take it this far.
I mean, the man's a patriot.
He founded Starkwood
to protect this country.
Yeah? Well, why's he attacking it?
It's complicated.
I don't understand it myself.
I should have done more to stop this.
I should have called
F.B.I. Months ago.
Well, you're doin' the right thing now.
I pulled together everything
we have on Starkwood.
Structural specs, aerial maps, topography,
company rosters- the whole works.
All right. Upload it onto
the interagency servers.
Let's get everybody on the same page.
That's good work, Janis. Renee.
I heard aboutJack. I'm sorry.
I'm still debriefing him, but I brought
a full description of the canisters.
Good.
Get this out to the field agents.
How's he doin'?
Hard to tell.
Larry, so many people have died today.
We cannot let their deaths be for nothing.
- We won't.
- Larry?
I've got Tony Almeida on the phone.
- Almeida?
- He says he's calling from inside Starkwood.
Put him through. Go ahead, Tony.
- Who am I talking to?
- It's Larry Moss. What's going on?
I'm on the Starkwood compound.
I was being held by a man named Jonas Hodges...
but I was released by one of his executives-
a man named Greg Seaton.
He wants to cut a deal.
He wants immunity.
- What's he offering in return?
- He knows where the weapons are being held.
All right, Tony, I gotta run this by the president.
Wait, Larry. Do you know what happened toJack?
He's here. He's in medical.
- Was he hit?
- No. One of the canisters was breached.
He's been infected.
Tony, I gotta call the White House.
Stand by. Janis, set up a secure connection
in the conference room...
with Almeida
and the White House for signature.
And get me the president on the phone.
[Beeping]
[No Audio]
- [Olivia] What is this?
- Footage recovered from Sangala.
It was smuggled out of the remains
of a biological weapons lab...
about 45 minutes ago.
It's a confirmation
thatJuma was experimenting...
with biological weapons
on the local population.
These poor people were suffering from
the effects of the weaponized prion variant.
And that's what we allowed Starkwood
to bring into this country.
We didn't allow this.
Starkwood is a monster we created, Olivia.
We have been feeding it for years.
We gave them military contracts.
We relied on their paid mercenaries
instead of our own soldiers...
outsourced intelligence
gathering operations.
My God, we even passed a law so
that they could build a military base...
13 miles from the nation's capital.
You fought against all that.
You've been trying to limit Starkwood's power
ever since you took office.
I didn't do enough... fast enough.
- And now it may be too late.
- [Intercom Beeps]
[Woman On Speaker] Madam President,
Tim Woods and Admiral Smith are here to see you.
- Send them in.
- Yes, ma'am.
Madam President, Larry Moss at F.B.I.
Is calling in. He says it's urgent.
- Put him through.
- Agent Moss, the president's here. Go ahead.
Madam President, we've been contacted
by someone inside Starkwood.
- Ma'am, it's Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
He's been working with Jack Bauer
to recover these weapons.
He was taken captive,
but then released by someone on the inside.
His name is Greg Seaton.
He's part ofJonas Hodges's inner circle.
Ma'am, he says he's willing to tell us where
the weapons are in exchange for immunity.
I've already started mobilizing
for a targeted raid.
We can catch 'em by surprise
and lock down these weapons.
But I'm gonna need you to sign
an immunity agreement for this man.
How confident are you
of Seaton's intel?
We believe it's genuine, ma'am.
Madam President,
we may not get a chance like this again.
- Admiral Smith?
- I concur.
But I would suggest we supplement
the F.B.I. With a SEAL squad.
They're ready to move on my order.
The Attorney General will raise hell about us
involving the military in this operation.
We'll deal with him later.
Agent Moss, you have my direct authorization
to move on Starkwood.
How soon can you be ready?
We've already drafted an executive pardon
and set it up via WebEx.
You'll be able to give a secure digital
signature, and we're good to go.
We have the document set up
at your assistant's computer.
Agent Moss,
the president is prepared to sign.
[Larry]
Go ahead, ma'am.
All right, it's done.
- Did you get a signature?
- Yeah, we're good.
- When can you be at Starkwood?
- We can be there in 10 minutes.
Agent Moss, thank you, and good luck.
Thank you, ma'am. Let's go.
Madam President,
we may have just caught a lucky break.
Until this plays out, I want everyone
to keep looking for other options.
All right, Mr. Seaton, go ahead.
The weapons are in a warehouse on
the northeast quadrant of the compound.
3244.23 North...
11710.42 West.
Mr. Seaton, it would help to have someone
on the ground doing recon.
- Can you get Tony to that warehouse?
- I think so.
See if you can get ahold of a hand radio.
We'll be on 480 kilohertz.
All right. We'll be there.
We land here, we'll be
within 50 yards of the warehouse.
Yeah. Support teams here and here,
shore us up. Coordinate with the navy.
- Get moving. I'll meet you upstairs.
- Let's move.
[Chattering]
You're mobilizing. What's going on?
We got a call from Tony. He's working
with an informant inside Starkwood.
We got a location on the weapon. We're getting
ready to stage a raid on the compound.
- I want to go.
- I can understand why. But I'm sorry.
- I can't allow it.
- Larry, I can help you with this.
I'm the only one who's seen the canisters.
I know exactly what we're looking for.
I read your debrief.
You gave us all the details we need.
Larry, please. I've earned this.
Jack, I know what you've done today...
the sacrifice you've made.
Under any other circumstances,
I'd want you out there with us.
But you're sick. We have no idea
when you're gonna start showing symptoms.
I cannot risk that happening
out in the field.
I need my best men for this operation.
I hope you can understand that.
[Exhales]
You're right.
Yeah. [Chuckles]
I always knew eventually we'd agree on something.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
[Beeping]
- Mr. Seaton?
- Murphy, I need to check the personnel records-
[Grunts]
[Gate Buzzes]
[Seaton] That's it.
The weapons are inside there.
[Tony] How many men inside?
Hodges, munitions team, security-
I'm guessing a dozen or more.
Wolves are
at the door, Tommy.
- How much longer?
- We're still an hour away from being armed, sir.
We just intercepted a government transmission.
F.B.I. On the way.
Sir, we haven't even run
the sequence checks yet.
Let's do it. Damn it.
- What's our E.T.A.
- Two minutes, sir.
- Tony, it's Larry Moss. Are you in position?
- Affirmative.
- I'm about 50 yards north of the warehouse.
- What can you tell me?
We've got two entrances,
north and south. Heavy steel doors.
Two guards, armed with automatic weapons.
Seaton says there's probably
about a dozen inside.
- I think we have to assume they're armed as well.
- All right, we're almost there.
I'm gonna need your eyes on the ground
in case there's any resistance.
- Copy that.
- Aerial 1 to home base.
Target has been confirmed.
We are go for tac plan alpha.
Copy that, Aerial 1. All feeds are live.
We're monitoring your approach.
- Sir, we're being signaled
by Starkwood's air tower.
- Let me talk to 'em.
- You're on.
- This is Special Agent Larry Moss from F.B.I.
We have an executive order
from the president of the United States...
to search one of your buildings.
F.B.I. I'll need to get authorization
from my superiors.
We have sent you a digital copy
of the executive order.
Check your wireless frequency.
That is all the authorization you will need.
Make no attempt to interfere,
or you will be arrested. Do you understand?
- Do you understand?
- Understood, F.B.I.
Take us in.
Aerial 1 to home base.
We are good to go.
Copy that, Aerial 1. Looks like you have
a clean approach.
No hostiles in sight.
[Helicopter Passes Overhead]
- (HDTV SUBTITLES FROM HERE) -
added by w3sten
MOSS:
You all right?
We have a medic.
I'm fine.
Seaton, I need you
to stay behind us.
Let's go.
Stand down!
You were told to stand down!
Lower your weapons
and get on the ground now!
Lock them down!
It's locked, sir.
Blow it.
Blasting!
Three. Two. One!
Go. Go!
Where are the weapons?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Almeida was threatening
to kill me.
I told him
what he wanted to hear.
You lying son of a
bitch! You came to me!
Now, where are
the weapons?!
Where are the damn weapons?!
Tell him to take
his hands off of me.
Tony? Tony! I need you
to stand down now!
You're not getting away
with this.
Secure him!
He's lying, Larry.
(panting)
He played me.
Yeah, I know.
It looks that way.
Well, what do you know?
Little old Seaton
bought us some time.
They're on the other
side of the compound.
We just have
to keep them there.
There's nothing here, sir.
(sighs)
Renee, the warehouse is empty.
Tony's informant
sent us to the wrong location.
This whole thing
was a diversion.
They couldn't have
gotten them out that fast.
The weapons are
there somewhere.
Larry, the weapons have to be
inside of Starkwood.
Tell them to
keep looking.
Stand by.
All right, everyone
outside now.
All right, listen up.
We're going
to do a point-by-point
search of this entire compound.
Good.
MOSS:
I want four teams sweeping
every structure
on this property.
(tires squealing,
engines revving)
(tires squealing)
Jack.
(engines revving)
MOSS:
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
(tires squeak)
Stay in position.
(mumbling softly)
Tell Larry to have
his men stand down.
Are you kidding me? They just
drew on federal forces.
If you don't want to lose
your men, you'll get them
to stand down now. Now!
(tires squeal)
MOSS:
Hold your fire!
That's far enough.
We cooperated
with your demand
to search this building.
Now, we're asking you to leave.
MOSS:
There are biological
weapons on this facility.
We're not going anywhere
without them.
Now, tell your men
to stand down.
Those charges are absurd,
and we're not going to
let you keep searching.
You're on private property,
and we're prepared
to defend it if necessary.
You are threatening
federal agents.
Stand down! Now!
We're protecting our rights
against a hostile government
that's using
false charges to
try to shut us down.
Now, we don't want
any bloodshed.
But if you try
to advance any farther,
you will be fired upon.
www.tvsubtitles.net