Previously on 24
This is counel Eka Dubako
We have the CIP device
We demand
the complete withdrawl of the U.S. Naval Strike Force
by this time tomorrow.
You are recalling
the invasion force.
Well, that determination
has yet to be made.
I implore you,
do not abandon my country.
It's Samantha Roth.
She says
she has new information
regarding my son's death.
Roger was tasked with auditing
the brokers in his department.
He uncovered
other blind accounts,
accounts that were traced
to a senior member
of your wife's
administration.
It's all here.
Account numbers,
trading records,
everything that he knew.
Bauer must have worked out
this escape
with Almeida's people.
That son of a bitch played me.
Had me believing
the Bureau was compromised--
someone on the inside
working against us.
I realize now
it was him all along.
MOSS:
He played us both.
I'm going to make
this right, Larry.
Whatever it takes,
I will find Bauer and Almeida.
You're out of time, Mr. Tanner.
Tell me what you know.
I'm not going to tell u
a damn thing.
(groans)
Where is Almeida?
Tanner says Almeida's crew
has a plan to abduct
former Prime Minister
of Sangala.
Matobo?
When?
Pretty much now.
Why didn't you call
the authorities?
BUCHANAN:
He couldn't, Jack.
Why not?
He found out Emerson's client
was Dubaku.
That's who you believe has
agents inside the government.
Dubaku is the key
to this thing, Jack.
If we're going to
uncover the conspiracy,
we have to get to him
before he leaves the U.S.
ALMEIDA:
I got away from the FBI.
Yeah, I heard.
I also heard it was Jack Bauer
who broke you out.
He's on board now.
The package is a person.
EMERSON:
Former Prime Minister Matobo
of Sangala.
The assignment is to grab him,
deliver him to Colonel Dubaku.
(explosion)
Where's Matobo?!
Where is he?!
It's a safe room;
reinforced concrete.
Jack, we leave here
without Matobo,
we lose our only chance
of getting at Dubaku.
???
Matobo's security chief
said there's a safe room
at his residence.
They should have him
and his wife locked down by now.
They'll be safe
till your team gets there.
Your priority is to grab Almeida
and bring him back here.
We'll make every effort
to use nonlethal force,
but Almeida's crew
is ex-military.
They're going to be hard
to subdue
unless my men can return fire.
I understand you'll be
exposing your men,
but it's a risk
you need to take.
Sir...
Almeida is the only
viable lead we've got
to retrieve
the CIP device.
You need to bring him in alive,
is that understood?
Understood.
Let's move out.
We'll get our
updates in the van.
(pained grunting)
Open the safe room.
(grunts)
I will keep going until
you open the door.
(panting):
I've already told you.
Once it's closed, you can only
open it from the inside.
Do whatever
you want to me,
but you will never
get into that room.
(blows landing, Eto'o grunts)
We've got to get Matobo.
Without him, we've got nothing.
I know.
Find a way in yet?
No.
Litvak, any luck
reconnecting the intercom?
Not yet.
I'm working on it.
(phone ringing)
Sir, this just came in...
I'm in the middle
of a field op, Erika.
I don't really have
a lot of time right now.
It's from the
attorney general.
I think you should
make time for this.
What is it?
Tanner's lawyers are
filing a complaint
against the Bureau.
(speed dialing)
(phone rings)
Walker.
MOSS:
Renee, it's me.
I'm less than 15 minutes away
from Matobo's house.
When I get there,
I'll recon for the Tac Team.
Stop a second.
What?
This information about Matobo
being abducted...
tell me how you got it.
You know how I got it--
I questioned Tanner.
You questioned him?
Yeah.
Tanner's lawyers
are saying
you locked them
out of his hospital room,
then cut off
his ventilator.
They said you
applied pressure
to his gunshot wound.
We needed Almeida's location.
Tanner was not about
to cooperate.
So you tortured him.
What the hell were you thinking?
I got the information we needed.
Information that
may not even be valid.
You know as well as I do,
coercive interrogation
is unreliable.
No, Tanner was not lying.
You know that?
How do you know
he wasn't just telling you
what you wanted to hear?
I'll find out when I
get to Matobo's house.
No, you're not
going to Matobo's.
You're coming back
here to the office.
The attorney general
is sending somebody here,
and you're going to tell him
everything that happened.
Larry...
it's my fault that Bauer
and Almeida are still at large.
Please, let me play this out.
I will deal
with the consequences
after we find the CIP device.
No, the field team is on the
way, they can handle this.
Renee,
get back here now.
I'm sorry, Larry,
but I need to make this right.
Renee?
(turns off phone)
Damn it.
I'm glad you're all right, babe.
The flight attendant said
something about us getting
a priority clearance to land.
Uh, you got lucky.
Did I?
I mean, it happened
just after we spoke,
so I thought maybe you had
something to do with it.
Me? How could I
have done anything?
Listen, I might
be late tonight.
There's a lot
going on at work.
I haven't seen you in a week.
I thought we could spend
some time together.
Dinner, and maybe...
...you know.
Sorry, I have to go.
I have to get back to work.
Call me later.
Okay.
Did you deploy the field teams?
Yeah, they just left.
We need to coordinate
with Matobo's security chief--
get him back on the line.
(keypad beeping)
(dial tone drones)
(hangs up phone)
These people, they work
for Dubaku, don't they?
Possibly.
Yes, probably.
But if they wanted me dead,
I would be dead.
Then what do they want?
Names.
Names?
Of my allies inside Sangala.
You would die before you exposed
them, they know that.
Yes, they do, but..
Then it's me.
It's me.
They want to use me
to get you to ta?
Don't worry.
We'll be safe in here
until they leave.
Ule, I'm scared.
Alama, listen to me.
We need to stay calm.
We'll be fine.
The FBI knows we are here.
They'll come for us soon.
Okay?
EMERSON (over intercom):
Mr. Matobo?
I know you can see and hear me.
Come out now
and nobody has to get hurt.
You are wasting your time.
(cocks gun)
Come out now or
I will kill your man.
You have one minute.
Fifty...
I am prepared to die, sir.
For you and for Sangala.
Eto'o is right.
Without you,
Sangala has no leader.
The people need you.
30 seconds.
Eto'o's courage is stronger
than your threats.
He is willing to die.
And for that sacrifice
he has my eternal gratitude,
and the gratitude
of the people of Sangala.
Ten seconds.
Time's up.
(phone ringing)
(phone line ringing)
I just got through to him
15 minutes ago.
Well, he's not answering now.
Then get me someone
else at the residence.
It's the FBI.
Does the FBI know we're here?
Tanner.
He's the only one who knew
we were grabbing Matobo.
He must have talked.
Sir, we need to go
before they get here.
Not without Matobo.
Those walls are
two feet thick.
Even if we blow a hole
with a shaped charge,
they'll kill everyone inside.
I think I found a way.
Yeah? Like what?
We can gas them out.
We don't have anything!
We'll find something!
There's a ventilation system
running straight
into the safe room.
If I can feed the gas through
that, it'll flush 'em out.
LITVAK:
The FBI is coming!
They won't be here
for at least 15 minutes.
What are you talking about?
How do you know?
If they knew anything
before we got here,
they'd have evacuated Matobo.
That's just guesswork.
The tac teams are staged
out of the DC branch office,
That's 21 miles from here,
with traffic.
That gives us at
least 15 minutes.
We're not leaving
without Matobo.
That's what Dubaku
is paying us for.
You're not seriously
considering...
Shut up!
What kind of gas are
you talking about?
Ammonium dysterate.
We can make it from basic
household products.
Do it.
Tony, give me a hand.
Jack, you do know ammonium
dysterate could kill them
as easily as flush them out.
That's a chance
we're gonna have to take.
Delivering Matobo
is our only chance
to get to Dubaku
and the CIP device.
I got it. Grab those bowls.
Gotten into the vent yet?
Yeah! The fbi will
be here any minute.
Mr. Matobo...
We've accessed the air
intake to your safe room.
We are now feeding in
ammonium dysterate gas.
If you do not open
the door you will die.
I believe that you are
willing to sacrifice your life.
But are you also willing To
sentence your wife to death?
Ule...
You know what they will do
if we open the door.
I know.
I can't let them
force me to name names.
Our cause is more
important than we are.
Take my hand.
- Janis gold?
- Yes?
I'm raymond howell From
the attorney general's office,
Is there some place
we can talk?
About?
What happened At
the hospital, ms. Gold.
Agent walker's being accused
Of torturing your suspect.
He's not my suspect,
i have no idea what happened After
i left that room, i am not involved.
The suspect's attorneys claim that
you sent them To the wrong hospital room,
To buy agent walker
more time.
So it sounds to me like
you were involved.
This is going to have to wait.
Janis, i need you on comm, now.
Agent moss, The a.G. Personally
initiated this investigation.
Howell, Open your eyes,
we have a situation.
She cannot deal with
this right now.
Please, Have a seat. Come here.
What's going on?
We think almeida and his crew
may already at matobo's.
And we can't reach
renee to warn her.
Why can't you reach her?
When i heard
what she did To tanner,
i ordered her back to headquarters
To talk to the a.G's office,
And she, uh, refused,
turned off her cell.
Oh.
- I need yourunning point On swat.
- Okay, thanks.
Hillinger, keep trying
to reach renee.
We're running out of time.
Put more gas in!
If we do, it'll kill
them instantly.
How much time is it
going to take, jack?
It's up to them.
I can't breathe.
Just close your eyes,
let it happen.
I know if we open that
door, it will be worse.
I love you.
Alama, no!
Get him out of there!
Get the woman, too.
Just breathe, you'll
be all right.
- Just breathe.
- Okay, let's go!
I'm so sorry.
Let's go.
- It's moss.
- Larry, it's renee.
Renee, listen.
Bauer and almeida may
already be at matobo's.
Yeah, They are, i've got a visual on them
Loading matobo and his wife into a truck.
Where the hell is swat?
How long for swat?
They're still about five minutes
out. Renee, listen to me,
i want you To stand down and
fallback until they get there.
Do you hear me?
Let me just get a plate
on the vehicle.
Drop the gun.
Renee?
Damn it!
Janis, try getting her back.
- Whose swat team will be first on scene?
- Remick's.
Get him for me, now.
Move!
Mr. Emerson!
Far as i can tell,
she's alone.
Damn you, bauer,
you son of a bitch.
She's fbi.
Her name is walker.
She's the one that pulled me Out of
the senate hearing to help me find tony.
Don't be stupid.
What are you talking about?
How much does tanner know
About your operation?
Enough to cause problems.
We need to find out from
her what he Told the fbi--
Till then We do nothing.
He's right, david.
We need to be sure nothing
else has been compromised.
Get her in the cage.
Don't you touch me.
Get your hands
off of me!
Shut up or i will
Shut you up.
She's clean.
let's go!
- Do you have matobo?
- Yeah.
And the wife,
but we ran Into a complication.
A complication?
Fbi knew about the operation.
Which means tanner talked.
- I don't like this.
- No, neither do i.
We got one of their agents
With us, her name's walker.
I need you to check With
your source at the bureau,
Find out how much she knows.
All right.
If your source doesn't
come up all right. With anything,
we'll interrogate her
when we get there.
Can't believe i trusted you.
You lying son of a bitch.
This is important, man.
To him and me.
Thanks, appreciate it.
- Any luck?
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry it took so long,
but I tracked down a friend who
does crypto for the private sector--
he says he should be able to
crack the files on the thumb-drive.
Provided the, uh, encryption
isn't military grade or better.
I doubt Roger would have had
access to anything like that.
He also said you'd have a lot easier job
if you just went to the NSA.
Not until we know how badly my wife's
administration's been compromised.
My friend said he'd meet us
at his apartment in 20 minutes.
Do you trust him?
Yes.
Samantha says the documents
will prove my son was murdered.
I'll make sure he understands
this can't go anywhere.
Thank you, Brian.
You don't know what
it's been like.
All this time, knowing in my bones
Roger didn't commit suicide,
and having people
just tolerate me,
tell me it was
my grief talking.
I'm going to find the people
who did this to my son, Brian.
And I am going
to make them pay.
Sir, if I ma..
What is it?
Shouldn't you at least tell
the President what you're doing?
I can't take this
to my wife...
until I can prove it.
You wanted to see me?
One thing I've learned:
presidents don't
make new friends.
That's why they lean
on their old ones.
I'll need your
support, Ethan.
I'm going to authorize the military
operation in Sangala as planned.
Madame President...
You don't need to list
the consequences, Ethan.
Any action I take in West Africa
will likely result
in a terrorist attack here,
but if I take no action, an entire neration
of Sangalans will be wiped out.
Your critics will point out you took
an oath to protect the people of this country.
And the way to do that is not
give in to blackmail and threats.
Ethan...
taking a stand
against the genocide in Sangala
has reestablished our leadership and our
moral authority in the eyes of the world.
I cannot and
I will not back down.
- Yes?
- Madame President,
Secretary of State Stevens
is here to see you. It's urgent.
Send him in.
What is it, Joe?
The FBI just reported that Prime Minister Matobo
and his wife were abducted from their residence.
What?!
Abducted by whom?
His bodyguards identified Jack Bauer and
Tony Almeida as two of the men involved,
which means Dubaku has
the CIP device and Matobo.
Where is the FBI on finding him?
Do they have any active leads?
Not yet, Madame President. They're just
beginning the search operation.
I think we need to talk about how
Matobo's abduction affects the invasion.
Matobo is the only man
with enough popular support
and strength to lead Sangala
after an invasion.
Without him, the country would collapse
in complete bloodshed and chaos.
Which means the best course of action
may be to meet Dubaku's demand
and withdraw our forces.
The best course of action is to find
Matobo and the people who took him.
And make sure the FBI brings
in every relevant agency.
Yes, ma'am.
So...
where do we stand with your decision
to go through with the invasion?
We still have 30 minutes
before Dubaku's deadline.
I want Matobo found by then.
I just sent you new
search coordinates.
Upload a grid to the ground teams, please.
I already did  they're
adjusting their perimeter now.
All right, thanks.
- Listen, Erika.
- What?
I'm sorry I was a jerk before.
You're worried about
your wife on a plane. It's cool.
She's on the ground now.
Her plane landed; she got lucky.
That's great news.
I'm glad she's okay.
Hey, Sean.
I can't stop thinking
about last night.
Yeah, me, too.
Excuse me.
Sean, I need you to babysit
the downloads on my computer.
They're coming in from the forensics
team at Matobo's residence.
Now, please.
Okay, sure.
Excuse me. Remick's team just finished a
sweep of the Matobo residence.
He's on line two
if you want to talk to him.
Janis, wait.
Did you findenee?
No, sir, but one of Matobo's bodyguards
saw her being taken by Bauer and Almeida.
Then she's alive.
She's with the Matobos.
We'll run a trace
on her cell.
Can't do that, sir.
We recovered Agent Walker's
phone and weapon on-site.
Forensics is still
sweeping the scene.
All right, I want to be the first to know
if they find something.
Yes, sir.
All right, um...
get Renee's picture and
description out to all agencies.
Put me in the queue for
a real-time update from Homeland.
Okay.
Janis.
I want everybody in this office
to make finding her their top priority.
Is that understood?
It is.
Are you going to be okay?
What are you talking about?
Just get to work.
I'm sorry I couldn't
protect you, sir.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
How much are they
paying you, Jack?
I hope it's enough to live with yourself when
they kill innocent Americans with the CIP device.
Shut up.
How many people will die
because of what you're doing?
- Emerson.
- You were right.
Agent Walker broke Tanner.
How much did Tanner spill?
Other than the details
of Matobo's abduction, nothing.
- You're sure?
- Positive.
Walker is extraneous.
Kill her before you get here.
Okay, we'll be with you soon.
Be quick about it.
Dubaku's anxious to get his
hands on the prime minister.
Nichols checked with
his source at the Bureau.
Walker doesn't know anything
that can compromise the operation.
You trust Nichols' source?
Nichols does.
That's good enough for me.
Litvak, change of plan.
- Take a right on Morrison Avenue.
- got it
What's on Morrison?
Abandoned construction site--
we'll dump her there.
Shouldn't we find out
for ourselves what she knows?
Nichols wants her out of the way???
I understand your
deployment's stretched thin,
but one of our own
agents is missing.
That's a priority, too.
Look, look, I don't care
where you find the men.
Just get them out
there looking.
I've never seen him like that.
He looks like his head's
going to explode.
Thank you.
Well, I'm not surprised.
- Meaning?
- Meaning it's fairly obvious he has feelings for Renee.
Why do you think that?
Instinct--
I just know.
Stay on task.
General Juma says the American carrier
troop still has nobegun to withdraw.
Well, they haven't launched
their invasion either.
I gave this president a deadline
and it's almost past.
Apparently, our demonstration
was not convincing enough.
This woman is more
stubborn than we expected.
Once she realizes we have
Matobo, she'll change her mind.
And if she doesn't?
You have the CIP module.
Launch another attack.
Let's see how stubborn she is after
American civilians start dying.
- When will Matoboe here?
- Within an hour.
What caused the delay?
An FBI agent
got in the way.
I needed to make sure she hadn't
compromised our operation.
- And has she?
- No.
As soon as my men
get rid of her,
I'll pick up Matobo personally
and bring him to you.
This friend of yours,
so you're sure he's going to have
everything he needs to access the files?
He said he didn't think
it'd be a problem.
Thank you, Brian.
For all your help,
and your loyalty.
You don't need
to thank me, sir.
Yes, I do.
You're risking a lot to do this,
especially after what happened this morning.
You can thank me after we confirm
the information is on that drive.
Said the key should be
under the mat.
There it is.
When will your friend be here?
He should be here any minute.
Would you mind turning on the air?
- It's really hot in here.
- Of course, sir.
It's Samantha and Roger.
This is Samantha's apartment, sir.
You.
I'm sorry, sir.
Why?
Roger was looking into things
he shouldn't have.
I tried to protect him, too,
but he wouldn't let me.
inherited your determination.
You killed my son.
You...
killed Roger.
It's Tetradyzine, sir.
It's a neuromuscular paralytic.
Don't try to speak, the Tetradyzine
also paralyzes your vocal chords.
If it's any consolation, sir,
Roger died quickly.
And I'm going to make sure...
you do, too.
Situation here is in control.
- Are you tracking Ms. Roth?
- Yeah.
Time to get her back
to her apartment.
- Are you sure this is going to work?
- It'll work fine.
Mr. Taylor came to her apartment
to confront her about Roger.
Lost his temper, killed her.
Took his own life, okay?
All right.
I'll let you know
if there are any problems.
I really am sorry, sir.
If only you'd left
well enough alone.
- Ms. Roth.
- Agent Vossler.
Henry Taylor sent me.
Mr. Taylor's been looking into
the matter you discussed.
He believes you're
in imminent danger.
My God...
What am I supposed to do?
He wants me to place you
in protective custody.
Escort you to a safe house.
- Now?
- My orders are to take you there immediately.
We can stop at
your apartment first,
so you can pack clothes,
essentials.
Uh, I just need
to call my office.
Not until we get you
locked down, ma'am.
Please.
Okay.
???
So it looks like your friend
from the A.G. is still here.
- I know.
- What's going on?
He wants to me about what Renee
did to Tanner in the hospital.
What did Renee do to Tanner
at the hospital?
I don't know, but Howell is
claiming she tortured Tanner.
Renee?
I don't believe that.
Maybe you should.
Tanner wasn't talking...
and she kicked me
out of the room.
And then the next thing I know,
the alarm on his ventilator is going off.
And Renee had
the information she needed?
Mm-hmm.
If you weren't in the room,
you don't have a problem.
I do, actually-- she asked me
to stall his lawyers.
And you did?
- Yes.
- Come on, Gold.
What were you thinking?
She gave me a direct order--
what was I supposed to do?
Say no.
Do you realize if they prove that
Renee tortured him you're an accessory?
And Larry is not
gonna protect you.
I know.
Let's just hope the A.G. will have moved on
to something else when this is all over.
I'm getting back to work.
Agent Moss.
- What do you want?
- Forgive my interruption,
but it's just been brought to my
attention that Agent Walker is missing.
Yes, she may have been abducted
by the same people responsible
for kidnapping
Matobo and his wife.
I'm very sorry to hear that.
And want you to know that I appreciate the
enormous pressure that you and the Bureau are under.
Glad to hear it.
Nevertheless, the Attorney General
is still pressing for a full account
of Agent Walker's handling of the
Tanner interrogation, and at this moment,
Janis Gold is the only witness
available to me.
She's not available
to you, Howell.
I already told you,
she can't be spared right now.
- I only need a short
time with her.
- You can't have her.
Are you going to force me
to get the A.G. on the line?
You've got to be kidding me. You really
want to press this right now?!
We're in the middle of
an international crisis.
- I'm aware of that.
- And all you seem
interested in
is condemning the actions of
an agent who's in God-knows-what danger
just so you can nail her to the wall.
If Agent Walker broke federal guidelines
and used illegal tactics to get information,
then, yes, she will
be prosecuted.
Then maybe you can let us get her back
first before you throw her to the wolves,
I mean, if that's okay with you.
- Yes?
- Larry?
NSA just relayed a call
they intercepted to us.
Renee was referenced.
Referenced how?
Janis?
I think you need to come
hear it yourself.
I'll be right there.
Excuse me.
We're not done here.
Agent Moss!
- Did you source it?
- Five minutes ago. It's legit.
Check it again.
I already did, twice.
Where's the intercept code?
Right there above
the decryption algorithm.
They routed it to us
on a priority channel.
Were we able to get
verbal confirmation?
It's not going to change
the content of the call, Janis.
I know, I just...
What's on the NSA intercept?
What? You said Renee
was referenced. What's on it?
It's only a fragment,
but she's referenced, yeah.
Enough to get a GPS fix?
The clip's not even 27???seconds long.
The best we can say
is that it's in the Metro area.
Play it.
- Emerson
- you were right,
Agent Walker broke Tanner.
How much did Tanner spill?
Other than the details of
Matobo's abduction, nothing.
- You're sure?
- Walker is extraneous.
Kill her before you get here.
We'll be with you soon.
Be quick about it.
Dubaku's anxious to get his
hands on the Prime Minister.
When was this call made?
Ten minutes ago.
- Run a trace.
- I already did.
Run it again!
Jack.
The ditch.
Kill her.
Yeah.
Tony.
Step down.
Step down!
You could either walk
or I could drag you.
You're really going to kill me?
- I'm not going to beg
for my life, Jack.
- Good.
So everything that you
told me was a lie?
I'm doing what I have to.
I don't expect you to understand.
I understand that you are
a traitor and a murderer.
Turn around.
No.
You're going to have to look at me
when you pull that trigger.
I said turn around.
If you trust me, I will get you
through this alive.
Get on your knees.
For a second there, I didn't
thk you were going to do it.
Now bury her.
We're on a timetable.
Can't have anyone finding the body
before we're out of the country.
Give him a hand, Tony.
www.tvsubtitles.net