Livy, it could take weeks
to find Ethan's replacement.
In the meantime, I'm going
to need a provisional
chief of staff.
I would like that to be you.
I have Larry Moss
calling for you.
Ma'am, we have evidence
Juma allowed Starkwood to use
Sangala as a base to manufacture
biological weapons.
Are you saying these
weapons are on US soil?
We suspect they're at the
Starkwood headquarters
in Virginia.
And you're not suggesting
that Starkwood intends
to use those weapons
to attack this country?
Given their actions today,
we need to move
on Starkwood immediately.
They're coming
and they'll be coming with
everything they've got
and the only thing
that's going to stop them
is getting these weapons
ready to deploy.
Tell me what
the FBI knows.
I don't know anything,
Mr. Hodges.
Get him out of here
and do what you have to do.
I'm not spending
the rest of my life
in prison because Jonas
Hodges has lost his mind.
You know where the weapons are?
Yes.
Where's Jack?
He managed to secure
the weapons,
but Starkwood got him back.
Jack was exposed.
There has to be something that
you can do to help him.
There's no cure.
We got a location
on the weapon.
nt to go.
I'm sorry.
I can't allow it.
I'm the only one who's
seen the canisters.
I know exactly what
we're looking for.
But you're sick.
We have no idea
when you're going to
start showing symptoms.
You're right.
Where are the damn weapons?!
He played me.
Little old Seaton
bought us some time.
We're going to do
a point by point search
of this entire compound.
There are biological weapons
on this facility.
We're not going
anywhere without them.
You try to advance any farther,
you will be fired upon.
I count three
platoons at least.
Everything mil-spec.
Yeah. They were
waiting for us.
This was one big trap.
Renee, we would really use
those satellite overheads.
Copy, Larry.
What have we got?
Nothing.
The subnet's been crashing.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Here we go.
I've got sat five
retasking now...
Somebody talk to me.
What are you seeing?
Larry, you've got
hostiles on all sides.
Damn it. Find
me an opening.
I'm looking,
but there's no way through.
Okay, heads up.
Is everybody seeing this?
Larry?
Yeah.
Yeah. we're seeing it.
It's Hodges.
The men are
at the ready, sir.
I appreciate
your presence.
Where else would I be?
Who's in charge here?
I am.
Agent Moss.
You need to move your men
and allow us to proceed.
I want you
off our property
and I want you
to release my man.
You have no right
to take him hostage.
I have an order from the
President of the United States.
To search this building.
For weapons that do not exist.
Have you looked?
Are there weapons
of mass destruction?
Are there weapons of any kind?
Is there anything
in here at all?!
Agent Moss,
who dreamed up this charade?
Give me a name.
Let's get to the bottom of this.
You want to talk
to me, Mr. Hodges?
Get these guns off my head.
You think you have
a gun at your head?
You know what I've got?
I've got the United States
government sending SWAT teams
and attack helicopters
in the middle of the night.
I've got a government that
I served faithfully for 30 years
dreaming up BS accusations
so politicians too cowardly
to show their faces
can dismantle my company.
That's what I've got.
You've got five minutes
to get these-these helicopters
flying out of here
with all of you on board.
You don't want
to do this.
Five minutes.
And I want my man back.
Renee, you get that?
Yeah, we did.
And what options do we have?
In five minutes?
I know there's no time
to bring in more TAC support,
so give me something else.
All right, Larry, give me
a second. Stand by.
That's it.
I want to show
you something.
Hodges just gave us five
minutes to clear the base.
We lost that situation.
We were outmaneuvered
but I think I found
us a new way in.
Look. These are
Senator Mayer's files.
This is Douglas Knowles.
He's the chairman of Starkwood.
He was actually helping
the senator with
the investigation.
He is the one who
brokered the deal
to open the company's books.
What, another insider?
Didn't we just get burned?
Just listen.
Knowles was loyal to
Hodges for almost 20 years
and now he's secretly helping
the senator take down Starkwood?
He's scared of something.
This man wants to help us.
It's worth a shot.
Yeah. Make the call.
Knowles.
Mr. Knowles,
my name is Jack Bauer.
I got your number
from Senator Mayer.
Senator Mayer is dead.
Yes, sir, I know. I was
with him when he was killed
by one of your employees.
A man named John Quinn.
You have no idea how much
I was hoping someone would call.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't understand.
Things are very
out of control.
Are you aware
of what's happening
on your base?
I'm watching it
with my own eyes.
The FBI is pinned down.
They say they're looking
for bioweapons.
Sir, Jonas Hodges
is in possession
of a military-grade
bioweapon.
A prion variant developed
in Africa with General Juma.
Well, it's not
where they think it is.
They're all standing in
front of an empty hangar.
The FBI was deliberately led
to the wrong location
by a man named Seaton,
but I promise you, sir,
the weapon is
on your base.
I was contaminated when trying
to intercept the canisters.
They were ferried
back to Starkwood
approximately 90
minutes ago.
90 minutes ago
Jonas was handing down
his new strategy to the board.
Stonewall the government,
no cooperation whatsoever.
I can't believe
this is happening.
Sir, this is happening
and I promise you
the weapons are on your base.
Do you have any idea
where they might be?
I think I might.
Mr. Knowles, I want
to put you in touch
with one of my men
in the field.
Can I call you right back?
Yes.
Thank you. Go.
Some of the men were unhappy
drawing down on federal agents.
It's understandable.
I had hoped not
to include the rank and file.
You can count on them.
Let's show our guests the door.
Let's move!
Into position.
Jack, I'm on comm.
You're on with me
and Agent Walker.
Hodges' men have
repositioned themselves.
Okay, we're going
to have to move fast.
Larry, I want
you and your men
to pull out on
Hodges' timetable.
Tony, you're going to need
to find a way to stay behind.
We're going to get your vectors
over to a man that we contacted
inside Starkwood.
His name is Douglas Knowles.
He believes he knows
where the weapons are.
Isn't this how we got
into this mess?
Almeida and some supposedly
friendly contact?
Knowles is chairman
of the Starkwood board,
but he was cooperating
with Senator Mayer's
investigation of the company.
Larry, he is all that we've got.
All right, I got 400 eyeballs
trained on me right now.
How the hell are we supposed
to get Almeida to stay behind?
Larry, I need you and your
men to create a diversion
to cover Tony's escape.
Look, we need to
make this work.
If you all get on those
helicopters together,
we are going to lose
this weapon for good.
Larry, are you
on board with this?
We got to go.
Larry, we need to know,
are you on board?
I'll do what I can.
Take his bag.
All right, let's go.
We're standing down.
You're coming with me.
Hey, wait a minute.
This wasn't part
of the deal.
What deal? As far as I could
tell, he couldn't care about you
one way or the other.
Moss.
You take these handcuffs
off of me
or it's going
to get really ugly.
Soldier!
Get the hell out
of here, Moss.
You don't want
to test us.
Let's go!
Don't move. No!
Doug Knowles.
Jack Bauer sent me.
Come on.
That street's
solid security cameras.
I'll take you to
a restricted area.
It's on the
east perimeter.
There's a good chance
the weapons are there.
The place is crawling.
I don't know how
we're going to make it.
I'll take care of that.
Jack, I'm with Knowles.
I'm going to need satellite
support on the east perimeter.
Jack, I need support.
Do you copy?
Copy, Tony.
I've got you just
off the landing pad.
No hostiles
in your immediate vicinity.
Proceed at your own discretion.
Copy that.
Which way?
Come on.
Jack.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Tony and Knowles have connected.
We're good.
It's time to call
the White House with an update.
Okay, good.
I'll be right there.
Madam President,
excuse the interruption.
Jack Bauer is on line seven.
Mr. Bauer, tell me you
have the bioweapon.
Madam President,
I'm afraid that's not the case.
Our search was stopped
by armed mercenaries
on Starkwood's base.
Agent Moss and his men
were forced to withdraw
from a firefight they most
certainly would have lost.
Are you saying Hodges
men were ready to fire
on federal agents?
Yes, ma'am, that's correct.
My God!
Who does he think he is?!
Madam President,
despite the setback,
I am confident
the weapons are still there.
I reached out to
Starkwood's chairman.
He's willing to cooperate.
He's with Tony Alameida now.
They are moving towards
a secure area on the base
where we believe the
weapons are being held.
Very good.
Tim, what's our
troop status?
Mobilizing.
The Secretary
of Defense says
they're still several hours out.
At which point we have
a war on our hands
against 1,500
mercenaries
armed with bioweapons.
Madam President, I do believe
that a surgical air strike
will work as long
as we can pinpoint
the exact location
of the weapon.
And you can do that?
Yes, I believe we can.
Mr. Bauer,
you've seen the canisters
containing the bioweapons,
you know what
they look like,
is that correct?
Yes, ma'am.
Then we'll need you
to verify the canisters
once Almeida
has located them.
No more mistakes.
We're gonna need
visual confirmation
from you, Bauer-- eyes on.
Jack, we have got
to get this part right.
I understand.
Anything else?
Jack, I have been told
that you were exposed
to the pathogen.
How you doing?
Right now I'm fine,
Madam President.
Thank you for asking.
Thank you for your service.
I'm not giving up on you.
Keep me informed.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go.
I don't have a lot of time.
What's going on?
That's what I've been
trying to ask you.
I called three times.
It's kind of crazy
here right now.
Unless it's urgent,
I gotta call you back.
I'm hearing rumors
that the Joint Chiefs
have been called in.
It's not a big deal.
They're just doing
a final assessment
before lowering the alert level.
Olivia, don't do this.
What?
I'm telling you the truth.
Really?
Because I've got a source
in the Port Authority
container yard who's
using terms like "weapons
of mass destruction,"
so naturally I'm wondering
if that's why the Joint Chiefs
are having a meeting.
Look, I can't
talk about it.
It's obviously a question
of national security.
But you have my word
I'll tell you soon as I can.
I want to know now.
I just gave you
a big story, Ken.
You'll have to wait.
I gotta go.
Don't hang up on me, Olivia.
That'd be a big mistake.
What's that supposed to mean?
You want me to say it,
fine, I'll say it.
Think how your mother
would feel when she hears
that you forced out
her chief of staff
so you could take
over his position.
He was incompetent.
Yeah, well, it won't play
that way on the morning news.
So, talk to me.
Now.
I can't talk here.
I'm in the Roosevelt
Continental, room 1271.
You've got half an hour.
Agent Pierce,
please get a car ready.
I have to make a quick run.
All right, Jack, we're here.
Knowles says there's
been increased activity
in this area
for several days now.
I'm looking at about
a half a dozen buildings.
Could be any one of them.
Copy that, Tony.
Hold on, we're getting
infrared up now.
I'm counting seven buildings
in your immediate vicinity.
The building directly
southeast of your current
position is showing
no infrared signal.
I'm guessing they're using
a blackout shield.
All right,
we'll try there first.
You see any patrols
coming our way?
Negative, you're clear.
Okay, let's go.
Jack, Knowles'
key card isn't working.
We're gonna need
electronic support here.
There should be an
R-6 interface module
on the back of your comm device.
It's a card key.
Yeah, I know what
that is, thank you.
I'm plugging in now.
Okay, we're up.
Cormac Z series.
We're looking
at a five digit key
protected by an AES
block cipher.
Running combinations.
Okay, Tony, you've got
a vehicle coming your way.
It's east of you
about a hundred yards.
Take cover down there.
How much longer?
How much more time do you need?
I only have two
out of five digits.
We're pretty exposed here.
Jack?
It's all right, I'm fine.
Come on.
Two more numbers, Tony.
What are we gonna do?
We still got two digits to go.
Move in for a closer look.
Sit tight.
Doug, where you-- Doug!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold your position.
May I see some ID?
Doug Knowles.
One to go.
I apologize, Mr. Knowles.
Mr. Hodges has ordered the base
cleared of all
nonessential personnel.
Nonessential personnel?
I'm chairman of the board.
I realize that,
but we're dealing
with a heightened
security situation here.
So, I need to know
what you were doing
in this area.
Jonas called a late night
board meeting,
that's what I'm doing here.
Sir, that meeting
ended nearly
- two hours ago.
- We got it; we're in.
I don't have to explain
myself to you, you know.
I'm sorry, sir,
but you do.
Sir, I don't believe
you're hearing me.
No, I don't you're hearing me!
Look, I built this company!
And I don't need you
telling me
where I can
and cannot walk!
Understood?!
You're gonna have
to come with me, sir.
Right this way.
I'm in.
But they got Knowles.
Do you think he's
gonna say anything?
I don't know.
But I better get in and out
as fast as possible
just in case he does.
Okay, Tony, the president
needs a visual
on the weapons before
she'll launch an attack.
She needs your eyes
on the canisters and a
confirmation by Jack.
Copy that.
I'm moving.
Good.
Jack?
Stay here, I'll be right back.
Jack! Jack?!
We need a medic! Jack!
Jack?!
Jack?
Get me the medic!
We just found
Mr. Knowles alone
just outside
the restricted zone.
Did he have an explanation?
Yes, sir,
he said he was walking.
Walking.
Should I take him to Stokes
for interrogation, sir?
You're suggesting what, soldier,
that we strap him down,
extract a confession,
because he was walking?
He's the chairman of the board.
I was just requesting
instructions, sir.
What you'd like done.
I'd like you to take him
to his office.
Make sure he's comfortable.
And stay with him
until I arrive.
Yes, sir.
Will that be all?
Call zone nine,
have them double down security.
Let's make sure that
Mr. Knowles was in fact alone.
Yes, sir.
How much longer?
Half an hour.
Good.
I'll need to know
the minute it's done.
Yes, sir.
Aaron, I'd like you to wait
in the hall, if that's okay.
Ms. Taylor, you tasked me
with handling your security.
I can't allow you
to enter a hotel room
I haven't vetted.
Aaron, I appreciate the concern.
But you can see
the door from here,
I have you on speed-dial,
and I can scream very loudly
when the occasion demands.
I just need two minutes
to wrangle a reporter.
Really, I'll be fine.
All right, I'll be here
if you need me.
Want a drink?
No.
I assume you don't mind if I do.
It's been a day.
I gotta tell you.
I don't like being threatened.
It was unfortunate.
I apologize.
We've known each other
a long time, Ken.
I thought we had
an understanding.
We do.
And I want to keep it that way.
We both do.
Am I right?
Okay, so, I told you,
I have this source.
Cop out at the Port
Authority container yard.
Okay.
He told me he saw these
professional assassin types
get into an intense firefight
out there a couple hours ago.
According to him,
someone hijacked a WMD
out to God knows where.
That's true.
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to know
all about it.
Look, if you think all you've
got to do is nod your head
confirming what I already know,
then we've got a problem.
It's national security, Ken.
I can't tell you.
I'm saying you can.
If this story breaks,
it would create a panic.
People would be hurt.
If you knew what it was,
you'd understand why
it's got to stay a secret.
Right, exactly.
I'd understand.
Have a little
faith, okay?
All right. There is a bioweapon
in the container yard.
That's what
they were fighting over.
It was developed by Starkwood
in Africa.
Starkwood?
Right.
They moved it to their base
about 30 miles from here.
So it's there right now.
So this is what the Joint Chiefs
are discussing,
what to do about that.
Olivia...
The president ordered
an air strike
as soon as the exact location
of the canisters was known.
So you see why you can't run
with this?
Really, Ken,
you can't.
A lot of lives
are at stake.
The entire plan depends
on surprise.
You get that, right?
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I need to
kill this story.
Thank you.
What I mean is maybe somebody
could convince me.
What are you saying?
You know what I'm saying.
You're very beautiful
when you get all
patriotic.
I ever tell
you that?
That's over. We agreed.
You agreed.
Really, I don't want to do this.
Ken...
Then say no.
Here, apply pressure.
You can give yourself
an injection
once every two hours.
More if needed.
You think I'll need more?
In all likelihood, yes.
The onset of symptoms so soon
after exposure suggests
the bio-agent is more virulent
than we thought.
All we're doing here
is just masking the symptoms.
I understand.
There's something you may
want to consider, though.
What's that?
Bryden University
has been funding some studies
on prion diseases.
The work is purely
experimental
at this point,
but it does suggest treatment.
That's good news.
I don't want to get anyone's
hopes up here.
We're talking a slight chance.
A possible treatment
using stem cells
from a genetically
compatible donor.
An immediate family member
would make the best
donor candidate.
I saw your file.
It says you have
a daughter, right?
I don't want my daughter
involved in this.
Jack, if there's
a chance.
Mr. Bauer...
Doctor, thank you
for everything you've done.
Excuse me.
I need to get back to work.
Jack...
This is none
of your business.
It's my business
when you're having
a seizure in the middle
of the FBI.
You heard the doctor.
The medication will
mask the symptoms.
Why won't you even
talk about this?
Talk about what?
The experimental
procedure.
Because there's nothing
to talk about.
She's your daughter, and you're
not even gonna let her know?
That's right.
So you're just
not even gonna try?
Renee, I know you're trying
to help,
but you don't know
what you're talking about here.
My daughter and I,
we don't talk, okay?
So, please,
just let it go.
It should be her choice.
Well, it's not.
I'm the one who's dying.
It's my choice.
No sign of the target yet,
but Tony's working on it.
You look better.
Thanks.
Tony, can you hear me?
Jack, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay, Tony, we're seeing new
activity outside the building.
Two vehicles,
eight hostiles.
Looks like
a security detail.
You think Knowles
gave him up?
Tony, they're moving straight
for your point of entry.
Eight hostiles and closing.
Yeah, I hear them.
You want to regroup?
No, I want
to get this over with.
Right there.
Two three, we're clear.
I haven't seen you here before.
They just sent
eight of us over here, sir.
Why, is something wrong?
No, sir.
Just, you know, precautions.
Right, right.
Can't be paranoid enough.
I'm in the main building.
Copy, we're with you.
Tony, it's Jack.
I've got you at 125 feet MSL,
approximately 40 feet
underground. Is that correct?
That's right.
I'm four floors down.
We've got no information
on any kind of subterranean
floors for that building.
Believe me, they're here.
Epoxy-hardened walls,
poured concrete ceilings.
I have a visual on the weapon.
Sending images
for verification now.
Copy that.
Okay, those are
the canisters.
I'll notify Admiral Smith the
target is located and confirmed.
Tony, those are the canisters.
Jack, it looks like
they're transferring
the pathogens
from the canisters
into some sort of
delivery system.
It's on the move.
Copy that.
It doesn't matter.
Renee's phoning
in the coordinates.
Everything's gonna be dust
in the next ten minutes.
Get out of there now.
Copy that.
Withdrawing.
Okay, men.
You want to explain this, Jonas?
I'm arrested by our
own security force.
Held captive
in my own office
like a prisoner.
They won't allow me
a phone call, even to you,
to find out what
the hell is going on!
Well, that's a lot
of complaints, Doug.
You done?
You were supposed
to be home hours ago.
Why'd they find you
snooping around?
I saw the FBI raid.
They say we have bioweapons.
Which they did not find.
That's not the point.
Is it true?
Remember when I first brought
you out here 20 years ago?
There was nothing here.
Nothing.
And out of the damn mud,
we built this place,
the largest private army in the
hemisphere, maybe the world,
and we pulled America's ass
out of the fire
again and again and again.
Answer the question!
I am.
Every day, we've done things
that the government itself
could not or would not do.
"Get this done,"
that's what they said,
"Here's your mission."
Nobody asked how anything
was gonna be done.
Nobody wanted to know.
All anyone wanted was results,
and we delivered.
No one's questioning that.
No one's questioning that?
You're not insane, are you?
The senate, the committees,
the president.
Every chattering nonentity
in Washington
is out there with their standard
operating procedures
saying,
"How was this done?
How was that done?"
Tearing at us, trying to bring
us down, every one of them.
I kept this country strong.
I kept it safe.
And I will not be persecuted
for that.
Jonas, you cannot start
a war against the people
you're supposed to protect.
We were at war, Doug,
the moment they decided
to dismantle us.
And as for particular
weapons,
as for your question,
let me rephrase it.
Are we prepared
to defend ourselves?
We are.
Jonas...
you can't take on
the federal government.
Yeah, well, you never were
one for thinking big.
20 years
I treated you like a son.
20 years.
A little loyalty...
wasn't that
the least I deserved?
Yes.
Sir, we just got an alert from
one of our radar intercepts.
There's a squadron of F-18's
heading our way
out of Virginia Beach.
Sir?
What's the ETA?
Less than ten minutes.
What's our readiness?
How many?
We have three loaded.
Place the call
to the president.
I'll be there momentarily.
You probably think I'm the scum
of the earth right now.
All I care about is that you
don't run the Starkwood story.
You're a real sport.
Taking one for the team
like this.
Look at me.
You won't run it, right?
I'm sorry, Livy.
What?
Breaking something
this big
will put me over
the top in New York.
I'll make sure nobody knows
any of it came from you.
You lying son of a bitch.
Come on, please.
I'm did what I needed to do
to get ahead--
just like you.
There's no comparison.
Running that story
will harm the country.
I've been in Washington
a lot longer than you.
You'll see, this is how
the way the game is played.
Actually, Ken, this is how
the game is played.
What do you mean?
You run that story, or ever
try to blackmail me again,
and I'll make sure
everyone knows
just how you get your leads.
I think your wife
will be especially
interested.
From everything
you've told me,
that's gonna be
one nasty divorce.
You bitch.
Find a new beat, Ken.
I don't want to see you around
the White House again.
Sorry, I've got to take this.
Hi.
Where in the world are you?
I'm sorry. I had a
meeting on K Street.
I had to run interference
with a reporter.
Are the press on to this?
Not anymore.
I took care of it.
I need you here, Livy.
We've had confirmation
on the bioweapons,
and the air strike
is happening now.
I'll be there in five minutes.
Where are we, Admiral?
The F-18's have been loaded
with bunker-buster ordinance
and will be in range
in seven minutes.
What's the risk
of the pathogen spreading
to the surrounding areas?
Minimal.
We're using white phosphorous
charges,
which burn at 5,000 degrees.
More than enough
to incinerate the pathogen.
And that's been confirmed
by the CDC.
It has.
Weapons are ready?
Yes, sir.
The call to the president?
The call is in process.
It's an historic day,
gentlemen.
A great day for Starkwood.
Too bad Mr. Knowles
can't be joining us.
I have an ETAC
with eyes on. Airborne.
Roger,
I need 9,000 feet
MSL and weapons control
status, over.
Weapons control status:
yellow tight.
Fighters entering the IP.
Engage airspace
coordination area.
Roger that.
Stand by.
Madam President, command
and control is reporting
that a phased array radar system
is active inside
the Starkwood compound.
Meaning what exactly?
They know we're coming.
Is there any evidence of an
antiaircraft artillery threat?
Intelligence is indicating no
such capability on the ground.
Madam President,
there's a phone call for you.
It's Jonas Hodges.
Put him on speaker.
Ma'am, he's requested
a private conversation.
He says he's established
a proprietary line
in the Ops Room.
A proprietary line?
How did he manage that?
I have no idea.
Hello.
Madam President,
let me begin by saying
that I am truly sorry
it's come to this.
at you turn your planes
around immediately.
You're in no position to
issue ultimatums, Mr. Hodges.
Well, maybe I am.
You remember several years ago,
Madam President,
Starkwood was deployed
to Pakistan.
Oh, I remember it
very well.
I fought that deployment.
And you lost.
You'll also recall
that we requisitioned a missile
system at that time--
Python Fives.
Well, three of those missiles
are now loaded
with the pathogen
and aimed at cities
on our eastern seaboard.
You're bluffing.
As a sign of good faith,
I'm willing to show you that
I'm... that I'm not bluffing.
You see that?
Madam President?
Hmm?
You call this good faith?
You are waging war
on your own country, Jonas.
Well, of course,
I wouldn't see it that way.
What do you want?
Well, we can have
that conversation
a little later on
at the White House.
You think we're going to just
sit down and discuss this?
Yes I do,
in the Oval Office,
in confidence,
within the hour.
But in the meantime,
I think it is
to both of our advantage
that the American
people do not know
the exact circumstance
of this standoff.
So you will keep this
conversation to yourself,
and turn the planes around.
And if you don't comply,
Madam President,
I will have no choice
but to launch those missiles.
Mr. Hodges...
And remember, I can detect
any action you take
against our facility.
You have 30 seconds.
Mr. Hodges...
Mr. Hodges!
Abort the air strike,
Admiral Smith.
Madam President...
Just do as I say.
Ma'am, with all respect...
Damn it, Admiral, abort
the air strike immediately!
This is Admiral Smith.
I have an abort order
from the president.
Take fighters off target.
Repeat: take fighters
off target.
Stand by for
confirmation code.
We're standing down,
Madam President.
www.tvsubtitles.net