Ioning sponsored by
20th century fox television
And brought to you by ford.
Drive one.
That was bob cornell at nsa.
They've detected
another firewall breach.
There's been another attack?
Not yet, but they believe the
cip device is being utilized.
We have to assume dubaku
is initiating another attack.
Madam president.
What is it, tim?
I've just been forwarded
a scrambled call.
It's from
colonel dubaku.
He's demanding
to speak with you.
The deadline for your forces
To begin their withdrawal
has passed.
Go to the window.
See what you have done.
Comply with my demands
within the hour,
Or 10,000 more americans
will die.
She's on her way up.
I'll call you when it's done.
Mr. Taylor,
are you okay?
(groans)
(grunts)
Audio forensics
cleaned up the recording.
Nichols (over computer):
walker is extraneous.
Kill her before you get here.
Larry, I don't think
it's worth it.
There's nothing here.
All right. Fine,
Help janis coordinate
with nsa.
I'm sorry
about renee.
She was a good agent.
We don't know
that she's dead yet!
I've devoted my life
to the bureau
And you just expect
me to believe
That the entire government's
been corrupted.
Jack:
not all of them.
But until we find out who,
we can't trust anyone.
And the four of you
really think you can stop this?
We have to.
It's as simple as that.
Dubaku wants you and your wife.
That's the deal.
You're asking us
to risk our lives
To be delivered into
dubaku's hands.
Listen to him, ule.
But how can we
trust this man?
Because
He has no reason
to lie.
Nichols:
how are you doing, tony?
All right.
Buchanan:
where's emerson?
He's dead.
You want matobo
or not?
(gunshot)
You got what you came for.
Now, get the hell
out of here.
Did everything go smoothly?
We have the matobos,
that's what matters.
I heard about the planes
on the radio.
The white house
still has not complied.
What do you intend to do?
Exactly what we promised.
We're ready, sir.
Where's the target
located?
Kidron, ohio.
Population?
30,000.
Casualties will be high.
Begin.
Larry.
We think this is the truck
the matobos were abducted in.
Where was this
image taken?
Near northwoods
airfield.
Were you able
to track it?
Not beyond this sector.
But they were heading
east on mckinley avenue.
All right.
Make sure the vehicle I.D.
Is disseminated
to all search teams
And local agencies.
Yes, sir.
Larry, I think I found
something.
Yeah?
I've been working nsa, trying
to back-trace the cip attack
That took down the two planes.
And I found a code fragment
Which I think could be residue
from the cip intrusion.
I'm running a pattern
match right now.
With any luck at all,
We may be able to anticipate
where in the infrastructure
They're targeting next.
And I need sean.
Janis, I don't want
to waste personnel
On some wild-goose chase.
Dubaku's threatened to kill
10,000 more americans
In the next 30
minutes.
I understand that,
And I will drop it
the minute it feels cold.
All right, I'm going to
brief the white house.
Keep me in the loop.
Sean.
Are you sure he's up to running
this operation?
Larry's fine.
Is he?
You're the one who told me
about him and renee.
This has got to be hitting
him pretty hard.
If I don't think
larry can do his job,
I'll let you know,
all right?
In the meantime, I need you
to open up a fresh socket.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
Gedge's voice:
you've reached
agent brian gedge.
Please leave a message
and I'll get back to you.
(beep)
agent gedge,
I expected to hear from you
by now.
It's urgent that I speak
with the first gentleman
As soon as possible.
(intercom beeps)
Call me back, agent gedge.
This is extremely important.
Yes?
Secretary:
larry moss with the fbi.
Where are we, larry?
We've I.D.'d a vehicle
That we believe was used
in the matobos' abduction.
We're still trying
to track it down.
And how long is that
going to take?
I wish I could tell you, sir.
I don't have a time frame.
That's not good enough, larry.
Unless you get some results,
we're going to get hit again.
A lot of people are
going to die
If you don't
find dubaku.
With all respect, sir,
I don't need to be told
what's at stake.
We're giving everything we can.
One of our agents
has given her life.
Yes, I was told about that.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'll call you the minute
we have something.
We'll be waiting.
(sighs):
god....
Chloe:
the matobos have been taken
into a building.
546 adams.
Okay, pull up the stats
on that address.
On it.
It's the ritter building,
four stories high.
The building
is two years old.
Give me the security specs.
Give me a minute.
We're coming up on it.
I'm going to need
your help.
(beeping)
I see you've
chosen a target.
The boyd chemical plant
near kidron, ohio.
The cip device
has enabled us
To take control of
the main tank.
We're about to cause the
primary safety valves to fail.
Do you remember the last time
we saw each other, ule?
It was at a state dinner
in your residence.
We shared an excellent
bottle of wine.
I offered my hand
in friendship
And you... Slapped it away.
You gave me an ultimatum--
To be the puppet
for your military.
You could have had a long
and prosperous career
As prime minister.
But now you're going back
to sangala
As a traitor to your people.
I am prime minister.
I was elected by the people.
It's you and juma
who are the traitors.
No.
We brought order to sangala,
But you are trying
to destroy
Everything
that we've built.
You'll be taken back
to sangala, ule,
And you will give
general juma
The names of all
your fellow traitors.
I will never do that.
Never.
Hmm...
Believe me, you will.
Take them.
Any response
from the president?
Not yet.
But once she sees
dead americans
Lying in the street,
she will be less stubborn.
I'm inside, jack,
approaching the front desk.
Copy that.
Are the motobos
still on the third floor?
Affirmative, jack.
They're being moved.
I'm just not sure where yet.
Copy that.
Good afternoon.
I'm agent walker
with the fbi.
I don't have
an appointment,
But I'm here to see
mr. Roane of roane
and associates.
I'll let them know you're here.
Actually, I don't
want to be announced.
I'm here on official business.
All right.
So as far as you're concerned,
I was never here, understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Past security.
Heading toward
the elevator.
We're on our way to
the service entrance.
Chloe, I'm on the third floor.
Law firm is
on your left.
On your right is a suite
of offices where matobo's
Being held.
I see it.
Stairwell's down the hallway
to your left.
(hissing)
Agent walker, we're at the door.
There's one guard outside
the suite, probably armed.
Bill, take the third floor.
Wait for my signal.
Go on.
Chloe, we're on the fourth floor
In what used to be
the computer room.
What now?
In the center
of the room
There are two
removable panels.
This should give you
access to the crawlspace.
Copy that.
Okay, we're clear.
Let's go.
We're in.
I should never have allowed
you to come with me.
It was a mistake.
It was not your decision, ule.
We will be all right.
Jack bauer will
be here soon.
Okay.
We're at the heating unit.
Okay, jack,
there's an airduct
Leading off that unit;
do you see it?
Yeah.
Follow that for about 30 yards
Until you see
an electrical junction.
Make a left,
then another 20 yards
You'll come to the vent.
This will give you a view
of the entire floor.
And the matobos?
They've been moved
into a adjacent room
Just off the main area.
Okay, copy that.
Come on.
Sean:
the entire nsa has been
combing the firewall
Searching for the next
cip device breach.
If this were something,
don't you think
They'd already know about it?
I can live without your
negativity today, sean.
There it is again,
that same code fragment.
"kidron, ohio."
what's in kidron, ohio?
Any sensitive installations?
Something dubaku
might want to hit?
I don't know.
Homeland has a high-value
Target database;
I'm cross-checking it now.
Okay. Okay,
nothing in kidron itself,
But in the neighboring
county there's...
Boyd chemical.
What do they make?
Insecticide. Please
get me that number.
Hello?
This is janis gold at fbi.
I need to speak
To your plant manager
immediately, please.
Ma'am, as I just stated
I'm with the fbi.
Does that sound vaguely
important to you?
Now, connect me
to john brunner.
Fbi? Uh, yeah, put her on.
This is john brunner.
Janis (on phone):
hello.
Mr. Brunner,
this is janis gold, fbi,
D.C. Bureau.
What can I do for you?
We've been tracking
some possible
Breaches in the government
firewall.
The firewall's designed
to protect installations
Like yours...
I know what it does, honey.
Um, we have tracked
And isolated
one of these breaches
In the kidron area.
I need to know
are you experiencing
Any problems right now?
As a matter of fact, we're
dealing with one right now.
What is it?
Three of our safety
valves just failed
On the primary storage tank.
We're having trouble
resetting them.
What's in that tank?
Methyl isocyanate.
It's concentrated
insecticide, highly toxic.
Can you-- what the hell
is this all about?
Mr. Brunner, I have reason
To believe that
this is a terrorist attack
On your facility.
Terrorist attack?
Yes, sir, I need
you to initiate
On-site emergency
procedures
And stay on this line.
Shut down the tank.
What's going on?
Do it! Do it!
My authority.
Damn.
What is it?
It's not responding.
What do you mean?
Try it again.
Nothing.
Pressure in the
primary tank is rising.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. Brunner?
We cannot shut down
the primary tank
And the pressure
is building.
If we cannot stop
this, we are looking
At atmospheric release.
Okay.
Get larry.
Dubaku has targeted
that facility.
We need to alert
the president.
Mr. Brunner,
You need to begin evacuating
people right now.
All right, agent moss,
keep me apprised.
I'll speak to the president.
I just received
an interagency alert.
The fbi just discovered
dubaku's next target.
A chemical plant, yeah.
I just got off the phone
with larry moss.
I need to brief
the president.
Has the first gentleman
spoken with the president?
Not yet.
I talked to agent gedge
40 minutes ago.
Mr. Taylor is
the only person who
can talk the president
Into withdrawing
our troops in sangala.
And that is our best way
to prevent this attack.
I know we need him.
I'm waiting for a call back.
The middle section's still
bothering me; read it again.
Angela:
"colonel dubaku and the
juma regime have killed
"countless thousands
of their own people,
"and now hundreds
of our fellow citizens.
They deserve your prayers
and your outrage."
I think the word "outrage"
might be too strong
If you're trying
to convey
Calm authority.
"outrage" is the only word
To describe how I'm feeling,
and how every person
In this country will be feeling.
The american people
deserve the truth.
Dubaku's already
killed 300 americans.
God knows what else
he has planned.
(knocking on door)
Come in.
Could you excuse us, angela?
What is it?
The fbi believes
they've detected
Where the next attack
will take place.
Dubaku's infiltrated
a chemical plant
Just outside of
kidron, ohio.
He's causing the pressure
on the facility's
Primary tank to go critical.
If the tank erupts,
over 3,000 gallons
Of methyl isocyanate will
be released into the atmosphere.
Given the prevailing winds,
A very large,
very toxic cloud
Will sweep into town.
Methyl isocyanate
Is a concentrated insecticide.
Even brief exposure
causes severe lung damage
And chemical burns
of the skin.
What's our time frame?
The tank could rupture
in less than 15 minutes.
They've begun evacuating?
We've already contacted
emergency responders
On the ground in kidron.
It's just not enough time
to get everyone out.
Kidron's population's
just over 30,000.
This projection says that
We could lose over 50%?
Oh, dear lord...
Ethan:
right now, our only chance
of stopping this
Is finding dubaku
and the cip device.
You ready?
Quietly.
Chloe (on earwig):
jack, I just intercepted
An fbi alert identifying
dubaku's next target.
A chemical plant
near kidron, ohio,
12 minutes from going
critical. There are 30,000
People in that town, jack.
We have to hurry.
Jack (quietly):
copy that.
Give me the scope
out of the bag.
(bag unzips)
Turning scope
over to night-vision.
I don't see dubaku.
We've got nichols.
Three men with
automatic weapons.
Three more over
at the control station,
most likely armed.
Copy that.
That's dubaku.
We got dubaku.
Chloe, are you seeing this?
Yes. The control station
looks like an s-dart.
's a really
powerful processor.
It could be driving
the cip device.
Copy.
Nsa's classified
infrastructure team
Is trying to plug
the firewall breach.
Any luck so far?
None so far,
but they're staying on it.
They have less than
Ten minutes left.
They're aware of that, sir,
But they're doing
what they can.
Not now.
What's going on
at the plant?
I'm on with them now.
John? Did you try
Flashing the memory cards?
(alarm blares)
Brunner:
three times, honey.
We're not in control
of the computer system.
I've already told my people
to get the hell out of here.
Normally, I don't
allow people
To call me "honey," but
we can discuss that later.
Yeah, well, it sounds
like you need to lighten up.
(alarm continues blaring)
good, good.
I'm heading
to the primary tank room.
I'm going to try to manually
Release some
of the pressure.
That's not going to stop it.
No, but it might buy us
A few more minutes
so people can evacuate.
I've got a thousand workers
at this facility.
And I am responsible
For their safety.
(door buzzes)
Now look, I need you to stay
on the phone.
I'm going
to need some help.
Absolutely.
What can I do?
I don't have access
To the override schematics.
See if you can pull up
The operating procedures
for tank one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got it.
I got it right here.
All right.
Now look
for the emergency valve
Release sequence.
Okay.
Uh, valve release.
I have it right here.
This, wait,
this procedure is going
To release the chemical right
Into the primary tank room
where you are right now.
I know that.
I have respiratory gear on.
I'll be okay,
just give me the sequence.
But how long will
that protect you?
Don't worry about it, honey.
Uh, okay.
Are you looking
at the routing board?
I am.
Go ahead.
Set the bus switches
To this sequence
from left to right:
Two.
Eight.
Seven.
Four.
Three.
Done.
The secondary flow valve
Should be behind you
and to your right.
I need you to turn
that clockwise please.
(steam hissing)
(grunts)
All right.
All right, I got it.
Okay, that's one valve down,
Three more to go.
(groaning)
(coughing)
(electronic beeping)
Pressure inside the tank
is approaching 400 psi.
How long before
the tank ruptures?
Seven minutes.
Nichols:
we've got a problem.
What is it?
An alert.
Our hidden surveillance camera
on the roof.
Almeida and bauer.
When was this taken?
20 minutes ago.
I thought you killed
almeida and bauer?
Damn it! You said
this location
Was kept secret
from everyone!
It was.
Then what are they doing here?!
I don't know.
How did they find us?!
I don't know!
600 psi and rising.
(low beeping)
Disengage the cip module.
Begin the offload.
What are you doing?
We're almost there.
We will continue this attack
from another location.
Let's finish this.
We can handle them.
We need to get out of here now.
The cip module's disengaged,
starting off load.
Sean:
hey, what the hell is that?
What the hell is that?!
What's the matter?
The firewall breach just closed.
Larry:
what?!
What are you talking about?
No cip intrusion,
the firewall is secure.
How? Nsa?
I don't know.
Bring the cip module.
Get motobo and his wife!
Bill, we should go
With the second option
on the assault.
Two-prong attack. You and tony
come through the main entrance.
We'll go in from here.
Copy.
Give me the c4
out of the bag.
Go!
Move.
Move!
(gunshot)
Get the cip device!
Clear!
All clear over here!
Get dubaku?
Negative!
Jack, I've got the cip device.
It's been destroyed.
Jack, it's renee.
The motobos are safe.
I'm taking them to the van.
Copy that. I want you
And bill to do a sweep.
See if you can find dubaku.
I'll cover the south side.
John? John, are you still there?
(weakly)
yeah.
John, listen to me.
The terrorists are out
of the system.
Please tell me what is happening
right now.
(steam hissing)
Automatic shutdown mode
has kicked in.
Pressure's dropping.
I think we're gonna be
all right.
Okay, that's great.
Now you-you gotta get out
of there right now.
(labored breathing)
(coughs)
John?
(labored breathing)
I can't make the door...
I'm sending the rescue team.
A rescue team
is on its way.
John, please
stay with me.
Stay with me.
(people clamoring)
Have they found dubaku?
Still searching.
Renee:
first responders are five
minutes away, jack.
Copy that.
Get up.
(gasping)
I said get up!
(whimpering)
(quietly):
they're coming.
Please don't make
me do this.
I will go to your home, michael.
I'll make you wife watch
As I kill
your daughter,
And then I will
kill her.
So do as I ask.
Save your family.
Let me see your hands!
It's latham.
Where's dubaku?!
I'm sorry.
(device beeping)
Cover!
Tony! Bill!
Yeah!
You all right?
Jack?
Jack, can you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, we're okay.
What happened?
Latham was wired
with explosives.
We still don't have dubaku.
What?
The cip device
has been destroyed.
I want you to stay
with the motobos.
Make sure they're safe.
(sirens approaching)
Jack the police are almost here.
If you get arrested,
this entire operation
goes out the window.
You have to get out of there.
Copy that.
He's gone.
Buchanan:
we need to get back
to the safe house.
Let's go.
(sirens approaching)
Sean, this stays both nsa
and homeland have no idea
Why the breach at the kidron
plant was stopped.
They're still looking.
We're working on it here also.
Janis is coordinating
with a digital forensics team
That she sent over to the plant.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why... Why would dubaku suddenly
stop an attack
When he was minutes away
from causing mass casualties?
Maybe there was a malfunction
in the cip device.
No, no, I don't want maybes,
all right? I want answers.
We're doing everything we can,
sir.
That's not good enough
right now, is it?!
I don't know what else
to tell you, sir.
I know you're upset
about renee,
But getting angry at me is not
going to make it go any faster.
If you think I'm yelling at you
because of my history
With agent walker,
you are mistaken.
There are thousands of lives
at stake here.
That's what concerns me.
Sorry, sir.
I want you and janis
to work with nsa.
Find out where that cip device
is being used.
If we find the device,
we find dubaku.
I appreciate the call.
Thanks a lot.
Janis, larry wants
you to interface with nsa.
See if you can back-trace
that cip code fragment
to its source.
I'll try.
Who were you talking to?
The head of the response team
at the plant.
What did he say?
Facility's clean.
A trace amount of the chemical
was released, but not enough
To do any damage,
and the site has been secured.
That's good.
What about
the plant manager?
John brunner.
Is he okay?
No.
Will you do
me a favor?
It depends.
I'd like to track down
mr. Brunner's family.
I was the last one
to speak with him,
And I feel they should know
how brave he was.
I'll see what I can find.
Thank you.
Janis, before you start
sending flowers,
You need to find out where
that cip device was being used.
I know. I'm on it.
Cleanup crews
are already on site
And we're continuing
our evacuation of
a one-mile radius
Around the chemical plant.
Casualties?
There was, in fact,
one casualty,
The plant manager.
13 other workers
are being treated
For chemical burns
and inhalation
of toxic fumes.
And there haven't been
any other intrusions
in the firewall?
No, ma'am.
It appears the crisis
has been averted.
Except that no one's been able
To explain how the firewall
break disengaged.
Not yet.
The fbi has no idea how
it happened... It just happened.
And that's not
an explanation.
Perhaps dubaku was firing
another warning shot.
No, dubaku's already down
two planes.
He's not afraid
to take more lives.
In any event,
we should be grateful.
I'm not one to accept good news
Unless I know
where it comes from.
Until we have more answers,
I want to maintain alert levels.
(phone rings)
Yes?
Madam president, I have
admiral smith on line two.
Put him through.
Thank you, tim.
Admiral?
I've been trying to reach agent
gedge, and he hasn't picked up.
Yes, I'm sure I have
the right number.
I just spoke to him
over an hour ago.
He said he was outside
samantha roth's apartment
Waiting for the first gentleman.
(sighs)
just find him.
I don't care who you
have to pull off shift.
Still can't reach gedge.
The secret service doesn't know
where he is either.
(sighs)
I need to tell the president.
Maybe you should hold off.
The domestic threat's been
lifted for now
And she's on the phone
with admiral smith.
I can't authorize
the air strikes
Until our post-invasion
plans are in place.
Finding a politically viable
replacement, until that happens,
You need to keep
your forces at full readiness.
The joint chiefs
are getting impatient.
Madam president, we need
to talk about your husband.
His theory
about your son's death,
He hasn't let it go.
What are you talking about?
He's been harassing
roger's girlfriend,
Accusing her of complicity
in the death of roger.
Henry and I went over it
Again and again
with the fbi,
And he swore to me
He was past all that.
Well, he's found a private
investigator who's feeding
His conspiracy theory;
Taking advantage
of him.
Please get henry
on the phone.
I'm afraid
I can't do that.
Henry's unreachable.
I don't understand.
Agent gedge hasn't been
answering his phone.
Now, I wouldn't get
too worried yet.
You're telling me my husband's
gone missing?
Secret service
has put out an apb.
They're going to
ms. Roth's apartment.
Whatever's going on, I
will find out soon enough.
Secret service dispatcher:
this is a priority order code
charlie zero charlie.
We need an immediate 20
on agent gedge.
All available
field agents proceed
To his last known location:
404 wilkinson drive.
I repeat:
code charlie zero charlie.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
(phone snaps shut)
(breathes deeply)
You're making a mistake.
Think about it.
Shut up!
You haven't killed
anybody yet.
You don't need
to do this.
Gedge's plan to frame me
is already blown.
If you kill me,
They'll know it was murder,
And they'll trace it
back to you.
(phone rings)
Go ahead.
Where's agent gedge?
I can't reach him.
Gedge is dead.
What happened?
Everything was going
according to plan...
But something
went wrong.
Taylor killed gedge;
I don't know how.
Where's mr. Taylor now?
He's right here.
Don't kill him,
bring him to me.
Yes, sir.
Prime minister matobo,
ma'am, please come with me.
Chloe, pull up the ritter
building on a satellite grid.
Look for any sign of dubaku
leaving the site.
We've got to find him.
It's going to take me 20 minutes
to task the satellite.
Then don't waste time
talking about it.
Pull up satellite
and traffic cams,
Street corners
and metro stations.
What's the priority?
I can only do one thing
at a time.
Satellite!
Fine.
Bill, we need to rethink this.
What do you mean?
You were set up to surveil
an undercover operation.
Your cover's been blown.
The police are after us.
We are not equipped to look for
one man in a city of millions.
We need additional
resources.
What are you suggesting?
It's time
to contact outside agencies.
The government?
Yes.
I thought you said the
government couldn't be trusted.
Right now,
we don't have a choice.
Almeida:
it can't be trusted.
We can't trust anybody,
That's why we're working
on the outside.
President taylor
can be trusted.
I'm not questioning
that, prime minister.
It's the people around her
who can't be trusted.
Mr. Buchanan, jack's right.
We need help.
It's too dangerous.
We can limit the flow
of information.
Prime minister matobo
can get us past
The president's outer circle--
that way, we can at least
Explain to her
why and what we're doing.
Renee:
I think jack's right.
We left a lot of clues
in that building.
We're vulnerable;
we can't do this
On our own anymore.
Am I supposed to remain
in hiding with you,
Pretend that my wife and I
Are still being
held hostage or dead?
I need to return
to the white house
And help the president save
what's left of my country.
Let my husband do this.
Let him call president taylor.
She will listen to him.
Bill, you want to find
dubaku, make the call.
All right.
Get me the white house.
Reporter: representatives
from boyd chemical
Have assured local authorities
That the immediate crisis
has passed.
However, this has done little
to calm the nerves
Of the citizens of kidron, ohio,
Many of whom have taken shelter
in neighboring communities.
Again, we have
confirmed one fatality
Inside the plant itself.
13 others, all boyd employees,
Are being treated
at local medical centers...
(intercom beeps)
yes?
Madame president, I have prime
minister matobo calling for you.
Matobo?!
Yes, ma'am.
You're tracing it?
We tried, madame president,
but it's a secure line.
Put him through.
Prime minister?
Yes, madame president.
Are you all right?
Thank god my wife and I
are both fine.
We were rescued.
By whom?
Where are you?
In a safe place.
Madame president,
you need to listen to me.
The people who rescued us, they
have acquired the cip device.
It has been destroyed,
And your country is no longer
under immediate threat.
Who are these people,
and tell me how this happened.
I will tell you everything
in person,
But, uh,
this must happen privately.
I must speak to you alone.
Why alone?
They will bring me to you,
madame president.
We will arrive in ten minutes.
I'll be waiting for you.
They tried to trace the call,
but the line held.
Ethan, I need to see you
right now.
Yes, madame president?
I just spoke
to prime minister matobo.
What?!
He's safe.
How? What happened?
He'll let us know
when he gets here.
He's on his way now.
He wants a private meeting.
Bring him in
through the south entrance,
And keep this
to as few people as possible.
All right.
Jack, I've mapped a route
for you to the white house.
It's mostly side streets,
But there will be
fewer traffic cams.
Okay, good.
Send it to my phone.
We're ready. Let's go.
As soon as we set the vehicle
in front of the building,
Agent walker will move
mr. Matobo.
Jack... Jack!
What?
I'm not going.
What are you talking about?
If the government
gets their hands on tony,
They'll arrest him.
I already told you--
I did some pretty bad things
before I teamed up with bill.
Tony, take it from me...
You need to deal with
the consequences.
And believe me, I will.
But not yet.
Not till we get dubaku.
I'm working on a lead.
I've got a guy
on emerson's crew
Who might have some
intel we can use.
Let him do this, jack.
He's the reason
we got this far.
Fine.
But you give me your word
as soon as this as over,
You turn yourself in.
We'll stand behind you.
All right,
you have my word.
Good luck. Be careful.
(keys jangling)
(knocking on door)
Hey.
I was on my way to
work, so I thought
I'd stop in and see you.
I tried calling you earlier.
I'm sorry;
I've been busy.
Are you all right?
You look exhausted.
It's just been a long day.
Well, I hope you're still
coming over for dinner.
I'm making lasagna.
And my sister promises not to
give you any more dirty looks.
You haven't forgotten,
have you?
No. No.
It's just that I've got
some business to attend to.
Samuel, you work too much.
Every time you come
into the diner,
You're always on the phone.
I have to, maria,
So that, one day,
I can finally take you away
From that awful place
that you work in.
Well, we met
in that awful place.
Don't forget that.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
(line ringing)
Vossler:
go ahead.
Have you got mr. Taylor?
Yes.
I'm about three minutes away.
There's a korean grocer
opposite my building.
One of my men
will meet you out back.
Bring taylor inside.
What are you gonna do to him?
Just make sure
you weren't followed.
Captioning sponsored by
20th century fox television
And brought to you by ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
www.tvsubtitles.net