Season07
Episode18
********
Mr. Knowles,my name is jack bauer.
Jonas hodges is in possession
of a military-grade bioweapon.
I was contaminated when trying
to intercept the canisters.
I promise you,sir,the
weapon is on your base.
Do you have any idea
where they might be?
Think I might.
I have an order from the
president of the united states.
To search this building.
Are there weapons of mass destruction?
Are there weapons of any kind?
You've got five minutes to get these helicopters
flying out of here with all of you on board.
Larry,I want you and your men
to pull out on hodges' timetable.
Tony,you're gonna need  to
find a way to stay behind.
We're gonna get your vectors  over to a
man  that we contacted  inside starkwood.
His name is douglas knowles. He
believes he knows where the weapons are.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Jack! We need a medic!
The bioagent is more
virulent than we thought.
All we're doing here is
just masking the symptoms.
I understand.
- There's something you may want to consider.
- What's that?
A possible treatment using stem cells
from a genetically compatible donor.
I saw your file,and it
says you have a daughter.
I don't want my daughter
involved in this.
Jack.It should be her choice.
Well,it's not. I'm the one who's dying.
I'm in. But they got knowles.
A little loyalty.
Wasn't that the least I deserved?
You can't take on the
federal government.
I have a visual on the weapon.
Okay,those are the canisters.
I'll notify admiral smith the
target is located and confirmed.
You remember starkwood
was deployed to pakistan,
that we requisitioned a
missile system at that time.
Well,three of those missiles
are now loaded with a pathogen
and aimed at cities on
our eastern seaboard.
You will keep this conversation to
yourself and turn the planes around.
And if you do not
comply,madam president,
I will have no choice but
to launch those missiles.
Abort the air strike,admiral smith.
- Ma'am,with all respect...
- damn it,admiral.
Abort the air strike immediately!
**********
Tony,it's jack. Do you copy?
Jack,what the hell is going on?
Where are those f-18s?
Tim woods just called
from the white house.
The president canceled the air strike.
What? Why?
She doesn't believe our intel is strong
enough to justify military action.
Is she out of her mind?
Jack,I saw those
canisters with my own eyes.
So did you. They're in that bunker.
She's not gonna get any
better intel than that.
I know. It doesn't make
any sense,but right now,
we've got a presidential order to
pull you out of the starkwood compound,
along with the perimeter teams.
Tony,larry's been told
the president's decision.
He's preparing to move his teams out,but
he's got to get you out of there first.
He'll be sending you coordinates for an
exfiltration point along the southwest perimeter.
- Tony?
- Hold on a second.
Tony,what's going on?
Jack,I might know why the president
called off that air strike.
What do you mean?
I think starkwood's got
surface-to-surface missiles.
That's how they're gonna
deploy the bioweapon.
How do you know this?
A fuel truck just pulled up next to the
bunker where they're storing the weapons.
They're pumping rp-7
into an underground depot.
What's rp-7?
It's a propellant only used in
surface-to-surface missiles. Tony,are you sure?
I'm looking right at it,jack.
Do you have any c-4 on you?
Yeah,I've got three charges
and a remote detonator.
Do you think you can gain access
to the underground fuel depot?
Yeah,I think we've got a
play,but I've got to move soon...
before that fuel truck pulls away.
Okay,I want you to maintain your
position. I'm gonna call the president.
Come with me.
What is it,tim?
Madam president,the joint chiefs are
beginning to question your decision
to call off the air
strike against starkwood.
They think the intelligence we received
from tony almeida was sufficient
and that we may be missing an
opportunity to destroy the bioweapons.
I gave my orders,tim. No air strike.
No military action of any
kind against starkwood.
Now,I asked you to handle
the joint chiefs; handle them.
I'll do my best,ma'am,but if I may...
what is our next move?
Jonas hodges is coming
to the white house.
He wants to speak with me alone.
- For what possible reason?
- I don't know.
Madam president,shouldn't your
advisors be at that meeting?
Tim,stop asking me questions.
If you want to help,make sure as few people as
possible know that jonas hodges is coming here.
and bring him in through the
southeast service entrance.
Yes?
Madam president,jack bauer and
renee walker are calling from fbi.
You did speak to fbi?
Yes,ma'am,five minutes ago. I gave them
your reason for calling off the air strike,
but I must warn you,they
were skeptical as well.
Be ready for hodges.
Mr. Bauer,agent walker,this
is the president.
Madam president,we need to talk.
No,mr. Bauer,we don'T.
You need to listen.
I appreciate everything that you
have done in gathering this intel,
but I still need more before I can
authorize an air strike. I'm sorry.
Madam president,with all due respect,I
don't believe you're being truthful with us.
Excuse me?
I think you called off the
air strike because jonas hodges
is in possession of surface-to-surface
missiles armed with the bioweapon,
and he's threatening to use them in
case you try to take action against him.
Madam president,tony almeida witnessed
a truck pumping rp-7 rocket fuel
into an underground depot situated right next to
the bunker where the bioweapons are being stored.
The only purpose for rp-7 rocket
fuel is to launch missiles.
Madam president,please
just tell us the truth.
Jack,hodges has 13 python
missiles armed with the bioweapons.
Three are currently
aimed at american cities.
He demanded that i recall
the planes,or he would launch.
- What does hodges want?
- I don't know...
but he's requested a
face-to-face meeting.
He'll be at the white
house in a few minutes.
Madam president,the only reason he wants a
face-to-face meeting is to lay out his demands,
and whatever they are,you
cannot negotiate with him.
I'm not planning on
negotiating with him,jack.
Once he places his cards on the
table,I am sure that I can...
I can make him realize the
futility of what he is trying to do.
Jonas hodges is a traitor and a terrorist,and
after everything that's happened today,
are you really naive enough to believe that
you can simply talk to him and change his mind?
I'm not new at this,jack,and right
now,I don't have another option.
Madam president,you do. Tony
almeida is still inside starkwood.
I ordered him exfiltrated immediately.
What's he still doing there?
I asked him to stand by
until I could talk to you.
He believes he can gain
access to the fuel depot
and lay a series of explosive
charges and take the missiles out.
Now,I believe this can
work,but we need to act quickly.
What about the bioweapons?
Rp-7 rocket fuel
burns at 5,000 degrees.
There will be nothing left.
Once the weapons are destroyed,larry moss and his
teams can move in on starkwood and lock it down.
Hodges gave standing orders to his men to
launch the missiles at the first detection
of government inrference.
If almeida is detected,thousands
of americans will die,jack.
Madam president,I know
that there's a risk,
but I would not be asking you to do
this if I didn't think it would work.
Please,I am begging you. Trust me.
How long did the
doctors give you to live?
Uh,they're not sure,but the
pathogen has started to take effect.
Then there's not much i can
threaten you with,is there?
I expect you'll do
what you think is right.
what the hell does that mean?
She wants us to go in.
But she didn't authorize it.
She can'T. She needs this
to be a covert operation.
If something were to go wrong and
those missiles were to be launched,
the president needs to be able to swear
under oath that we were working on our own.
She wants us to go in. Notify
larry. We need to move fast.
I told you I'd get
you to the white house.
I just didn't think it would
be under these conditions.
It was brilliant,you know.
What was that,sir?
What you did to make almeida
think that you were betraying me.
- Quite brilliant.
- Thank you,sir.
You put yourself in harm's
way,greg,and I'll never forget that.
I can't believe... I'm feeling nervous.
You're gonna do fine,sir.
- Thank you,tim.
- You're welcome.
So,it sounds to me like the president
didn't actually authorize this.
Technically,no. It was more of an...
an indirect order,but believe
me,larry,she wants this to happen.
She's gonna meet with hodges,and
we're gonna blow those fuel tanks.
Larry,do you have a problem with this?
As a matter of fact,no. None whatsoever.
These starkwood bastards drew on my men.
I'm looking forward to getting back in there.
All right,have your teams hold
their position and be ready to move.
- Believe me,you'll know when it happens.
- All right.
- Tony,it's jack. Do you copy?
- Yeah,I'm here.
You were right about the missiles.
The president confirmed it.
We're gonna have to carry
this out as a covert operation.
Larry and his men are standing by to lock down
starkwood as soon as the missiles have been destroyed.
- Good.
- Tony...
I need to know that you can
do this without being detected.
Hodges's given his men standing orders to launch
those missiles if there's a breach of any kind.
Yeah. I can do it.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Yeah.
We're done here.
I'm going to go run a perimeter check.
You said you just finished one.
I know.
But I don't think we can
be too careful right now.
- Yeah.
- it's me.
Auxiliary tanks are fueled and ready.
Confirmed. I'll be
down in a few minutes.
Copy that.
Freeze! Let me see your hands.
Almeida.
Put your gun on the ground. Slowly.
Kick it.
drag him under the truck. Now! Let's go!
Hands up.
What do you think you're doing?
You're going to take me
down to the fuel tanks.
Let's go.
Open it up.
Go ahead.
President will see you now.
Very good. Thank you.
Mr. Hodges.
Madam president.
This is greg seaton,my associate.
He's a remarkable man. Doesn't look
remarkle,but believe me,he's a genius.
Yes,I know mr. Seaton.
Thank you,gentlemen.
It never gets old,does it?
Stepping into the... the oval office.
Almost smells of history.
- Can we sit?
- Please.
You know,this is the first time I've
been in this room since you were elected?
I'm aware of that,yes.
Under your predecessor,I used to
drop by every couple of months.
I'd brief president daniels on what
was really going on in the world.
And you've been excluded now.
- Is that what this is about?
- No,ma'am.
It's about allowing starkwood to fulfill
the purpose for which it was founded:
Protecting this country.
You have been attacking this country.
You and general juma have killed
hundreds of innocent people,
including my son.
Madam president,I'm
deeply sorry for your loss,
and my heart breaks for all
the lives that were taken today,
but I'm shocked that you would think
that I had anything to do with it.
We have evidence that you've
been working with juma.
Your intelligence
agencies have failed you.
If I had kno what juma was up to,I would
have done everything in my power to stop him.
So let's push aside all these baseless
accusations and maybe we can do some business here.
I'm listening.
Madam president,I know
you're a student of history,
and so you're well aware
that our nation's independence
was won with the aid of private armies,
and we can't survive without them.
Look how easy it was to get
bioweapons into this country.
Our defenses are fragile.
They're on the verge of collapse.
But it's not too late
to do something about it.
So what are you suggesting?
In short,I want a seat at the table.
Starkwood needs to be involved in the shaping
of military policy,domestic and global.
It sounds more like you want a
seat at the head of the table.
Madam president,I'm notere
to supplant your authority.
What I'm proposing is a partnership.
Think of starkwood as the fifth
branch of the military. Greg?
This contains the protocols that will
serve as the basis of our agreement.
I suggest that we review them together.
Jonas,I agreed to this meeting because
I wanted to hear what you had to say.
But what you're proposing is blackmail.
Well,that's putting it in
the worst possible light.
You are threatening to
kill thousands of people.
I'm not proud of this chapter.
I'm the first to admit it.
And it's time to turn the page. This
country has seen enough bloodshed today.
For the sake of the american
people,madam president,
I implore you to work with
me,and let's move past this.
Pick up the document,madam president.
Let's go. Come on. Get up
now,or I'll leave you down here.
And you don't want that
believe me. Get up! Let's go!
what is it?
Code 363. That's a government breach.
- We're supposed to launch.
- Are you sure it's not a false alarm?
No way to tell.
We've got standing orders,though.
Let's start the launch sequence.
too late.
Launch sequence complete.
Target is locked.
Enter the firing codes.
Sir,we need to confirm this.
That's not the correct protocol.
We're about to kill 10,000 people.
We should get someone on the phone.
Enter the codes. Now!
No,sir.
that's it. That's us. Let's
go. We're a go! We're a go!
- it's done.
- Tony?
Tony,do you copy?
An explosion of that magnitude
would have shorted out his com.
We're gonna have to wait for
larry and his men to move in.
It says here that you want active status
in the pentagon's strategic planning group.
That's correct.
That would give you access to
level 6 classified material.
Not even the vice president
has that clearance.
These points are nonnegotiable.
I'm not here to debate them.
Let's review the next section,which concerns
senate oversight of starkwood field operations.
I'm sorry to interrupt,madam
president,but I need to speak with you.
Can it wait?
No,ma'am,it can'T.
- Will you excuse me for a moment?
- Of course.
satcom has just detected a massive
explosion on the starkwood compound.
The bioweapons facility
has been destroyed.
- Are you sure?
- Yes,ma'am.
Judging by the size of the
explosion,nothing could have survived.
But I don't know how this
happened. This wasn't us.
- Call fbi and have them lock down starood.
- They're already moving in.
Good. And when this is over,I
want to speak to jack bauer.
- Yes,ma'am.
- You know...
I'm not sure I'm reaching her.
I think you handled it perfectly,sir.
We'll see.
What the hell is this?
Put this document into evidence,and
take these men into custody.
What are you thinking?
Have you lost your mind?
Jonas,we've taken out
your missiles. It's over.
That's impossible.
It's the truth.
And you're under arrest.
You are a terrorist and a murderer,
and I'm gonna do everything in my power to
make sure that you pay dearly for your crimes.
My only crime is that I'm
trying to protect my country!
You think this ends with me?
I'm just a small cog
in a very big machine.
Hold on.
You can't even begin to
imagine what you're up against.
What are you talking about?
You'll find out.
Get him out of here.
the advanced biohazard team is reporting no trace
of the bioweapon anywhere near the blast sight.
- It was incinerated in the explosion.
- Good.
- Any word on tony?
- Not yet. Larry's searching the compound now.
We should hear something soon.
Mr. Bauer,you have a phone
call; it's the president.
I'll take it in the conference
room. Thank you. I'll be right back.
Madam president.
Mr. Bauer,jonas hodges is under arrest.
That's good news. That's very good.
Jack,you and your team
provided me with an option.
And for that,I am deeply grateful.
And so are the american people.
Madam president,it was tony almeida who
risked his life to destroy those missiles.
And as you know,he's facing arrest
for things he did leading up to today,
and I was hoping that maybe you could...
yes,mr. Bauer?
Jack?
Um,I'm sorry,I...
completely forgot what I was saying.
You were talking about mr. Almeida.
And my answer is yes,I-I will
take his actions into account.
Thank you.
What's happening?
I-I-I'm not
exactly sure.
Jack,I am so sorry
you're going through this.
I wish that there were
something I could do.
M-madam president,I
appreciate this phone call.
But I'm sorry. I-I have to go.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
jonas hodges has been arrested.
Let me know as soon as you got tony.
I need to go see dr. Mace
Yes,madam president?
Call ben landry at cdc.
Tell him that I want real-time
updates on jack bauer's condition.
Yes,ma'am.
we've secured all entry points and command posts and
are sweeping the compound on a grid-by-grid basis.
- Are you meeting any resistance?
- No.
They're surrendering
peacefully and cooperating.
St of the men on this base,I don't think
they had any idea what was going on.
What about almeida?
- Uh,he's here. We found him.
- Is he okay?
Some cuts and bruises,but
otherwise,he's in pretty good shape.
Good. Good. Jack will
be glad to hear that.
Listen,renee...
we've known each other
a long time,you know.
Um,so much stuff has happened today.
Yeah. We have a lot
to talk about. I know.
Excuse me,agent walker.
- Your visitshe's in the waiting area.
- Okay,thank you.
Larry,I've got to go. Kim bauer's here.
- Jack's daughter? - Yes.
I-I asked her to come.
There's this experimental treatment for jack's
disease,but he needs compatible stem cells.
It's a long shot,but it's
the only hope he's got.
Okay. Let me know how it goes,all right?
- I will. I'm going off com.
- All right.
did they say something about kim bauer?
Yeah,she's at fbi helping with a treatment for
jack,some,uh,some kind of stem cell therapy.
So they think he's gonna be all right?
Didn't sound promising.
Listen,tony,this isn't
easy for me,but,uh...
I'm under orders to take
you into federal custody.
- Yeah,I know.
- You did a brave thing here.
Probably saved thousands of lives.
For the record,I don't think
this is how you should be repaid.
I appreciate that,but,uh...
I'm ready to pay for what I've done.
Get the cuffs off him,will you?
Chopper's on the way. I'll be
taking you back to fbi,all right?
Memory loss is consistent
with the disease,mr. Bauer.
I just wouldn't have expected
it to manifest this quickly.
It's not just memory loss.
It feels like...
I don't know exactly how to explain it.
I feel like,uh,like I'm
losing some part of myself.
The disease profile includes personality
changes,sometimes even hallucinations.
But this is a weaponized
pathogen we don't know much about.
Military's still combing through the
remains of the bioweapons lab in sangala,
so we expect to learn
something very soon.
You were able to give me something
that controlled the shaking.
Is there anything that you can give
me that would help me with this?
No. I'm sorry.
Okay. Thank you. Excuse me.
jack,is it all right?
Yeah,um,I'm gonna need to go on record
about everything that happened today.
And we need to do it soon.
I'm not sure how much longer I'm gonna
be le to provide you with the details.
Okay. First,there's something
that you need to know.
What?
It's about kim. She's here,jack.
I told her that you were sick and that she
might be able to help with the treatment.
You did...
you did what? Come here. Come here.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You think this is easy?
You think you understand what I'm
going through? Because you don'T.
I am dying.
And I was okay with
it. I could handle it.
And now you've put in
front of me the one thing,
the one thing that is
gonna make this unbearable.
- Jack,listen...
- no,you listen to me.
I specifically told you do
not drag my daughter into this.
No one dragged her into anything.
She's been trying to see you all day.
What?
She was at the senate
hearing this morning.
She flew out from L.A.To be there,but we
pulled you out before she could see you.
She's been leaving messages
at our office all day.
They just didn't get to me till now.
If you want,I can tell
her that you're not here.
I can tell her that you can't see her.
Can't do that.
- Where is she?
- Down the hall.
Show me.
daddy.
How are you feeling?
I'm-I'm okay.
You're not in any pain?
No.
Come sit down.
Did agent walker tell you
that I was trying to find you?
Yeah.
I've tried everything to track you down:
State department,private investigators.
Every time I got a phone number or
an address,you were already gone.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was doing the best
thing for you by staying away.
Daddy,I've missed you so much.
I've missed you,too.
You need to know how sorry I am for everything
that you've had to live through because of me.
No,don't do that.
Don't put that on yourself. I'm
the one that should apologize.
I pushed you away.
And instead of taking responsibility for all
the mistakes I've made in my life,I blamed you.
And it was stupid and immature.
And now,all the time that we've lost...
agent walker told me that there's
a chance-- a small chance--
that I could help you,and
you don't want me to.
The treatment is experimental.
and I don't think it's going to work.
And you don't want to because
you're afraid to ask me.
No.
There's a risk to you.
A small risk... worth taking.
Not to me.
Kim... I'm dying.
And whatever small chance there
is to stop that from happening--
it is not worth the pain for me to
let you sit there and watch me die.
Daddy,I don't want to lose you.
- Come here.
- I don'T.
sweetheart,it's going to be all right.
It's gonna be all right. I promise you.
what is it? what?
sweetheart,I'm sorry...
but you need to go.
Please,baby,please,I'm begging you.
- I love you so much.
- Honey,I love you,too.
Please,baby. thank you. Go.
perimeter 2 to dispatch:
Auxiliary gate 6 is clear.
Copy that,p-2. Hold your position.
Freeze! Show me your hands. Get 'em up!
P-2 to dispatch.
I have an agent down and a
suspect in custody. Code red.
Copy that,p-2.
All available agents
respond to auxiliary gate 6.
Drop the bag.
Hands on the hood.
P-2 to dispatch. Put me through
to agent moss. It's urgent.
agent moss.
Agent moss,this is davis
at auxiliary gate 6.
I have a starkwood op in custody.
He killed one of our agents.
He was carrying a canister of the bioweapon,trying
to smuggle it out using one of our vehicles.
What? Are you sure?
I'm looking at it right now.
Agent davis? Davis?
- walker.
- Renee,we got a breach in the cordon at gate 6.
One of the starkwood ops-- he's
got a canister of the bioweapon.
What?
It was id'd by agent davis,who
I believe has just been shot.
The suspect may be
fleeing in an fbi vehicle,
so I need you to close down all access roads,and
alert perimeter units  and metro police.
- Janis,get me dc metro.
- I'm gonna pursue it from the air.
Let's go! Let us up!
renee,alert homeland,let
them know what's going on.
Are we thinking this
is another attack,larry?
I don't know,but there's enough prion variant in
one of those canisters to take out a small city.
Agent miller,are there any major roadways in our
perimeter that starkwood eratives could have used?
Yes,sir. We're coming up on highway 42.
Should I turn us that way?
Yes,until we get a stronger
directive from agent walker.
Roger that.
Yes,sir. We'll keep homeland
apprised with real-time updates.
Did you access the gps locator system?
Yeah,I'm scanning transponders
for the stolen fbi vehicle.
How long will that take?
As long as it takes for
the satellite to reposition.
When you spoke to larry,you
mentioned an attack?
The starkwood operative we're trying to
find stole a canister of the bioweapon.
I thought tony almeida
destroyed all the weapons.
Apparently not.
how did this operative
get past our perimeter?
Shot and killed two of our agents.
This is it.
The suspect is getting off
highway 42 at smoketree avenue.
He's heading toward
the industrial corridor.
- Put me on the interagency channel.
- Go ahead.
All units,this is agent walker with fbi.
Suspect has exited
highway 42 at smoketree.
He's heading north into
the industrial corridor.
Units in the vicinity,please respond.
Renee,it's me. We're
over smoketree right now.
We're redirecting,and
we'll tighten our pursuit.
Got it. I'll reroute swat
team alpha to the scene.
Swat team alpha,we need to set up a
roadblock at the fairfax county line.
Dc metro's covering the district
line in case he tries to double back.
********
Sir. I have a visual.
Yeah. Got him.
Send us lower.
yeah,he's pulling off the
road. Get us down there now.
renee,it's larry. Suspect is on
foot. We can't wait for backup.
- We're moving in right now.
- All right. Swat team's a few minutes out.
- Careful,larry.
- Yeah.
Remember,suspect has a
canister,so pick your shots.
If possible,let's take him alive.
Yes,sir.
we got to get out of here.
Almeida,cover. Let's go.
Come on!
- relax.
- I'm okay.
Relax.
Tony.
tony! Tony!
what...
I'm sorry,larry.
god...
let me see it.
How the hell do we get out of here?
I want you to take
this,find a place to hide.
- Wait for my call.
- What about you?
I'm gonna wait on the fbi,figure
out a way to get you out of here. Go!
www.tvsubtitles.net