[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
What the hell is this? All our screens
for the eastern quadrant are locked.
I took out your control units.
I want you to see what we can do.
Get ready to make the course change.
- G.S.A. 117, this is Northeast Three Control.
- Go ahead, Air Traffic Control.
We have a new runway assignment for you.
Sid, there's another plane landing on 4 Right.
It crosses 31 Left.
G.S.A. 117, pull up.
4 Right, pull up.
[Passengers Screaming]
That was just a warning shot.
Whatever we do next, it'll be the real thing.
- Get the module ready.
- [Emerson] As promised.
GeneralJuma will be pleased.
Perhaps now would be a good time to make
your demands known to President Taylor.
Make the preparations.
Your government is about to pay...
a very steep price
for interfering in our affairs.
They assumed my son killed himself.
They didn't look deeply enough
at anything.
The authorities have already questioned
your son's girlfriend, sir.
You're not going anywhere
till I get the truth.
- Sir.
- You know who murdered my son.
He killed himself.
I'm gonna find out what you're hiding.
And when I do, God help you.
You're right.
He's not one of ours.
- We'll follow him, see if
he leads us to Almeida. Dornan!
- That's not the right move.
You can't bring anyone else into this.
- What the hell's goin' on?
We're following up on a lead, and
I will fill you in if and when we find something.
I do not like this.
I just flat-out lied to my boss.
I told you I would help you find Tony Almeida,
but you're gonna have to let me do it my way.
Tony! Stop!
The device is gone.
The locator files have been deleted.
Where is it?
What the hell happened to you?
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 10:00 a.m. And 11:00 a.m.
- Where's Almeida now?
- He's in transit to F.B.I. Headquarters.
- He'll be formally interrogated there.
- I don't understand.
Almeida was orchestrating these attacks.
Lfhe doesn't have the C.I.P. Device,
who does?
[Kanin] The F.B.I. Has learned that Almeida
handed off the device to someone else.
- They don't know who.
- I may have an answer to that question,
Madam President.
- I'm listening.
- Almeida's working for theJuma regime.
Approximately five minutes ago, an audio message
was routed to the State Department subnet.
It's from Colonel Iké Dubaku.
He's Juma's right-hand man.
He's known as the Butcher of Sangala.
- Over 300,000 people were murdered.
- I know who he is.
What did the message say?
Think you should hear it yourself.
President Taylor,
this is Colonel Iké Dubaku.
As you have no doubt confirmed...
the near collision atJ.F.K.
International was no accident.
We have the C.I.P. Device.
We have the capability...
to kill tens of thousands of Americans...
and we are prepared to do so.
We demand the complete and immediate
withdrawal of the U.S. Naval strike force...
to a position west of the 23rd meridian
by this time tomorrow.
In order to meet this timeline...
we require satellite confirmation
within three hours...
that the carrier air wing
is in full retreat.
Don't sacrifice your fellow countrymen...
Madam President.
Allow the people of Sangala
to determine their own destiny.
Stand your forces down.
Voiceprint's an 89% match.
It's Dubaku.
- There's little doubt.
- Looks like your suspicions were correct,
Madam President.
- This is about Africa.
- My God.
Dubaku should have been tried
for war crimes years ago.
Now he's giving us ultimatums.
We cannot let this monster hold our country
hostage. Where do we stand on the planes?
There's still 2,500 planes in the air.
We have got to shore up the firewall...
so that the C.I.P. Device
will be rendered useless.
We now think we can reengineer
the code in six days.
Six days? We don't have
the luxury of six hours.
I'm sorry, Madam President, but there's no way
we can rebuild the firewall in that time frame.
I want you to instigate
a series of restricted alerts.
Keep it to first responders only.
We want people to be ready
in case we're attacked again...
- but we don't want to start a panic.
- Yes, Madam President.
And gentlemen, Almeida is our only lead.
Make sure the F.B.I.
Is aware of the demands.
They need to work Almeida
from the Africa side...
- and they need to know
we don't have a lot of time.
- Yes, ma'am.
Come on.
Keep your head down.
Get him ready for questioning.
I want an explanation.
You went after that shooter without backup
or authorization, and then refused to tell me why.
- Now, I wanna know.
- Look, we didn't know who might be listening.
- Someone in this office is helping Almeida.
- What?
The F.B.I. Has been compromised, Larry.
There's a leak.
Based on what?
Excuse me! This is private.
Tony knew we were going to Schector's
office before we even got there.
That's how he managed
to get a sniper in position.
The tip had to come from your office.
And whoever it was helped Schector's
assassin get out of the building.
He's right, Larry.
That's why we couldn't tell you.
You had a full perimeter, right?
Covered every exit?
How else do you think he got out of there?
All right. Assuming this is true,
you got any idea who it could be?
No. We didn't see it.
But we know that it went down.
It could be anyone in the Bureau.
You need to tighten
your circle around Tony.
You can't let any information that he gives you
get back to the people he's working with...
otherwise you will never
get that C.I.P. Device.
- All right.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
We'll limit access to
Level Four clearance and above.
HaveJanis run the security protocols.
- See if she can track down this lead.
- [Cell Phone Beeps]
- It's Moss.
- [Man] Sir, I have the White House calling.
- Yeah, I'll- I'll take it in my office.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
- [Cell Phone Beeps]
It's the White House.
From now on, keep me in the loop.
And he doesn't do a damn thing
without telling me.
[Exhales]
- We had to tell him. We had no choice.
- You trust him?
No question.
There's no one I trust more.
Where are they gonna hold Tony?
I am gonna have to lift up your shirt.
Is that comfortable for you?
Take that as a yes.
- [Renee] Is he hooked up?
- [Janis] Yeah, we're ready to go.
Janis, I'll run this session.
I want you to handle something else.
- What else?
- Plugging a security leak.
What?
We think someone in this office
has been helping Almeida.
They've kicked this up
to Level Four clearance.
I want you to vet all communication
and information flow.
Red tag every data point
that has to do with Almeida.
[Janis] Okay. Well, do we have
any idea who it is?
- No, we don't.
I'm hoping you can help us find out.
- Okay.
[Exhales] Okay, there's a 0.2 deviation
on the blood pressure monitor...
and you're gonna have
to compensate for that.
Thanks, Janis.
[Door Closes]
Sorry about your friend, Jack.
I know you were hoping...
he wasn't capable
of doing something like this.
Yeah.
[Chattering]
- Hey, what's going on?
Why are we in Level Four lockdown?
- Don't worry about it.
- Just do your job.
- How am I supposed to do my job...
when I can't get through to half
the server nodes in the building?
You're sifting through the evidence
gathered at Almeida's arrest site.
That does not require
Level Four clearance.
You have everything you need
to do your work. Please.
[Speaking French]
Nichols.
It's confirmed.
The F.B.I. Has Almeida.
Then we should move on.
There's nothing we can do.
No. We have assets inside the Bureau.
We use them to help get him out.
No, it's too risky. We'd be
jeopardizing the entire mission.
- Almeida's not that important.
- What about the next operation? Tony's prepped.
- He's ready to go.
- You'll just have to find someone else.
I realize you and Tony are friends.
I don't like throwing him to the wolves
any more than you do.
But he knew what he was getting into.
I just spoke with Juma. The American troops
are still in position near our country.
TellJuma to be patient.
President Taylor just received
your demands.
Then perhaps it is time for
a more forceful demonstration.
If it comes to that, we'll be ready.
For now, let's give the White House
a little more time to respond.
For now.
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Door Opens]
Agent Walker.
[Door Closes]
Almeida's working for theJuma regime.
- What are you talking about?
- The president just received a set of demands.
- They're from Colonel Iké Dubaku.
- Dubaku?
Looks like he contracted Almeida
to build the C.I.P. Module.
- And now, he's using it
to blackmail the White House.
- How?
- Excuse me?
- How is he gonna blackmail the White House?
By insisting we stand down
the invasion force off the coast of Sangala.
If the president doesn't
comply with his demands...
Dubaku is gonna start killing Americans.
I can get you your C.I.P. Device.
Just let me talk to him.
I know him. I know how he thinks.
We have a history.
I can use it against him.
He's gotten us this far, Larry.
It makes sense.
You're running out of time.
You don't have a better option.
[Sighs]
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Door Opens]
Give us the room.
[Door Closes]
I watched you die in my arms.
You want to explain to me
how you're still alive?
[Scoffs] Didn't think so.
Why don't I tell you what I know.
I know that you're working
for theJuma regime.
The White House
just got their demands...
and you have to know
that I will never let that happen.
So why don't you
save yourself some time...
and some pain...
and tell me
where the C.I.P. Device is.
- I can't tell you that, Jack.
- Damn it, Tony.
You are not just facing charges
for domestic terrorism.
You are gonna face international charges
for aiding and abetting a genocide.
They will give you the death penalty.
Come on. Just work with me on this.
I could help you cut a deal.
I can maybe even get you immunity.
You're wasting your breath, Jack.
If I were you...
I'd tell the president to withdraw those troops,
because Dubaku's serious.
He's ready to take thousands of American lives
unless his demands are met.
Why the hell are you doing this?
Juma wanted the C.I.P. Module,
and he was willing to pay for it.
- I don't believe you.
- Come on, Jack.
Don't act so surprised.
Money is the only reason
I have left for doin' anything.
The government took care of that.
The government did not kill Michelle.
Charles Logan did.
Charles Logan is a product
of his environment.
The government poisons
everything in its path.
You know that better than me, Jack.
Look what they did to you.
Damn it, Tony!
We are not talking about me!
Oh, we're not?
You're asking me why I'm doing this.
I could ask you the same question.
Here you are, working for the same people
who wanna put you in prison.
The same people who killed everything
you love and left you with nothing.
- Your daughter wants nothing
to do with you, Teri's dead-
- Shut up.
- Audrey Raines, Miles-
- I said shut up!
No, Jack! No! You need to hear this!
You need to start living in the real world!
Because every second you help the government,
you're spittin' on Teri's grave!
Get up!
- He's losing it.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Tell me where the device is!
- [Breathing Rapidly]
So help me God, I will kill you,
and you will stay dead this time.
Where is the device?
[Grunts]
This is your last chance.
Where is it?
- Where is it?
- [Grunting]
Deep Sky.
What did you just say?
- Son of a bitch.
- Give him a few more seconds.
- Few more seconds, he'll be dead.
- Deep Sky.
Jack, let him go!
Get him out ofhere!
- [Gasping]
- Get him out of here, now!
[Gasping Continues]
I need a medic in here to check him out.
- Keep an eye on him.
- You got it.
- [Beeps]
- Deep Sky.
[Beeping]
[Modulated Voice]
Hello.
- This is Jack Bauer.
- Yes?
- I was told to call you.
- By whom?
Tony Almeida.
He gave me this old C.T.U.
Emergency phone code- Deep Sky.
[Beeps]
It's Bill, Jack.
Bill, what the hell's going on?
- Where is Tony?
- F.B.I. Headquarters. He's been arrested.
Arrested?
He orchestrated a terrorist attack
on the United States today.
I was interrogating him.
- How'd you get involved in this?
- The F.B.I. Brought me in to help track him down.
We need to talk, Jack.
I'll call you back
on a secure V.P.N. Line.
- What the hell is going on?
- I need 10 minutes to set up the V.P.N. Line.
- I don't have 10 minutes!
- Ten minutes, Jack.
I can't believe this.
LfTony's been arrested, it's over.
Are you gonna tellJack everything?
We wanna get Tony back undercover,
we'll need his help.
I don't thinkJack's
in a very helpful frame of mind.
He's our only hope.
[Beeping]
- Hello, Henry.
- Ethan.
I got your message about Sangala.
- Where's Allison?
- She's in her office.
Henry-
The president is in
an impossible situation right now.
She needs your support,
but you can't give it to her...
if you keep going off on these
paranoid fantasies about Roger.
I know about Samantha Roth.
I know you accosted her in her office.
She's hiding something
about my son's murder.
Roger wasn't murdered.
He committed suicide.
The coroner's office made that determination,
and the F.B.I. Confirmed it.
They didn't look hard enough.
Ethan, I know my son.
He did not kill himself.
- He wasn't depressed. He had no reason.
- What if he did have a reason?
- I would have known.
- Not if he didn't tell you.
Not if he was too ashamed to tell you
or the president.
What are you talking about?
Roger was about to be investigated
by the S.E.C. For insider trading.
He'd used information
he could only have gotten...
through his access to the president.
Before the S.E.C. Opened the investigation,
he killed himself.
I don't believe it.
It's all in here...
in the S.E.C. Case file.
Why is this the first time
I'm hearing about this?
Frank Boylan agreed to bury the case...
as a political favor to the president.
My wife knew about this,
and she didn't tell me?
She wanted to. But she also wanted
to protect your memory of your son.
- You were in so much pain-
- Damn it, Ethan, he was my son.
I deserved the truth.
And keeping it from you
was a terrible mistake.
I realize that now.
But the president and I both thought...
you were moving on with your life.
Mr. Kanin.
The president wants to see you.
Does she know you're telling me this now?
No. And I think it best
we keep it that way...
at least till this crisis is resolved.
I felt I had to tell him, sir.
I'm sorry.
[Man, Indistinct]
All right. Thank you.
[Kanin]
Madam President, you wanted to see me?
Admiral Smith laid out the timeline
for withdrawing our forces.
He's saying to meet Dubaku's demands...
we need to order the pullback
by 1:00 p.m.
- [Exhales] That's not much time.
- No, it isn't.
Well, maybe this man Almeida will tell us
where to find the C.I.P. Device.
No. Tim Woods
just heard from the Bureau.
So far, Almeida's
refusing to cooperate.
- Well, maybe he's just positioning for a deal.
- Tim doesn't think so.
He said we shouldn't count
on Almeida to talk.
I see.
So...
unless I order our forces
to stand down...
I'll be condemning
innocent Americans to death.
And if we capitulate...
thousands of Sangalans
will be slaughtered.
How did this happen, Ethan?
How could we have been
so caught off guard?
And now, to have to decide
between two impossible choices.
Well, at least one of those choices...
does stand a good chance
of preserving American lives.
- You mean withdrawal.
- We are nearing the time
where we may have to consider it.
We're not there yet, Ethan.
I can't discuss this...
not until we have explored
every possible option.
Tell the F.B.I. To keep
working on Almeida.
Yes, Madam President.
[Beeping]
Mr. Buchanan,
I've got the secure line.
- All right. Dial the number.
- [Beeping]
[Ringing]
Bill, stop screwin' around.
Tell me what the hell is going on.
Jack, Tony is not a terrorist. He's working
deep cover. He's working with me.
We have proof that he tried to bring down
two commercial airliners.
You don't know the whole story.
It's part of an ongoing operation.
Operation? What kind of an operation puts
hundreds if not thousands of lives in danger?
Jack, please. You need to listen.
Our government is corrupted.
There are people on the inside who are
actively aiding Dubaku and theJuma regime.
Point is, Tony was supposed
to be near the C.I.P. Module the whole time.
With him in custody, we've lost our ability
to control it and to attack this conspiracy.
Who's a part of the conspiracy?
Give me names.
We don't know the extent of it,
but we have reason to believe...
that members of the president's
inner council are on payroll.
Who's shepherding the investigation?
Which agency?
That's just it, Jack.
There's no shepherd.
There's no agency.
This corruption runs deep and wide.
We're working outside the government.
That's why we have to
get Tony back undercover.
He's at F.B.I. Headquarters, Bill.
I never said it was gonna be easy.
But we have to try.
- Chloe's already into their system.
- Chloe's working on this?
- Hi, Jack. It's good to hear your voice.
- Yeah, you too.
I saw the hearings on C-SPAN.
I can't believe what the senator said to you.
You looked good, though.
[Buchanan] Jack, we need your help
to get Tony out of there.
There's an agent at the F.B.I.
Renee Walker.
- She could help.
- No, the F.B.I. Been compromised.
Somebody in the Bureau is aiding Dubaku.
You don't understand, Bill.
I trust her.
If you think you need to use her to get Tony
out of F.B.I. Headquarters, then do it.
But you'll be making her a target.
No, you're right.
You're right. We'll do it your way.
I can get to Tony myself.
- But Chloe's gonna have to
get us out of the building.
- We're already on it.
- Get back to me as soon as you're ready.
- I'm on my way, Chloe.
[Beeping]
Hey, Sean, you know those data-mining
plug-ins we downloaded last week?
Where did we file those?
Uh, yeah.
File folder A-76.
- Do you need help with something?
- No. Why?
You seem confused.
I just don't like havin' to dance around
this Level Four lockdown.
Oh. I thought you'd welcome the opportunity
to complain about something.
[Cell Phone Rings]
- [Beeps]
- Hello?
Mr. Taylor, it's Samantha.
I was going to call you.
I owe you an apology, Sam.
- I was wrong to confront you like that.
- Uh, no, you weren't.
- I wasn't completely honest with you.
- What do you mean?
Roger didn't commit suicide, Mr. Taylor.
He was murdered.
I need to see you, alone.
Will you meet me?
Of course.
[Larry]
Where's the C.I.P. Device, Tony?
Who'd you give it to?
The people you're taking money from-
thought you'd might like to see
some of their handiwork.
You know how many people they've killed
since they went back into Sangala?
Huh?
200,000 and counting.
Most of them women and children.
Tony.
You really want this on your conscience?
My conscience is clear.
And nothing you can say or do will change that.
So why don't you do the smart thing...
and tell President Taylor
to stand down the strike force.
Because unless she does,
planes will be falling from the sky.
And then you'll have a whole new
batch of photos to look at.
Only this time...
they'll be of dead Americans.
Larry, we need to talk.
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Door Opens]
- Almeida's not gonna break.
- We don't know that.
He's a trained C.T.U. Agent.
He's conducted interrogations
just like this one.
There's nothing you can say to him that
he hasn't said himself a hundred times.
- So what are you suggesting? We give up?
- No.
I'm suggesting we might need
a more forceful approach.
- You mean torture.
- There are methods of coercion
we haven't even considered.
- Pharmaceuticals-
- I can't believe you want
to have this conversation.
- You're not hearing the argument.
- The argument is crazy.
It's illegal, and it's over.
As a matter of fact,
I want Bauer out of here.
He's a wild card. He's dangerous.
I want him out of the building.
Go. Process him out.
I will continue here.
Go, go, now.
[Sighs]
Renee, I was just about to call you.
I may have found the leak.
Someone did a runaround
on the Level Four lockdown.
They circumvented the security fence
and they hacked into the F.A.A. Database.
- F.A.A. Are you sure?
- Positive. I don't know what
they were doing in there...
but they had to navigate some
very sophisticated tagger software.
- When was this?
- Just a few minutes ago.
- Any idea who it was?
- No, but I might be able to pull
a user I.D. Out of the terminal.
- Okay. Which terminal?
- Mainframe room, terminal three.
- Check it out. Let me know what you find.
- Okay.
Agent Teller. I need you to prepare
a debriefing packet forJack Bauer.
- And bring me his personal effects.
- I'll bring 'em right to you.
Thanks.
I'll be in my office.
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Lock Clicks]
[Keyboard Clacking]
- [Door Closes]
- What are you doin'?
What's the matter?
S-You just stay where you are.
Janis, stop it.
Would you just talk to me?
I know you've been helping Tony Almeida.
What?
Are you crazy?
No. You broke into the F.A.A. Database.
That's your server I.D.
Yeah, it's my server I.D.,
but I'm not helping the terrorists.
You wanna know why I was in there?
I'll tell you.
I was worried. My wife is on one of
those planes up there.
- I had to see if her flight had been grounded yet.
- You expect me to believe that?
- Why are you sneaking around?
- Because of the Level Four lockdown.
It cut me out of the F.A.A. Database.
I couldn't monitor her flight.
Look.
See for yourself.
- [Keyboard Clacking]
- Flight 112 out of Las Vegas.
- Christina Hillinger.
- Okay. Just stay there.
[Beeping]
God, Sean!
You scared the hell out of me!
Why wouldn't you just tell me that?
'Cause what I was doin' was borderline illegal.
I didn't wanna get you in trouble.
Plus, you looked like
you had enough on your plate.
Damn it, I told Renee
I'd found a security leak.
Is that what's going on around here?
There's a security leak?
Don't worry about it.
Go back to your station.
Keep this to yourself,
and I will clean up your mess.
Go.
- [Door Opens, Closes]
- Idiot.
- [Cell Phone Rings]
- Go ahead.
Jack, Agent Walker is on her way. She's
heading down the corridor toward your room.
Copy that.
How you doing with the loops?
I'm dropping the first one in now.
I have a series of loops.
I'm gonna drop them as you go.
Security won't see a thing.
- [Renee] That's all right.
I'll take it from here.
- Understand.
Standing by.
[Door Opens]
Hey.
Sorry, Jack. We're proceeding without you.
It wasn't my decision.
We wouldn't have Almeida without you.
We owe you a lot.
Thanks.
- That paperwork for me?
- Yeah. Need you to fill this out.
I want you to know I'm gonna put in a good
word with theJustice Department for you.
- Maybe it'll help.
- Thanks.
Jack!
- Don't fight it.
- Jack!
Don't fight it.
[Loud Thud]
[Beeping]
[Chloe] Jack just took out Agent Walker.
He has her key card and her weapon.
He's going to get Tony.
What's your location?
- About 10 minutes out.
- Did you get my rendezvous point?
- [Electronic Tone]
- Just showed up on my G.P.S.
- Okay, great.
- [Beeping]
I've gotta go. It's Jack.
Jack?
I'm ready.
I've got access to Interrogation One.
- What's Bill's E.T.A.
- About 10 minutes.
- How's the corridor?
- Clear.
Wait for my call.
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Lock Clicks]
[Door Opens]
- Put your weapons down. Now!
- What the hell do you think you're doing?
I said do it now!
- Do it, or I will kill him.
- Okay. A II right.
- Put it down. It's all right. Do it.
- Slowly.
Slowly!
Now you.
Do it!
All right.
Kick your weapon over to me.
- Come on!
- Okay. All right.
Uncuff him.
- Where's Agent Walker? What did you do to her?
- Shut up.
- Bauer, you're not gonna make it out of here.
- I said shut up!
- I talked to Bill.
- How much did he tell you?
Enough. We're gonna get you out of here.
Chloe's tapped into their security.
She's gonna walk us out of this building.
- All you need to do is follow my lead.
- All right.
- Chloe, it's Jack. Do you copy?
- Copy, Jack.
I got Tony at the door of Interrogation One
leading out to the hallway.
Okay, I see you. I'm gonna
direct you to the southwest exit.
Right now, you're in the least
populated area of the building...
but you're gonna run into a lot more resistance
before you get out of there.
- Copy that. You ready?
- [Chloe] Clear to move.
Let's go.
Hold up. There's two people
coming out of the elevator.
Copy that. Come on.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Listen, Jack, I'm sorry
about the stuff I said back there.
I just needed to get you close enough
to give you Bill's code name.
I'm just glad I didn't break your neck.
Well, uh, you came close.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
- [Chloe] Okay, clear.
- We're clear.
I cleaned up your trail. So we'll just keep
this little transgression between us.
Although I don't know
what I'm gonna tell Renee.
Have you heard one thing I've just said?
Yeah. Yeah, that's fine.
Take a look at this.
- What?
- There's a performance hit
on one of our signal routers.
It's down 0.7%.
You're right.
Somebody's riding our bandwidth.
Hacking in? Is that possible
with all the safeguards?
Anything is possible
if you know what you're doing.
They're inside our security subnet.
They've accessed the surveillance system.
- What are you gonna do?
- Lock them out.
Okay, Jack, you're gonna make
a left down the next hallway.
There's an emergency stairwell at the end.
- Will that stairwell
get us down to the ground level?
- Yes.
Copy that.
- Hold on.
- What's wrong?
- I've lost my feed.
- Chloe's feed just went down.
What'd you do?
I pinged the line,
and it automatically reset.
Someone was hacking in.
They were taking out our surveillance cameras.
- Janis, take a look at this.
- Send it to me.
[Gasps]
- [Beeping]
- Security, this is Janis Gold.
We have a code 12 in progress.
We need a team to Interrogation One.
[Man On Phone]
Yes, ma'am. Right away.
- [Alarm Blaring]
- [Man On P.A.
All agents, security breach, code 12.
- We gotta keep moving. Let's go.
- Security breach, code 12.
[Beeping]
[Alarm Continues]
[Man On P.A. Continues, Indistinct]
[Chattering]
Security team's between us
and the southwest exit.
Chloe, what have you got?
We're boxed in.
Someone at F.B.I. Blocking my every move.
It's really starting to piss me off.
You need to get back into their system.
Otherwise, we're not gonna make it out of here.
Jack, I'm sorry.
I'm trying.
[Beeping]
[Man On P.A.
All non-security personnel-
- We gotta make a move, Jack.
- I know.
- Copy that.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- Come on, Chloe. Talk to me.
- I'm still locked out. Trying to work around it.
- Jack, we're sitting ducks if we stay here.
- I know.
Chloe, we have to take the stairwell.
We don't have a choice.
- Quietly.
- [Man] All clear!
Where are they?
- We're lookin'.
- Find 'em!
Ow!
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- They're still in the building.
We're trying to locate them.
- I can't believe this.
- What the hell is Jack doing?
- He's helping his friend escape.
- That's what he's doing.
- I'm-I'm sorry, Larry.
I shouldn't have trusted him.
- It's all right.
- I got 'em!
- Southwest stairwell.
Security, this is Agent Moss.
Suspects are in the southwest stairwell...
descending past the fifth floor.
Lock down the building perimeter and deploy
two teams in the first floor service corridor.
Be aware. The suspects are armed.
We need 'em alive.
- Okay, I'm back up, Jack.
- Copy that.
- What was that?
- Hacker's back in.
- Whoever this is, they're very good.
- Well, lock 'em out.
I'm trying!
- Jack, hold up.
- What is it?
You're heading into an ambush.
It's a six man team.
- They're heading up toward you on the stairwell.
- Understand. We'll evade.
- They're coming up the stairs.
- [Man Shouting, Indistinct]
Pass me that fire extinguisher.
- We're on the roof of the parking lot.
- I see you. Good work.
Go to the north end, Jack.
Bill's almost there. He's in a blue van.
Copy that.
They're outside. They went through
the third floor window. Let's go!
Perimeter teams,
they're in the parking garage.
Notify Metro Police. I want them
to cordon off a five-block perimeter.
On our right!
Get down!
We gotta get you out of here
and back undercover.
I'll be right behind you.
Go!
Go! Go!
[Man]
They went inside. Let's go!
[Tires Screeching]
[Engine Starts]
This is gonna hurt.
[Yelling]
Tony, let's go!
[Shouting, Indistinct]
Come on, Jack!
Get in.
Let's go, Bill!
Agent Moss, they're gone.
They got outside the perimeter.
[Muttering]
All right, Chloe, I got 'em.
- Any sign of pursuit?
- Not so far. They must still be mobilizing.
- We caught them off guard.
- Traffic cams?
I'm cycling frequencies
to clear a path now.
Good. Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Where are we going?
- It's not far.
Bill, I did what you wanted. I got Tony out
of there. Tell me what the hell is going on.
When we get there,
I'll tell you everything.
[Beeping]
www.tvsubtitles.net