[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
You son of a bitch.
You're behind my son's death.
[Over Speaker] Madam President,
I have your husband.
You will have your forces withdrawn
from around my country, Sangala...
immediately and permanently...
or your husband will die
a slow and certain death.
I just wanted to make sure that you
were still coming to dinner tonight.
Marika, I can't.
I'll make it up to you.
If you're looking for Marika,
she's not with me.
I'm looking for you, Samuel,
or whatever your real name is.
Now, I don't know who you really are
and I don't care.
I just want you out of my sister's life.
Keep an incident quiet
until whatJack and I are doing goes down.
- What incident?
- Vossler's dead.
Jack killed him at the hotel
on 18th and Reagan. It was self-defense.
Damn it, Renee.
What the hell are you doing with this guy?
We're supposed to bring suspects in,
not murder them.
Until we know who Dubaku's source is,
you've got to handle this outside of the Bureau.
Dubaku is the only person
with the names...
of the people who betrayed you
within your government.
It's imperative that we find him.
You resigned from government service...
and the Senate regards you
as having been a renegade agent.
How am I supposed to know
where your loyalties really lie?
With all due respect,
Madam President, ask around.
I got an address for Henry Taylor.
Get an ambulance!
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 4:00 p.m. And 5:00 p.m.
[Sirens Wailing]
No one else gets through here.
Follow me.
It's Henry Taylor,
the president's husband.
- But that information is not
to be disseminated. Clear?
- Yes, ma'am.
- L-
- Mr. Taylor, don't speak.
I need you to save your energy.
[Groaning]
Over here!
Excuse me.
Step back, please!
This is Unit Six.
We got a gunshot trauma to the chest.
- Nine-millimeter round.
- Nine-millimeter, substernal.
- Pulse is rapid.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna call the president.
I want you to search all the rooms.
See if you can get anything off their hardware
that's gonna tell us where Dubaku went.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Line Ringing]
- [Woman] President Taylor's office.
- This is Jack Bauer.
- I need to speak with the president.
- One moment, please.
Madam President,
I would encourage you not to lose hope.
Dubaku knows that we tried to deceive him,
Ethan. He has no reason to keep Henry alive.
- [Intercom Beeping]
- [Woman] Madam President,
Jack Bauer's on line one.
Put him through.
Mr. Bauer, this is President Taylor.
Madam President,
we have your husband.
He's alive, but he sustained
a gunshot wound to the chest.
How bad is it?
E.M.T. Are stabilizing him.
They're getting ready to transfer him
to West Arlington Hospital.
Mr. Bauer, be more specific.
Is my husband going to be okay?
We're not gonna know anything
until the doctors see him.
Ma'am, I have to warn you.
He has lost a lot ofblood.
Jack, it's Bill.
Do you have Dubaku?
Negative.
He was gone before we got here.
Madam President, since your husband
was the only leverage that Dubaku had left...
it's safe to say that he's
trying to leave the country now.
Have you any idea
how he intends to do that?
Not at this time. Unfortunately,
all his men were killed during the assault.
Agent Walker and I will stay behind.
We'll continue to search the area.
We have to assume that Dubaku
has an exit strategy already in place.
Whatever we're gonna do to find him,
we're gonna have to do it fast.
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Bauer.
Please keep me apprised
on everything.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
[Beeps]
I am so sorry, Madam President.
Ethan, I'm going to the hospital
to be with my husband.
Ma'am, that's not possible.
You're executing a military invasion.
My generals can execute it
perfectly well without me.
We can't ignore the fact the Secret Service
has been compromised.
There's no way we can ensure your safety
outside the White House.
I don't give a damn.
I am not gonna be held prisoner in this office...
while my husband is fighting for his life.
Now either find someone to take me
to the hospital, or I'll drive there myself.
Madam President, you know
my record of service.
If it's acceptable to you, I'm willing
to assume responsibility for your security.
Bill, you're no longer credentialed.
You don't have the authority.
Until we capture Dubaku
and interrogate him...
we have no idea who in the government
is working for him.
- You do not know who you can trust.
- But I can trust you?
I brought this conspiracy
to your attention, Madam President.
I would hope that I've earned it.
What do you need from me?
Reinstate my government clearance...
allow me the authority
to vet White House staff...
and allow me to bring one
of my own people into F.B. I...
to provide Larry Moss
with tactical support.
- Who is it that you want to bring in?
- Chloe O'Brian.
I can vouch for her.
She's the best there is.
Her clearances were also revoked
when C.T.U. Was decommissioned.
Isn't there anyone capable of handling these
duties without our having to reinstate her?
Someone in the Bureau is on Dubaku's payroll.
Until we find out who it is...
Larry Moss can't take the chance of bringing
his own people into a manhunt for Dubaku.
All right.
The director of White House
Secret Service operations is Agent Hovis.
I'll order him to turn over
security protocols to you.
I know Ted Hovis, Madam President.
He's not gonna like this. He's gonna fight us.
Considering that agents
under his charge are responsible
for what happened to my husband...
I don't give a damn what he likes.
You have your provisional appointment, Mr.
Buchanan, under the authority of this office.
- Thank you, Madam President.
- You can thank me by getting me to the hospital.
I'll make the arrangements.
- Madam President-
- Your concerns are clear to me,
but I've made my decision.
I'm only trying to do my job,
looking out for your interests.
My interest right now
is catching Iké Dubaku.
He has killed scores of Americans today...
he tried to kill my husband,
and he has corrupted our government.
Whatever it takes,
I want that son of a bitch found.
[Whispering]
Marika! Marika!
- Samuel? What are you doing here?
- We need to talk.
- Uh, okay. Well, I get a break in 20 minutes.
- No, now.
- Come.
- What is it? You're scaring me.
Uh, something has come up.
I need to leave the country.
- What? When?
- Right away.
I don't understand.
When are you coming back?
Marika, listen to me.
I haven't been entirely honest with you.
My passport visa expired a couple of months ago,
and I've been in the country illegally.
I'm afraid the Immigration people
have caught up with me.
It was my sister, wasn't it?
- She reported you, didn't she?
- That doesn't matter now.
What is important is, I have to leave the country
tonight and I want you to come with me.
- Tonight?
- Marika, we've talked about this.
I promised that one day I would take you away
from here, give you the happiness you deserve.
Samuel, I want that too, but-
but not tonight, not so soon.
Marika! Marika, I don't
have time to argue with you!
I'm sorry.
I can't leave Rosa.
I mean, she needs me.
I'm the only one she has to take care of her.
You know that.
I know. I know.
- Which is why she's going to join us.
- Join us?
As soon as possible.
I could only arrange tickets
for both of us tonight.
But I want you to promise not to
tell your sister of our plans, at least not yet.
- I have to. I can't just run off.
- No. No, no.
She might cause trouble for us,
make it impossible for us to leave.
Look, I promise you...
your sister will join us within
a couple of days of our arrival.
- Okay?
- Our arrival where?
Belize. I have shown you
the photographs of my home there.
Do you love me?
You know I do.
Then trust me.
Say you'll come.
I'll get my things.
Now, I still need to
finalize our arrangements.
I want you to go home and pack.
Wait for my call.
All right.
[Beeps]
- [Line Ringing]
- Yes?
It's me. Have you
made the preparations?
Almost. It's been tricky
clearing a flight corridor...
since F.A.A. Still has most private
and commercial aircraft grounded.
I have faith you'll manage.
- The arrangements are for two passengers.
- Just as you requested.
Are you sure you want
to leave now, Colonel?
Can't imagine GeneralJuma will be pleased
to learn that you're abandoning your mission.
Mission is over.
I have done what I can do.
If that is not enough forJuma,
then to hell with him.
Got your passports
and itinerary in hand.
We meet at our usual spot in half an hour.
I'll bring them.
No. We meet in the lobby of
the Roosevelt Continental Hotel.
That's not a good idea.
It'll be crowded there at this hour.
I know.
I want to make it earlier.
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
[Engine Starts]
Go.
[Motor Whirring]
Can't get it to boot.
Hard drive must be fried.
Let's search the bodies.
Start with him.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Yeah?
- Renee, it's me.
Bill Buchanan just briefed me on your situation.
What's Henry Taylor's status?
We got him in an ambulance
en route to West Arlington Hospital.
I don't know his current condition.
Buchanan told me
you and Bauer were in a firefight.
Yeah. We took down six of Dubaku's men,
but Dubaku was gone before we got there.
- You all right?
- Been in worse.
You sure?
- I'm fine, Larry.
- Really?
I'm not so sure about that.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
I'm looking at a report
faxed to me from Metro Police.
A Mrs. Carol Vossler is claiming
an unidentified woman...
held her and her child
hostage at gunpoint.
- She says the woman threatened to kill her son.
- Larry, we discussed this.
We needed to get Vossler to tell us where Taylor
was being held. It was the only leverage we had.
Yeah. Right.
Whatever's necessary.
Jack Bauer's rationalization for
every unethical action he takes.
Well, it worked, Larry.
Doesn't that count for something?
Renee, Jack Bauer is about to be strung up
by a Senate subcommittee...
and you are following his playbook.
You got the A.G. Office looking into that thing
you pulled with Tanner's respirator.
- And now this.
- No one was actually hurt.
- No one-
- [Slaps Desk]
Renee, Bauer killed the woman's husband!
Renee, I swear to you here...
I am scared
of what is happening to you.
You put these people through hell,
and it doesn't bother you.
I didn't say that it doesn't bother me, Larry.
I said that it worked.
Of course it bothers me.
I can see that woman's face...
she and her child
staring at me with such-
She had no idea that her husband
was a killer, a traitor to his country...
and she looked at me
like I was the monster.
- Agent Walker.
- Hold on.
I cross-referenced the
information on these P.D.A.'s.
I came some across
banking transactions-
all from a series of accounts
registered to the same address.
- You think it's a safe house?
- It's worth a shot.
Larry, we may have
an address on Dubaku.
21917 Euclid Street,
Apartment 6.
Unit 6.
We're moving out now.
Can you provide sat surveillance?
Yeah. Bill Buchanan's sending
somebody over to run tech.
But until she's up and running,
you're gonna have to go in blind.
- Okay. We'll be in touch.
- You sure you're okay?
Fine.
Let's go.
[Beeping]
[Woman]
We're back with Lila Lee...
talking about her wonderful book,
Recipes from My Family: A Living Genealogy.
Thank you for coming
on the show today.
Oh, it's my pleasure, Pam. I mean,
it has been quite a journey to this moment.
I had no idea that what I started
would end up here.
[Pam] You were telling us earlier
that this just started...
as gathering recipes and traditions that
you remembered when you were growing up.
[Lila] That's right. You know,
I was trying to tell my children...
as I would make them lunch, I was reminded
of where did this recipe come from.
Then as I did that, I remembered,
well, this was my grandmother's-
[Radio: Reporter] Federal investigations
continue into the terrorist acts...
that have gripped
the nation's capital...
as well as the people of Kidron, Ohio.
- Despite assurances by President Taylor...
- Hey, sweetie.
That the threat has passed...
sources at the White House
will not confirm...
that all those responsible
have been accounted for.
[Miles] Now you sure you're
not gonna need my help?
I'm just running F.B.I. Ops temporarily
until they catch Dubaku.
Once they find him,
hopefully he'll tell us the names...
of all the people on his payroll
that are inside our government.
- And then we can go home?
- Then we can go home.
Well, just be careful.
All right?
Because if Buchanan's right and Dubaku
has someone working inside the Bureau-
I'll watch my back.
You just watch Prescott.
Hey, sweetheart, Mommy has to go to work.
You be good, okay?
Bye, Mommy.
- You be good too.
- I will.
Bye.
And if you get all jammed up,
you know where to find me.
- [Man] I.D., please.
- Chloe O'Brian.
All right, go ahead.
Need you to cross-reference
our deployments with Homeland.
Make sure the
requisition numbers match up.
- After that, you can catch up on the hourlies.
- Are you joking?
That is busy work,
administrative crap you're handing me.
Janis, I don't have the time nor the inclination
right now to explain my assignments to you.
- Just get it done.
- Agent Moss.
- Chloe O'Brian just cleared security.
She's on her way up.
- All right. Thank you.
Janis, set up a secure V.P.N. Socket,
port it to the conference room.
Why do you need a V.P.N. Socket?
I'm bringing in
a consultant from Homeland...
to confirm there are no lingering gaps
in the C.I.P. Firewall.
That's fine.
Take that downstairs.
Ms. O'Brian. Larry Moss.
- Welcome to the F.B.I.
- Hi.
- You can call me Chloe.
- We're right in here.
- Buchanan said you'd be up to speed?
- I'm up.
Good. Agent Walker and Bauer
are pursuing a potential lead on Dubaku.
They're en route to this address
in the Mount Pleasant district.
Agent Walker's
requesting satellite support.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
I'm feeling a little exposed here.
If someone out there is working for Dubaku,
shouldn't we be doing this more covertly?
As far as anyone knows,
you're working on shoring up our firewall.
Besides, this is the only space available
where you'll have full access to our server.
- Our network doesn't support remote modules.
- That's inefficient.
Whoever set your network up that way
didn't know what they were doing.
I set our network up that way.
Oh. Okay.
Something else?
You worked with Bauer
for a long time, didn't you?
Seven years, on and off.
That's impressive.
That you survived the experience.
- What are you talking about?
- Only that a lot of people didn't.
Curtis Manning,
Ryan Chappelle, his own wife.
Are you saying it's Jack's fault
his wife was killed?
You tell me.
Jack Bauer is the most trustworthy,
honorable man I know, and he's my friend.
Maybe you should worry less about him
and more about the mole in your office...
working for Dubaku.
Is that Chloe O'Brian?
- What?
In the conference room-
Chloe O'Brian.
She was senior analyst at C.T.U.
I once took a seminar she gave.
What's she doing here?
Larry said Homeland sent her to check for
residual breaches from the firewall attack.
- Huh.
- What?
It just doesn't sound
like her area of expertise.
Besides, as far as I know, she's been inactive
since C.T.U. Was decommissioned.
Passports and travel itinerary.
Hawker Siddeley 748
is fueling at Taft Airfield.
Be ready to fly within a half hour,
get you to the Cayman Islands.
Shouldn't have any trouble
getting to Belize from there.
I need a car to the airfield
and a driver.
I assumed you had
your own transportation.
- It's not for me.
- I see. It's for the girl.
Well, I'm not sure I can find
someone I trust on such short notice.
Really?
- What about your man at the bar?
- Excuse me?
Or one of the two
on the balcony watching us now?
Or the two in the black Town Car,
waiting for me to leave?
Do you think I'm a fool,
Mr. Burnett?
I know you people
see me as a liability now.
These men are here to guarantee
your safety, Colonel, not to threaten it.
Guarantee my safety.
How nice.
[Chuckles]
And said with such sincerity.
I want you to take this message
back with you.
If anything should happen to me
on my way out of the country-
an accident or an assassination attempt,
anything-
the plane that you were so generous
to donate decides to explode-
a data file with all the names
and bank transactions of all those involved...
will be sent to theJustice Department.
That is completely unnecessary.
Same holds true if anything
should happen to Marika Donoso.
I swear to you she knows nothing of this.
She's no threat to you.
Make sure your driver knows this
before he brings her to me.
Do you understand
what I am saying?
I want you to tell me
that you understand...
what I am saying to you,
so there will be no mistakes.
- I understand.
- Good.
The one thing I have learned in the company
of mercenaries, Mr. Burnett...
is that ultimately they care about nothing
but their own survival.
Good day.
- [Line Ringing]
- I was right. Dubaku suspected
we were gonna take him out.
And apparently he's assembled evidence
to use as an insurance policy.
We need to make sure
he gets out of the country...
and safely into exile,
otherwise we're all compromised.
I'll make the calls.
What are you doing?
- Rosa.
- Where are you going?
Rosa, listen to me.
We're going away from here, all of us.
[Scoffs]
Well, what do you mean, "all"?
Samuel told me the truth.
He's an illegal,
just like you thought.
He has to leave the country,
and I've agreed to go with him.
- You're leaving me?
- No, no. Only for a short time.
You're gonna come too.
Samuel's made plans. We're gonna
live with him in his home in Belize.
Marika, he's lying to you.
- He's not.
- I won't let you do this!
My God, Rosa!
I have taken care of you my entire life!
I've sacrificed everything for you.
- Why can't you let me have this?
- I don't trust him!
Well, you've never liked any man
who's ever shown any interest in me.
Every chance I've ever had at happiness,
you've found some way of ruining it.
- But not this time.
- Marika, I'm begging you. Listen to me.
- No.
- Marika, please. Stop.
- Move!
- Marika, please.
Listen to me.
I'm begging you, Marik-
- F.B.I. Don't move!
- Get on your knees now! On your knees!
Both of you, put your hands behind
your head and interlock your fingers! Now!
Do not move!
We're clear.
- Where is Dubaku?
- Who?
Don't play games with me! Iké Dubaku!
We traced bank accounts to this address.
- Now, where is he?
- We don't know wh-who you talking about.
Let me try and make this easier for you.
You know this man?
No.
You're lying to me.
Why are you lying to me?
L-Let me see.
That's him.
We know him.
He calls himself Aboa.
Samuel Aboa.
- Rosa, shut up!
- She was going to meet him to leave me.
- Where were you gonna meet him?
Where were you going?
- I don't know.
- How do you know him? You work for him?
- No.
- Do you work for him?
You know what he's doing here
in this country?
Do you have any idea...
what this man is?
He's everything to me.
[Beeping]
[Man]
Notify C.P. Iocation. Will hold.
Once the floor's secure.
- Nurse-
- Mitchell.
Nurse Mitchell, I'd like to see my husband.
Ma'am, I don't know if that's possible.
I was told that Dr. Schulman
will be doing the surgery. Where is he?
Excuse me, Madam President.
I'm Lee Schulman,
your husband's surgeon.
If you come with me you can see him now,
but you'll need to keep it brief.
Thank you.
You should know Mr. Taylor's looking
at a minimum of five hours in surgery.
The bullet lacerated
his pulmonary artery...
and lodged in his thoracic region.
He's also suffered
massive internal bleeding.
Can you offer any kind of prognosis?
I'm a blunt woman, Dr. Schulman.
I appreciate bluntness.
His chances aren't good, ma'am...
but I'll do everything I can.
If you'll excuse me,
I need to scrub up now.
Henry!
- Darling, can you hear me?
- Ally.
Yes, sweetheart.
I'm here.
I'm so sorry I didn't listen
to you about Roger.
You were right. It wasn't suicide.
I know that now.
You were always right.
- [Moans] He was a hero.
- Yes.
He was.
And so are you.
I'm sorry, Madam President,
but the anesthesiologist is ready now.
- [Monitor Beeping]
- [Woman On P.A. Mr. Carlisle, Admitting.
Mr. Carlisle,
come to Admitting, please.
Mr. Buchanan.
Yes, Madam President?
There's something
I need you to do for me.
Have someone find my daughter Olivia
and bring her to me.
Have you had a chance to tell her?
My daughter and I haven't spoken
for some time, Mr. Buchanan.
She'd never get on the phone with me.
She works for a consulting firm-
Martlin Norris.
Do you have someone trustworthy
you can send?
Yes, ma'am. I believe I do.
And here he is again,
in the uniform of the presidential guard...
at the gates of
the notorious Mukatu Prison.
And here, inside the soccer stadium
after the Barakar Massacre...
the event that earned him the nickname
the Butcher of Sangala.
Oh, please.
No more.
What did you say
his real name was again?
Dubaku.
Iké Dubaku.
I've seen firsthand
what he's capable of.
I was in Africa a few months ago. He was
responsible for murdering a friend of mine.
Oh, God.
I know this is a shock...
and I'm sorry, I really am.
But here's the situation-
we need your help and we need it now.
- [Sobbing]
- What kind of help?
We need to put this man in custody
before he can leave the country.
She already told you
she doesn't know where he is.
You said earlier that you
were gonna meet him. Where?
He didn't say. Just told me to go home
and pack and wait for his call.
Give me your phone.
- Why?
- When he calls, I want you to answer.
- No. No, no. I can't. I can't.
- Yes, you can.
- [Gasping]
- Listen to me. Just listen to me.
L- It's over.
The man you thought you knew,
the man you had feelings for, he doesn't exist.
All you've been left with
are his lies and his betrayal.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
Is that him?
- [Sobbing, Gasping]
- Marika, please.
All I want you to do is answer
the phone and talk to him...
so that we can find out
where he wants to meet you.
- Please, you can do this.
- [Ringing Continues]
Please just try.
- [Beeps]
- Hello?
- [Dubaku] Marika?
- Yes.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
What took you so long
to answer the phone?
I was in the bedroom, packing.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
You sound strange.
It's- It was Rosa.
She caught me packing
and we argued.
- Is she going to be a problem for us?
- No!
I'm sorry, Samuel.
I had to tell her everything.
It was the only way.
But, uh- But she understands now.
- Are you certain?
- Yeah.
Yeah, she's fine, now that she knows
she and I will be together again in a few days.
Hmm. She should thank heaven
she has such an angel for a sister.
- Are you ready to go?
- Almost.
Hurry up then. I've had a car sent for you.
It should be there very shortly.
Go downstairs and wait for it.
- Where is it taking me?
- Don't worry. The driver will know.
I just want the woman I love
to get downstairs as quickly as possible.
Okay.
[Beeps]
[Gasps, Sobs]
It's all right.
- You did great.
- Did we get the rendezvous point?
No. He's sending a car
with a driver.
Come here.
[Chattering]
There's no one on the street yet.
We could grab the driver,
get him to tell us Dubaku's location.
There's no guarantee
we can get him to talk...
and if we take too long,
Dubaku's not gonna wait around.
So then what do we do?
We can get her to go meet with him.
What?
We could track her. We could use
her cell phone as a transponder.
- You want to send that girl to Dubaku?
- We don't have another choice.
- Jack.
- You want to get Dubaku? This is our shot.
Marika...
I have a favor to ask of you.
We can't make you do this,
but when the car arrives...
we would like you to go with the driver
so that we could follow you back to Dubaku.
What are you talking about?
You want her to go to him and face him?
It's the only chance we have of finding him
before he disappears forever.
I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- No! I'm your older sister,
and I won't allow it!
It's not your decision
to make, Rosa. It's mine.
And it's the right thing to do.
Let me see your phone.
- What are you doing?
- Getting your S.I.D. Number.
That's how we're gonna track you.
You're not gonna be out there alone.
Agent Walker and I will be following you.
We'll never be more than a mile behind.
As soon as you reach the destination,
that's when we'll move in.
Marika, a mile.
Are you crazy?
Rosa, enough.
You heard what he said!
He's a murderer!
- He could hurt you!
- He won't.
Rosa, I should've listened to you.
- Sweetheart.
- You warned me about him.
Listen, the only reason why I said those things
was because I was jealous...
and I didn't want to lose you.
Larry, this is Jack. Renee said you had
someone running operations support?
- Yeah, she's right here. I'll put you on speaker.
- [Beeps]
Jack, it's Chloe.
- Chloe.
- What do you need?
How long's it gonna take you
to set up a sat beacon for a mobile line?
Usually a few seconds, but with
the backward way they have this system set up...
it's gonna take at least a few minutes.
Okay. Let me give you the S.I.D. Number:
1 -C-4-8-6-8-9.
- You got it?
- Got it.
Jack, who are you tracking?
A woman who's involved with Dubaku.
He's sending a car to take her to him.
- She's one of his operatives?
- No.
It's more complicated than that.
[Beeping]
[Exhales, Mouths Words]
Arthur, you're not going to find another firm
that's done more high-level consulting work...
for a relatively small
pharmaceutical company like yours.
Remember, my firm helped
the governor craft a plan...
to swap property taxes for sales taxes
in his last budget reform.
Tell me that didn't save
Dexter Carr a bundle.
Oh, it did, Olivia.
But since I'm specifically looking to hire you,
I need to know what you yourself can do.
Whatever you need. You know my
accomplishments. You've seen my résumé.
I mean White House influence...
considering your family.
We're not lobbyists, Arthur.
It states that clearly in the contract.
I just thought since
you have the president's ear-
I don't. Is that
going to be a problem?
Excuse me. Ms. Taylor?
Do I know you?
My name is Aaron Pierce.
Your office told me you'd be here.
I've been dispatched
at the request of the president.
Your credentials say
you've retired, Mr. Pierce.
Perhaps no one informed you I refused
Secret Service protection months ago.
I'm aware of that, ma'am.
This is a special circumstance.
Well, as you can see,
I'm a little busy right now.
- This isn't a good time.
- I'm sorry, but I have to insist.
- Really, it's all right.
- No.
No, it's not all right.
What is it that's so important for my mother to
steal me away while I'm trying to do business?
I'm not at liberty to say, ma'am.
That information is confidential.
Olivia, we can pick this up
at a later time.
- Arthur, wait. It-
- We'll be in touch.
Ma'am, please.
I'm not going anywhere with you
until you tell me what this is about.
It's your father, Ms. Taylor.
He's been shot.
He's in surgery at West Arlington Hospital.
Your mother's there now.
None of this is public knowledge.
My God. L-
My car is just outside.
[Whimpers]
Excuse me, Sean. Can I please
get the digital beta key for the server?
Why?
Larry asked for it. Something to do
with the firewall assessment.
- If Larry wants it, why doesn't he come to me?
- I don't know.
- Maybe I oughta go ask him.
- No.
Okay.
I think that Larry brought in this woman,
Chloe O'Brian, to replace me...
and I just want to get a bead
on what they're working on, that's all.
That's all? That's enough
to lose us both our jobs.
- Well, maybe I should stop covering for you.
- What are you talking about?
Erika and you and your
little sexual indiscretions?
I've said nothing
to Larry or your wife.
I'm sure you'd like me
to keep it that way.
[Lock Clicks]
You're a little bitch,
you know that?
You're a little bitch.
- Okay, Jack. The link's up. I've got the signal.
- [Beeping]
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
We're on.
[Whispering]
I'll be all right.
Marika, we gotta go.
Okay.
You. F.B.I.
You keep her safe,
you hear me?
We will.
I'm really scared.
You're gonna be fine.
Just remember, we're right behind you.
- Hold up here.
- Okay.
Now, listen, if you get into trouble,
you can signal us by dialing 1-0-
No. No, I don't want you to do that.
Don't do anything that's gonna
raise the suspicion of the driver.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- I'm ready.
- Okay.
- What the hell are you doing?
- She was scared.
I wanted her to know there was another option
than waiting for us to swoop in.
If we're gonna find Dubaku,
there are no other options.
You understand?
Come on. You've run operations like this.
Not without full tactical support
and at least two backup units in the scene.
- She's naked out there, Jack. I don't like it.
- This isn't about you.
This is about her and Dubaku.
Listen, life gets ugly.
Innocent people get hurt.
That's a reality.
At least she got to make a choice
to be involved, to do the right thing...
which is a lot more than I can say
for Dubaku's other victims.
We have one job here-
that's to get Dubaku.
Outside of that, don't get involved.
[Vehicle Approaches]
Chloe, the car's here.
[Chloe]
Copy that.
She's getting in the car.
[Chloe]
Copy.
She's moving.
Are you locked in?
Yeah. I've got them
heading south on 14th.
Can you upload the tracking grid
to Agent Walker's P.D.A.
- No. I'll have to direct you.
- Just keep us close.
Understood.
Head towards 14th, make a right.
Copy that.
[Engine Starts]
[Beeping]
How much further?
Continuing west on R Street,
crossing Hampshire Avenue.
- You're less than a mile behind the target car.
- [Jack] Copy that.
[Chloe]
Target car is turning left on Connecticut.
[Jack]
Okay. Rounding Dupont Circle.
Agent Moss, is there anything
in the northern quad of the grid...
that would indicate where Dubaku
could hide a plane or a helicopter?
[Larry] No. Nothing definitive.
It could be any number oflaunch sites.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What was that? What happened?
- [Chloe]Jack, we've got a problem.
- Chloe, what's wrong?
We just lost the tracking grid.
- What?
- I don't know. It just glitched out.
We can't afford to lose them, Jack.
I gave this woman my word we'd protect her.
- I know. Chloe, get it back up.
- [Larry] We're doing our best, Jack.
Wait. It's back up.
- What the hell happened?
- I don't know. I'm running a diagnostic right now.
Jack, they're moving southeast
on Massachusetts Avenue.
You've closed the gap to about a half a mile.
You may wanna back off a little bit.
- Okay. Copy that.
- Oh, no.
- [Larry] What?
- Somebody was in the system.
What? What are you talking about?
I'm saying someone in this office
was mirroring my terminal.
Whoever it was knows
exactly what we were doing.
Can you backtrace the breach?
No. The link was severed.
It could've come from anywhere.
[Sirens Wailing]
[Larry]
Jack, you getting this?
Looks like we might have a security breach.
Someone is mirroring our comm.
Jack. They're coming from all sides.
Larry, we got a situation here!
- What's going on?
- I got Metro P.D. Trying to
build a roadblock around us.
[Larry] What?
Why would they be doing that?
I don't know!
Just get 'em off us!
Larry, do something!
This is Agent Moss.
Connect me with Metro district command.
- Hands in the air! Hands in the air!
- My name is Jack Bauer!
- Get out of the car!
- My passenger is a federal agent!
Get out of the car right now!
On the ground!
- She's a federal agent!
- On the ground!
- Face down!
- Keep your hands behind your back, sir!
Come on, Larry!
Do something!
- Captain, you've got to
release these people immediately.
- But we have a federal warrant.
No! That is a mistake. No federal
warrants have been issued for them.
Yes, they have. A warrant
was called in for the vehicle.
"Occupants armed and dangerous,
to be apprehended with decisive force."
- Issued by whom?
- F.B.I. This office.
There's no attribution,
but the routing code's real.
This was definitely done
by someone here.
Marika's carjust turned east
onto N Street.
Captain, listen carefully. I am
the special agent in charge of this operation.
I am revoking
these warrants immediately.
- Sir, you'll have to
clear that with command.
- No.
No, I don't have time to deal
with your chain of command.
You need to release
these people right now!
Hey, thank you.
- So, is O'Brian here to replace you?
- I don't know. No?
Larry's using her for some kind of
covert operation with Jack Bauer.
They're tracking a car to Dubaku.
- Why would he keep us in the dark
about something like that?
- I don't know.
I don't know, but I don't like it.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Line Ringing]
- Yes?
- Hey. I took care of Bauer and Walker.
They're pinned down.
Why am I being brought in
on this so last-minute?
Moss is running this op on his own.
It took me some time
to tap into his phone line.
He's on with Metro right now.
Can you at least disable the tracking signal
they're using to follow the girl?
No. Not from my console.
But judging by the frequency,
they're using her cell as the tracker.
All right. Good work.
You told me that once Dubaku
served his purpose, you'd take him out.
Why are we still helping him?
He's threatening to expose us
using a database he's kept...
with names and accounts
of everyone involved.
- Including mine?
- I mean everyone!
We don't know where the file is,
so you just better pray that he gets away.
Yes. It has to do with the terrorist threats
that happened this morning.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- Hello?
- You got a problem.
- What is it?
Your girlfriend's
been turned by the F.B.I.
I don't believe you.
They met with her a half hour ago,
told her who you really are.
That's impossible.
- Marika would never do this.
- I got it from my source inside the Bureau.
It is definite. She agreed to lead them to you
using her cell phone as a tracker.
Look, my source managed to
stall their surveillance team for a while...
but you need to get to
the airfield immediately.
I'll call my driver,
have him take care of her.
- No. I'll do it.
- Colonel, I told you. They are tracking her.
If you let her come to you,
you're risking your chances of escape.
I said I'll take care of her.
[Beeps]
[Beeping]
www.tvsubtitles.net