Season07
Episode21
******
Have you secured the canister?
I'm afraid not,ma'am.
Our suspect escaped
beyond the perimeter.
I was told that the area was
locked down. What happened?
He had help from tony almeida.
Almeida? He was working for us.
It only appeared that way.
Apparently he was pursuing his own
agenda,trying to get his hands on the canister.
We're all regrouping to develop leads.
I may have one.
As hodges was taken into custody,he
yelled at me about some larger group
that would continue on after his arrest.
If that's the case,madam
president,we need to talk to him.
I need you to call the attorney general and draft
a witness protection agreement for jonas hodges.
There's no other way he'll talk.
This man mdered your son,not to
mention hundreds of innocent civilians.
Is there anything else
that I can do for you?
Other than kill jonas hodges,no.
I didn't mean that.
You know,you're right. We shouldn't
be talking about this over the phone.
How soon can you be at thehite house?
- How's 15 minutes sound?
- Good.
The plan was to launch simultaneous
attacks early next year in multiple cities,
so the public would finally see that
the government can't protect them.
They'd demand drastic
measures,and we'd step in.
We were going to supply the  enemies
that want to destroy this country--
muhammad this,achmed that.
Mr. Hodges,I need the names of the
people that you are working with.
- I don't have any...
- I want the names!
I don't know any!
Another attack today is all we need
to push this thing right over the edge.
This is no time to pull back.
I say we take that canister
and finish the job off today.
I'll contact the group.
The attack will be
attributed to this man--
jibraan al-zarian.
We're talking about launching a new operation
in the next few hours and with only one canister.
The plan for this operation
was already in place.
We'd just be accelerating the timetable.
Jonas hodges was a loose cannon,and
the group is well rid of him,
but,in his lunacy,he did us a favor.
I say we take it.
Hamid!
Keep your mouth shut
and no one gets hurt.
- You understand?
- Yes!
******
How much more time do you need?
The material's almost
finished downloading.
Financial records are in place.
I'm gonna need about another 15
minutes to alter the time stamps.
Good.
I'm gonna take this off.
You yell for help,you and
your brother die. Understand?
Who are you people?
You're putting jihadi
propaganda on my computer.
These weapons--
you're...
you're trying to make me look like
a terrorist. Why are you doing this?
Listen to me,jibraan.
There's only one thing you need to know.
If you d't do exactly as I say,
you're going to watch your younger
brother die right in front of your eyes.
And then... I'm gonna kill you.
However... if you cooperate...
there's a good chance the two
of you will live through this.
What do you want me to do?
First off...
you're going to read this
statement in front of a camera,
and you're going to
read it like you mean it.
No,this is insane. I can't read
this. I'm not going to do this.
Okay,see,that sounds to me like
you think you have a choice.
Please,this is not right.
You can't do this to us.
Okay,fine.
Okay,okay,please please don't hurt him.
I'll do whatever you say. Okay?
I'll give you five
minutes to look that over.
I just finished the first
sweep with the ctu servers.
There's been no
chatter,no activity at all.
You updated the watch list?
Yes,everyone on that list is already
under surveillance by law enforcement.
If one of them was gonna do
something,we would know about it.
Damn,well,we're going to
have to widen our parameter.
To include what?
I want you to check out every
muslim in the washington D.C.Area.
Target anyone who's working in a sensitive
government position or in a place that might get hit.
Then I want you to start pulling the files on every
political activist working in the muslim community.
Also,I want you to contact ins.
I want a list of every recent
immigrant from an islamic country.
Excuse me,has anybody
heard of racial profiling?
Janis,not now.
No,she's right.
You're right,this is racial profiling,and
I don't like it any more than you do,
but hodges told me specifically that he
was going to utilize muslim extremists
in an effort to offload
the blame for this attack.
I need to know who he's working
with,and we're running out of time.
I don't know a better way of doing this.
So if you do,please tell me now.
No.
Okay,thank you.
Chloe,I need you to
run down the list of...
I-I'm sorry,I forgot what I was saying.
Ins records,jack?
Yeah,run those down first
and then work backwards.
Excuse me.
This is the second time he's done this.
He keeps forgetting
things,he looks like hell.
He's doing pretty well,considering.
Considering? Considering what?
- He didn't tell you?
- Tell me what?
If there's something wrong
with jack,tell me now.
He's sick,chloe. He was
infected with the prion variant.
How?
He was trying to recover the bioweapon canisters
and one of them ruptured. He was exposed.
Oh,my god.
I'm sorry,chloe,he probably
didn't want you to worry. Chloe...
why didn't you tell me you were sick?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter? I'm your friend.
We need to stay focused on finding tony.
Jack,you should be in the hospital.
There's no treatment for this.
There's no cure.
so you're telling me you're dying?
Yes.
How long?
A day,maybe two.
I've been taking this anti-seizure
medicine to keep me on my feet.
It's been working so far.
Oh,my god. I'm so sorry.
Chloe,it's all right.
I've accepted it...
and I need you to accept it,too.
Whatever time I've got
left,I want it to matter.
We need to find tony,put an end to this.
chloe.
I can't do this without you.
Please,I need you to go back to work.
okay.
We strike this blow for our brothers and sisters
who have died at the hands of this corrupt nation.
The hour is here,and we are
ready for the war that is to come.
Our fighters will not rest until
amica lies crippled and dying,
her streets running with blood,and her people
begging for mercy,but there will be none...
- only our vengeance.
- We have a problem.
- What is it?
- Police.
Why don't you,uh...
close down the computer
and get out of sight.
Take everything down
and watch the brother.
- You need to come with me.
- What is happening?
There are two police officers outside.
I want you to find out what they want and
convince them that everything's okay in here.
jibraan...
don't try to warn them.
Dcpd. Open the door,please.
Yes?
"Jibrain" al-zarian?
Jibraan al-zarian.
Uh,we got a call from
one of your neighbors.
They said they heard some yelling
coming from your apartment,
saw some people they didn't recognize enter the
premises,thought there might be some trouble.
No,everything is fine.
Those were friends of mine.
And what about the yelling?
We got into an argument.
They were drinking a little
too much. Uh,it was nothing.
Where are your friends now,sir?
you know,they got too
loud,so I asked them to leave.
They won't be back.
I'm very sorry for the noise.
it won't happen again. I-I promise.
Okay. Just keep it down from now on.
I will.
- Have a good night.
- You,too.
All right,we're clear.
You did good,jibraan.
We have to finish reading this
statement before we take off.
Where are we going?
Don't worry about that.
You just keep doing as we say,and you and your
brother are gonna make it through this,all right?
Set him up.
And there will be
none,only our vengeance.
And this is only the beginning.
We will strike again and again in the
name of all that is great and righteous.
I think I've got something.
Agent walker? What is it?
One of the filters flagged this a few
minutes ago. I just finished vetting it.
These are multiple deposits
over a period of six months.
They're from an overseas muslim relief organization
called the islamic league for world peace.
A total of two million dollars to
the washington continental bank.
Every penny of it was
withdrawn within 30 minutes.
What name's on the account?
Jibraan al-zarian.
He's 27 years old,moved here from
pakistan on a student visa four years ago.
This is his personal web account.
These are some of the sites
he's been looking at recently.
We got an address on him?
No. This address is
false. It doesn't exist.
Yeah,his visa expired. He's here illegally,and
he probably doesn't want to be found.
- He does have a personal reference on his ins form.
- Who?
Muhtadi gohar. He lives at the
g street mosque in georgetown.
He's the imam there.
He might be able to help us find
al-zarian. We need to talk to him.
Put out an apb on al-zarian,run it
through the interagency database.
See what else you can find.
Fax everything over
to the car. Great work.
Jack,wait.
Are you sure you're up for this?
I have to see this through.
Please. I can help.
Okay. Let's go.
come in.
Ma'am,mr. Collier to see you.
Thank you,agent pierce. That'll be all.
I appreciate you coming,martin.
It's been a long time. You look good.
Thanks.
So,olivia,I know why you asked
me here,but I have to tell you,
having me dig up dirt on
noah daniels is one thing.
This is a whole different animal.
I'm aware of that,martin.
I want this to happen. I want
this person taken care of.
- It's jonas hodges.
- Starkwood?
Yes.
What in god's name do
you have against him?
I don't know how much of this will get out,but
hodges was behind everything that happened today,
from the planes going down to
the attack on the white house.
- What?
- It's true.
He's also responsible for
the death of my brother.
I thought your brother killed himself.
He was murdered,and
hodges was responsible.
Okay. But why?
It's complicated,martin,and I
don't have time to go into it.
All you need to know
is,hodges worked a deal.
Witness protection. My mother
approved it,and he's going free...
unless someone intervenes.
Okay,can I give you a little advice?
- What?
- This is big game. Walk away.
I can't do that.
Once this happens,once it goes
through,you can never go back.
You will live with it
for the rest of your life.
I don't need a lecture on
conscience from you,of all people.
I have thought this through.
What I can't live with is that
monster getting away with this.
He has to pay for what he did.
So,uh,where's hodges now?
In fbi custody,downtown bureau.
Deal has been signed.
He's being released into witness
protection within the hour.
Here's his itinerary.
When he walks out that door,we lose him.
He disappears forever.
This has got to happen fast.
Martin.
All right. I'll make a call.
I'll get you contact information,a price,and
instructions on how to transfer the funds.
Thank you.
You'll hear from me soon.
mr. Hodges,this is U.S.Marshal sullivan.
I'm placing you in his custody.
He'll take you to witness protection.
Thank you for your
hospitality,young lady.
This dossier outlines your
newdentity,your new place of residence,
all the information you're going
to need to make this transition.
Robert tippett? That's my new name?
Yes,sir.
Sounds like a dog breed.
Our first stop is the
witt-sec facility in colorado.
We'll put the finishing touches on your
new biography,fabricate your new id,
- get you into counseling.
- Counseling?
It helps entrants deal with
their new circumstances.
Son,you know who I am.
Do I impress you as someone who needs
therapy to cope with new circumstances?
The service is available if you want
it,sir,courtesy of the american taxpayer.
You think I'm getting
off easy,don't you?
I don't think anything.
I can smell attitude,son,and
you're giving it off pretty thick.
I've lost
everything--
my company,my family,and
most importantly,my name.
Do you know how much blood and sweat
went into making that name mean something?
We leave for andrews air
force base in 30 minutes.
I suest you get ready.
Jack?
I'm fine.
What are you doing? We don't even
know that they've done anything yet.
- They could be innocent.
- Innocent?
You heard hodges. They're gonna use
sleeper cells to carry out these attacks.
Al-zarian might not have been knowingly
complicit about everything that happened today,
but innocent?No.
Yes?
This is agent walker
with fbi. Mr. Gohar?
Yes.
We're sorry to bother you at such
a late hour,but we need your help.
My help?
To stop a potential terrorist attack.
mr. Gohar?
I know you.
My name is jack bauer.
Of course.
I watched your testimony on television.
Sir,can we talk to you inside?
Please.
what do you want?
We're looking for a man who worships here.
We believe he may be helping to plan another attack that may be happening soon,in D.C.
I knew the blame would eventually fall on us.
His name is jibraan al-zarian.Do you know him?
And why do you think he's a terrorist?
He fits a specific profile.
You mean,he is a muslim.
He's a pakistani national.His visa lapsed a year ago.
And he has no legal address.
He listed you as a personal reference on his ins form.
Where someone worships is private information,protected by law.
Right now,finding al-zarian is the only way we're going to prevent an attack against civilians.
So,I ask you again,sir,do you know him?
Look at the photo!
Yes,I know him.But he is not a terrorist!
What makes you so sure?
Jibraan has come to me many times for spiritual advice.
I know the man.
He is not violent and he is not an extremist.
We have evidence that indicates otherwise.
I would like to see this evidence.
Listen to me.We did not come here to debate this with you.
Where does he live?
-I don't know where he lives.
-Where does he work?
-I don't know that,either.
-And I don't believe you!
But you expect me to believe you?
I watched your hearing at the senate,I know what you have done.
So,tell me why should I belie anything you say to me?
First because you don't have a choice.
Second,because I am telling you the truth!
The truth is that you come into a house of worship with information you should not have,
an outrageous accusation,no legal warrant,and threaten me.
I have not threatened you.
Not yet.
But we both know where this is going.
If you're so sure he's innocent,why are you afraid to tell us where he is?
-Jack...
-where is he?
I told you,I don't know.
But even if I did,I would say nothing.
I would not help you arrest an innocent man.
this is agent walker.
It's janis.
A dcpd officer recognized jibraan al-zarian from a domestic disturbance call he took 15 minutes ago.
The address is 2700 eastbrook,apartment 3.
All right,good.Coordinate with dcpd.
Set up an envelope and put the building under surveillance.We'll be there in 10 minutes.
We have an address on al-zarian.Let's go,jack.
-Turn around.
-Why?
I said turn around.
-Put your hands up,now!
-Jack?
What are you doing,jack?
I'm not letting him call al-zarian before we get there.
He's coming with us.
You have no right!I have done nothing wrong!
Shut up!
There will be none,only our vengeance.
And this is only the beginning.
We will strike again and again in the name of all that is great and righteous.
All right,fine.
The staging team's ready and waiting on us.
This'll be uploaded in two minutes.
Good.
Jibraan...
we're getting ready to move out.
I'm gonna need you to talk to your brother.
Tell him what we discussed.
Go ahead and wake him up.
Please,I can't do this.
Yes,you can.
And you will.
How do I know you won't kill hamid anyway?
Because we need him  to tell the police that his brother's a terrorist.
Believe me,you're saving his life by doing this.
Now,come on,let's go.
Hamid,hamid,calm down.Don't be scared.
Jibraan,what is this?
Sorry we had to do it th way.
But you're not going to be hurt anymore,okay?
We?Who is we?What's happening?
I'll explain everything to you,okay?
Who's he?
Um,he's a friend.
Your friend?I know all your friends.I've never seen him before.
That's because I have kept him from you.
What are you talking about?
I have to tell you something.
I'm not the person you think I am.
What?
I hate what this country has done to our people.
And I'm working with these men.
They're going to help me strike back against the evil that has been done to us.
Strike back?
I can't say any more than that.
I don't believe it.
This country brought us in,gave us a home,that's what you always said.
Yeah,that was a lie.
I have been protecting you from this rage I've always felt inside.
But now it is time for you to know the truth.
It was the americans who killed our parents,hamid.
I'm going to make them pay.
What have you done to my brother?You've poisoned his mind!This isn't my brother!
They have not done anything to me,okay.
It is very important you accept what I'm saying to you.
Why are you telling me this?
When they ask you why I did what I did,
I want you to tell them.
Okay,no one will blame you for anything.You have done nothing wrong.
I know this is very difficult for you to understand.
But over time,you will see.
I love you,hamid.
You said today was a bad day to be a muslim.
Well,it's an even worse day to be your brother.
All right,let's go.
Staging area's ready.
You stay here and finish up.
Understood.
Jibraan,don't do this.
Everything set?
Yeah,was the brother convinced?
I'm not sure.
But even if he wasn't,once the attack happens,he will be.
Let's go.
Hello?Hello?
Yes,yes,martin collier said you'd be expecting my call.
He gave me the target's itinerary.I'm set to go.
Good.
Good,so the terms are acceptable.
They are.I just need you to transfer the funds.
What's the account number?
International banking code is victor-six-bravo-one-bravo-one.
Account number: Zero-five-nine -nine-zero-seven-two-four-seven.
Ter the funds have been transferred,I'll proceed.
There'll be no need for us to have any further contact.
All right,but what e you--  hello?
yes?
Excuse me,ms.Taylor.
I thought you should know your father has asked to see you.
My father's here?
In light of the potential bioweapon attack,the president ordered him moved to the white house for his safety.
Thank you,aaron.
I just have something to take care of.
Tell them I'll be right there.
Yes,ma'am.
You've reached martin collier.Please leave a message.
Martin,it's olivia taylor.
I spoke to the contact,but I couldn't go through with it.
I decided to take your advice and walk away.
Please call me as soon as you can.
-this is bauer.
-Jack,it's chloe,
I found something weird about these hits on jibraan al-zarian.
Go ahead.
You know how I said that the two million dollars
was deposited into his account over a period of six months?
Well,that wasn't right.They were backdated.
What do you mean?
One of the trace algorithms caught a discrepancy,
all that money was really just deposited 30 minutes ago.
What about the extremist websites he was visiting?
Same thing with the time stamps.
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
Are you absolutely positive?
It looks that way.
Jibraan could be innocent.
Okay,thanks.
What's going on,jack?
Chloe found evidence that jibraan is being set up.He's been framed.
Why would almeida frame an innocent man?
Because they wouldn't want to risk the attack not being carried out properly.
How could I be so stupid?
An innocent man is so much easier to control.
All they needed was a muslim,they could create whatever background they wanted.
god...****
I am surprised.
Why?You were right.
Not about jibraan.
My experience with the authorities,the police is that they will go to any lengths
not to admit they were wrong.
Even at the expense of an innocent man's life.
At least you didn't do that.
Please know that I forgive you.
I'm not asking for your forgiveness.
Then I hope you can at least forgive yourself.
I gave up on that  a long time ago.
It's never to late to turn towards god,mr. Bauer.
-That's enough?
-Yeah,thanks.
Thank you.
You don't need to stay with me,ally.
But they know where to find me if they need me.
I thought it was important for you to hear what's going on.
And for you to understand why I did what I did.
You're the president,sweetheart.
You don't owe me an explanation.
There's my girl.
Hi,dad.
Livy,you can squeeze a bit harder.I won't break.
Oh,I might!
I'm sorry I couldn't come to the hospital.
Don't be silly.
You're a godsend being here helping your mom.
Just knowing you two were speaking again,let alone working together,that's enough.
Henry,I'm not sure that our détente is holding at the moment.
Olivia,your mother told me about the deal she made with jonas hodges.
And I know you,understandably,have serious concerns about that.
Well,I've had some time to think.
To put myself in mom's position.
To be objective and pragmatic-- the way a good leader should be.
Has to be.
I know that decision was horrible for you.
But I do understand.
I'm sorry I made thehoice even harder.
Jonas hodges will face judgment one day.
If not in this life,in the next.
Mr. Tippet.
Sorry.
It's going to take me a little while to get used to that.
Always does.
I'll need to confiscate the wallet.
We can't let you hold on to anything that ties you to your former life.
And the picture.
You like your job,mr. Sullivan?
It has its challenges.
You strike me as someone who wouldn't be totally satisfied ferrying prisoners around.
I don't plan on doing this my entire life.
Good to hear that.
Maybe you and I can do some work together some day.
Sir?
I don't intend to be mr. Tippet forever.
Sign here acknowledging transfer.
Fbi's identified the man they believe is going to carry out the bioweapon's attack.
Jack bauer and agent walker are on their way to a possible location for him.
Have they found out anything that would give us an idea of the target-- or a timetable?
No.Nothing actionable.Not yet.
Um,madam president.
This is woods.
Are you sure?
How did this happen?
Call me as soon as you know more.
What is it,tim?
Jonas hodges was just killed.
What?How?
Car bomb.As he was leaving fbi.
What else do they know?Are there any suspects?
Not yet.
Um,excuse me.
My guess is this was an inside job.
Inside job?
Whoever ordered the hit knew exactly when and where hodges was being transported.
Damn it!
Tim,get on top of this.
I want to know exactly how this happened.
Yes,ma'am.
Ms.Taylor,is everything all right?
Oh,it's fine.I'll be right back.
Yeah?
Hodges is dead!
Okay,calm down.We shouldn't be talking on the phone.
You don't understand,there's been a terrible mistake.
I spoke to the man whose number you gave me.
But I didn't go through with it.
I couldn'T.Didn't you get my message?
Olivia,I said calm down.
I can't!
Hodges is dead and I'm responsible.
We cannot have this conversation over the phone.Do you understand?
Do you realize what could happen to me if this gets out?
Olivia,you need to stop talking now.Do you hear me?
Take a deep breath,lien to me.All right,we'll hang up,okay?
All right.
Okay,I'm listening.
Can you get to pershing park?
No,not right now.I'm in a meeting with my mother.
Fine.I'll wait.Get there as fast as you can.
We'll talk about this face-to-face.Okay?
All right.
Thank you,aaron.
What do you have,agent?
Armed hostile in the back room,holding a hostage.
What about almeida?
He's not in there.See for yourself.
Reed,give us another look.
Yes,sir.
Move in closer on the hostage.
Is that who you're looking for?
No.That's jibraan's brother,hamid.
They're using him as leverage,to make jibraan do what they want.
How can you be sure?
'Cause that's what I would've done.
Agent,it is imperative that we take this hostile alive.
Right now,he's our only shot at finding out where this attack is going taking place.
Understood.I've already informed my men.
I want to run point on this.Is that all right?
Thanks.
You're going to stay here with the backup teams.
Are you sure that's such a good idea?
What?
Agent bauer-- he doesn't seem to be too well.
Maybe you should be in charge.
I am.
Jack was infected with the bioweapon.
The same one that they are going to use in this attack.
Then he should be in the hospital.
There is no treatment.He probably has less than a dayo live.
So if he is strong enough,trust me,he's the best person for this job.
I'm sorry,I didn't realize.
Agent walker,we're ready.
Please,mr. Bauer,do what you can to save hamid.
We've checked the windows.We have a clear approach.
Let's go.
Agents,stay with mr. Gohar.
On my count.
Three...two...one.
Hamid,stop!
Put it down.We're fbi.We need him alive.
Put it down.He made my brother into a terrorist.
Your brother is not a terrorist.He's innocent.We know that.
He's being set up.He's being forced to do this.
-What?
-Please.
The only one who can tell us where your brother is that man right there.
Now put it down.
Stand up now,put your hands behind your head.
Do it!
Agent walker,move in now.
Damn it,he's bleeding out.
We need a medic,now!
We need a med team on site.
Sit right there.
Are you in their system?
I've tapped into the main security trunk line,
but I'm still looping in breakers to make sure the tap doesn't get flagged.
All right,well,we're on a timetable here.
How much longer is it going to take?
Ten,maybe 15 minutes.
Hand me that case.
What are you going to have me do?
You'll find out soon enough.
Is the subway on schedule?
Yeah,it's on schedule.
www.tvsubtitles.net