[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
- Jack!
- Put down your weapon. Now!
[Buchanan]
What the hell's going on?
- Where's Ryan Burnett?
- What?
Senator Mayer's chief of staff.
Where is he?
Tony doubled back
to one of his contacts...
who gave him information
of a second attack.
It's gonna take place here in Washington
within the hour.
Juma's operatives are carrying it out.
Burnett's been supporting them all along.
He knows where the attack's
gonna take place.
So you can either tell me where he is,
or I will find him myself.
- Mr. Burnett, you are a traitor and a terrorist.
- I'm not. I love my country.
- [Electricity Crackling]
- [Groaning]
[Over Intercom]
Mr. Bauer, this is President Taylor.
Where's the target?
What you're doing
is against the law, Mr. Bauer.
I am ordering you to stand down.
Where is-
Take Mr. Bauer away.
He's under arrest.
You should have come to me.
You should have presented your case.
And would it really have
made a difference, ma'am?
- [Monitor: Steady Beep]
- Colonel Dubaku is dead.
Laurent must never know about this...
or about his father's cowardice.
There is no sign of my father.
Let me take his place on the assault team.
Spoken like a true Dubaku, Laurent.
It is time for us to go.
This is it, Larry. No question.
They're moving out.
- Any idea what the next target is?
- No.
From here, it is approximately
100 meters to the entrance.
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 7:00 p.m. And 8:00 p.m.
[Man]
Put it there- this bag.
Over there.
Right there.
[Chattering]
- Let's move.
- Yes, sir. Let's go.
[Olivia]
That's it. I need to see her right now.
Ms. Taylor, the president will see you
as soon as she's able.
Well, you tell her
her daughter is done waiting.
I'm going to the hospital
to be with my father.
I think it'd be a good idea to talk
to your mother before you do that.
The president's orders are that
you remain in the White House.
So if I try to leave...
you will actually physically restrain me?
Now, that would never happen, Ms. Taylor.
Because I know you have too much respect
for your mother and her office...
to ever let things get that far.
[Scoffs]
Well done, Agent.
You've been at this a while.
- Five administrations, ma'am.
- [Knocking]
Olivia, your mother asked me
to fill you in on what's happening.
Well, with all due respect, Ethan,
you're the last person she should be sending.
There's about to be
another terrorist attack on this city.
That's why she wants you to remain here.
You're talking about
more planes going down?
We don't know, but whatever's
going to happen will happen soon.
I'm heading to the Pentagon.
On top of all of this...
there's also the invasion to deal with.
So bear in mind, your mother's under
tremendous pressure right now.
It's only a matter of time before the media
picks up on the heightened security measures.
I want to issue a statement
before that happens.
Play down the actual
likelihood of an attack...
talk about the security measures as being
due diligence rather than-
No, Meredith.
The public deserves the truth.
We stress caution and calm...
but we acknowledge we have intel
about another terrorist action.
Yes, ma'am. Angela and I will have something
for you as soon as possible.
- [Knocking]
- [Door Opens]
Madam President,
Larry Moss is calling in.
- He says he's got a lead on the attack.
- Put him through.
Agent Moss, you're on with the president.
Madam President, we've discovered
what we believe was a staging area...
being used by terrorists
on the south shore of the Potomac...
near the I.T.P. Rail and shipyards.
Madam President, we've identified
one of the men as GeneralJuma.
- What? Juma's in D.C.
- Yes, ma'am.
And we know that there are at least
a dozen other men involved in the attack.
And they are armed for a small war.
Have you found evidence that tells us
where the target might be?
No, ma'am, but we have search teams
out looking for the men...
and we're hoping that Agent Walker
has more information.
She's the one who I.D.'d Juma,
but, uh...
we've lost contact with her.
- Lost contact?
- Yes, Madam President.
But we have every reason to hope that she's
still alive and in pursuit of the terrorists.
If she's out there, ma'am, we'll find her.
Hold it right there!
I'm Agent Renee Walker, F.B.I.
Agent Walker?
We just got an alert on you.
You need to call Larry Moss
at F.B.I. Right now.
Tell him there's gonna be
a terrorist attack on the White House.
Yes, ma'am. I'll call it in right away.
This is Thompson-
[Machine Gun Fire]
[Man on Radio, Indistinct]
[Man On Radio] Ranger Thompson,
please respond and report your location.
Ranger Thompson. Ranger Thompson,
Ranger Thompson.
Bill.
The Attorney General wants you transferred
to his custody so I can file criminal charges.
Have you learned anything else
about the attack?
I reached Tony. He couldn't get
any more information from his guy.
According to F.B.I., Renee Walker
followed a lead on her own...
to an abandoned warehouse
on the Potomac.
Got a visual on a heavily armed commando unit
led byJuma himself.
- But she went missing right after she called in.
- What do you mean, missing?
We're not sure. F.B.I. Searching the area,
but there's no sign of her...
- or any evidence telling us
what the target might be.
- Burnett knows.
The president offered him an immunity deal.
He turned it down.
- Hasn't said a word since.
- Damn it, Bill. He was talking
when they stopped me.
Put me in a room with him for five minutes,
and we can stop this thing from happening.
Jack, even if I was willing to release you,
he's being transported to Kennedy Memorial.
- You couldn't get access to him.
- Fine. Then you do it. You can get access.
- I'm not trained in coercive techniques.
- This is not a maybe.
Ryan Burnett is an accessory
to a terrorist attack.
If you don't do this, people will die.
I'm not arguing about what needs
to be done, but I can't do it. It's not me.
- That's not good enough.
- Jack.
Damn it, Bill. That's not good enough.
You were the one who told me-
people who stand by...
they might as well help them
plant the bomb.
You can do this.
Bill, you have to do this.
I can't, Jack. I'm sorry.
Bill.
I can't.
[Hushed Chattering]
- [Computer Beeps]
- This is it, General.
Cimbe.
We're on the other side of the conduit.
Are you in position?
Yes, General.
I will be ready for you.
- [Door Opens]
- What was that?
I thought I heard you say somethin'.
Just, uh, talking to myself.
Yeah. Hey, I tell you
we're having people over on Saturday?
Nothing fancy.
We're bringing in Chinese.
You think you're gonna make it this time?
Oh, Chinese.
I was looking forward to Sheila's cooking.
[Gasps]
[Tool Clatters]
[Lock Clicks]
- All clear, General.
- Excellent.
We'll have access in 10 seconds.
Once we're in, we'll have two minutes...
until the proximity alarms come back up.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Move!
I've accessed
the Secret Service tracking grid.
[Computer Beeping]
Where is she?
Right here, in the Oval Office.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
[Yelps]
- Clear.
- Keep moving.
[Murmuring]
[Beeping]
We will meet resistance,
which we must counter quickly, silently.
We have nine minutes
until the next Secret Service roll call.
We must find the president by then.
[Beeping]
- Yes, sir.
- Keep me up on your status.
[Silenced Gunshots]
Quiet.
The president is preparing
to issue a statement to clarify that.
Yeah, I'll let you know
as soon as it's ready for release.
Let go of the phone.
- Huh?
- [Silenced Gunshot]
Five minutes until roll call, General.
- [Chattering]
- Stay with me.
- I'm on it.
- Let's get this secure.
Down that way.
All the way around. All the way.
[Man]
Move it! Go! Go!
- [Chattering On Radio]
- It's clear.
[Radio Chatter Continues]
Heads up. 10:00.
Let's go.
[Panting]
- Juma had your father killed.
- What?
Listen to me. I know that Dubaku
is your father. Juma's been lying to you.
- Your father is dead.
- My father is alive!
Juma had to make sure
that your father didn't talk...
so he sent a man named Udo
to murder him.
No. L- I don't believe you.
I was there when Udo did it.
That's how I found you-
by following him back to the railcar.
GeneralJuma betrayed you.
You are lying.
You are lying!
[Gasps]
[Muttering]
[Choking]
[Gasps]
- Renee!
- [Man] Set it up.
I know the target!
Reissued warrants
and order for transport, sir.
- [Man On Radio] Transport is set. Stand by.
- Sorry, Jack.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- [Man] This way, Mr. Bauer.
- Bill Buchanan.
- It's Larry Moss.
Renee Walker says
the target is the White House.
- How good is her intel?
- Firsthand.
She says they're getting in
via subterranean access.
I'll initiate a lockdown.
You alert C.I.R.G.
This is Bill Buchanan.
I have confirmation the White House
is the target of a terrorist attack.
Condition red. Repeat. Condition red.
Secure the president.
- Get to your posts.
- [Man On Radio]
All teams be advised. We have breach.
Jack, I could use your help.
I need to know you'll do exactly as I say.
You have my word.
- Where's the president now?
- Oval Office.
- What's the meaning of this?
- You need to come with us.
The White House is under attack.
- What?
- Madam President, we need to go.
Ma'am, we need to go right now.
Ms. Taylor.
I've got the president's daughter.
We're on our way to the lockdown.
Men are down.
There's no safe path out.
- We need to secure her in the first floor lockdown.
- Bill, we're clear.
- What the hell is he doing here?
- He's with me.
Madam President, right now
you need all the help you can get.
How is this happening?
Where's my daughter?
Aaron Pierce is taking her to lockdown
as we speak. But we need to move.
Agents in zones five, seven and nine,
please respond.
[On Radio]
Five, seven and nine, respond.
I can't reach anyone in the quadrant.
Juma's men are headed straight for us.
They know where she is.
They're tracking her, Bill.
Madam President, let me see your tracker.
- Bill, what's the most direct route
to the lockdown?
- From the east.
I'll head west with the tracker
and draw them away. You go with Jack.
Mr. Bauer?
This is your house.
I'll follow.
[Man On Radio]
We're moving the president to lockdown.
Agent Hovis, we've got agents down
in multiple quadrants.
- We need reinforcements, sir.
- Copy that.
We're on our way to the lockdown now.
Let's go!
[Beeping]
General.
The president has left the Oval Office.
She's heading down the west corridor.
Udo, take your team that way.
We'll trap her in between us.
We're getting close to the president, sir.
Up ahead, around this corner.
The president's tracker, sir.
[Groans]
They know we're here.
They're moving the president
to the lockdown.
Find her.
Take him. We need hostages.
Start gathering them.
Let's move.
- Cleared five. Seven!
- [Man On Radio] Code red! Code red!
Where?
[All Shouting]
We've engaged hostiles
on the way to the lockdown.
We do not have a visual on the president.
We're still two minutes away.
- [Woman Screaming]
- [Man] Don't shoot!
Get up!
- Move! Move!
- [Shouting]
Move it! Go! Go!
Get up!
Aaron, it's Jack. I'm with the president,
approaching the lockdown.
- Where are you?
- [On Radio, Whispering]
We're still upstairs, Jack.
[Man]
Keep walking!
- Shut up! Move!
- [Woman] Please! Let us go.
Hostiles are in control of the area.
Looking for a way past them
to the lockdown.
Copy that. Juma's men
are closing in on our position.
You're gonna have 30 seconds
to get here before I have to seal this door.
- [Aaron] Understood.
- You will not close this door
until my daughter gets here.
Madam President, right now, your life
is a priority whether you like it or not.
- Please, step inside.
- [Machine Gun Fire]
Madam President, are you all right?
Aaron, it's Jack.
We're sealed off in the lockdown.
We came under attack.
We didn't have a choice.
We couldn't have made it anyway, Jack.
- We'll try to find a way out of the building.
- Copy that. Aaron-
- [Static On Radio]
- Jack. Jack, do you read me?
Aaron, it's Jack. Do you copy?
Damn it. Juma's cut off our communication.
I need to know that my daughter's safe.
Madam President, I can't answer that yet.
[Bullets Thudding]
Abo.
[Man]
Yes, sir.
Let's roll!
[Men Shouting]
GeneralJuma.
They brought in reinforcements.
I don't know how much longer
we can hold them off from your position.
Stand by.
Ngozi.
Agents are moving in from all directions.
We will be heavily outnumbered.
Does Secret Service know
their president is secured in the lockdown?
The only ones who saw are dead.
Put me on to their communications channel.
- [Beeps]
- Go ahead, sir.
This is GeneralJuma.
I have the president.
Evacuate immediately, or she will die.
[Men Shouting In Distance]
I need proof you have the president
before I can give that order.
- Let us speak to her.
- Who is this?
- Special Agent Hovis.
- Agent Hovis.
Move your men out of the building
and beyond the fence line...
or I will kill the president.
And her death will be on your head.
Agent Hovis?
We're pulling back.
All agents fall back immediately.
[Man On Radio]
Wilson here. Pulling back.
I repeat: All agents, fall back.
[Man On Radio]
Copy that. Pull back. A II teams, pull back.
- [Men Chattering]
- [Radio Chatter Continues]
General, Secret Service is retreating.
They are retreating, General.
- All of them?
- Yes, sir.
Gather all the hostages
and bring them here.
Come on, move!
- Lock down the exits. Move.
- Sir.
- [Chattering]
- [Radio Chatter]
[Juma On Radio]
Cimbe. Status report.
Confirming Secret Service retreat
in western quadrant.
- Continue sweep.
- Copy, General.
[Whispering]
The only reason Secret Service would retreat...
is if they thoughtJuma had the president.
But that man Bauer said
he got my mother into the lockdown.
Juma's bluffing them.
We need to get out of here...
and let our people know that as soon
as possible so they can retake the building.
Get out of here? How?
They're everywhere.
- Move it!
- Get them in the back!
Everyone keep moving!
Keep your hands on your head.
Move it!
- Stop lagging! Let's go!
- Move it!
[Chattering Continues]
Move it! Move!
- Move it! Come on!
- [Men Shouting]
Move it!
Move your feet!
[Shouting Continues]
- Right here! Come on!
- Keep going!
- Sit!
- Everybody down! Get down!
[Shouting Continues]
Turn around!
- [Men Shouting]
- [Women Whimpering]
[Beeping]
Can you open it?
Yes. Assuming the specifications
Hodges gave us are correct.
- How long?
- Fifteen minutes.
[Beeping]
Right here, Agent.
Copy.
We confronted them
in one of the first floor corridors.
At that point,
Juma ordered us to retreat...
threatening to kill the president
if we didn't comply.
But he never gave a visual confirmation
he was holding the president?
He didn't, but I felt at that point,
I had no choice but to pull back.
His men were killing civilians and agents.
Any idea how many people
are still trapped inside?
Cross-checking the evacuees
with the White House manifest...
so far, it looks like 53.
- Any Secret Service?
- As far as I know...
we have no agents
left in there still alive.
Hostage rescue teams
are moving into place.
They'll be prepared to storm the building
as soon as the order's given.
Yeah, well, at this point, that order
has to be given by the vice president.
- What's his status?
- Secret Service has him en route
to a secure location.
All right. Let me know
as soon as he's locked down.
And, Hovis, I need an infrared sat scan
of the building.
- Highest resolution possible.
- Got it.
You didn't tell me
thatJack was in the White House.
He was under arrest, being held under guard
when the attack took place.
Under arrest for what?
He found out an aide
to Senator Mayer named Burnett...
was part of the conspiracy.
He was caught torturing him-
in the White House.
Almost killed the man
before he was stopped.
[Slide Clicks]
Renee, the president is our priority,
notJack Bauer.
- Are we clear on that?
- Clear.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
They're bringing in more hostages.
- Get in there!
- Sit down!
Sit! No talking!
- No talking!
- Silence!
I don't see Olivia.
Madam President, that's good news.
I know Aaron Pierce.
He will do everything in his power
to make sure that your daughter is safe.
This is the White House, for God's sake.
How was it possible that they were able
to get around our security protocols?
There's only one explanation.
They had help on the inside.
From whom?
Oh, this is insane.
Juma must realize that there's no way
for him to get out of this alive.
I'm afraid he does.
This is his endgame.
He came here to make a statement,
and he's willing to die for it.
As soon as the rescue teams
realize that you're secure, they'll move in.
It's only a matter of time.
What's he doing?
- Is that some kind of explosive?
- No.
- Mr. Bauer?
- Oh, my God.
- [Beeping]
- They've got the access codes.
- I need to get into that panel.
- Is there something I can do?
Yeah. Get me that toolbox over there.
Put it on the table.
Damn it.
Madam President,
plug the cord into the wall, please.
Now.
Okay.
General.
- What's wrong?
- It just went dead.
Somehow, they must have
disabled the circuitry from inside.
Do we use C-4 to blow open the door?
We'll have to drill sinkholes
into each of the 11 locking rods.
It would take too long.
Depending on how the steel is hardened,
C-4 might not even work.
Then you will find another way.
There can be no room for doubt.
We have the president trapped.
We open up that door,
we become a part of history.
We will find another way.
[Beeping]
- [Reporter] Despite previous predictions...
- [Phone Ringing]
American forces have met
surprisingly little resistance...
in establishing a protective ring
around Sangala City.
Top military leaders
are pleased with the progress-
Yes.
Oh. Just a moment.
Call came in on the dedicated uplink.
- I heard it.
- It's him, sir.
Put him on speaker.
General, didn't expect
to be hearing from you directly.
- What is it I can do for you?
- We have a problem.
The president is secured in the lockdown.
Well, we prepared you for that possibility.
We gave you the specs
for the locking mechanism.
They shorted the lock out from the inside.
I need you to find me another way in.
General, I've given you
everything I have to give.
My part in this thing's over.
Are you forgetting
that you don't have the shipment yet?
Now, General,
I expect you to be an honorable man.
We made a deal.
We held up our end of the bargain.
We got you in the White House.
I expect you to hold up yours.
I don't care about your expectations.
You help me, or I will destroy that shipment
before it ever arrives to you.
Hang on.
Well, Seaton, what do you think?
Can he do what he says?
Shipment's not due in the port
for another two hours.
His men will have plenty of time
to destroy it...
render it useless.
General, tell me.
Who else is in the lockdown
with the president?
My men saw her enter with another man.
Well, I'm looking
at the White House manifest.
And according to this, Olivia Taylor
is presently in the building with you.
The president's daughter?
Are you sure?
Their system logs everyone
in and out electronically.
If it says that she's in there,
she's in there.
Now, you find Olivia Taylor, and you'll
get the president to open that door.
Your shipment will arrive as planned.
Thank you.
There, you see? Stress.
Stress is the fertilizer of creativity.
Let's play some darts.
The president's daughter
is somewhere in the White House.
Let's find her.
Raise your heads.
Show me your faces.
[Man]
Silent.
[Snapping Fingers]
Eyes down.
What do you think's going on?
I asked you a question, Mr. Buchanan.
You think I made
the wrong call with Bauer.
You think that if I'd signed off on him
torturing Ryan Burnett...
all of this could have been avoided?
You don't know
what I'm thinking, Senator.
Your hands where I can see them.
She's not here.
Go and find her and bring her to me.
[Helicopter Passing, Distant]
Our orders are to hold tight
and wait for them.
What happened?
What'd you see?
- Door's guarded.
- There's gotta be another way out.
There are only three exits to this wing,
and they're all covered.
The windows are sealed
and hardened- unbreakable.
We have to let them know the terrorists
are bluffing, that they don't have my mother.
Our only option is to get a signal out.
- We can do it from the windows of the residence.
- Okay, good.
You'll be safer
if I leave you in a secure area.
I'll get the signal out
and come back for you.
I'm not gonna sit and hide
in some damn vent, Agent Pierce.
Ma'am, it is a long way, and we're probably
gonna encounter more ofJuma's men.
- It's too dangerous.
- I don't care.
I'm going with you, and don't try to argue.
We don't have the time.
Okay. Stay behind me.
[Beeping]
[Men Shouting, Indistinct]
- [Chattering]
- Inside.
Agent Moss, sat scan's all set up here.
We can see the cluster of hostages,
but not the individual bodies.
The best they can do?
They can't boost the resolution?
No, sir. The White House is one of the most
heavily shielded buildings in the world.
- [Man On Radio] You copy?
- Yeah, I got it.
Vice president's ready.
They're initiating communication.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- [Moss] Give us the room.
- [Woman] Yes, sir.
You're on with the vice president.
Mr. Vice President,
I'm Special Agent Moss...
head of the F.B.I. D.C. Branch.
This is Agent Walker.
I've been briefed
on the general situation.
What are the latest facts on the ground?
There's nothing further
from GeneralJuma...
but an infrared scan of the building
shows he's holding the hostages...
in a hallway outside the Roosevelt Room.
- This is very possibly good news for the president.
- Explain.
The area's not one of the more
defensible places in the building.
Tactically, it makes no sense forJuma
to have chosen it as a base.
However, the area is adjacent
to the ground floor lockdown...
which we know the president
was en route to.
So you think the president
made it into the lockdown?
That's our best explanation
for him being there.
We're therefore asking you
to authorize the rescue operation...
beforeJuma manages
to penetrate the lockdown.
Do you have any other evidence...
that supports your theory
that the president is in the lockdown?
There's the fact that he couldn't
produce the president...
when we asked him to prove
that he had her.
Couldn't or wouldn't?
You can't be certain which one it is, can you?
Certainty is not possible in this case, sir.
We're giving you our best estimation...
and we urge you to allow us to launch.
What if you're wrong?
What ifJuma does have the president?
He will kill her as soon as he realizes
what you're doing.
Inaction has its own risks too, sir.
The more timeJuma has
to reinforce his position...
the more difficult it'll be
to take the building and to save lives.
I understand...
but my priority must be
the president's life.
Prudence dictates that I hold off
on authorizing the rescue operation...
till we can be more certain of her status.
Mr. Vice President, terrorists
are in control of the White House.
I would ask you to consider if prudence
is the appropriate response in this situation.
I thank you for your thoughts,
Agent Walker.
But until you can provide me with more intel
on what's goin'on in there...
you are instructed to refrain
from launching any action.
Keep me apprised
of any further developments.
- All he's interested in is covering his own ass.
- He's the vice president.
Right now, he's calling the shots.
It was the right call, sir.
You can't order an operation
that results in the president's death...
and your own elevation to the job.
It would be politically untenable.
Never let anyone hear you
talkin' like that, Derek.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
[Olivia]
Oh!
[Groans]
Oh, my God, Aaron.
They would've heard those shots, so you're gonna
need to get the signal out before they get back.
There's a security kit behind that door
in the bureau.
It's got first aid and a flashlight.
You'll flash Morse code out the window.
Reach in my jacket.
I got a pen.
Here. Give it to me.
[Groans]
Give me your hand.
This is called "code green."
A dot is a short blink. A dash is a long one.
Code green will signal them to move in.
Go.
[Screams]
- General Juma, I have the president's daughter.
- [Gasping]
[On Radio]
Bring her to me.
- Bring him.
- [Man] Come on. Get up.
Get up! Go!
[Man]
Go on.
[Beeping]
- (HDTV SUBTITLES FROM HERE) -
added by w3sten
Sources have confirmed that the siege inside the
white house began approximately 40 minutes ago.
We do not yet have confirmation on
the number of hostages being held,
or if the president is among them.
Behind me, you can see dozen of
tactical assault units standing by.
Government analysts tell us the order to
launch any operation in these circumstances
would rest with the vice president.
General, I discovered fiber-optic
cameras embedded in the chandelier.
- Get me a chair.
- Yes, general.
He spotted the cameras.
Give me a secure channel.
Go ahead, sir.
President taylor, I see now
that you've been watching us.
Good. There is something
I think you should see.
God, no.
If you don't open the door,
I'm going to cut out your
daughter's eyes one by one.
And then I'm going to
cut out her tongue...
- and then her head.
- Mom, don't listen!
I know what you're thinking.
How do you know if you open
the door that I won't kill her?
All you need to know is that I most
certainly will kill her if you don'T.
- open the door.
- Madam president,
- No.Open the door.Open the door!
- I can't! I can't!
That is my daughter out
there. Do you understand?
I've already lost my son.
Have you any idea what
it's like to lose a child?
Madam president, I am genuinely
sorry, but I cannot let them take you.
There is nothing you can do for her now.
Do you have children, Jack?
I have a daughter.
Could you do what
you're asking me to do?
Ju stand by and watch her butchered?
No, ma'am. But I am not the
president of the united states.
Well, i am the president.
And I am ordering you to open that door.
You're running out of time.
mom...
perhaps this will make your
mother decide more quickly.
mom, you shouldn't have...
I wouldn't let them hurt you, darling.
Damn it, bauer. What have you done?
all right, general, you've got me now.
There's no reason to hold anyone else.
Let them go.
You... don't give orders to me.
Get the camera ready for her statement.
What statement?
The last one you'll ever give.
www.tvsubtitles.net