[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
Agent Walker told me that there's a chance-
a small chance that I could help you.
I'm dying, and whatever small chance there is
to stop that from happening...
it is not worth the pain...
for me to let you sit there and watch me die.
Daddy, I don't wanna lose you.
- Come here.
- I don't.
- [Grunts]
- What is it?
Sweetheart, I'm sorry. But you need to go.
Hodges was behind everything that happened
today, from the planes going down...
- to the attack on the White House.
- What?
He's also responsible
for the death of my brother.
All you need to know is Hodges worked a deal.
Witness protection.
My mother approved it, and he's going free.
Unless someone intervenes.
I'll get you contact information, a price...
and instructions on how to transfer the funds.
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor.
I spoke to the contact,
but I couldn't go through with it.
Listen to me, Jibraan.
If you don't do exactly as I say...
you're gonna watch your younger brother die
right in front of your eyes.
And then, I'm gonna kill you. Hmm?
It was the Americans
who killed our parents, Hamid.
- I'm going to make them pay.
- What have you done to my brother?
You've poisoned his mind. This isn't my brother.
We're looking for a man who worships here.
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian.
Do you know him?
I know him, but he is not a terrorist.
We did not come here to debate this with you!
Where does he live?
You come into a house of worship
with information you should not have...
an outrageous accusation,
no legal warrant and threaten me.
- I have not threatened you.
- Not yet.
But we both know where this is going.
Jack, it's Chloe. I found something weird
about these hits on Jibraan Al-Zarian.
You know how I said the two million dollars...
was deposited into his account
over a period of six months?
That wasn't right. They were backdated.
What about the extremist
Web sites he was visiting?
Same thing with the time stamps.
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
Jibraan could be innocent.
- What do you have, Agent?
- Armed hostile in the back room,
holding a hostage.
- What about Almeida?
- He's not in there. See for yourself.
- [Man] Is that who you're looking for?
- No.
It's Jibraan's brother, Hamid.
They're using him as leverage
to makeJibraan do what they want.
- How can you be sure?
- That's what I would have done.
- Hamid, stop!
- [Gagging]
Put it down.
We're F.B.I. We need him alive.
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 5:00 a.m. And 6:00 a.m.
[Hissing]
[Woman] The canister's being retrofitted
to maximize dispersion.
We're on target
to release the bioweapon...
at Washington Central Station
within the hour.
- Your casualty estimates are holding up?
- I think they're conservative.
A significant portion of the pathogen...
will escape into
the station's ventilation system...
which will circulate it for us.
Between 8,000 and 10,000
commuters will be exposed.
Tell me about Mr. A l-Zarian.
Is he compliant?
Yes. His primary concern at
this point is for the safety of his brother.
And what's his level
of awareness regarding the plan?
He won't know anything
about the canister until it's too late.
- Good. We'll talk once it's done.
- [Beeps]
- [Electronic Tone]
- [Hissing]
Trigger mechanism's working.
[Grunts]
This device will tell me
where you are at all times.
- [Beeps]
- It'll also allow us to talk to each other.
Talk about what?
You still haven't told me
what you want me to do.
Right now I just want you
to get on the subway...
and take the Red Line all
the way to Washington Center.
- And when I get there?
- I'll let you know then.
I'm not stupid.
I know you are going
to blame me for something.
- Jibraan-
- What's your plan, huh?
You are going to hurt people?
Jibraan, the only person you
need to worry about right now...
is your brother.
You follow my instructions,
and Hamid lives.
You do something stupid,
and he dies- badly.
Understood? Good.
Red Line, westbound,
to Washington Center. Got it?
Let's go. Come on.
[Beeps]
[Rapid Beeping]
Sorry this had to happen like this.
We will find your brother.
[Groaning]
- [Man] How you doin'back there?
- You should talk to him.
Kid doesn't know anything...
except that his brother was taken
by Tony about a half an hour ago.
He didn't overhear anything
about a target or the time frame.
Right now, he's our only lead.
He's badly injured. I don't know
if he's in any condition to talk.
- Oh, God!
- Hold his head. I'm gonna
give him some morphine.
No, you're not.
His wound is in the middle
of a nerve cluster.
- He can go into shock from the pain.
- I know.
Back off.
[Groaning]
You should step out of the room.
Do what you need to do.
- Where's Almeida?
- Please, just give me the morphine.
I'll give you the morphine as soon
as you talk. Where's Tony Almeida?
- What's the target?
- I don't know.
[Screams]
God!
- What's the target?
- I don't know! I'm telling you the truth.
My job was just to watch
the kid and monitor things here.
Almeida didn't tell me where
he was going or where the target is.
How'd he contact you?
I can't.
[Screams]
Okay, okay.
I have a number.
But I'm not supposed
to use it unless there's a problem.
You better start thinkin' of one fast.
- Where's his phone?
- I have it here.
Give him enough morphine so that
he can take the pain out of his voice.
- Nothing more.
- [Groans]
I want you to get Chloe
to run a trace on this number.
- Tell her to feed it back to our cell phones.
- [Beeping]
You better start thinkin'
about what you're gonna say.
You try and screw with me on this-
It'll be the last thing you ever do.
You understand me?
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
- [Ringing]
- Janis Gold.
It's Renee. I need Chloe to run
a peer-to-peer cellular trace...
- from a G.S.M. I.D.
- I can do that.
Jack asked for Chloe to run point on this.
What's the number?
- Alpha-Charlie-3316.
- Got it.
- I'll need you to run it
back through to me and Jack.
- Hold on.
- She's working on it.
- Good.
I'll open up the locate
protocol. You establish a secure V.P.N.
- All right, opening a channel
on the inter-satellite-
- Why would you do that?
- What?
- You know, connecting...
through a D.M.A. Node
would be a lot faster.
No, I don't know it's quicker to use a D.M.A.
Node, or else I would have done just that.
- I had no idea the D.M.A. Nodes
were up and running.
- Really?
Because they've been
up and running for about two years.
It's obvious I'll never be able
to do things as well as you did at C.T.U.
All I ask is that you not make me feel
like an idiot while you're pointing that out.
All right.
- [Beeping]
- Agent Walker...
the trace is up and running
whenever you're ready.
- Jack?
- Chloe, I'm on.
You ready? What's the number?
202...
555-0147.
[Beeping]
- [Ringing]
- It's ringing.
- Why are you calling me?
- I was checking Al-Zarian's computer...
double-checking everything we planted.
- And?
- The bank that we used in
Switzerland just e-mailed him...
rejecting one of the transfers
we made in Al-Zarian's name.
You know how to resubmit it?
- I'm not sure.
- Are you getting this?
Tony's got something on his phone that's
encrypting his location.
I'm trying to get around it.
All right. Call our man in Zurich.
He'll walk you through it.
All right. I just wanted to get
your authorization before I did that.
- Any other problems?
- No.
- Good.
- Chloe, did you get that?
I didn't have time to decrypt
all the location data.
All I know right now is that he's somewhere
in the Adams Morgan district.
[Jack] We're running out of time.
We're gonna have to narrow that down.
I'm trying. I have to decrypt the rest
of the location data.
- [Jack] How long is that gonna take?
- I don't know.
Damn it, Chloe,
we've gotta do better than that.
- I need to get off the phone.
- Janis, I want you to contact Metro P.D.
I want you to get them to move
their hazmat teams...
and their tactical teams
over to Adams Morgan.
We're on our way now. Let's go.
[Woman On P.A., Indistinct]
Metro passengers, this weekend
there will be no Blue Line express service...
to Arlington-McLean.
Express service will be resumed on Monday.
- I need you to call the police.
- Excuse me?
- Speak up, sir.
- I can't do that. They're listening.
- Who's listening?
- The people who have my brother.
The terrorists.
They're gonna kill my brother
unless I do what they say.
They want me to get on this train.
- That's it?
- Just get on the train?
Yes, please. You have to help me, okay?
You have to call the police.
- Is there a problem here, sir?
- Yes.
Yes. Thank you, Officer.
Please, I need your help.
Sir, just calm down. Step this way.
- What is it?
- Listen.
They have my brother hostage, okay?
You have to believe me.
Put the earpiece back in.
- What?
- I said, put the earpiece back in.
Now.
[Woman On P.A.
Metro cards are available at all Metro stations.
- [Beeps]
- Listen, Jibraan...
I understand you had to try,
but don't do it again.
Your brother's life depends on it.
Yes, okay. Please-
Just don't hurt him, okay?
- Well, that's up to you.
- Yes. Uh, I do whatever you say, okay?
- I won't cause any more problems, I promise.
- All right.
You remember your instructions?
Uh, yes. Uh-
Westbound Red Line to Washington Center.
We'll be watching.
We're always watching.
- [Woman On P.A., Indistinct]
- [Gate Clicking]
[Beeping]
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- Hello.
- Ms. Taylor, this is Agent Pierce.
- Yes, Aaron?
- Secretary Woods was asking for you.
You told me you were retiring
to the residence...
but upstairs detail confirmed
that you're not there.
Why is Tim looking for me?
TheJustice Department is investigating
theJonas Hodges car bombing.
They're requesting phone
and Internet records...
and want to interview everyone as well.
I didn't realizeJustice
was getting involved.
Apparently there were only 11 people
who knew Hodges was alive.
It stands to reason
that information was leaked.
- Okay. I'll get there as soon as I can.
- Where are you?
I needed to run a personal errand.
Ma'am, am I to understand
that you left the White House premises...
without Secret Service protection?
I won't be long, Aaron. Ten minutes.
Ms. Taylor, this
is a serious breach of protocol.
Your safety is my responsibility.
Aaron, I know.
I promise you, it won't happen again.
Just cover for me till I get back?
Will you do that for me, Aaron?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
[Exhales]
[Rustling]
This is a mistake, Martin.
We shouldn't be meeting. This-
Okay, you need to calm down, Olivia.
I needed to see you.
You were hysterical on the phone.
No, you don't understand.
There's an investigation.
Look, theJustice Department
is asking about my whereabouts.
Okay. Did you think no one would bat an eye
when a government witness was murdered?
I told you. I changed my mind.
I didn't transfer the funds.
The man you put me in touch with said
he wouldn't act until he received payment.
Why would he go ahead
and kill Hodges if he wasn't paid?
Because I told him to.
What?
He called me and told me
the money hadn't come through yet.
I told him you were good for it
and to proceed.
Why, Martin? Why would you do that?
Hodges was going
into witness protection.
There was a finite window of opportunity.
And because it's what you wanted, right?
Despite all my warnings
for you to reconsider...
you looked me straight in the eye
and you said...
you wanted Hodges dead,
to make it happen...
and I did, and he's dead.
Oh, my God.
My phone records. My-My computer-
- Everything-
- Don't worry about any of those.
I'll send you a program to erase
your Internet tracks.
The calls to me mean nothing. Olivia,
the time to worry about your conscience...
was before you put this in motion.
If you let this eat away at you...
people are gonna notice
and get suspicious.
You will bring us both down...
destroy your mother
and her administration.
Think about it. Is that what you want?
- No.
- Okay, then pull yourself together.
I promise you, this will all pass
if you do what I say.
Can you do that?
Say it.
I can do it.
You need to transfer the funds, Olivia.
You do not want this man unhappy with you.
- [Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- Hey, honey.
- Sorry I woke you.
No, no, no. That's okay. I've been up
with Teri a couple times anyway.
She's been havin' a rough night.
I think she misses her mother.
Oh. Well, listen,
I just called to let you know...
- that my flight's been delayed.
- Yeah?
- How long?
- Well, they're saying an hour,
which probably means two.
- Okay.
- What?
I don't know. Maybe you
should see this as a sign.
- A sign?
- That you should stay there.
Try to convince your father that
he should be spending...
whatever time he has left
with his only daughter.
As much as I want to...
he made it very clear that he does not
want me around to watch him die.
Okay. All right. Sorry I brought it up.
- [Beeping]
- Teri and I will be at the airport to pick you up.
Wh- Oh.
[Groans]
My battery is dying.
Is the hospital okay with that?
Yeah. I talked to Kevin.
He said he'd cover my rounds.
Well, that's-that's great.
Well, I can't wait to see you guys.
- Love you.
- Okay. Bye.
- [Groans]
- [Beeps]
[Woman]
I saw you put it in your coat.
- Oh!
- Excuse me.
- It's all right.
- Sorry.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah. Yes.
- [Tone Sounds]
- [Man On P.A. This stop, L Street.
This stop, L Street.
[Beeps]
[Air Brakes Hissing]
- [Tone Sounds]
- Next stop, Washington Center.
Next stop will be the last stop.
Next stop, Washington Center.
The package is in place.
The dispersal mechanism
is set to go off...
while the train is stopped
at Washington Center.
Good. We're on the move.
I'll pick you up at 22nd.
[Engine Starts]
[Electronic Chittering]
- Jack, I unlocked Tony's location data.
- Where is he?
Three blocks immediately south
of your position, on 22nd.
Where exactly on 22nd?
West side of the block.
They're coming up on-
900 feet ahead of you.
800 feet.
All teams, bring your units up
from the south.
- Prepare to move in.
- [Chloe] You're almost on him.
- Okay, we've got him.
- Suspect is in a black van.
We can't let this
turn into a pursuit. Hold on.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Hold on.
[Sirens Blaring]
[Men Shouting]
Tony was trying to destroy
some kind of device when I grabbed him.
- I got it.
- [Grunting]
- [Man] That van- We want it moved.
- [Man #2] Yes, sir.
Lock down this piece of crap.
- [Man #3] Sir. You got him?
- [Man #4]Just drag him over here.
- What do you got?
- Some kind of mobile computer,
but he damaged it pretty badly.
This has gotta have something
to do with the attack. Contact Chloe.
- See what we can find.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna sweep the van
for the canister. [Groans]
[Beeping]
[Chloe] Tony's U.M.P.C. Device
is damaged everywhere I look.
I don't think there's a way
to get it back up and running.
Try a partial reconstruct. Anything that can
help us find out what Tony's been up to.
At this point, I don't even know
about our chances of even doing that.
- Chloe-
- I know.
- Do me a favor. Send me your screen.
- Why?
- Why not?
- [Electronic Chittering]
Huh.
- What?
- [Computer Beeps]
Looks like I can reconstruct the memory state
of the U.M.P.C. At the time it was damaged.
- No, there isn't enough intact data.
- Yeah, there is- in the PROM module.
A lot of handheld devices
back up their memory state there.
That can't be done,
not without the file headers.
Really?
Mr. Bauer? Almeida
just regained consciousness.
Thank you. Stay with this.
I need you to walk away.
Please. You and your men, just walk away.
Where is it? Where's the canister?
I am not gonna stop
until you tell me where it is.
Why did you betray me?
Why?
I have nothing left to lose.
You either tell me where
that canister is, or so help me God...
I will lay you down right here, right now.
You think I've got
anything left to lose, Jack?
Do it.
[Helicopter Passing Overhead]
[Janis] There were
a number of applets running.
We should be able
to run them on our hardware.
I'm uploading a mirror to you now.
You should have it.
- You think it's Jibraan?
- I can't tell, but whoever it is...
they're southbound on Connecticut
at 30 miles an hour.
And theyjust went right through St.
Matthew's Cathedral and out the other side.
He's gotta be on the Metro.
Yes. The Red Line,
ending at Washington Center.
Washington Center's the target.
Put these in the car.
Jack, we haveJibraan.
[Engine Starts]
[Siren Wailing]
Jibraan is on the Metro,
headed to Washington Center.
Chloe, this is Jack. I'm back on comm.
How much time do we have?
Not long. He's almost there.
Okay, listen. Tony had to be able to
communicate with Jibraan somehow.
See if they were using
some kind of comm frequency...
that was strong enough to work in the subway.
- Looking.
- Okay. Wait. There's a proprietary K-band running.
- [Renee] That's it.
- Okay, patch me through.
- [Chloe] Go ahead, Jack.
- Jibraan?
- Jibraan, my name is Jack Bauer. Can you hear me?
- Uh, yes.
Your brother is safe.
I'm working with the F.B.I.
The man who was holding him hostage
has been taken into custody.
- Let me talk to Hamid.
- He's not with us right now.
No, no. I need to talk to him.
Jibraan, listen to me.
Your brother is safe, but you are not.
People who are doing this,
they gave you some kind of a package.
No, no, no. They didn't give me anything.
- We've got real-time coverage of the station.
- Okay.
Jibraan, these people are trying
to frame you for a terrorist attack.
- They had to give you some kind of a package.
- No.
Then it's gotta be on the train.
I want you to start looking
for an abandoned suitcase...
gym bag, knapsack, anything like that.
No, I can't. Sir, there is nothing.
It's gotta be there. Keep looking.
Uh-There was a woman.
- What woman?
- She was with him when, uh-
when they took Hamid.
I think maybe I saw her get off the train.
- Are you pulling into the station right now?
- Uh, yes.
Okay, I want you to stay on the train...
and wait for all
the passengers to get off.
[Brakes Squealing]
- [Tone Sounds]
- [Woman On P.A. Doors opening.
Thank you for using the Metro.
[Woman On P.A.
Welcome to Washington Center Station.
- It's a bomb, isn't it?
- It's a biological weapon.
If it goes off,
a lot of people are gonna die.
- Are all the passengers off the train?
- Yes.
Can you see the package?
- Uh, no.
- Jibraan, keep looking. It's gotta be there.
- Jibraan?
- Yes. Yes, I see it there- I see a duffel bag.
Okay. I need you to open it.
Wait. Why me? Wh-Why must I do this?
You're the only person that can, and if you
don't, thousands of people are gonna die.
Jibraan, I need you to open the bag.
Look, I know I'm asking you a lot.
Please.
- Jibraan, are you still there?
- Uh, it looks like a bomb.
- [Beeping]
- I see a light.
It's a timer, and it's counting down.
- How much time is left?
- One minute, 18 seconds.
That's not enough time for us to get down
to you. Try and get the device outside.
There's an escalator to your right.
I want you to start moving now.
Start moving now.
I'll meet you on the street.
- We're about a minute out.
- Okay. Okay.
[Panting]
Hey!
- Oh!
- That's him.
- Hold on!
- No. I have to get out.
- Hold on. What's the hurry?
What is that? Is that even yours?
I have a bomb! Okay?
This is a bomb! Get back.
- Get back! I have a bomb!
- [Screaming]
One side. Move. Move!
Move. Move, please. Watch out. Move.
[Sirens Wailing]
- [Man] Don't move!
- [Tires Squealing]
Wait. He's with us. Jibraan!
Jibraan, I'm the man
who was talking to you.
Give me the canister.
Go with these men. They'll help you. Go!
[Beeping Continues]
[Hissing]
[Knocking]
I got it from here, sir.
- Is he all right?
- Yes, sir.
- You are Mr. Bauer?
- Yes.
You did great. Thank you for everything.
I want to see my brother.
I know. We're gonna bring him here.
But right now I'd like you to go with Agent
Moran so he can take your statement. Please.
[Moran]
Follow me.
[Groans]
It's all right. It's all right.
- You need to give yourself a shot.
- I already did, 20 minutes ago.
- It's not working.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- We stopped it.
- Yeah.
You can finally rest.
- [Groans]
- It's okay.
[Beeping]
[Man On P.A.
... and pending for Indianapolis...
we do apologize for the delay at this time.
No, uh, departure time at this point.
- [Woman] Can I have a piece of the paper?
- [Man] Yeah. Have all this.
- What's that?
- [Clears Throat]
This is Section "A."
It's the only thing I want.
I'll give it to you soon as I'm done.
Excuse me. Do you mind if I sit here?
No, of course not.
- [Exhales]
- You heading home?
- Yeah.
- Us too. We live in Glendale.
- Woodland Hills.
- Oh, my husband's parents live there.
You know the Pelusos?
I don't think so.
- Do you mind doing me a favor?
- Sure.
Do you see the man behind us at a table?
He's wearing a suit.
- Uh, short, dark hair?
- Yes.
Yes. Is he staring over here?
No. You know him?
No. It's just that he
was staring at me earlier.
Well, you're very pretty.
[No Audible Dialogue]
- Oh-
- What?
No, he's moving away now.
I've got her in sight.
She's waiting at the gate now.
They should begin boarding
within the hour.
Okay, look. I know that
the bioweapons threat is over...
but I'd feel a lot better if you'd watch
over her until she gets on that plane.
- Yes, sir. I'll let you know when she's in the air.
- Thanks.
I need you to contact the Bureau office.
Tell 'em we need a full interrogation
package ready for when we arrive.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks.
[Man]
Folks, help us out here, please.
[Renee]
Jack. I just got word-
Jonas Hodges was killed
with a car bomb less than an hour ago.
- What? How?
- We don't have any leads yet...
but obviously somehow the people he was
working for found out he was still alive.
That means they're
gonna be comin' after Tony.
We need to transport him in a convoy.
Full guard detail, weapons ready.
- We're not losing him again.
- Okay.
[Helicopter Passing Overhead]
The F.B.I. Iocated Al-Zarian.
There was nothing we could do.
You're telling me the canister is gone.
Damn it!
Without that pathogen, everything
that we worked for is finished.
You should also know the F.B.I. Has Tony.
Then you need to have him eliminated.
- Alan-
- He knows too much, Cara.
We can't take the risk that he'll break.
You need to take him out.
I'm trying to tell you
that won't be necessary.
Tony won't be in custody for long.
- What are you talking about?
- Trust me.
I've got another play.
You better have.
The incoming flight from Boston
will be arriving shortly.
Once the passengers have deplaned...
and the maintenance crew is given
a chance to clean up the aircraft...
we should be able to begin boarding.
We appreciate your patience. Thank you.
Well, at least we know
the plane's on its way.
I'll believe that when I see it.
Well, I'm gonna get some coffee.
- Does anybody want anything?
- I'll take a decaf.
- Nothing for me, thanks.
- Oh, come on.
- Are you sure? It's my treat.
- No, no. Thank you.
- Your husband's really nice.
- Hmm.
- He has his moments.
- [Laughs]
You know what? I'm- I'm gonna use the
restroom. Do you mind watching my bag?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Your attention, please. Passengers on
delayed flights, please check the monitors...
for the new departure times
and gate assignments.
... is now ready for boarding.
All passengers,
please report to Gate 17-A.
[Gagging]
[Neck Cracks]
[Beeping]
Ms. Taylor.
Agent Pierce...
I know you're upset I went off protocol...
but as I told you, it won't happen again.
No, ma'am, it won't...
or you'll need to find
someone else to do this job.
Aaron, that won't be necessary.
Ma'am, you said you left the grounds
to run a personal errand.
May I ask what it was?
I just needed to get out of here-
be alone, clear my head,
if only for a short time.
Everything that's happened today-
being held hostage...
Jonas Hodges's murder...
and seeing my father
so weak and vulnerable-
I was feeling overwhelmed.
Aaron, I'm trying to live
up to my mother's expectations...
and I didn't want her...
or anyone else, for that matter...
to know I was being affected
by the pressure.
I hope you can understand that.
Yes, ma'am.
I think I can.
You feeling all right now?
I am, actually.
I guess I just needed to tell someone
what was going on with me.
I'm glad it was someone I could trust.
Well, thank you, ma'am.
I'll have those phone
and Internet records...
ready for theJustice Department
investigator shortly.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, Aaron.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- This is Kanin.
Sir, this is Agent Pierce.
- I hope I didn't wake you.
- No, Agent Pierce, I'm wide awake.
- What can I do for you?
- Mr. Kanin, some years ago...
while I served
on President Palmer's detail...
I was made aware
of some modifications made...
to the chief of staff's office.
- You mean during Mike Novick's tenure?
- Yes, sir.
Specifically the installation
of a voice-activated recording system...
that allows staff meetings
to be logged and archived.
If you're asking whether I used the
recording equipment, the answer is yes.
Sir, did you disconnect it
when you resigned and left your office?
No. Why are you asking?
I'd prefer not to answer that at this time.
I need to know how to access
the digital recorder.
You can't. It's secured with a biometric lock.
You need my thumbprint.
Look, Aaron, if you want my help...
you're gonna have to tell me
what this is about.
Olivia Taylor's still using my office.
Does this have to do with her?
I really can't talk about this
over the phone right now.
I'll be at the White House
within the half hour.
Thank you, sir.
[Beeps]
[Beeping]
[Inhales]
[Exhales, Clears Throat]
- Do you have something you'd like to say to me?
- Like what?
- Oh, I think you know.
- I don't think I do.
How about, " Good job, Janis,
on reconstructing the U.M.P.C."?
Or, "Just maybe I should have considered the
possibility that you know what you're doing"?
Oh, you don't know me,
but if you did, you would understand...
that this is the last place you should look
for any type of validation.
How about just acknowledging
you were wrong?
- We're almost ready to go.
- Okay.
- Is this her?
- Uh-
Yes, but when I saw her
in the Metro, she had on this dark wig...
and a leather jacket.
Jibraan, your brother's here.
Hamid!
- Let's pack up.
- Hamid!
[Sobbing]
[Woman On P.A.
Service to San Francisco now-
Well, the coffee place over here-
'scuse me- didn't have decaf...
so I had to go all the way
to the other end of the terminal.
But I want you to know, I got it.
Thank you.
- [Cell Phone Ringing]
- [Beeps]
- This is Bauer.
- I'm sending a link to your phone.
It's something I think you should see.
Who is this?
Open the link, Mr. Bauer.
[Beeping]
- Who the hell is this?
- Your daughter's in the company of our operatives.
And Agent Franks
has already been neutralized.
You will help Tony Almeida escape,
or my people will murder your daughter.
Any effort to contact her
or warn anybody about this...
will have the same result.
- Do you understand?
- What you're asking me to do is impossible.
Tony Almeida's already been secured.
He's under heavy guard.
Well, that's your problem.
Put this call on your earpiece
and keep the line open.
I'm gonna be listening
to everything you say.
Now, Bauer.
You're gonna pay
for what you did to Larry.
[Mouthing Words]
- [Door Slides Shut]
- I thought you were going with Moran.
[Panting]
Changed my mind.
I wanna see this through.
You're gonna make your move
to break Almeida out soon.
I'm gonna tell you
what to do and when to do it.
Oh, and Mr. Bauer? If any of those agents
in that van get in the way...
you will have to eliminate them,
or your daughter will die.
[Beeping]
[Crickets Chirping]
www.tvsubtitles.net