Mommy?
Here, keep it.
- Dr. Seger?
- Yeah.
I'm Melania Ortiz.
Melania, in person.
Jonathan.
I can't thank you enough for
all your help with the move.
Dr. Hanson asked me
to come meet you.
You're late.
Wow. This is a
beautiful hospital.
This is an old hospital with
groaning pipes and cracking tiles
and ghosts in the attic.
Would have shut down a long time ago,
if it weren't for Dr. Hanson.
The Neuro Wing keeps
this place alive.
Working here is all I've thought
about since I became a surgeon.
When I had my interview
with Dr. Hanson,
I had no idea the position
would come up so soon.
Yeah, the turnover
here is fairly high.
I know how lucky
I am to be here.
This is the most competitive
surgical fellowship in the country.
Luck had nothing to
do with it, Doctor.
Welcome to Hanson Neuro.
He's expecting you...
for a patient consult in his office.
They're about to start.
Right now?
I haven't even unpacked my things.
Why don't you leave 'em in the box,
see how it goes.
The scans show a
well-differentiated astrocytoma.
We were playing a concert.
She was fine.
I can't lose my daughter, Dr.
Hanson. Not Cassie.
Uh, Melania said to come in.
Is that Cassie?
No, this row here
is your daughter.
The others are other patients.
It's like a week at a glance.
So the question is
whether this tumor
is infiltrating
eloquent cortex.
Uh, that's the part of
the brain that controls
movement, language, perception.
Stretched out, the eloquent cortex
is about the size of a bathroom rug.
It's the only thing that
separates us from the crocodiles.
- Your daughter's right-handed?
- Yes, she is.
I-I... I should
break this down.
- What did you just say? Astro...?
- Astrocytoma.
I need a pen.
Dr. Hanson's asking
you about Cassie's hand
because right-handed people will
usually have their language areas
in their left temporal lobe,
where her tumor is.
- Who are you?
- This is Dr. Seger, my new Fellow.
I'll be assisting Dr.
Hanson, here on the Neuro wing.
Hey, Lani, I need you free up a
block on the O.R. this afternoon
for an awake craniotomy,
left temporal.
O.R. One is booked.
I'll figure it out.
Cassie Mack.
Okay, we'll map the language
centers first, and then, um,
we'll go back in and take
out the tumor, okay?
Okay.
Tu...?
Did he just leave?
Your daughter has a very good
chance of recovery, Mrs. Mack.
Dr. Hanson's the best there is.
Is that your new job?
I've been a practicing brain
surgeon for several years.
No, is it your new job to
tell people how great he is
after he takes off?
At first,
it was just an annoyance.
I'd forget where I
parked my car, Doctor.
Tell me when you
stop feeling this.
Now. But it's gotten
much worse lately.
Now.
I'll get confused
going somewhere new.
Even reading maps is difficult.
You know, this seems
kind of old-fashioned to me.
I don't know, I just...
expected something more high-tech
from a brain surgeon.
I'm a neurologist. We like to
try and solve all your problems
without actually
exposing the brain.
Smell this.
C hristmas.
Peppermint.
Can you tell me what smelling
peppermint has to do
with me getting
lost all the time?
Well, lucky for you, nothing.
Follow the light.
If you smelled sewage
or turpentine
we might have had a problem.
Do you do all your
exams barefoot?
Eyes closed now.
Tell me what's in your hand.
A... rubber ball.
We have as many nerves in our
feet as we do in our hands
or lips,
but we box them up all day.
I think neurologists,
of all people, should go barefoot.
All right, no peeking.
Oh, you remind me of my ex.
She hated rules, too.
Is this a pair of eyeglasses?
Oh, I don't like random ones.
One more.
This is a cigar.
You have some
mild astereognosis.
Together with the disorientation,
we should probably get some scans.
Hey, I didn't know if you
wanted to take a moment
to go over your
expectations for me.
This is a tricky
little astrocytoma.
Uh, Mrs.
Mack's pretty shaken up.
I reassured her this surgery was
just to map her daughter's cortex,
but I think she'd like to hear it
from you again, before we start.
Yeah, I'll have Lani
give her a call.
Right, well, you know, it's my
experience that the emotional state
of the family can impact the
physiological resilience of the patient.
Yeah, I've also found taking the
tumor out of the patient's skull
is fairly effective, as well.
Doug Hanson!
Who's that?
You in here?
Oh, hi, Penny.
How are you?
Meet my new Fellow,
Jonathan Seger.
What happened to Zellman?
I don't know.
Penny's a stewardess
for Air France.
Screw you. This is the sales uniform.
We have to wear it.
- Who was Zellman?
- You have his locker.
Hey, Penny, if you're pushing pills,
you're outta luck.
You're gonna have to leave
your samples with Melania.
I am not repping
pharmaceuticals anymore.
I sell doctor toys for Ulysses.
The Swiss company? Respirators?
Next-generation-image  processors.
I'm setting up a demo on the floor.
You look great.
Thanks, but we don't
need any new toys.
How about surgical robots?
We make those, too.
told you I have
surgical robots.
They're called "interns."
But interns make mistakes and
they don't have four arms.
Think about the imager, Doug.
The hospital will take it seriously,
- if you're interested.
- Yeah, but I'm not.
It's nice to see you, though.
Bye, new guy.
What do you think? Will we all be
replaced by surgical robots someday?
I don't know.
When a robot can't decide
what it wants for lunch
or flips off another robot for
not letting it merge into traffic,
that will be real
artificial intelligence.
It'll never happen.
The brain's too mysterious.
Don't you think?
It's wires...
in  a box.
How long are you staying here?
A week. Visiting my son.
He's busy with work, so I figured
I'd see a doctor about this.
What's his name? Your son?
Otis.
My dad fixed elevators.
I helped him out every summer
till I went away to school.
Otis's mom never knew
where I got the name until
we were riding on the elevator
down to the maternity ward.
He's a lawyer like me.
They work him like a dog.
Your father must have
been very proud.
He was.
And I still miss those summers.
Does this hurt?
No, it's loud.
Just scoot down.
Is this gonna be bad?
When I opened my eyes this morning,
the alarm clock read 9:11.
Bad omen.
I know you're going to find
something terrible in there.
That's the beauty
of being human.
There's not another
species for a billion miles
that can make itself scared.
We think too much.
She's back.
You might still feel a little
groggy from the general, Cassie,
but I'm gonna show you
some flash cards now,
and I want you to
name what you see.
Dr. Hanson will be using
a small electric probe
to see where the language areas
on your cerebral cortex are.
Uh, don't you, like,
have to open my head up first?
We're way ahead of you, dear.
All right, let's go.
Um, an umbrella?
Next.
A tree.
Good.
A b...
b...
A book.
Mark it. That's language.
Next.
Arterio-Venous Malformation.
That's where Mr.
Wills is getting lost.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Lilacs.
Sometimes the probe can
trigger a sense memory.
Did you smell lilacs?
We had these bushes outside,
by our old house.
Jenna and I used to
call it our oasis.
I could smell the flowers,
and the wood shingles
drying in the sun.
It was morning.
Do you think you
could do that again?
Doug?
Let's keep going.
We have to keep going.
It's... It's best if
we don't go back.
It's a suitcase.
Who's Jenna?
My twin sister.
She was killed in a
car accident last year.
She died in surgery.
That's how come my
mom is so freaked out.
That's a heart.
- Oh, sorry.
- No... Uh, good morning.
- I'm Jonathan Seger.
- Adrianne Holland. Neurology.
Were you meditating
when I came in?
Uh, this girl's got a mass
right on top of Wernicke's area.
She could lose her language.
I've got a guy who's convinced
he was gonna have a bad day
because his alarm clock
said 9:11 when he woke up.
Turns out he's got an AVM.
Maybe the clock was right.
Is Hanson gonna operate?
He'll be supervising
Dr. Coffey.
You'll be there.
You're Hanson's shadow now.
When  I look at these...
I don't know, I feel like I'm
looking at an undiscovered country.
There is nothing I love more.
Except, except darkness.
I-I love darkness.
Yeah, the hospital
power's being upgraded.
It's a bit flukey.
You were meditating.
Yeah, I-I do it before surgery.
Acknowledge the stress and
let it pass through me.
Doug hates all that sort
of touchy-feely stuff.
How do you have the
time to meditate?
Oh, well, if I'm on the run, I'll just
be still, put my hand on my heart
and breathe for 30 seconds.
That is such a
doofus thing to do.
Yeah. Well, Vicky,
Vicky thinks, thinks that, too.
- Vicky's your wife?
- Girlfriend.
I-I'm trying to convince
her to move out from L.A.
And just like that,
the sexual tension is gone.
Not completely.
I  have been waiting
for 45 minutes.
No, it can't wait.
This is important.
Sir, everyone who walks through
those doors has something important.
Are you are having
a medical emergency?
What is this place?
We're a neurological clinic.
The car rental people
gave me this address.
- The car had a GPS.
- Okay, breathe.
- Tell me your name.
- Otis. Otis Wills.
My dad is Jim Wills.
His car is in your lot,
and he's been missing since last night.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Excuse me, Dr. Seger?
I'm Jerry Cole. I run
Radiation-Oncology here at St. Abigail.
Of course. Jonathan.
I'm Hanson's new fellow.
Yes, I know.
The sorcerer's new apprentice.
Cassie Mack is a
difficult case.
I did all her scans when
they brought her in.
Yeah, they should be prepping
her for surgery right now.
I'd mentioned to the mother
that Gamma Knife therapy
might be an option.
I did some Gamma training
with Grady in L.A.
It can do amazing things.
It's a miracle technology.
Brain surgery with a
beam of radio energy.
Bloodless, painless.
Patient's in and
out in a few hours.
My practice is the fastest
growing on the East Coast.
It might be right for Cassie,
and I'd still trust Doug
to get in there and eyeball the tissue,
but I'm a surgeon.
It's my job to say that.
How's it going with
"Dr. Handsome"?
Fine.
He's a tough nut.
Where are you going exactly?
I'm still figuring
this place out.
Do you think, in this business,
you have to have
some glaring personality defect to
be taken seriously as a genius?
His own kids don't talk to him,
all right?
I heard he literally
drove his ex-wife crazy.
Dr. Seger? Dr.
Flores is looking for you.
Jonathan, the only thing
Hanson can teach you
is to be exactly like him.
Is it bad?
It's a small tangle of arteries and
veins in the white matter of his brain.
He's probably had
it since birth.
So it has to come out?
The risk of hemorrhage is high.
He's scheduled for
surgery tomorrow.
He could be anywhere.
He could be depressed,
alone, lost.
Without his car,
he can't have gone far.
How can you give
people news like that
and then just send them
out the front door, huh?
Otis.
Where's my dad?
They just woke her up to
prep her for surgery.
She was disoriented.
Any headaches, more seizures?
She can't talk.
I... I...
I... I... I... I... I...
I... I... I...
I... I...
I... I... I... I...
Sedate her. Ativan.
One milligram I.V.
What's going on?
What did you do?
I wonder what it's like
not to be able to speak.
You know when you forget your
high school P.E. teacher's name
and you just can't fall
asleep till you remember it?
Yeah, except she's got
that for every word.
Skulls should come
with a warning label:
"Removing this bone will
change you forever."
Take it easy.
Dr. Cole.
I came when I heard about the aphasia.
Is it global?
Expressive. She
can't speak or write.
Onset was acute.
Her mother's convinced we
did something yesterday,
but all we did was
probe the surface.
It's probably transient.
Some sort of focal brain seizure.
Yeah, she doesn't want to
hear "probably" right now.
She lost the girl's twin on an E.R.
table last year.
She's waiting to
talk to Hanson.
Want me to talk to her?
She really wants Doug.
I can reassure her, you know.
Every minute she sits there,
she's just imagining the worst.
Okay.
But tell her
Hanson's on the way.
I'll use my most
reassuring doctor's voice.
Dad!
Dad...?
Dad.
Good guess.
When I left your office,
I just started walking up the stairs.
I figured someone who's
scared of being lost
probably woun't
leave the building.
If I close my eyes up here,
I'm 15 again.
I know about your surgery.
You're going to be okay.
I don't know.
I got a bad feeling about this.
- If I die...
- Dad!
If I die, Otis,
you're going to have a moment in time
where everything important
in life rises to the top.
You gotta grab that moment.
It's the only
chance you'll get.
You may live.
She's very encouraging,
isn't she?
Fear is the brain's
magic trick,
and you can choose to
believe it or not.
Come on.
Let's get you to surgery.
What's Cole doing in there?
He did Cassie's scans.
They're talking.
And that was your idea?
I changed my mind.
I'm going to go with
the Gamma Knife.
But we already discussed
radio surgery and agreed that
it  might not be the
best choice for Cassie.
Yes, I guess that was back
when she could discuss things.
No, I understand, but changing
therapies this late in the game...
Actually, the language
mapping you performed
will be invaluable to
us in Gamma therapy.
Looks like she's made up her mind,
Dr. Seger.
My daughter came in
here with seizures
and now she can't
speak or write.
You did something.
And Dr. Cole explained to you
the risks of radio surgery.
Intracranial swelling,
radiation injury,
and it could be weeks or even months
before you even know the outcome.
The tumor is perfectly positioned
for me to burn it out.
Aren't you afraid of
missing abnormal cells?
With all due respect,
there's nobody in this city
better at reading brain scans.
I don't miss anything.
I think we need to stress the benefits
of each treatment here, not the risks.
Yes, and as we
discussed earlier,
Dr. Seger agreed that I might
have the better solution.
Excuse me,
I said both options are viable.
I didn't take a side.
I was just laying out the...
There he goes, walking away.
Your daughter has lost her language
because she has a very aggressive tumor.
Every minute that you hesitate,
it invades healthy cells.
You need to let me operate.
You act as if this is some
sort of exact science,
but you don't know
what you did.
You opened up her head with
a saw and you poked around.
It's primitive, is what it is.
No more surgeries.
I want the Gamma Knife.
I thought you said you
weren't interested.
Why don't you give
me your pitch.
Okay.
Medically, the advantages to
investing in Ulysses are obvious:
foremost, the fact that I
could add a deck to my house
and eat my sad frozen dinners
alone in the sunshine.
Want to take it
for a test-drive?
You want to scan yourself?
Yeah. Come on.
Quick.
Okay.
Why don't you type
in "Anonymous."
You are one of a kind, Doug.
"I am what I am."
Was that Descartes?
No, Popeye.
See ya.
I didn't realize Cole was
going to be so aggressive.
All I said was,
Gamma was an option.
Who's "Anonymous"?
That's the default when it's
loaded from another system.
It's a colleague's patient.
What do you make of these?
Presenting symptoms?
Visual hallucinations.
Auras? Flashes?
Yeah, getting more complex.
Like what? Flying elephants?
I thought you were
good at this.
My hunch is something's off.
I'd run an angiogram.
FMRI.
I don't run tests
without evidence.
Okay, you want the neurological
correlates of a hunch?
My eyes see something wrong with
this scan, ahead of my brain.
- I'm good at it.
- Are you?
We do things differently, Doug.
That's the first useful thing
you've said since you got here.
Oh come on, mother brings her
daughter in. We pop the top,
check the oil and
the engine drops out?
Coincidence or not,
I might change mechanics, too.
Gamma therapy's effective.
I am effective.
The Gamma Knife is a tool.
And Cole is a
glorified technician.
Besides, he would do
anything to steal a patient.
You think this is personal?
Of course it is.
He's been envious of my
success for ten years.
Now he thinks his new toy of
his puts him in my league.
What if he's right?
You got played, Jonathan.
Or maybe I'm the only one who
didn't let his ego get in the way.
- What ego?
- I'm sorry?
What ego?
I have yet to see one.
Do you know what "ego" means?
Self-- it's what opens
our eyes in the morning.
It's the thing that allows us
to have an effect on the world.
Our loved ones don't like it,
but it saves lives.
Do you even know
her name, Doug?
Do you know that brain you
touched is a brilliant musician?
Do you know that her string
quartet plays as a trio
with an empty chair since
her sister was killed?
- And those details help you?
- Yeah, these details help me.
Then you're as dangerous
as you are naive.
Then I should go take polyps off colons,
because I can't
screw around in somebody's
head and not know
whose soul I'm
bumping up against.
Then go.
Melania?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know anybody was in here.
Dr. Hanson?
Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
I thought you sounded
kind of manly.
Lucy Canet. Do you remember me?
Hemangiopericytoma.
Salud.
I'm here for my
six month post-op.
This is Ruby.
Makes me sound shallow, but she's
the best thing about going blind.
Hello, Ruby.
Lay down.
So, uh, no improvement, huh?
Not really.
I had hoped your optic
nerve would recover.
Do you mind?
I'm forgetting what
things look like.
Oh, no, no.
That's perfectly normal.
Your, uh...
your visual cortex is
starting to, uh...
reorganize to process
your other senses--
particularly touch.
I'm sorry about your sight.
That was the cancer.
Thank God you saved the part
that can bitch about it.
Ooh, you should
smile more often.
I'll try.
Why aren't you assisting
with Wills' AVM surgery?
AVM's not really my specialty.
How about lying.
Is that your specialty?
Hanson's punishing me...
or testing me.
- What do you think?
- I don't know--
what do you call it when a cat bats
around a crumpled-up piece of paper?
Thanks.
He thinks I screwed up by letting Dr.
Cole talk to Cassie's mother.
Is that some traditional
way to eat those?
They forgot to put in a fork
and I'm too lazy
to go and get one.
I'm pretty sure Dr.
Cole is evil.
Who told you that?
Hanson, probably.
Look, Doug sees the world
as a purely logical place.
The brain is wires in a box,
all questions have answers,
and he knows if he can save
someone's life or he can't.
There's no gray area.
He's like Spock, you know...
if a girl designed the outside.
Do you and Doug have a history?
Not the one you imagine.
Meditate on that.
The thing about our Creator...
even when He ties the veins in
your head into an angry knot,
it's beautiful.
Don't mess with the output
until all the feeders are done.
Fine.
- But back to God...
- Oh, no.
Not today, Angus.
Doug, this could easily
take another three hours.
Surely we can settle
the question.
Intern-- God or no God?
I suppose I can't rule Him out.
Then why am I fixing
His mistakes?
Cancer's alive, too.
How do you know we're
not the disease?
Touche for the nobody.
Flores, actually.
I think we'll call you nobody.
Mrs. Mack.
How's Cassie?
I wish I had her drugs.
Dr. Cole's going to start
the treatments tomorrow.
I know Dr. Hanson is brilliant,
but the surgery...
Cassie's sister Jenna
had the best, too,
and she bled out on the table.
They were so close.
Cassie's not Jenna, Mrs. Mack.
I still miss her every day.
I know.
And with everything that Hanson's
going through, personally...
Personally?
Dr. Cole explained
it all to me.
Thank you, Dr. Seger.
Hi.
Look, I know you're scared of losing
Cassie like you lost Jenna, but...
if you can believe, for a moment,
that it wasn't Hanson's fault
that Cassie stopped speaking,
then you gotta see it was the tumor.
That's the enemy.
Give us a minute.
I don't know what Dr.
Cole told you about Hanson,
but it doesn't matter.
The Gamma Knife is an
incredible piece of machinery,
but the most advanced
equipment in this hospital
is Doug's judgment.
He doesn't hold your hand--
he doesn't know how, but...
there is not another
mind on this planet
I would want focused on
saving my daughter's life.
How's Mr. Wills?
Yeah, good.
The surgery went well.
I heard Jonathan
wasn't invited.
Well, it was probably
a mistake hiring him.
I think he's gifted.
I think he should be teaching
medical ethics at Columbia
and confessing his affairs
with his graduate students
to his wife or his
girlfriend or whatever.
He would, too.
It's too bad.
He looked so good on paper.
You know how female
praying mantises
will often eat male praying
mantises when they mate.
That's why I have cable.
Well, most of the time,
they do it right before the sex.
Now, you'd think as far as evolution
goes, that'd be kind of retarded.
But it would spare you the
awkward chitchat afterward.
This is the beautiful thing.
Yes?
It turns out the boys perform
better without their heads.
- Hey.
Hi. We were just
talking about you.
You were right about Cole.
He's spreading rumors
to steal your patients.
Yes, I know.
But I've moved on.
I have acknowledged the stress
and let it pass through me.
Walk with me, Doctor.
Is this a school?
You know when you told
me that you'd rather
take polyps off of colons
than operate on a patient
that you don't know?
Yeah?
Were you just making that up?
I mean,
did you just come up with that?
Because it's very dramatic.
Listen, Doug, I feel like we've
gotten off on the wrong foot.
I'll be back in a minute.
Keep the car moving.
Otherwise, the moms in
line get very upset.
Doug? Doug?
Excuse me!
You can't just leave your car there!
Who are you?
I'm Jonathan.
Are you Doug's daughter?
Tell me he didn't
hire a driver.
No, no, no, I'm...
What's your name?
Is my phone up here?
Could be worse.
He could be hitting
on a teacher.
I don't think that's
what he's doing.
My friend Geordie,
he says sex is like gravity.
He's more likely to fly than
to stop thinking about it.
I don't...
I don't know. Uh, Doug!
Dad said he cheated on Mom
because the love was gone.
I'm pretty sure it's just
'cause he couldn't fly.
Wh-Why are you telling me this?
If you're gonna drive me every day,
it's gotta come up eventually.
I'm not your dad's driver;
I'm a doctor.
Oh... Then why are you
driving him around?
What are you doing?
- Dad...
- Yeah?
Joey Cole's mom is married.
Cole? As in Jerry Cole?
Yeah, he moved out
three months ago.
She caught him with
a maternity nurse.
This is how you move on?
You hit on his wife?
I'm just saying hi
to an old friend.
He can take it however
he wants to take it.
This is he.
Okay, we're on our way.
Roberta and Cassie Mack
want you to operate.
Good.
Hi.
Radio?
Music?
Oh, yeah-- no, no, no.
Hold on. No...
Music's over here, okay?
It's safe.
Here.
Take this.
I'll get your words back.
She can't bring
that in with her.
Really? Why don't you take
it up with the surgeon?
See, there's some tricky attachments
here by functional cortex.
I think the best way in...
is the natural
cleavage plane here.
I see it.
There's some mass effect, too.
Yeah, but that tissue
should recover.
If you're ever resecting
tissue in my temporal lobe,
do me a favor--
burn out junior high.
Wouldn't that be great?
Yeah, you can take most
of high school, too.
Just leave the part where
Carmen Ramirez got drunk
and made out with
me by mistake.
You're sucking air.
I'm hearing bubbles in the heart.
It's an air embolus.
Damn it.
All right,
put her in the Trendelenberg.
Let's go. Let's irrigate her.
Internal CO2's plummeting.
Flush the central line.
BP's crashing.
There's still air in
the central line.
- Aw, damn!
- She's bradying down.
- Calm down. Calm down.
- She's in the 30s.
She's arresting.
V-fib.
Do it, Seger.
Charge it to 200.
She squeezed my hand
about an hour ago
and she's been
mumbling obscenities.
That's actually a very common
way to regain consciousness.
The more obscene the better.
Good.
I'd like to thank Dr. Hanson.
I'll make sure he knows.
Is it true you almost lost her?
She was gone for a moment.
Johnny got her back.
Cassie's a survivor.
Her language areas were being
compressed by the glioma.
Once the swelling goes down,
she can expect
real improvement.
You make it sound so simple.
Wires in a box.
Did you write this?
That's Cassie's handwriting.
What's it say?
"Jenna says hi."
How'd it go?
Why couldn't you give
those to Cole yourself?
Because he'd never
do me the favor.
He does his best work when he thinks
he's stealing one of my patients.
He saw something weird.
Said he wants to see my
friend to run more tests.
Is something wrong, Doug?
Yes.
It looks like we won't be
buying your fancy new scanner.
That was a test?
You just can't help messing
with people's heads, can you?
It's my job.
Want to get a drink?
Sure, why not?
Life is short.
T
>
www.tvsubtitles.net