You need a baby monitor.
Not yet!
Oh...
You shouldegister
for your baby shower.
At three months?
Why not?
'Cause that's just greedy.
You think the only reason
you get pregnant is
to accessorize.
What about a stroller?
You don't have one, do you?
Check this one out.
Ugh, costs more
than a house payment.
Maybe you and Dennis
should just get a dog.
(thud)
What is that?
What are you doing?
Kate?
Kate!
33-year-old married
woman admitted
this morning after
a grand mal seizure.
Scans show an inoperable
grade-four gioblastoma,
and she's pregnant.
So she chooses radiation
to save herself,
she'll lose the baby.
I know.
I read the chart.
She's had no symptoms
before today.
I mean,
completely healthy.
Are you creeping up
on some pithy observation
about humanity, Seger?
Forget humanity?
How about Kate Larson?
This morning, she woke up
and wondered whether to
have corn flakes or oatmeal.
Now she has to
make the toughest
choice of her life.
Why do you do this, Seger?
I care.
Oh, stop it.
That's too easy.
No. Try to put yourself
in their shoes.
Oh, because fourth year
I took a seminar entitled "Putting Yourself
In Their Shoes."
Do you really want me
to explain empathy?
Can you really empathize
with a person who's dying?
That's impressive.
I mean, can you
really feel what
they are feeling?
I can imagine.
Oh, so you're pretending.
Okay, so I shouldn't try?
Look, there are neural
epithelial cells
in Karen Larson's brain
that woke up a few
months ago
and decided,
decided to replicate
with multiple genetic
and chromosomal
abnormalities.
They don't care
what Kelly had for
breakfast or whether
she's pregnant or...
They only care about
invading healthy tissue.
And all I care about
is trying to stop them.
It's Kate.
Her name's Kate Larson.
Oh. Oh.
Then this will make an amusing
anecdote, won't it?
Yes, it will.
But I mean what I say.
Treat the disease.
Kate.
Your seizure was caused
by a high-grade tumor,
which means it's
moving very quickly.
It's also involved in Broca's area,
which complicates...
I'm not getting radiation.
Honey, let them talk, okay?
Well, she's a step ahead.
But we're talking
about surgery.
No. We can't
remove this type of tumor surgically.
Not from this part
of the cortex.
The damage from surgery
would make things worse rather than better.
It could impact
her language,
cognitive skills,
but surgery's not
the only option.
If I get the radiation,
I lose the baby.
That's right.
Okay, this is difficult
to accept, Mrs. Larson,
but you're not due for six months.
If you don't
get radiation,
you may not live that long.
I appreciate
what you're
saying, I do,
but I'm not going
to lose this baby.
So I'll take my chances.
Guys, it's not a hard
decision for me.
Then we'll support it.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@XXY Sync:FRM@Uranus
MAN:
She's seizing.
???
Nurse! Nurse!
I'm going to go out
to get a posh coffee.
Does anyone want one?
Everything okay?
Hmm? Oh, yes.
Do join us,
Dr. Holland.
I think that Dr. Seger has
finished his critique
of my handling
of this case.
I'm sorry you missed that.
I didn't mean to...
Mrs. Larson's having
drop attacks which are
rapidly becoming more frequent;
one every three hours
and the seizures are cutting oxygen off
to her baby.
Anticonvulsants?
Mm-hmm. She's maxed out
on two of them.
The seizures continue, I'll
consider a corpus callosotomy,
and you'll monitor side-effects.
What was your problem?
It's the tumor killing her.
She could miscarry whether
or not she gets radiation.
You think we should convince her
to give up her baby?
Well, I think we should
take a position.
And if the radiation
doesn't work?
How are you gonna explain
that to Mrs. Larson
after she's given up her child?
What I'd say to her
isn't the point.
This woman is facing a decision
that has no right answer.
And the only thing
that she's got going for her
is that she's made a choice
and she's at peace with it.
And you want to take
that away from her?
Don't answer.
Okay.
He means well.
It's easy to be a saint.
Do you know if we're
allowed to use cell
phones in here?
I mean in the hospital.
Officially, no.
Well, that would imply that you use one
unofficially.
I have no comment.
So some guy's heart-lung
machine goes out
and basically
it's your fault.
(elevator door opens)
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
Oh, thanks.
You are so sweet
for thinking of me.
What's with them?
Oh, Trauma brought in
a homicide suspect.
Always a lot
of paperwork.
Men in uniform.
Oh, and I thought
mind control didn't work.
You know, I don't want some
superficial display
of power and authority
to have this effect.
Mmm...
How do you do that?
HANSON:
You've decided to forgo radiation for
the tumor.
But there is another
decision that has
to be made.
And that's how
we going to treat
these seizures.
Okay.
Right.
Well, during
a drop-seizure,
synchronous electrical waves
pass back and forth
from one side of the brain
to the other, and they do this
via this dense bundle of nerves
called the corpus callosum,
which is this right here.
See this pink?
If we cut this neural bridge between
the two hemispheres...
the seizures will stop.
Cut the brain... in half.
Yes.
Is this permanent?
It is.
And this doesn't
affect the tumor,
it only stops the seizures?
Right.
Well, the seizures
are dangerous.
For the baby.
I know, but what about you?
Right? This is
major surgery.
The seizures are dangerous
for both of them.Remember that.
When-when you cut
the callosum...
Callosum
callosum, uh...
what are the side effects?
Well, normally the left
brain tells the right
brain what to do.
After the surgery,
you'll find that
that is not the case.
You'll probably find
that one half of your body
is going to be
slower to react than the other.
But I'll be able to move, yes?
And-and... walk and think?
That's the idea.
Think about it.
Do we know what ppened?
Had an argument
with his neighbor.
A guy playing his
stereo too loud.
And the neighbor shot him?
No, Mr. Marks here
shot the neighbor,
killed him, and
then shot himself.
God, that explains the cop.
Any alcohol, drugs?
No, he's totally clean.
That's his girlfriend.
Where, her?
Sitting down?
I think so.
Her name is Mary.
Mary?
Yes?
Dr. Seger. I thought you'd
want an update on James.
Oh, we met on the elevator.
Right.
The rebel cell
phone user.
So you're
James's girlfriend?
I'm what?
Oh, I was told...
I'm his lawyer.
(laughs) Oh,
so you thought that while my
boyfriend was in the ICU,
I was winking at guys
on the elevator.
Were you winking?
No, I was not.
So, James has fluid pressure
building inside his head.
We'll need to relieve
that tonight.
And what are his chances of recovering?
Well, we don't know the extent of the damage
yet;
he probably won't be conscious for a while.
Is there someone
we should contact,his family...?
Yeah, his father's in a Florida
retirement home.
That's who
hired my firm.
I will let him know
what's happening.
They allow cell phones
in the waiting room.
So, Kate, this is Dr. Kim,the one here
with the retro glasses.
I'm putting sedative
into your IV.
Wait.
I'm, I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm a little freaked out.
It's okay.
We don't have to do
anything until you're ready.
Okay? Take your time.
What does it feel like?
What?
When you wake up and...
the two sides of your brain
aren't connected anymore.
We had one patient
who said it was, um...
it was as though she had been
living with a roommate all her life,
and she'd finally
gotten her own apartment.
You're joking.
No, I'm not, I'm serious.
Oh, this is so weird.
I know.
You'll be all right.
Okay...
I'm ready.
Okay.
Here comes the anesthetic.
Which leg are we
taking off again?
(chuckles)
Funny every time,??
One piece, on the surface,
in the subarachnoid.
Pretty lucky.
Yeah, probably not
what he was thinking
when he shot himself.
"Gee, I hope I don't
do any damage."
I meant lucky for us.
You see anything else?
Yeah, there's that.
And what is that?
It's...
not the point of entry...?
All right, look at it here.
Oh, hematoma.
Mm-hmm. This one's
a bridging vein
with a slow leak.
Wait. Nothing to do
with the gunshot?
Separate deal?
New hematomas are white.
This one's black,
so it's chronic.
Could've been
there for years.
Ever had your own
head scanned?
No way.
Don't want to know.
Oh, Dr. Seger.
Morning, Lani.
I scheduled a block
in O.R. One for your surgery.
Oh, thanks.
You should be out in
time for a late dinner.
Great.
In case you have a date.
Excuse me?
Well, I could recommend some
nice places, too, in case...
you really are
on the rebound.
Right.
Thank you.
Hey, when you see Doug,
tell him our gunshot also has a chronic
subdural hematoma.
I'll fix it when I
go in for the bullet.
Better discuss it
with the patient's lawyer.
Is my personal lif
some sort of Web-cam?
Did you ask her out?
What?
First of all, I don't
even know if she's single.
Really.
Yeah, and I need
some time.
I'm still getting over Vicky.
You think you
need time,
but we don't choose
who we're attracted
to, or when.
It's not about
what's good for us.
It's the survival
of the species.
It's pheromones.
Pheromones?
We sniff out the best genetic
matchup for our children,
even if it's someone we
know is a complete idiot.
That's romantic.
Which is why after sex,
many couples have
nothing to talk about.
"Has it not been observed
how after copulation,
the Devil's laughter
can be heard?"
Okay, who said that?
Schopenhauer.
Also Wilt Chamberlain.
Right.
Okay, well, I'll try not to be
led around by my pheromones.
You'reissing the point.
And what? What is your point?
To resist is futile.
I could try a cartwheel.
(giggles)
Well, let's hold off
on that.
Kate?
Yes?
Tell him.
My left hand shook a little bit.
Tremor.
Twice. Just... for a moment.
Is it the tumor causing that
or the surgery?
It's hard to say.
Honey,
the seizures are under
control, the baby's okay.
That's the whole
point of this.
Thank you.
So surgery... on James...
Tuesday.
1:00 p.m.
Oh!
(laughs):
You, uh...
you bring your office
with you.
I just came from court.
Highly important case.
What's that?
I'm suing my husband
for divorce.
Oh. Sorry.
Eh. Years of marriage,
I never thought
it would come to this.
You're not married,
are you?
No.
Uh, going through a breakup--
went through.
Uh, something.
Ah. In court I
kept thinking
how good it's gonna
feel to be alone,
at least for a while.
You know,
just take care of me.
I feel exactly the same way.
(music playing quietly)
A coworker of
mine would say
that our attraction to each
other is out of our control.
And why is that?
Survival of
the species.
Mm.
We find a good genetic
mate, our brain releases attraction chemicals--
that way our children--
I mean, our hypothetical
children...
Whether or not
you want children...
Are we having this conversation?
My coworker explains it better.
So I'm given by forces
beyond my control?
'Cause that's how it feels.
I guess we don't
really have a choice.
Mm-mm.
Kate...
I'm Dr. Flores.
Hi.
Dr. Hanson wanted
to make sure
everything's kosher
with the baby, which,
of course,
it will be.
Should I lie down?
Um, no. Take that off.
And I'm gonna put
some gel on your belly.
It'll feel
a little cold.
Hm.
Everything all right?
I'm, uh... I'm not
doing this
on purpose.
Doing what?
Zipping it up.
I don't... I don't mean to.
Come sit on the bed.
(exhales):
Uh...
I can't move my leg.
Um... what's happening?
Page Dr. Hanson.
It's okay.
What's the matter?
(cries out)
Just relax. Relax...
I'm not doing this!
it's ok
Dennis?
I need my other medication,
the Lamotrigine.
(sighs)
(yells)
(slow, steady beeping)
SEGER:
Mr. Marks, we're scheduled
to get that bullet
out of your head tomorrow.
We're also gonna drain
the subdural hematoma, okay?
He said he had some
pain in his face.
Uh, James, can you show me...
Come near me and I'll rip
your throat out of your head!
So the baby's okay?
Yes.
You said Kate
might have
lessened control
over one side, but...
is this unusual?
Her left side seems
to have a mind
of its own.
It does.
Each brain
hemisphere controls
the opposite side
of the body.
Right brain controls
left side, and vice versa.
Both brain hemispheres
are almost identical.
They're interested
in different things.
Left likes to be logical,
and the right side
is more emotional.
Well, that's
an oversimplification...
You're saying that we have
different people in our heads?
Yeah.
No.
Well, anyway...
No, the left brain is dominant,
tells the right brain
what to do,
it says,"Back off, I'm in charge,"
but in your case,
those signals are not getting
across to the right brain.
So the right brain...
Does what it wants.
And what does it want?
We store language
in the left brain,
so it's hard to ask
the right brain...
...what it's thinking.
Does it get better?
Sometimes.
SEGER:
Hey.
Is this okay?
It's perfect. I got an hour
and about three minutes.
Yeah, I got an hour.
When I first got
here,
I thought maybe we should just go
to my place, but then I
thought, no, this is good.
We'll be grown-ups
and have lunch.
Yeah, I've heard people do this.
They-they sit at tables
and they eat food...
Yeah. With their
clothes on.
(laughs):
The-the restaurant's
supposed to be great.
I heard that.
How hungry are you?
I had a big breakfast.
Me, too.
HOLLAND:
You know Adam Serkov?
HANSON:
Mm.
He developed a way of
communicating directly with the right brain--
I was thinking
it could work with Kate.
To what end?
Well... we might learn
what her right brain
was experiencing.
Why would we want to?
I mean, doesn't she
have enough problems?
If there's
no scalpel involved,
you think it's fringy
neurologist voodoo.
No... I-I do, but that's
not why I'm against it.
I mean, you're not just
pasting electrodes on college kids,
you know,
for some experiment.
You're talking
about doing research on a pregnant woman
who has
a grade-three astrocytoma.
Where is the benefit
to the patient?
(laughs):
I feel bad for him.
For James?
Well, he is my client.
And guaranteed, he's gonna have
some violent outburst
in the courtroom
and scare the jury.
(laughs):
He could be nicer by the
time you go to trial.
And why is that?
Well, the blood clot's
pressing on his frontal lobe,
which can make
people aggressive.
If we drain it, it
might mellow him out.
Here's hoping.
So, uh, you know that thing
your coworker says
about how we hooked up because
of genetic compatibility?
Yeah.
I'd take that off your list of things
to tell a girl
after having sex.
(laughs):
Hey, of everyone
I work with,
I'm the one who thinks
there's more between people
than chemicals and neurons.
More between us?
S-Sure.
I'm gonna be late.
Me, too.
Lift both arms.
Both arms.
Is the left not up?
Not yet.
Now it is.
(groans)
I wish I knew
what was going on over there.
There is a way
of finding out.
What do you mean?
It's experimental.
I'm not exactly sure
what you'd get out of it.
Hey, Dr. Seger.
Eddie!
Where's that going?
Helping Dr. Holland.
This is wild, man.
What's that?
All right, the lady with
the... callosotomy.
Right.
She's answering questions
directly from her right brain.
It's crazy, man.
Wait a minute,
is this Kate Larson?
HOLLAND:
She's wearing
special contact lenses
to block half
of her vision field.
We leave out a key
word in each question,
show it to her on a card
so that only her right brain
gets the whole question.
How does she respond?
Her left hand.
First she was writing,
now she's typing.
Have you told Doug?
Mm.
Great.
I know Doug-- he'll forgive us
if we learn something useful.
Yeah, and if you don't?
A little ambience?
Do you want to watch or not?
Next question.
What is your favorite...
COMPUTER VOICE:
Green.
KATE:
W-Wait, what was
on the card, color?
'Cause green is not
my favorite color.
It is on the right side,
apparently.
(laughs)
HOLLAND:
Tell me your least favorite...
COMPUTER VOICE:
Brussel sprouts.
(laughs):
Mm, well, we can
agree on that.
Name me something
that makes you...
Ocean.
Something that makes you...
Baby.
Ah. What did
the card say?
HOLLAND:
Let's keep going.
Why does baby make you...
need radiation
It's Dr. Holland.
Yeah?
What?
When did you do that?
(groans)
(quiet chuckle):
She's still talking.
Hang it up.
Doug.
Are you planning
to publish? Huh?
I think you should--
and I hope that your
results are a boon
to the scientific community,
because they are absolutely
no use to Mrs. Larson.
Her-her right brain was
telling her something.
Mm-hmm.
Sounds crazy, but it was
helpful for her to hear.
She already had
a difficult choice,
and then you gave her
the impression
that her right brain
disagrees.
Well, because it does.
She lost control
of her left side
when she got an ultrasound
of the baby.
And I don't think
that's just a coincidence.
Do you think
that every time the right brain interferes
with some pearl of wisdom,
some indisputable truth
from the subconscious?
Maybe.
But what is that
based on?
If there's a part of Kate
that's unhappy...
Then that half of her brain
should go and get therapy.
She can call my ex-wife.
But from now on,
why don't we just try to cure
the patients with tumors,
as opposed
to confuse them, okay?
No, no, no, it's okay.
I'll do it.
We've been talking, and...
we'd like to
reconsider radiation.
I don't know what I want.
Come on, we
discussed this.
Look, I know
that Dr. Holland's experiment
has led to some
frank discussion,
and that's... good.
But I would like
to point out
that you do not have to
listen to your right brain.
It has no legal rights.
And... frankly, I
think it's overrated.
I mean, all these
books about... how to
get in touch with it,
how to paint with it,
how to have sex with it,
how to, you know, I mean,
look, the truth is--
and I'm speaking to
your left brain now--
there is only
one hemisphere
that can be boss,
and that's the hemisphere
that can speak
and sign consent forms.
Y... Yes, but you said that-that
the right brain was emotional.
No. I never said that.
Isn't that the side that
would know what I'm feeling?
No. Your emotions are
gerated at the base
of the brain in
the limbic system,
and they're shared on both sides.
Well, so could both sides
be feeling scared and...
and only one side know why?
Y-Yes. Theoretically, yes.
I want to be a person who could
never give up her child.
I know.
Maybe...
...maybe that's not who I am.
What exactly is the nature
of your relationship
with James Marks's lawyer?
You've been talking
to Adrianne.
Actually, no.
For years my client has had
a blood clot
pushing on his frontal lobe.
This condition is known to cause
violent fits of aggression.
It's our believe that Mr. Marks
was wholly under the influence of this condition
when he shot Mr. Connell
and is not responsible
for his actions.
Please tell me this is
only on the Web site.
It aired this morning.
This would be
an important precedent,
an example of the legal system
keeping pace with science.
The blood clot was diagnosed
earlier this week
by a surgeon
at Hanson Neurological.
(bangs desk)
I need to talk to Doug.
Go ahead.
What I can't figure out
is how come I've been
getting so many calls
and they're all
wrong numbers?
What did they want?
Uh, some unnamed doctor
made a statement
to the press
about a blood clot?
Let's see, the Times
called, the Post,
Channel One-- oh, and
the New York District
Attorney's Office.
And they want this doctor
to come in for a deposition.
Does Hanson know about this?
He doesn't ask
about wrong numbers.
If you want to
go in still...
Maybe later.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
(footsteps approaching)
(light knock on door)
I came to apologize.
Did you.
I thought the experiment
would be helpful...
or at least harmless,
but you're right,
it was research
for its own sake.
??
and without clearance
from the institutional
review board.
Yeah.
And you feel terrible about it,
don't you?
I do.
Did you tape the session
with Mrs. Larson?
Well, I'd like to see it.
Tell me your
least favorite...
(Kate typing)
COMPUTER VOICE:
Brussel sprouts.
KATE (laughs):
Mm, well, we can agree on that.
HOLLAND:
Name me something
that makes you...
COMPUTER VOICE:
Ocean.
Something that
makes you...
COMPUTER VOICE:
Baby.
KATE:
Ah. What was on the card?
Dr. Hanson?
I'm going home,
unless you need
something else.
Did you find what you
were looking for on that tape?
Yes, um,
but I will have to talk to Kate Larson
at some point tomorrow.
All right.
I'll walk you out.
Well, you don't have to do that.
No, it's my pleasure.
Well, we still
have cops in ICU,
but it's nice to see
a little chivalry.
(chuckles):
Leave it, it's fine.
Don't worry, it's okay.
I used to hate being
alone at night. Ugh!
Yeah?
Afraid of the dark?
Who isn't?
My father came home
from a trip once
with a bunch
of aboriginal masks,
hung them around
the apartment.
I still think of them
when the lights go out.
(chuckling):
Shall we?
Thanks again.
Mm-hmm.
Morning.
Hey.
Sleep well?
You're funny.
Hanson find out about
the press conference?
My hope is that he was
so exhausted last night,
he didn't have the energy
to pull the rubber band
off his newspaper.
Yeah. Let's hope his TV, radio
and telephone were busted, too.
Did you talk to her?
No, not yet.
Mm. Well, it could've
been worse.
How?
Well, the
shooter's lawyer
could've been a big, fat guy,
and now you'd have to
go break up with him.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Doesn't really matter,
'cause I couldn't be more
annoyed than I already was.
You say that my client
was driven to murder
by a leaky valve
in his head.
I'm supposed to keep
that a secret?
I said it might
make him aggressive.
Might.
You said
there was a precedent for
a blood clot.
No, no, I didn't use
the word "precedent."
I don't use that word.
You implied...
Anyway, save it for your
big moment in court
or when you're on TV,
but leave me out of it!
You think this was
a career move?
Uh, Yeah. Yes, I do.
My job is to do everything
I can to defend this guy,
just like it's
your job to do
everything you can
to patch up his head.
It's a little
different.
How?How is it
different?
Do you believe the blood clot
made him do it?
If you knew
anything about law,
you would know that what I
believe is beside the point.
And you're the one
who rants on about brain chemicals
and
how they make us do things.
Well, now I regret it.
I regret some things, too.
Doctor.
Shouldn't you be in surgery or something?
(chuckling):
Well...
maybe we'll have class
outside today.
(laughs)
How are you feeling?
Good.
Look, Kate, I wanted
to talk to you...
because there is a
third option here.
You have an exceedingly
rare ability
to handle language
with your right brain--
more than we ever could
have known or expected.
You can combine words,
you can write,
you can... type responses.
which means that if we remove
this tumor surgically,
you most likely
are going to be able
to retain a lot
of those functions,
at least partially.
What will I lose?
Language.
I w-won't be able to speak?
Not ever?
No.
But...
you could be around
when your kid starts to.
Want to turn a boneflap?
Sure.
I like the
confidence.
I've used these tools before.
(device buzzing)
In fifth grade, when I made
my mother a bookshelf.
How'd it come out?
Lopsided.
That was fifth grade.
It's really grown in.
I know. A highly
vascular tumor.
We'll be
treading lightly.
You with me?
I am.
Okay.
Arterial branches
here... here...
probably underneath
from the sylvian fissure.
We'll try and avoid those.
Barely pierced the dura.
Let's give him
some manitol. Saline.
It's out.
Bullet fell out.
I kill myself getting
his skull open.
You step in,
the slug falls
in your hand.
All about timing.
(clink)
Okay, I'm gonna cut underneath.
I need you to put a cicada clip
right here on the MCA feeder.
The clip just...
I think it ripped the artery.
HANSON:
Okay.
Dr. Kim, I have
some bleeding.
I've got two units ready.
Okay, can you type and
cross two more, please?
I was putting
the clip underneath.
Suction, please. Suction.
Pressure's low.
Mm-hmm. Okay. All right.
Give me a clip. I gotta
stop the blood flow.
Clipping the MCA here.
Doctor... Aspirate.
All right.
I need to attach a
temporal artery bypass.
The clip's pretty low.
I can't think of a better
way, can you?
What are you saying?
She's paralyzed?
Kate suffered an arterial
tear during surgery
and we had to stop the
blood supply to her brain
for about two minutes
in order to make a bypass.
DENNIS:
So not only can she not speak,
she can't move.
At this point, no.
It may not
be permanent.
May not?
May not be permanent.
I should
have stopped this.
And the baby?
The baby's fine.
Baby's fine.
Okay, why don't you just...
try to get some rest?
And I will check back
in a little bit.
All right?
I'll be around.
Oh. Thank you.
Tell them they
can't do this.
They're taking him
to the prison hospital.
Look, he's okay to go.
There's nothing I can do.
The deal was that
he stays here
until all critical health conditions
have been addressed.
Do they look addressed to you?
Doc.
I'm sorry. James?
Did you just say something?
Appreciate what
you did for me.
Sorry, I... flipped out on you.
That's okay, James.
You're welcome.
You did it.
You made him nice.
Uh, I'm not sure I
should take credit.
Did you hear him?
Like he'd been
to finishing school.
Well, I hope it helps
with your case.
We can't use the blood clot
thing in court.
Why not?
According to the judge,
we're responsible for our decisions
regardless of biochemistry.
Unless we're insane.
But we're not, are we?
Just reckless.
Take care.
??
How are you
doing, Kate?
She's moving
both hands.
She's not paralyzed.
That's wonderful.
Nice going, honey.
* *
No date tonight?
No date.
What happened to that
attractive lawyer?
Complete
disintegration.
Doug?
That lawyer--
you probably heard
she was on the news.
I did.
So do you believe that
there's a subconscious?
I mean, really, that there's
this other intelligence
there inside of us?
Not where I thought
you were going.
And?
Uh, well, you know,
I think that Freud was wrong
about some things,
but the right hemisphere
is pretty mysterious.
I mean, how do you
explain dreams? Uh...
inspiration?
Random firing of neurons.
If you're so sure,
then why did you ask?
See you in the morning.
'Night.
<
>
www.tvsubtitles.net