WOMAN:
Is it the galaxies?
Yes, exactly. Very good.
You just stumbled upon astronomy's
dirty little secret--
mostly it's gas.
And what are the astrophysical
implications of that?
Come on. This is great stuff.
You are infinitely tiny points
of matter alone
in an endless sack
of mostly nothing.
How do we know this?
Final exam's tomorrow, people.
I pay attention
to what people wear,
how they walk,
their voices,
anything to help me
tell them apart.
Only now it's getting worse.
I go to a movie,
the characters
blend together,
all my students...
When you said
"smudged faces..."
More like...
indistinguishable.
I can't recognize anyone.
Wears you down.
And what do you teach?
I'm a visiting associate
professor of astronomy.
That's the only thing I wanted
to be my entire childhood,
an astronomer.
What happened?
My brother pinched
my telescope.
You're easily dissuaded.
So, what's your absolute
favorite thing in the sky?
Arcturus, I suppose.
Fourth-brightest star
in the heavens.
Impressive.
You officially know more
than every single one
of my students
this semester.
I love the night sky.
It reminds me
that I'm a lucky coincidence
of water molecules
floating through
space on a rock.
Wow.
Can we get married?
(chuckles)
So how long's this
been going on,
people looking
the same to you?
I've had trouble with faces
my whole life.
Now I can't even pick my own
face out of a group photo.
What's happening
in my head?
When did you first notice
the double vision?
Yesterday.
Follow my finger.
You're worried.
I'll tell you
when I'm worried.
I think you just did.
Hi, I'm Dr. Seger,
Dr. Hanson's Fellow.
Rebecca Ellis. You must be
Hendrickson's replacement.
No, actually, I think Zellman
replaced Hendrickson
and I replaced Zellman.
No, Zellman
replaced Le Fleur.
What happened
to him?
Le Fleur didn't last
too long.
I believe he wilted.
(chuckles)
There's a support group
for Dr. Hanson's ex-Fellows.
Chapters all over
the country.
We repaired a vascular
malformation for Rebecca
three years ago.
You make it sound
like car repair.
He clipping an aneurysm
near my brain stem
before it burst.
Saved my life.
Now I've got
double vision again
and he thinks
I've got another one.
Seems that when I operated
last time,
I slipped with the knife
and accidentally gave her
the power to read minds.
Ms. Ellis, I'm sure
whatever's causing your
double vision is...
a cause of double vision.
Dr. Hanson hates
rosy predictions.
You're learning fast.
Yeah, I got the ghost
of Le Fleur in my office.
He doesn't shut up about it.
Dr. Seger's going
to set you up
with a CT angio scan
first thing in the morning.
We have a new machine.
So if there are
any vascular defects,
we'll see them.
Can't we use some
old crappy machine?
Honestly, I would
rather not know.
We'll talk after
the scans, okay?
Rebecca's back.
Yep.
False alarm?
I'm afraid not.
* I need a sign,
let me know you're here *
* I need a hand to help build up
some kind of hope inside of me *
* I'm calling all angels *
* Calling all you angels. *
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@XXY
Sync:FRM@¡¤D¡¤
This is so strange.
Shh. Concentrate.
Can you tell anything here?
Yeah, you're testing positive
for short attention span.
Seriously,
concentrate.
You're almost finished.
Sorry.
That one I haven't seen before.
Okay.
So, of the 20 faces
you were shown only once,
you incorrectly identified
62% as repeats.
Of the actual repeats,
you missed half.
What does that mean?
You have prosopagnosia;
face-blindness.
And that's an actual
neurological diagnosis?
I know it sounds very X-Men.
Until recently, there were
only 100 reported cases
in the world.
Now there's studies
suggesting
that two percent
of the population has it,
but we only understand bits
and pieces.
Well, do I get better?
That's not yet one
of the bits and pieces.
You could come back tomorrow.
There are few more tests
I could run...
if you fancy it.
I do fancy it.
I'm giving my final
exam tomorrow
and then all I have
to do is pack.
You're leaving?
Yeah.
That's what we visiting
untenured associate professors
do when the semester's over.
We come and go
like comets in the sky.
There you go.
Hey, Rebecca.
Did you do your scans
already?
I'm not getting scanned.
I can't go through this again.
Not another aneurysm.
Okay, well, we don't know
for sure
that's what it is yet.
Surviving the last one,
that was the hardest
thing I have ever done.
I know.
My parent's
can't take it.
You remember how
my brother was.
Yes.
If I have another
time bomb in my head...
Well, pretending
it doesn't exist,
that's going to help how?
Yeah, I can still take
a walk in the park
without thinking, "This is the
last grass I will ever touch,
this is the last
patch of sunlight..."
Did you do that the first time?
What?
Say good-bye to everybody?
Yes, jackass, everything.
See? It worked.
So do it again.
Come back inside
and get scanned,
so I can plan
your surgery.
You do think
I have another one?
You have double vision
and a history of
cerebral aneurysms.
Of course you have
another one.
Unless it's a tumor.
You're a terrible,
terrible doctor.
I know, but I have
very steady hands.
That's all you need
to care about.
It's not the first time
I've been attracted
to a patient.
This was the first time
I made up a reason
for him to come back.
I can't run any more
tests on face-blindness
because there are none.
And then he says
he's leaving in
a couple of days,
so of course he's
twice as attractive
because a serious
relationship's off
the table, you know.
It may be a bit
of "I always want
what I can't have."
I just want
to understand--
have I become
your girlfriend?
Because that's
how we're talking.
You're a colleague
with whom I'm sharing
a dilemma over
patient-doctor ethics.
Well, as long as you don't
call me a good friend
and start dating
my older brother,
we should avoid
the high school flashbacks.
You should have
been more aggressive
as a teenager.
(chuckles)
Thank you.
So curious.
I spent less than an hour
with a complete stranger,
and for whatever reason,
he's starting to
take over my head.
I believe that phenomenon
keeps the species alive.
I'd love to get an MRI
of my cerebral cortex, right now
see where this is
coming from.
Why don't you strap on
some EG electrodes
and go on a date?
You can call it research
and skirt the whole
ethics problem.
I'm so kidding.
What do I do?
Somewhere in the oath
it I believe says
we treat patients,
not get to second base.
Only second?
Thank you again.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Hi.
You wouldn't have
any change?
You're using
the pay phone?
Yeah.
Oh, for real? Nobody uses
the pay phone anymore.
I left my cell at home.
I have to call my brother.
My nephews are
asking me about this.
I was, like,
"In the old days,
we actually had
these booths."
Now you can discuss
your herpes test results
with your doctor
on a crowded bus.
And where's Superman
supposed to change?
Like, some construction site
Porta Potti, I guess.
I've been up for 24 hours.
I get a little...
so I apologize.
Thank you
for that quarter.
Okay.
SEGER:
Rebecca Ellis.
Yeah.
Tricky.
Tricky?
Doug, this is impossible.
It's giant.
Basilar aneurysm
incorporated
into the posterior
cerebral artery,
not to mention
completely inaccessible.
I was hoping to do coils...
but it's going to have
to be a bypass graft
under full cardiac
standstill.
It's the only way.
The odds against
a graft on the MCA
are small enough.
You add in the standstill
and she's only got
a 20% chance.
What would you suggest then?
That she live with it.
And yeah, I know, it
could burst at any time.
Yeah, so does she.
Could you live with that?
Odds are she dies
on the table.
I thought you were
the guy who went with his gut.
Yeah, well, sometimes my gut
says to look at the risk.
Odds are fear
expressed numerically.
They give people who don't
trust their judgment
a meaningless number
to hide behind.
A meaningless number
you have to disclose
before you ask her
to sign the consent form.
When you wake up in the morning,
and you hear that
the chance of rain is 80%,
do you always grab
your umbrella?
Yeah.
I always look out the window.
I know what
the odds are.
I'm doing the surgery.
Look, if you tell her
the risks straight up,
there is no way
she'll sign off.
Join us, won't you?
The last time
we did this,
it was in some awful
windowless room.
Yeah, that describes
half the hospital.
If you're giving
me bad news,
it's going to be out
here in the sunshine.
Well, I thought
you'd earned enough
surgery miles for an upgrade.
It's happening all over again,
isn't it?
Yeah.
But it is much worse.
The aneurysm is sitting
on the main artery that supplies
the blood to your brain stem,
and the surgery to remove it
carries a lot of risks--
seizure;
memory, vision, speech loss;
paralysis; stroke;
and death.
(laughs softly)
You're not done, are you?
No.
The only way for me
to get at this thing,
the only chance
that I have,
is to temporarily stop
the blood flow to your brain.
In order to do that,
I have to stop your heart--
and you have a one in five
chance of surviving intact.
Give me a minute to resent all
the healthy people in the world.
Especially the kids.
(chuckles):
So you are a terrible doctor,
I'm a terrible patient.
Yes, you are--
I told you that.
Do you need some time
to think about it?
Can you do this, Doug?
I can.
Okay, then,
I'll sign the consent form.
I need a few minutes.
Is that straight enough
for you?
Hi.
What can we do for a man
with prosopagnosia?
Validate hiparking.
What else?
(groans):
Nothing.
That's what the literature
says, but I'm asking you.
Well, is it developmental
or acquired?
Developmental.
He's had it his entire life.
He's only seeking
treatment now?
That's not unusual.
Most people don't realize
there's anything wrong.
That's how adaptive
the brain is.
I could scan his fusiform gyrus
for abnormalities.
What are you looking for?
Maybe he wasn't
born with it.
Maybe he acquired it
at an early age.
A scan might unearth
something we could fix.
There's lots of "if's"
and "could be's" in there.
What about scanning him?
Wouldn't that be useful?
Did you just say that?
(exhales)
Hi.
Rebecca's been admitted.
You've got the O.R.
for as many hours
as you need tomorrow,
and Dr. Waell is ready
with his cardiac team.
Good. Thanks.
Did you come out here
just to tell me that?
Brad Ellis is in your office.
Rebecca's brother.
wonder what
took him so long.
I think the last little pig
had a house of bricks.
Slowed him down.
Mr. Ellis.
Well.
Hey, Mr. Ellis.
Jonathan Seger.
Mm-hmm. Now,
as I've tried to make clear,
the family has serious
concerns that need to
be assuaged tonight,
before Rebecca has any surgery.
My business is law,
so I would appreciate specifics.
Yes, I remember.
So, what do you want
to hear?
Well, let's start with
the odds, unvarnished.
(laughs softly)
Now, why is that funny?
No, it's not funny.
It's not funny.
Dr. Seger can give you
those numbers.
SEGER:
Okay, um...
Well, as you may know,
this procedure's
considered high-risk.
I mean, the success rate
is approximately
20 percent.
But left untreated,
the aneurysm
almost certainly ??
Almost certainly.
Give me a number.
Well, i-it's impossible
to say exactly.
This particular aneurysm
is so extremely
delicate, very close
to the brain stem,
rapidly expanding...
That wh... that what,
it's too dangerous
not to open her up?
Doctor, do you think
she'll survive
the operation?
I think she has
a better chance...
Yes or no?
In your professional opinion,
will she survive?
HANSON:
Objection, Counselor.
Badgering the witness.
Look, the first time,
I was out of the country.
You couldn't wait to rush in
and operate then, either.
Yes.
And you're welcome.
Is this your routine,
Dr. Hanson?
You talk people
into operations
where their chance
of dying on the table is 80%?
Okay.
Rebecca's chances
of dying on the table
are 100%.
This operation is performed
under hypothermic
cardiac standstill.
We cool her body temperature
to 16 degrees centigrade,
which lowers her
brain metabolism to
practically nothing,
and we stop her heart--
so technically...
she's dead...
before we even begin.
Since you wanted specifics.
Anything else?
The surgery's off.
I'll have her sign a
retraction to the consent,
and you can release her
first thing in the morning.
Is this personal?
Yes.
With her-- yes.
He tried to stop
me last time, too,
and she would have died.
This is different,
with the standstill.
I mean, maybe it's for the best.
Maybe.
(high-pitched whirring)
I didn't mean for you
to come right over.
I just live a few blocks away.
Oh, really?
Me, too.That would be so
convenient if I weren't
leaving in a few days.
Convenient? To what?
To... remain your patient
and see you for regular...
checkups... here and...
at coffee shops
or little restaurants,
with exam tables.
That's against the rules.
Lean back.
The least you can
do is cure me.
No promises.
It's a long shot.
We'll know more after the scan.
(turns machine on)
Nurse.
The chart says point-five
milligrams of Alprazolam?
Oral dose.
She was complaining
of anxiety.
She got Zolpidem
as well, 7:53 p.m.
Yeah. Yeah. Good.
Good. She deserves
a good night's sleep.
Thank you.
You play?
No. No, I-I used to.
I know it must be frightening
to see your sister back here.
Is this your best "good cop"?
I appreciate it.
But I'm not changing my mind.
The last time he operated
on Rebecca, were you here
for that?
No. Singapore.
There was this bank merger.
I wanted to get back,
but it happened so fast...
I-I wasn't here, either.
But I read the notes.
What Hanson did was...
extraordinary.
I mean,
maybe five guys
in the world
could've gotten that result.
It's luck.
He throws the dice.
When it turns out well, you're
geniuses, you beat the odds.
If it turns out poorly,
who's left to complain?
I'm not letting my sister
make a life-or-death
medical decision
in the panic of the moment
and under the spell
of this prima donna.
Not when the percentages are
as lopsided as they are here.
She trusts him.
Why are you doing this?
You don't even believe
she'll survive the surgery.
Yes, I do.
I'm a trial lawyer, kid--
I know what a bluff looks like.
(elevator bell dings)
Rebecca's going home tomorrow.
U ARE here early.
I thought you chose
neurology for the
bankers' hours.
I couldn't sleep.
Wrestling with your
ethical dilemma?
(chuckles):
I wish.
Did I just say that?
(chuckles)
(groans):
His scans are normal.
There's nothing
I can do for him.
All this man wanted
to do was look in the
mirror and recognize
the face staring
back at him.
Are there other options?
You know, I read a study
that some prosopagnosics
retrain their peripheral vision
to access facial identity.
How do you know
about that?
Jonathan Seger.
I work in the medical field.
Pleased to meet you.
People come in here and have
miracles performed all the time.
How's Brad taking this?
He doesn't know.
I didn't page you,
because this is
an excruciatingly
difficult operation.
It can't be done by people
who think it can't be done.
It's not confidence I lack,
it's arrogance.
Yes, you're exactly right.
Maybe with all
your free time,
you can think about
the difference.
(door opens)
Adrianne?
Love the dress.
I was just examining
your fusiform gyrus.
Oh, thanks.
I've been working out.
I'm afraid it's
completely normal
in both shape
and function.
I'm sorry, Nick.
I'm afraid that really means
there is nothing we can do.
I wanted to give you this.
I found it
at a second-hand store.
Just don't
tell your brother
where you keep it.
It's fabulous.
How much longer do you have
till your next appointment?
An hour.
Since neurology is clearly
a waste of my time,
how about some stargazing?
Shouldn't we wait
until it gets dark?
Why?
(chuckles):
I don't know.
How come you're not
in the standstill?
I think Hanson wanted me
to guard the village.
It's a long story.
You haven't seen
the patient's brother,
have you?
Like five-foot, ten,
outraged?
He's right behind me,
isn't he?
Be my wing man?
Dr. Seger?
I've already spoken with
hospital general counsel.
They're looking
into all of this.
Why don't you calm down,
Mr. Ellis.
Be advised
that I placed a call
with the New York
city police department.
How'd that go?
Sorry?
Yeah, when you called
the NYPD.
Press one if you're
reporting a robbery
or homicide.
Press two if you're
really angry
that your sister legally
consented to brain surgery.
I said wing man not bastard.
I was very clear
with my wishes.
Yes, for your sister's surgery.
Yes, and if I'd been allowed
to discuss it with her,
she would never
have agreed to it.
Because you would
have terrified her.
She should be terrified
of this surgery. You are.
This was her choice.
I was there.
That wasn't
a choice.
This is blind faith
in Hanson.
Maybe it was blind faith,
but if she's willing
to step into that abyss
with her eyes closed,
then she has twice as much
courage as the rest of us.
Sit down, Mr. Ellis.
Your sister has
a long day ahead of her.
Keep an eye on him.
HANSON:
Okay, everyone, I'd just like to
go over what we're about to do.
Phase one,
I go in, I navigate my way
to the aneurysm,
dissect the perforators.
Phase two, we cannulate
her femoral artery,
put her on the heart/lung
machine
and we cool her down.
Phase three, cardiac standstill,
when we will have 30 minutes
to go in, take the aneurysm,
bypass the artery
before her chilled brain becomes
starved for oxygen.
Not one minute more.
Okay, let's administer.
If I may,
Doctor, before
we begin...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would just like to note
that this is indeed
a consequential moment--
neurosurgery and cardiac surgery
joined together
at medicine's frontier.
Okay.
The procedure
we're attempting here today,
is risky.
To stop a beating heart
in order to repair
a damaged brain.
Only a handful
of these surgeries
in a year anywhere
in the world.
But one day, they
won't call this
cutting edge.
One day, perhaps,
they will call it ordinary.
One day, perhaps...
we'll begin.
OK SHALL WE
???in New York
thanks to sky glow.
HOLLAND:
Sky glow?
Light pollution.
All the billboards,
airports, street lights.
Most big cities, you can't see
the constellations anymore,
or meteor showers, or
the Northern Lights.
Two thirds of the world can't
even see the Milky Way.
You recognize that?
The Northern Cross?
My Dad showed it to me on
a camping trip when I was nine.
It had been raining all day,
and he said the nebulae
were red from rust.
It's funny, I can close my eyes
and I can always see
the Northern Cross
but I can't remember
what he looked like.
Constellations.
What?
Your face blindness.
Your brain can see all
the pieces of your face,
but it can't
recognize the whole.
Like seeing all the stars...
But never seeing
the constellations.
You recognize this?
I see the Big Dipper.
It's also where the stars were
on the day we first kissed.
It's today.
We've only got an hour,
Adrianne.
You gotta keep up here.
You are my patient.
You said it was hopeless.
Excellent point.
We have at least
five more hours left.
You going to baby-sit
me the whole time?
Well, depends.
I've had a lot of coffee.
If I can't leave, I might
need a catheter soon.
(chuckles)
You think this is funny?
I've been up
for way too long.
Everything starts
to seem funny.
You going to be cracking jokes
if my sister dies?
Why can't you just be sad?
What?
Yeah, you keep looking
for a fight.
It's like...
you're in the water,
and if you stop
swinging your fists,
you'll go down.
All this and free
therapy, too.
I will sue
this place.
All of you.
Be sad.
Idiot.
What the hell do you know
about anything?
I don't know,
but you'll feel better.
Go to hell.
Okay.
(sighs)
Word is the aneurysm is
in sight.
They're ready to put her
on cardiac bypass
and start chilling her down.
Where's he going?
I think next time you should
stay and I'll get the update.
(playing piano)
What's he doing?
It's okay.
I'm getting a lot of PVCs.
Doug,
We need to anti-coagulate.
HANSON:
Not yet...
You're running the risk
of a clot here.
I know the risk
I'm running.
Wouldn't protocol
argue for...?
I'm sorry, who are you again?
What is your name?
Helen Clark.
Cardiac Fellow.
We all feel, in light
of the bypass time-line,
the anti-coagulant
would be prudent.
Why don't we take a vote?
Although I have to say,
if it's split down party lines,
hearts outnumber brains
in this room two to one.
That was even more clever
than I intended.
No anti-coagants yet.
Don't ask.
Why not?
This surgery's going
to be on the news.
You should be in there.
He didn't want me.
Where were you?
On a lunch date.
With a man I completely
failed to help.
Only after unreasonably
getting his hopes up
for a cure, by the way.
Did you kiss?
Then he's fine.
He's a guy.
You could chop his
arm off and he'd still
think it was even-steven.
He's taking me out
again tonight.
Could you
fall in love with someone if you
couldn't remember their face?
You want the answer that wins
me a prize for being sensitive
or the truth?
A face can launch
a thousand ships.
There's a reason the brain has
a part just to remember it.
Where are you going?
Get another update.
I wasn't invited because he said
I didn't believe in the surgery.
I'm sorry, but didn't the
brain-surgeon-as-cocky-bastard
thing kind of peak with
Dr. Frankenstein?
I mean, I had some reservations.
Doug's the one who made it seem
like a battle for my soul.
Yeah, but...
This isn't a battle
for your soul, is it?
Okay, I'm done
with the perforators.
Do the bypass, Henry.
We're having some trouble here.
Her femoral artery is a mess.
We can't cannulate anything.
Then what do we do?
Prudence and protocol
argue for no bypass.
You'll have to take
the aneurysm without it.
Then she'll die.
Dr. Seger.
I didn't take this job
to work the lobby for you.
Where are we here?
Well, our colleagues
are telling me that they
can't cannulate anything.
That we're going to have
to perform this surgery
without the help
of cardiac standstill.
Because prudence and protocol
both argue for it.
Who's Prudence?
Henry, what do we do?
May I?
What are the odds of you
dissecting
this woman's sclerotic artery
when you try and cannulate,
Dr. Wardell?
I would estimate almost 23%.
Interesting.
The odds of a basilar aneurysm
like this bursting
without cardiac standstill
are 25%.
I believe that means prudence
plays for our team.
Come on, Henry, do it.
If anything goes wrong,
it'll be my fault.
SEGER:
Nothing's going to go wrong.
Now that I'm here.
Glad you came.
All right, let's go.
(phones ringing)
(sighs):
This is stupid.
Hey.
Is Dr. Holland in her office?
Adrianne.
Hi.
I'm so sorry.
I'm used to seeing you
in your office.
Of course.
I have bad news.
Oh, no.
Doug's thrown
this whole
grant application at me
for a new
research project.
He's asked for it tomorrow.
No dinner?
I could bring some in.
No. No, I get it.
Been there.
I'm so sorry.
And it's your
last night, too.
No, no, I understand.
Keep in touch.
Okay?
Yeah.
Of course.
Thank you.
For everything.
It was fun.
Bye.
(machine whirring)
Body core temperature
is 16 degrees Celsius.
She's chillin' out nice.
HANSON:
How's your cannulate
holding up, Dr. Wardell?
No visible leakage.
Set the clock
for 30 minutes, please.
HANSON:
You ready?
ISAIAH:
15 degrees.
We're there, Dr. Hanson.
Okay, let's arrest her
circulation and drain her out.
Shut it off.
(beeping)
She's flat.
Start the clock.
HANSON:
Watch the vasculature.
When the aneurysm deflates,
we go at it.
!h
She's still draining.
Just watch,
it'll deflate.
SEGER:
Pressure's out. It's drained.
She's dead for...
26 minutes, people.
We're not done by then,
she's dead forever.
All right, cowboy.
Give me a break.
No, I like it.
WARDELL:
We need to restart bypass.
NURSE:
Three minutes.
Graft is almost in...
CLARK:
There's some fibrillation.
I'm getting...
A heartbeat.
What just happened?
What was that?
The heart will do that
on standstill.
A single beat out of nowhere.
It's a rogue event.
Two minutes, 45.
Did the graft hold?
I can't see yet.
Give me
more suction.
No, it slipped.
It's not tight.
Give me more.
Here you go.
NURSE:
Two minutes, 30.
We need to restart.
HANSON:
Hold on, wait.
Hold this.
Got it.
Go.
Pump on.
HANSON:
It's holding.
The graft is holding.
Okay, cut it.
Warm her up, Henry.
Get that heart started.
My pleasure, Dr. Hanson.
Dr. Seger,
nice job.
18 degrees
and rising.
The beat goes on, man.
She's back.
(alarm beeping)
Somebody shut that thing off.
* *
(knocking)
Who is it?
NICK:
The idiot.
Hello.
(chuckles)
Don't worry,
I'm not moving in.
I was on my way
to the airport.
I wanted to apologize.
You? It was me
who was the nitwit.
Standing there.
When you didn't
recognize me,
some vain little fuse
blew in my head.
But I should have
called you on it,
not walked away
like Tiny Tim.
I like your place.
Yeah? Well, next time
you're in one like it
and you see
a brunette girl there, it's me.
That's just mean.
When you look at me,
what do you see?
I see you.
Maybe I can't remember
your face, Adrianne, but...
I'm missing something
every minute I'm not with you.
And I have a plan.
Maybe I can't remember
the constellation,
but I can still take away
the stars that make it up.
Well, that would
have been romantic
if you hadn't taken
a picture of my nose.
Turn your head.
I want all the pieces.
Chin please.
When are you
coming back, Nick?
It's funny you
bring that up,
because I've been having
some troubling new symptoms
that you may
need to investigate.
Do tell.
I've been having trouble
remembering people's bodies.
Yeah, I've heard about this.
Body blindness.
Well, I may have
to run some tests.
Morning, Brad.
Dr. Hanson.
I need to say thank you.
You're welcome.
It looks like
she's going to be okay.
Yup.
But if this ever
happens again...
(softly):
Good Lord, Brad.
Shut up.
Becky?
If it happens again,
I guarantee you,
I will shoot myself,
save you both
the trouble.
Yeah, but with the double
vision, you'll probably miss.
You're a
terrible doctor.
Hey, want to grab
some breakfast?
I got a few minutes
before the first consult.
Yeah.
Hang on.
I heard you had
quite a night last night.
Yeah, it was exciting,
to beat the odds.
What's that?
It's a picture.
From your older brother.
I met him at
a bar last night
and we went back
to his place.
And now we're dating.
And since you're
such a good friend,
I'd like to tell you
all about it.
That's funny.
Oh, it is a sore spot.
He did it
more than once.
<font color
>
www.tvsubtitles.net