Oh, hey.
You ready?
I can't. I just can't.
Everyone feels like that the
first few times you eat here.
It's like heroin.
It makes you sick,
and you think,
"I'll never do that again,"
and here we are.
No, we put our project
on Kickstarter,
and we're getting
major funding right now.
And I can't. I just can't.
Kickstarter...
that's the website
where strangers
give money for crap
that no one in the real world
would invest in, right?
Exactly, but our project isn't crap.
It's bananas.
We design candles with arms.
I can't. I just can't.
Don't you have
a passion project...
something you've
always wanted to do?
Yeah, you can't just want to
be a waitress your whole life.
Actually... I do
have a Kickstarter idea.
I'd like to start
kicking your asses!
You know we work
for tips, right?
Yeah. This one
got away from me.
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ♪
Sync & corrections by no1
www.Addic7ed.Com
okay, listen up, it's Tuesday,
and like Martin Luther King,
I have a dream.
Tonight you will do side work.
Hold up, girl. I have ten
minutes till my shift starts.
Max, that is not appropriate.
I'm your boss.
Don't call me "girl."
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, you want to play?
I'll play.
Hey, sir. Hey, big Manny man.
Why don't you show me
your penis?
Han, you know
I don't have a penis.
It's the only thing
we have in common.
Where's Caroline?
In the back
at our cupcake shop.
Why you don't open
your walk-up window
till you close here at night?
She's getting a jump
on our side work.
What? We can't do
ours and yours.
Relax, Marjorie.
Keep it up, Max, and one day
I will show you my penis.
And you'll be sorry.
Yes. Yes, I will.
That's it! New rule!
No more making fun
of the boss!
Han doesn't want us
calling him names anymore.
It's like, if you don't
want to be called names,
don't look like that.
♪ When a fire
starts to burn, right... ♪
Why is the window open?
What is all that?
It's me, if I had lived.
♪ When a fire
starts to burn, right... ♪
Oh, my God.
Did you see that rack?
See it? I have to carry it
around all day.
I've been wearing
the same clothes
every day for two years.
Now, I know that's
your dream scenario,
but to me, it's a horror show.
Go get new clothes.
Just go to the place
around the corner
and buy some cheap ones.
Max, they sell clothes
by the pound.
That's why it's called
the fashion pound,
and that is why it is awesome.
Look, I'm willing to cut
a lot of other things,
including my wrists,
but I need quality clothes.
The only reason I've been able
to wear these pants every day
is because they're quality.
Well, that and a lot of
febreze, which reminds me...
I used to smell like money.
Now I smell like pennies.
And, Max, you need a hit.
'Breze me.
Hi, girls.
Did you see the high-fashion
model shoot?
I was too short to be
a model in Poland.
Well, I guess you can't
have it all, right?
Do I smell febreze?
That's my
second-favorite scent.
Oh, and there's
my first-favorite scent.
Hey, Sophie.
I'm sorry. Have we met?
I'm not good with faces that
I never want to see again.
What happened?
I thought you guys
were gonna be friends.
Yeah, messed-up,
passive-aggressive friends
who occasionally
sleep together,
like Ryan Seacrest
and Simon Cowell.
Oh, okay, I see
what you're doing.
You're pretending
like we don't have
movie-character names
for our private parts.
Well, good-bye, miss,
and give my regards
to Mrs. Doubtfire.
Okay, E.T., go home!
Here's your mail, girls.
Max, Sophie had a new purse.
Everybody has something new.
Even the homeless lady on
the bus had a new barrette,
and even though
her feet were split open,
I still felt jealous.
Oh, this is not a bill.
Now, that's a first.
"We are offering you
a new phone,
"as older flip-model phones
such as yours
have been degraded."
They're
slut-shaming phones now?
I don't want a new anything.
And I like my old flip.
Where's my damn letter
from the pants company,
saying, "girl,
those things are tired..."
here's a new pair for free"?
If you want something
for free,
why don't you just go on
Kickstarter like everyone else?
You can't use it for clothes.
Can you?
And if you can, can I?
Why not? It's no stupider
than candle arms.
Now, if the candles
had real arms
and could slap
the idiots who bought them,
I'd invest in that.
Max, we have nothing,
and if anybody is giving us
something for free,
we're taking it.
You are getting
that free phone,
and I am begging
for free clothes.
Things are looking up.
You might want to Kickstart
some underwear.
Well, obviously,
they don't have anything.
Let's go.
Max, stop. My pants
just ripped some more.
I have to fix them again.
Hey, quality, why don't
you just take them
to Office Depot
and get them tailored?
Let's shop.
Ow.
Uh-oh, they're ripping again.
I feel a breeze
up in my febreze.
How can I help you?
Oh, hey. Hi, uh, Cchiandra.
Where can I get
a new flip phone?
Mm, let me think.
Guatemala.
I'll miss you, phone.
This is breaking my heart.
Come on, boo.
It's a phone, not Bruno Mars.
Now, I need that letter.
Oh, here it is. I have it.
It's in my purse.
What's her story?
Why is her hand on her ass?
Her staples popped.
Lap band?
Happened to my cousin.
She had a diet 7 up
and exploded.
Then she got M.S.
According to judge Joe brown,
it was not related.
Uh, here,
I'll just take this one.
Slow down, now.
Take a look around.
You got a whole world
of possibilities.
Pick 'em up, get a feel, hold
it in your hand for a while.
Chiandra, it's a phone,
not Bruno Mars.
Oh, "Texting is easy"
with the new
finger friendly keyboard."
My fingers are already
too friendly.
Ask my fourth-grade boyfriend.
Wow. These sample texts
are getting kind of racy.
"Bad news... I think
the condom broke last night."
Why would anyone put that
on a display model?
That's mine.
I left it there by accident.
But that's not your problem.
Now, tell me,
what are your phone needs?
Uh, my needs are simple.
I need a phone that can draw
a mustache on people
and occasionally will call
my mother and hang up.
And she needs one
with a good camera,
because I have to film
my video pitch for new pants.
I have a hole in my butt.
You know
you're supposed to, right?
Max, I might be
a virgin again.
I love my new phone!
It's so cool and red.
It feels like
anything could happen!
But it probably won't.
My first call.
What do I do?
Oh. Hello?
Oh, hey, girl,
good for you. Bye.
Chiandra's not pregnant.
Max, why are you taking calls
from Cchiandra?
We have to do my video.
I had to take her call.
She gave me a bunch
of free apps...
Angry Birds, Doodle Jump.
If you want to look like
a dog, I could do that.
Look, here's me
as a St. Bernard.
See my neck keg?
Okay, I've done some research,
and here's some things
other people want money for.
One woman wants money
for a new leg.
Scrolling.
Wait. If she only has one leg,
shouldn't she be
on can't-Kickstarter?
Oh, I'm no longer
working with them.
They denied my project.
Apparently, I'm not artsy
enough and have too many legs.
So now I'm
on go fund yourself.
Oh, perfect.
I've been telling you
to go fund yourself for years.
The future of my pants
hinges on the video pitch.
The tone needs to be
sad and pathetic.
Uh, preparation done.
What's sadder than former
billionaire Caroline Channing
asking for money for pants?
Oh, they're not
gonna know it's me.
Are you being funded
by Al-Qaeda?
If they're buying, I'm taking.
And action.
Hi. I can't tell you my name,
and I can't show you my face
because I'm too ashamed.
Sadly, I find myself
in a situation
where I am no longer
able to provide myself
with the garments I need
in order to be the best
in my day-to-day life.
I'm aware that this is
not a problem for everybody.
Stop, stop! I need to take
a picture of myself
having the most fun
I've ever had.
Your nose is coming
out of your eyehole.
No.
No, no, no, Max, don't stop.
I'm in a groove.
No, you're in a bag.
Please let me take
a picture of you in a bag
and then turn it into a dog
and then call it a doggie bag.
Go, Max, I'm running
out of oxygen,
and I think there
was cheese in here.
And action.
If I achieve my goal...
specifically, a new pair
of quality pants...
then I promise I will give
back to the community,
wearing said pants.
All I need is $1,500.
Stop! Whoa! $1,500?
How many pounds of clothes
are you getting?
Look, it's for one pair
of amazing dries van Noten silk
brocade pants... super cute.
And, yes, it's a lot,
but my investors will get
something in return.
For $5, they will get
the feeling of goodwill
in their heart.
Pbbt!
For $10,
I'll send them a selfie
in the new pants
that they bought.
For $20, I'll send them
a selfie without pants.
Nobody is gonna give you money
for the stuff you offered.
"Goodwill in their hearts"?
This is the Internet.
We're animals.
You're right.
I have an idea.
Camera up.
And action.
I'm sure a lot of you
are probably thinking,
"look at this spoiled,
indulgent, clueless girl."
Well, I am.
And you're also
probably thinking,
"God, I want to slap her."
Well, guess what. You can!
For $500, you can come here
and slap my spoiled,
clueless face.
And cut.
Pretty good, huh?
Genius. Now, here,
take the camera.
I want to film my video
to raise $500 to slap you.
Earl, look!
I just got 20 more dollars
from one of my backers!
Now, let me get this straight.
You just ask people for money,
and they give it to you...
without using a weapon?
Well, Earl, I guess desperation
cuts like a knife.
Man, being white is easy.
Um, we're ready to order.
Caroline, I just unlocked
the candy hammer.
Can you go over there
and take those girls' orders?
I can't. I just can't.
Oh, no way! I just hit $1,000!
That's almost
both legs paid for!
Uh, hello?
You're dinging and donging
right in front of my face.
Can't you at least
put your phones on vibrate?
I don't like to mix
business with pleasure.
You two need to be
off your phones and working.
Now. And no back talk.
Totally.
- Totally.
Oh, I know what's going on.
You're group-texting
insults about me!
We are not.
I got your text!
Han does look like those Minion
things in despicable me!
Oh.
And I thought bullying would end
when I hit four feet.
Oh! Oh, my God!
I'm getting my new pants!
I just got a $500 pledge!
Somebody wants to slap me!
Just one person?
Hey, han insists we can't leave
tonight without doing our side work,
so I made him into a chihuahua
wearing a diaper.
Check your phone.
Caroline?
Someone
got some new pants!
♪ When a fire
starts to burn, right ♪
♪ And it starts to spread ♪
♪ She gonna bring
that attitude home ♪
♪ They don't want to do nothing
with they life ♪
♪ When a fire
starts to burn, right ♪
I wasn't finished!
No, I was.
Max, I didn't want to
tell you this,
but I was secretly worried
my Booty was gone.
Turns out,
it was just the pants.
It's still there.
Take a picture of it.
Okay, let me see.
Perfect!
Now, let's send a group-text
to our diner family,
and I'd like you
to copy me on that,
because I want to send it
to my dad in prison.
He'll be so proud.
Yeah, 'cause I'm sure he's
not seeing any asses there.
You know what I love
about these pants?
How they make my butt look...
can you see it
through the window?
I got new pants.
Hey, Earl,
you got my text, right?
You mean that picture
of Caroline in her pants
that said,
"I'm so sick of her"?
I know, right?
If she ever gets
a new shirt, just kill me.
I hear you, Max,
but I just can't believe
you included her on the text.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, my God.
I didn't take her off the chain.
I mean, if you're
gonna trash a child,
you got to take her
off the chain.
Look, Earl, they're here!
Look what your $10
is buying you!
Uh-uh, not looking.
Don't want to know.
I'm taking myself
off the chain.
Uh, hey, Caroline.
Uh, did you get my text?
Not yet.
The front of the diner
is a bad reception area.
Uh, no, no, no, no.
Don't reach for that.
It's probably
just an Amber alert.
Why are you acting weird?
Oh, are you jealous
of my new pants?
No, but I may have texted
something about you
that I didn't mean,
so just please
don't look at your phone.
Uh, okay.
If it's something bad,
I don't want to see it anyway.
She's gonna look at it,
isn't she, Earl?
I would.
She just did.
You're so sick of me?
'Cause it's funny!
"I'm so sick of you!"
You know, said funny.
You know how I am.
Ask Earl. Earl, help.
Oh, I am off the chain.
Oleg, help.
I'll be in my car.
Oh, look, look! Here's han!
He knows how I'm always
just joking.
Han, nod your head
and don't ask why.
Oh, no, last time you
asked me to do that,
I wound up on a date
with an albino.
And who didn't call who back?
I don't know how
they're so confident.
Max, you said
you were sick of me.
Oh, why are you so upset?
I say worse things
to you all the time.
Yesterday I said
you were sad and pathetic.
But that was to my face.
I can't believe you talk
about me behind my back.
It's bad. I am sorry.
What can I do?
Hit me. Punch me.
Tell my mother where I live.
Congratulations, Max.
Now you're like
all my old girlfriends,
talking behind my back.
Stop looking at that.
Delete it.
This is not what I think. I'm
not sick of you. Really?
'Cause when I see it in writing,
it feels like you are.
It's not me. It's this phone.
It brought out the ugliness
that was kind of already there.
There!
I killed it
because it hurt you.
I swear I didn't mean it.
You have to believe me.
It's fine, Max.
I feel like
I'm gonna throw up.
There...
I French-fried my phone.
What else can I do?
I mean, really,
it is technology's fault.
It's turning us
against each other.
Caroline, I swear,
I will never accidentally say
anything about you again
that I never meant.
I have to get ready for work.
It's fine.
Stop saying that.
Please stop saying it's fine.
"Fine" doesn't mean fine.
The scale goes great,
good, okay,
not okay, I hate you, fine.
If "fine" meant fine,
that'd be great,
but it doesn't, okay?
You're right. It's not fine.
It sucks. I'm hurt.
You're the one person
I care most about.
No, you are the one person
I care the most about.
Well, right now
it doesn't feel that way.
It has to feel that way!
You are my best friend,
Caroline!
I love you.
Oh, my God, now I'm
really gonna throw up.
Max, is that the first time
you said "I love you"?
Don't look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
Now what do we do?
So you're not sick of me?
You are the only person
in the entire world
I am not sick of.
Caroline...
There's a woman here who said
she paid to slap you.
If I had known
it was an option,
I would have thrown my name
into that hat.
Well, time to put this on.
That's my $500 pledge.
I'll go. What?
I'll take it. I deserve it.
You've already gotten
a slap in the face from me.
But she's expecting to see me.
No, she's expecting
to see a clueless woman
wearing a paper bag.
And even though
I wasn't planning
on becoming that woman for
another 20, 25 years, I owe you.
Seriously?
You're not gonna stop me?
Nope.
And, Max... I love you too.
I'm so sick of you.
Sync & corrections by no1
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net