Today's a good day for playing catch.
I wonder who will play catch with me today.
What the? Stop! Where's everyone going?
Well, first off, all those people are actually following me,
because I have a seven thousand mile global head start. So if you think I'm following them,
you are wrong. I am a leader, not a follower.
You play catch with me now.
No, uh... no way in hell.
Do you know how to play catch?
I know how to play you give me forty dollars.
It's easy. I throw ball, and you catch ball. Try it now.
You didn't catch the ball. Try again.
I don't have any arms.
Oh.
And now that you've made me admit what you wrongfully think is a medical inconsistency,
I have to go. I'm extremely late, and you are the one who has problems, not me.
Hey! You wanna play catch?
Uh, no! I do not. Hey, uh, d'ya happen to see where everyone went to?
Yes.
OKay. Which, uh, way was that to?
You're ending your sentences in prepositional phrases. You better stop ending your sentences in prepositional phrases.
Or what?
Or I'll make it look like you killed me.
Yeah, look, I'm, I was late because I had to close the bar, and I don't ever close the bar, but I closed it, okay?
So if you wanna live, tell me where they went to.
Never.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Skillet, down, down, Skillet. Stop. Everybody stop.
When I go like this: , that's when you hit the cymbal.
No, man. You're still doin' it wrong.
What'd you, um... what'd you do with the cymbals?
Come in.
Welcome to the shark show.
Um, tonight is gonna be really fun, 'cause we have, uh, Pronto here.
And here's Pronto.
Anyway, Pronto, to my left, lives in a condo down off Quiver.
He's into, uh, archery. Archery, mouse. You hear that?
Pronto's into archery. He's the best. He's an archerist, Mouse. An archerist.
That's a good show.
Oh. You're right. It's not a good show at all.
I know, um, I'm hungry too, but there's only a hand and a cold phone in the icebox.
Everybody, don't move.
St- stop moving around so much. Around.
Now, gimme the cash!
Come- come on, guys! I'm, I'm totally s-, I'm totally serious.
I'm not foolin'.  F-f-f-f-foolin'! Around. Give it to me! Gimme the cash.
Oh, god!  The Leppard rocks. Right?
F-foolin'.  I'm starving!
I'm gonna count  to like three, okay, and everybody who can gimme the cash , they better give it to me.
All right? Like, now. Everybody.
Okay. Gimme the cash!  Gimme some fries.
Is it, is it kinda hot in here?
Everybody? Where'd ya go? Gimme some fries.
You better gimme the cash, right, 'cause then, I'll have the cash, okay, and then people, they come up to me, and they, and, I'll say, they'll say...
Hold on, hold on. Let me start over. Let me start over.
People might come up to me, and they, and say, can I have some cash, or some money? And I'll say, no way dude!
Awesome. When did that happen?
Who was that... person we were fighting?
I don't know either.
Where is everyone? And why?
He, uh... he doesn't count, man.
Officer, you can't sleep here. Officer? Officer, you can't sleep here, officer.
Stop.
You can't sleep here, officer.
You can't sleep here. Stop. Officer- Stop it. You can't sleep here. Stop it.
Who are you?
I don't have to tell you who I am. You don't ask me who I am, you don't know me, you don't need to know who I am,
you don't know who I am, you don't ask me who I am, you don't know me, you don't need to know who I am, you don't know who I am.
I know. No one knows who you are. Congratulations.
I don't have to say thank you to you. I said, I don't have to say thank you to you.
I don't have to say thank you to you.
Oh, it's you.
No one will play catch with me.
Good!
My job at the diner is not workin' out.
I would rather play catch all day than work at that diner with the food.
I have an idea, and it's a good one.
Tell me.
Go outside, stand in the road, every time you see a car, flip it off.
What will that do?
It'll be neat.
I hope you know how very lucky you are to know me, since I'm so incredibly incredible.
Yeah. I am.
I heard that your greeny friend had a hankerin' for circus dogs.
I know.
And that new guy got himself a prize. That's what I heard.
You are so... talk so much.
Well I'm just stating the obvious, which makes me one hundred percent right during all conversation.
Yeah, so uh, you sure this'll work?
Has it ever not succeeded? Notice how I didn't use the F word because that word is to be not found in my vocab.
Keep that thing away, or I won't do this.
Do it.
Do it, please. Okay, you win. Miglo lamafla verniminin.
It is done. I did it.
Get out.
I will bill you.
All the way out.
In a huge way.
Yeah, keep goin'. Keep goin'.
Just, no, just keep goin', 'til i stop saying keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
Can you even still hear me? Good.
What the?
What's up with your problem?
Sea cells run dry over the sea cell.
The what?
Um...
Sea cells run dry over-
Stop. Get in.
No way.
www.tvsubtitles.net