Hey, can I, uh, can I get you som'n?  Uh, partner?
I'm sorry, it sounded like you said "partner".
Y'know, buddy, guy, chum
square.
Let me see if I can get you something.
Huh.  W, w, what're ya gettin' at?
Shark, I am running a tad late, but I am super excited to be attending your little soiree.
Just get here.  And uh, don't hurt Rhoda.
Well, I... promise I won't touch him.
Got to... do something.  But I can't.
Nobody look at him! Get outta here before the song finishes!
Wait.  What about Skillet?
No time, Mouse, he's a goner.
But he's my only friend.
Dude.  We need... we need to totally like... what we need to do is...
Wow.  We're in trouble.
We gotta roll, giznites. Outta here like last year. Peep this. This is what you were tryin' to lay down, right?
Lay down!
He's right, mouse.
Gimme that.
Gimme that, please?
Take the taxi.  And meet me in town in one hour.
What's an hour in this town.
He's totally on target, man. What time?
Time, shime, hime, pime. Golden Joe gots to go! Like right no!
Get goin'.
Dude, gimme the keys. I think I should be driving you.
No way, fuzz.
But I insist! Ahhh... gimme the keys.
Don't let him drive, Roost! You crazy, you straight up crazy to let him drive. I, I'll drive.
Step off, man. I'm a good driver, I'll drive.
No, you ain't. No way you ain't.
Man, I'm a good driver, I drove my mom crazy all last year. I'm a good driver.
He, he, he, he, he is, he is, I know.  Give him the keys.
I'm drivin'.  Now get on in.
Oh, my head.
He does?
Well,  let's go to the party.
This party isn't that great. I've been to better parties that have been much greater. If you think I'm having fun at this party, I am not.
There are no bacon-wrapped goodies at this party.
Bacon-wrapped goodies are my very favorite. I need a bacon-wrapped goody like you need plastic surgery.
Hell... of a party, Shark.
Shut up. How's Rhoda doin'.
She has a small head injury, but nothing too fixable.
If you killed her, I'll-
Eye'll?
Yeah.  You. Glad you came.
I'm having fun at your part-eye.
Yeah, thanks, uh... love it over there. Away from me. In Canada. Or farther.
I... saw your slideshow.
I know. I showed it to you.
I was there, your big wet eyeball was there, we were both there. 'Member?
I do.
Who told you about the party? 'Cause I don't have people in that often. And you're not even people.
You round, wet, unblinking, horrific orb. You're gross. I really wish you would leave my party.
Can I have this? I want this thing here. Give it to me. Did you hear me? I need this for me.
Hey, so, what do you all do?
No kidding. In town, or...?
That is a treat.  Excuse me. I've enjoyed our chat.
I have read all these books, and they are good books.
Out of all these books, I would say that they are all these my favorite.
Hi.
And hi to you.
Leave us alone, we're reading.
All these books are the same. They're all titled, "Rules".
so?
So, I mean, are you reading "Rules", or "Rules"?
And if you've read one, don't you already sort of know what the other one's about?
Selur eht era selur!
I'm sorry?
your mama. Okay?
Hey, Buttermilk, is this your new car?
This looks like your new car.
uh-huh.
Dammit Joe, I'm the pilot around here, not you.
I told you to let me drive, and leave these controllers alone.
You did?
Have we been driving? Driven?  Because Jesus saves!
shut up!
What am I? What am I talking about?
Dammit, Joe!
Aloha.
How do I open this thing?
Dude, that's a mouse.
well rear my ear stoney, that's crazy!
Shut up! I'm tryin' to get us outta here! It takes concentration, and you two are ruinin' mine.
Now Mouse, how do we get out?
I think it's better that you... stay in there.
Don't even think about it, Fitz.
What? Don't think about it, what?
Trust me, you don't wanna go in there.
What did you call me?
I didn't call you anything.
This is awesome. You're a mouse.
No no no, you, you called me Fitz. Liquor called me Fitz once.
's just a name, like Butch. It don't mean nothin'.
Shark... called me Butch.
Butch is nothin too. 's like when you wake up and tell your son's friend,
"Hey, man, you gonna sleep all day, Butch, or you gonna mow the lawn?"
That's it, that's what it is, that's all it is.
And so much... more than that.
Roost!
What?
Man, I gotta do the trickle! You gotta open this up so I can go.
Me too, dude, up top!
Drivin' with you guys 's like drivin' with a buncha damn babies!
And that's where we cut.
The circle effect... is effective.
That's a good show. How does it end?
It never ends.
But ever-eye-thing ends, somehow.
You are becoming a real problem.
I'm... sorry.
Shark, I think he should prove his sorryness. With these.
Wow. Yeah it's, that's menacing. We gonna hire the hand next, to uh, operate those?
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Shhh. I'm making it happen.
This party's weird. No one seems to be... partying. Oh wait, wait, hold on.
That smells good.
This is some good shee.  Um, you want any?
Ah, Fitz.  You shouldn't be here.
You know me.
No I don't. You're my friend.
My head.
Get out while you can. Stay here forever, with us.
I think I need to-
"amputation, emulation, Lorenzini."
I have read all these books, and they are good books.
Whoa!
Down, little buddy. Down. I don't wanna have to tell you again. I will, but I don't want to.
I hurt! I hurt!
I need help.
www.tvsubtitles.net