Hello?
Hey, it's me, your buddy. How are ya?
I couldn't be... busier.
Doing what?
I'm... I'm on this phone.
That's fair. I'll call you back when you're not on the phone...
Um, when will you be not on the phone?
I'm not on the phone. I'm talking to the phone.
That works.
Hey, it's uh, it's me again.
Are you, are you not on the phone, still?
No.
Is that a yes?
It is? Then yes.
If I were you, I would not check my ice box.
Wouldn't check yours, either.
What's in there in the icebox? Get on your little tiny mousey tiptoes.
Tell me what's in the icebox.
Hello? Mouse?
Heh, you know word is, and I'm not saying that this is what I think, know, or have heard to be true,
seriously, but Liquor said that Mouse is up to his cans.
WEYEeird.
Yeah, and not only that, but New Guy, heard he got out, right?
Like someone got him out. And he got a thing for squirrels.
I'm not talking as though he's cheesy green up on 'em.
I'm saying more like... Equadorian sleep, if you get the picture.
Pic-ture.
Oh, and another thing. Roostre, you know Roostre?
Up on the farm guy? All right.
Well Liquor also says that a letter accidentally got delivered to him,
but before he could open it - BOOM! - just like that, clock shows up.
Next thing he remembers, it's day 97.
What's up, GAs?
N-nothing.
EYE saw you crash.
I'm sure that you did, cause you seem to see everything.
EYEfirmative.
I see, you see, you mean we. Come with me, and fly away.
But first-
Set up the cameras.
No, the 50 mm - yes, the only ones we have - the hidden ones.
Uh...
I'm still lookin at you not setting up the cameras.
And, you know, just planning my day.
How long do you think I'll be watching you not do what I told you to do?
You kill trees.
Shut up.
Trees make oxEYEgen.
Up yours.
I breathe it; you breathe it.
I shut up; you shut up.
See it?
EYE see NEYEgh.
It was right F'n here.
Where the F is it? It was a, it was an F'n arrow, Nand it was right the F here.
Uh huh. EYE hungrEYE.
Good. That means you're leaving.
That will happen... now.
Well.
The litte guy's cameraphobic. Should've known.
What are these; these... are formulas, or.. these papers.
These papers are driving me crazy. Crazy into the night.
Skillet, you're back.
Where've you been?
Wow, tell me about the nightmare.
Holy shee-
Go-damn. Shark!
What's new, Rhoda?
Uhh... nothing, um... sir.
Drink.
You know, uh, I'm a shark.
Uh... thank you.
I attack when I'm hungry. It's instinctual. You know?
Yeah, mmhmm. Th-thank you.
It's like one minute
I'm just hanging out watching lemmings go by, lemmings who might need money,
probably not, but you never know.
Part of me just says, "Hey, whatever."
And then something goes off in my brain, and sends an impulse to my jaw, and bam!
A thousand pounds of pressure lock in like a press.
You know what I mean?
I, I know what you mean. And, and... thank you.
I mean a head your size would burst like an infected kidney,
and all I'd remember was how warm the juices were that lapped the back of my uvula on their trip down to stomach land.
Yes, sir.
But we're friends, right? We know each other.
We know what we do, and who we talk to, and what we say to them.
We do.
I knew we did.
Check out, momma. Slap me a s-
Now let's talk about the letter that Liquor got.
well, that sounds like he was a good dancer, but yet...
These papers are... suddenly useless, and now I must burn them.
For a reason that... I don't know.
I'm getting an idea from your yelling mouth, your so yelling mouth.
We're gonna be rockstars.
But first, we must burgle.
Oh, there's a pretty amp.
Uh, what song was that?
Because it totally rocks. Mmm, mmm, mmm-mmm. Ro-ock and ro-ollll.
It's called "F-Off... to You." So take a hint.
No way! That is...
huh... a great song.
But uh, huh, hmmm, I'm here...
because um, did uh, somebody break in here?
Well, it waasn't us.
Hey! Fellas! Stop, stop it! Why that there is a mean beat, I'm telling ya.
It is?
Yeeeeah, it is. It'd sound great on my record label.
In fact, it should already be on it. Where are we at on that?
You have a record label. For... records?
Yeeeah, I do. Up top! Come on, let's tour.
Hold it, hold it, dude.
Hold it yourself, pops. Haha! Zinger!
Are you the one, who broke in here now?
Nyet, kid! I never have to break in when I am in ma-nihm. You know what I'm saying?
Um, no.
My head!
Woah! Is that ice cream? Awesome.
Dear dad, I have spent over 10 years and $94,000 putting together my mosquito costume,
and now I am pleased to announce that I have... become a mosquito.
My costume is quite realistic, and I have even attached bladders to the nose things
so I can suck up liquids when I puncture them... with my nose thing.
I could be buzzing all around you on a hot summer day, and you wouldn't even recognize me as your son-child.
You would just think, "Get away, mosquito."
From my point of view, you would be 3,000 dads because of the way I've designed the eyeballs.
I'd be saying, "Dad, it's me. Dad it's me," but you wouldn't be able to understand my language because of its buzzing.
I am also into plastics now, and I am making plastic tubes that you can suck liquids through,
kind of like my mosquito nose, but used for different reasons. Hope you're doing well at camp.
See you soon, Mos, Mosq, Mosquito, Mosquitor? Mosqui, Mosquithing...
I don't know who that is.
What's this?
My new record. It's called, um, F-Off.
Is it good?
Mmhmm.
So you've been making records?
No.
Cause, uh, I've always kinda wanted to be in a band.
No way. What do you play?
I play, uh, I play with minds. Shhhhh....
Go home and think about that. Uh, and don't look under your bed.
Heylo?
Did you find my record?
You found it, didn't you? Now spin it.
www.tvsubtitles.net