What is that?
It's got your name on it.
Somebody left this
at Katherine's grave.
- Who knew you were gonna be there?
- Remember that student... Carl Axelrod?
I forgot today is the death of
your wife, the birth of your daughter.
It's just a prank. Some junior egghead
trying to screw with you a little.
Doesn't it bother you
that your name's on it?
If it has to do with homicide,
it better be.
Look at this bullet hole.
Is there such a thing
as "grad school for Photoshop"?
Yesterday I was given a blue parka
just like in the file.
This morning, the rental car company
drops off this green Cherokee...
Just like in the file. You asked why
I changed my mind about this.
My wife told me I had
a doctor's appointment next week.
Next Tuesday,
same time as the autopsy.
- So you miss the autopsy.
- Get me a copy of this, will you?
That oak tree
is not going to survive the storm.
It's going to fall, Mandy!
- You saved my life. Oh, my God.
- It's real.
It's about that Bremmer character.
The action on the South Side of Chicago
is controlled by a handful of guys.
- And he's one of them?
- No, he controls the handful of guys.
I know Roy Bremmer.
I married him.
- And I'm still married to him.
- Why would you not tell me?
- This is for you. You need to take it.
- What the hell are you doing?
You need to take it.
You're in danger. Jesse is in danger.
- Er...
- I...
- I thought that...
- Sorry.
What are you doing?
Er...
You know, people get killed
who keep guns in their house,
so I was trying to...
I was just gonna sort of...
Claudia...
Oh, boy.
You wanted to test
one of my bullets?
- No, Claudia...
- Go for it. I don't care.
- Claudia, listen...
- Do you really think I'd shoot you?
No. This was
a very good way to prove...
If you wanted my gun, you could have
asked, I would have given it to you.
- I didn't want to wake you.
- Oh, please.
Claudia...
All I want to do is see Saturday.
I'll do whatever it takes to get there.
That doesn't count.
Carry, carry, carry...
Go around the corner...
down the way...
Oh, we are way
down the hall, Alice.
Jump, Rover. Jump.
Come on,
why doesn't that...? It does.
Why? Why?
It's real.
Jess?
Jesse?
- Come on, Jess, we gotta go.
- Dad?
You always tell me the truth.
Always.
Even when
I didn't want to hear it.
Er, ahem...
I just... you know, I didn't want
to burden you with any of this.
But not knowing
is worse, Pop.
Secrets are worse.
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you
what's in that case.
You see, Jess, it seems
someone wants to hurt me.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- Can i seet?
- No.
But maybe I can help
figure it out.
I appreciate that,
but I showed it to the police,
and they're taking care of it.
As a matter of fact, we have
the top homicide investigator...
Homicide?
That means "murder. "
- No, it's... it's sort of
- Papa...
promise me
that's not going to happen.
Aw, Jess,
Jess, Jess...
I promise.
Detective Sikorski's
in a meeting.
- All right...
- You hungry?
Listen, I shot this
from Claudia's gun this morning.
Claudia's got a gun?
Yes, and a husband who she's been
on the run from the last two years.
Yeah, Roy Bremmer.
I found out who he is.
I know who he is.
Here's what we have to do.
We have to run a ballistics check
on that bullet,
get the results back
this afternoon...
Hold on. You've been watching
too much "CSI," pal.
Ballistics takes
at least two weeks.
Well, I only have two days, "pal,"
so make things happen.
Hey, I don't need
this crap from you.
I wrote a killer obituary.
Not to mention my eulogy...
"Ashes to ashes, dust to dust,
Photons to neutrons... the particle
hunter reduced to particles. "
I scanned this
from the newsprint,
and these
from the 8x10s.
They're clean images, unadulterated
and technically impossible.
Make some sense, Yoshi.
This is a new car, but
the photographic paper it's printed on
Is 40, maybe 50 years old.
The pigments, the dyes,
they follow a fading pattern
that only comes with age.
How does a new picture
get to be 50 years old?
It sits in a file for 50 years.
What?
How is that possible?
Yoshi, show me
my funeral again.
This is wrong. This is all wrong.
I was there two days ago.
This is empty...
there's no grave there.
Wait... can you read that?
M- A... M-U...
"Mandy Murphy. "
What?
That means...
that means...
That means...?
What the hell does it mean?
Hey...! Tell Frank to keep
page three open.
Hey, my hero!
- Butchle, hush up.
- I have a question for you.
- Fire away
- It's kind of personal.
- I think we're past that, JT.
- All right, okay.
Do you own a burial plot?
And if you do, where is it?
Yeah, I own a plot.
My parents left me one.
- It's in...
- Evergreen Park?
- Yeah. How did you know that?
- Thank you. That is the best...
..best news I've heard all week.
Thank you. Thank you for the flowers.
They were spectacular.
Dog's just too little
to be that mean.
So catch me up here, Teach.
"Remedial course 101."
That photo... the file?
- Not a hoax, right?
Right.
Mandy Murphy was supposed to die...
underneath that tree?
That's right, but she didn't.
She's alive and well
instead of six feet under
like in that photo
because I changed her destiny...
which means I can change my own.
Wait, wait a minute.
You can't leave now!
This is huge!
I need the damn story.
What are you doing on Monday.
I'll buy you lunch, tell you everything.
But this is gonna change the face
of the universe as we know it.
"The future is not immutable. "
You can print that.
Professor?
Ah... Mrs. Silviera, I am canceling
classes the rest of the week.
Excuse me, Brad?
JT, just the person
I was looking for. Excuse us.
- We have hit the jackpot.
- What are you talking about?
Are you okay?
Carbon nanotubes, ground
to workable length...
woven and coated
to make this...
an ultra light, super-strong material
that's gonna replace metal,
it's gonna replace plastic, fabrics...
I mean, the implications
for the auto industry alone...
It's amazing, Brad.
it's incredible.
I'm going out of town for a few days.
I need the case.
Hello, Professor.
You're not listening to me.
- I'm listening, Brad...
- We're holding the future in our hands.
Do you have any idea
what that's worth?
- My life.
- I can reverse engineer this,
take out a patent in both our names,
and we can buy Hawaii
Brad, you've been up
all night, right?
What?
Yeah, yeah I have.
- You're serious?
- I'm dead serious.
I've got enough data
to start lining up investors.
Can you imagine the bidding war?
We're gonna be bazilionares.
This is ridiculous.
It's theft.
"Theft"? From the future?
Come on!
All right, okay.
So what?
Someone's gonna come from
the future and sue us? I don't think so.
I'm going.
Don't start getting all righteous on me,
okay, brother? I really need this.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, I do!
Yes, I do.
Chantal and I really need this...
really need a break.
This isn't it.
I'll call you Monday.
Let's see...
What are you doing in my house?
Er... I came to tell you...
What?
- You're going to die.
- Eventually, yes.
No, on Friday.
The physics demand it.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I checked and rechecked
the Vidnet nexus,
every major STP...
I stayed up all night.
There's a lot of that
going around.
Don't joke about this, Professor.
It is basic, and it is bad.
If you're supposed to die
and then you don't...
it's like you make a rip
in the fabric of the universe.
Yeah, I'm listening.
The effects of your death
are ripples in time and space.
They've already been written.
That's not science, Carl,
that's theology.
Excuse me? It's string theory
applied to multiverses,
assuming that time
and gravity can be... look,
the dog that made you
swerve on Monday...
I was wrong. It wasn't random,
it was part of the design.
Everything is part of the design,
especially births and deaths.
- It can't be changed.
- Nonsense. I changed the design.
I used information from the file
to save somebody's life.
Oh, my God!
Universe seems
intact to me, Carl.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- Carl, whoever sent that case
knows a lot more
about space and time than we do.
Do you think they'd risk
their existence to save mine?
But you have a duty to everyone
around you... to physics.
Take a break from physics, Carl.
You need to.
Huh...
Claudia, it's me.
I'm sorry about this morning.
But that's not why I'm calling.
I'm on my way to pick up Jesse.
We're going to the airport,
taking the first flight out.
We'll be back on Monday,
provided no oak trees have fallen.
Listen, I really want you
to come with us...
we both do.
Give me a call. Bye.
Keep the change.
Excuse me?
We really do need to talk, Professor...
about my wife.
No, we don't.
Now.
Take five.
Have a cigarette.
Go.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Hmm? Last night,
when I saw that,
my first impulse...
was to pick up the phone
and have you...
Ah, never mind. I don't go
with first impulse anymore.
I'm a reasonable man.
Nobody takes phone calls
when I'm talking to them.
Okay... her real name is Angela.
She's as slippery as a fish.
Three times I've found her,
three times, she's disappeared.
Until now... thanks to you.
Oh, and...
lovely little girl, Jesse.
Leave Jesse out of this.
Don't even mention her name.
Angry man.
I like that.
I like that a lot.
Okay.
Here's the deal, Professor.
If I lose Angela this time,
I'm coming after you.
If you warn her,
if you try to help her escape,
I'm coming after you.
It's as simple as that.
Give me back my wife...
and you can get on
with your life.
Basically...
it's the only way
for you to have one.
This is JT.
Pease leave a message.
Vasco da Gama rounded
the Cape of Good Hope in 1497.
Now, can anybody tell me
where he sailed to?
Come on, people.
Jesse?
Mike?
Mr. Watkins' room.
Recess is in 10 minutes.
Can it wait?
Okay.
Jesse...?
Whoa!
- I thought something happened to you.
- No, no, no...
Something did happen,
but something good. Come on.
- We're gonna go on a trip.
- A trip?
- Yeah. Why not?
- Right now?
I've got to make a phone call.
I want you to stay where I can see you.
Jess, please?
Do as I say.
What happened
to your cell phone?
It broke.
- Denorvo Insurance.
- Hey, it's me.
I've been trying to reach you. I think
there's something wrong with your phone.
Oh, my phone? Yes... I ran into a guy
who doesn't appreciate you
taking calls while he's talking to you
so he smashed it.
Oh, my God.
- Roy.
- Yeah.
Claudia, this is not just
about me and you anymore.
It's also about Jesse.
Listen,
I gotta go.
Okay.
They found you, didn't they?
The people who threatened you?
The ones from the case?
- What's happening, Pop?
- Well...
We are doing what
Mandy Murphy did, only better.
We're getting as far away
from our oak tree as possible...
...before it falls, all right?
Hmm?
Jess?
Jess, listen...
I know I'm running low
on promises,
but we've got
to get through this.
I'll make it up to you.
Put your seat belt on.
Did the policeman
tell you to leave town?
No.
Jess, no one's following us.
Dad!
Learn to drive, you jerk!
Oh, boy.
Jess, I've got to get to a pay phone
and call Sikorski.
No, you don't.
- Sikorski here.
- This is JT, heading for the airport.
- Is Claudia with you?
- No.
- Wait for me.
- I'm not waiting for anyone.
Wait for me!
Damn it!
Honey?
Brad?
Bradley...?
Stop! Stop it!
- Stop this!
- No!
Give me...
give me this!
Drop it!
What are you doing? Brad?
Brad, what is it?
Shh!
Tell me, tell me, honey...
Nobody will understand!
So, where are we going to go?
New York, if this line
gets a move on.
Come on.
You know what, kiddo?
We're gonna travel in style. Come on.
Final boarding call
for flight 32 to Boston,
- Flight 32 to Boston.
First class.
Awesome.
- Hey.
- Claudia!
Hey. We need to talk.
It's business, it won't take long.
Jess, could you do me
a huge favor?
Would you go and grab me
a pack of gum
and you can get something
for yourself?
There's a kiosk down there,
but make sure I can see you, okay?
- Look, Claudia...
- No, it's okay. Don't say anything.
I understand. If you have
to choose between Jesse and me,
that's not a choice.
That's why I did this.
I doubled your payout.
Jesse gets four million now.
Hey, call me callous
if you like
but I've learned the hard way
to be practical, and this is practical.
Two million is not enough these days...
not for an entire lifetime.
So all you have to do is...
Tell me something, Claudia.
When was the last time
you saw your husband?
Two years ago.
I told you that. Why?
Well, you gave me
a blue parka,
you arranged for the green
Cherokee,
now you present me
with this...?
You think this is all
some elaborate scam?
- You think I'm working with Roy?
- I don't know what to think anymore.
JT, I left Roy.
I've been running from him.
He did horrible,
ugly things to me.
You met him... you saw him.
There's nothing...
nothing he won't...
You know what? Forget it.
Do whatever you want.
Tell Jesse I said goodbye.
I'll miss her.
... all passengers
on flight 117 to Wichita,
that's 117 to Wichita...
- Claudia?
- Leave me alone.
Claudia...
You're coming with us, right?
Walk through, ma'am.
Back.
Neumeyer, hold up.
Neumeyer.
Oh, no. Here.
Go, go. You can't do this.
She's a felon.
- What do you mean?
- Identity theft.
She's not Claudia Whitney.
Which means that gun of hers
was acquired under an assumed name.
- That's a felony.
- It's not one I care about.
There's more.
Brad is bankrupt.
- What?
- He's not the picker you think he is.
They're ready to repossess
everything he owns
including the gold fillings
in his back teeth.
He gets custody of Jesse
if you croak, right?
Along with your estate?
Listen, you didn't need to come here
just to tell me this, did you?
Running
never solved anything.
Just stay and face whatever
you have to face. I'll help you.
Look, Sikorski, I appreciate
your involvement. I really do.
But how about focusing on the only
person who's ever threatened me?
Claudia's husband.
- Claudia's got a husband?
- Yeah.
The flight's been canceled.
Mechanical problems.
All right.
Well, they can't all be grounded.
You up for a relay race?
- If you go, I can't protect you.
Well, how about helping us
instead of slowing us down?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please fasten your seat belts
and put your seats
in the upright position.
You have a husband?
Yeah, I do.
It's complicated.
He's a bad guy.
And I mean literally... a bad guy.
I didn't know that when I married him.
I just fell in love.
Thought he was rich
and powerful, like a king.
The truth is,
I didn't want to know.
What's his name?
Roy Bremmer.
Ugh... I don't even
like saying it.
I ran away from him two years ago.
He's been chasing me ever since.
Why?
What do you mean,
"why"?
If you ran away from me,
that would mean
you didn't like me anymore.
I wouldn't want you back,
so why does he?
You just see
the back of that one.
- Oh, look at them.
- Love Siamese cats.
- What was that one?
- Like...
- Like, "Get away from me. "
- Vampires!
Either that, or he says, "Mouse".
I had a cat who liked that,
actually.
You could pick her up
by the tail...
by the tail and toss her.
Sir, are you all right?
Heather... sir?
Are you okay?
Ladies and gentlemen,
may i have your attention, please?
This is your captain speaking.
Unfortunately, we have a medical
emergency and must return to Seattle.
We are sorry
for any inconvenience.
- Claudia, I'm scared.
- Don't be scared, sweetie.
We're gonna be fine.
- Are all these people sick?
- I don't think so.
- Is everything gonna be okay?
- Don't worry. Dr. Dan's gonna be here.
- We're gonna be okay.
- I want to go home, Dad.
- Did you get Dan?
- No. Maybe a quarantine's not bad.
Hello, sweetheart.
How would you like
a "Get Out Of Jail Free" card?
Okay... everybody, you can all
take off your masks and go home.
Oh, good.
Come with me.
- So we're not contagious?
- No, you're not.
- The guy on the plane...
- Is he okay?
Peanut allergy.
I kind of gotta
use the restroom.
Okay. I'll take you.
Meet you outside?
Okay. Come on.
See you later.
JT, do you mind
if I ask you a question?
Sure.
- A flight in the middle of the week?
What are you trying to do?
Change my destiny.
Take a short cut
through ER.
I got the results back
of that lab work you asked for...
your blood, the blood
on the bullet...
It matches, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
Listen, can you tell me
what the hell's going on?
We've got a multi-car crash coming in.
Not this one.
We lost her on the way over.
I gotta go.
All right, I've got it,
I've got it.
Any trouble breathing?
You saved my life. Oh, my God.
www.tvsubtitles.net