It seems someone wants to hurt me.
We have the top homicide investigator--
- That means murder.
- I shot this from Claudia's gun
Claudia's got a gun?
And a husband that she's been
on the run from for the last two years
- Roy Bremmer.
- Professor, we need to talk
about my wife.
Her real name is Angela
Three times I find her,
three times she disappears
This time, if I lose Angela,
I'm coming after you
You're going to die... on Friday.
The physics demand it
- Nonsense.
- What's happening, Pop?
We're going to do exactly what
Mandy Murphy did, only better
We're going to get far away
from our oak tree before it falls
Mandy Murphy was supposed to die
underneath that tree
But she didn't. She's alive and well
because I changed her destiny
which means
I can change my own
We've got a multi.crash coming in.
We lost her on the way over
"I, John Tracy Neumeyer...
being of sound mind
and body...
do declare the following
to be my last will and testament
# Fare thee well... #
Everything I own,
I leave to my daughter--
Jesse Tracy Neumeyer
I name Dr. Dan Westville
and his wife, Jan Mercer Westville
the legal guardians for Jesse
And I also name Dan...
to be executor of my estate...
# Though I go 10,000 miles... #
# 10,000 miles #
# My own true love... #
Now Dan, this is crucial...
# 10,000 miles or more... #
Brad... Brad and Chantal
must never have access
to Jesse's trust. Never
And Jesse, it's really...
it's funny
because I never really
gave much thought to...
what was coming for you.
for us
# That long summer's day #
# Sitting on an ivy tree #
# She's looking for #
# Her own true love #
JT:
Driving you to your first dance
watching you graduate
walking you down the aisle...
I can't imagine that
You know, holding--
holding your newborn child
# Oh, come ye back #
# My own true love... #
JT:
Okay, I'm trying to think...
trying to think ofthe right thing
to say here, the fatherly thing
that's going to help you through
all those moments, but I can't
So I'm going
to tell you this, Jess.
You are stronger
than you think you are...
and you are smarter
than the rest of us put together
And Jess...
I guess the biggest thing
I want to say to you
is that you have
a huge capacity for love
and if you give that
to those who deserve it...
you'll always be okay
# You've been a friend to me. #
Jess?
I'm sorry. You were never
supposed to see that
Is it real?
It seems so
How do you know?
Well, you know,
things keep happening--
the storm
the oak tree
people changing...
Everything that's in that file,
it's come true
Everything?
So far
But...
the only way...
Are you saying this...
this is from the future?
Who sent it?
I don't know
Why did they send it?
Well, you know...
I assumed it was
to help me stop all this
But now, I think, Jess...
that maybe it was--
it was to help me...
prepare
To prepare?
No, no, that's like giving up.
You can't give up
I mean, you can't
give up because...
I mean, whoever sent it
wouldn't have picked it out for you
unless if... unless
if you could change
They chose it for you because
they knew you could figure it out
Okay, okay
We have to fight.
I mean, "us" have to fight
You know?
Please
You are right
You're right.
We do, we do have to fight...
or at least, I do.
You have to go to school
- No.
- Yeah
Claudia!
- Can you take Jess to school?
- Is she ready?
- Five minutes?
- Not soon enough
I've got urgent business
JT: Now, Jess, I need you to be
where I know you're safe
Jesse:
What if something happens to you?
It won't, it's Thursday.
Okay?
Come here
Please?
Fine, but don't expect me
to learn anything
You're not supposed
to be here
Well, I can't get away.
I mean that literally-- I cannot run
so I'm going to deal
with this thing head-on
Meaning what?
I'm going to remove each suspect's
motive or opportunity to kill me
- Carl, Brad, Roy--
- Wait a minute
You can't just "cowboy up"
on a guy like Roy
You'll only get yourself killed
a day early
- So arrest him, put him in jail.
- On what grounds?
You know, maybe
I should put you in jail
for your own protection.
It sounds like I should
No, listen, he would find
a way to get to me
Sikorski, someone
wants to kill me--
a deliberate act.
So that means I have to act first
All right, well,
we'll see you around-- I hope
Wait a minute
You left out a suspect
Claudia.
What are you going to do about her?
She's your weakness,
isn't she?
Claudia is the least
of my worries
Oh, please,
don't tell me you trust her
There's more to this
than just a marriage gone bad, JT
There's bigger things
at stake here
And what do you mean
by that?
There has to be
Listen, if Claudia
really wanted to kill me...
she's so good at hiding it, there'd be
nothing anyone could do about it
What you should be doing right now
is focusing on the real threat
which is the homicidal husband
Where is she?
Sikorski:
It's the weaknesses that get you
Okay Roy,
where is your weakness?
"Acquitted."
"Charges dropped."
"Acquitted again."
- Woman: Everett Hospital.
- Dr. Dan Westville, please
Announcer:
Your attention, please
Passengers are now boarding
at platform four...
This is Angela Bremmer.
I need to speak to Roy
Carl, we need to talk.
Maybe you could ride with me
while I run some errands.
I don't have much time
You talked yesterday about a rip
in the fabric of the universe
- Yes, if you don't die.
- What exactly does that mean?
I mean, scientifically?
Do the laws of physics get repealed
if I'm still alive on Saturday?
Does gravity cease?
Does "E" not equal "MC squared"?
Well, impossible, yes,
if you apply the bootstrap paradox
but not if you include five-dimensional
supergravity-- I don't know!
Nobody does. The point is,
we can't afford to find out
Well, I intend to
Professor, has it occurred to you
that by fighting your destiny
you could make things worse?
Hmm-- what's worse
than a bullet in the head?
Not for you, for everyone
and everything around you
- Where are we going?
- Oh, I had a friend check my blood
against the blood found
on the bullet fragment in the case
so I'm going
to check the results--
That's a waste of time,
it matches, has to
You want to bet? No, I'm serious,
if the blood doesn't match
will you drop this whole thing
and leave me alone?
And if it does?
Well, then you have to do
what you have to do
JT:
You can stay here
or you can come with me
and check the results
My name is Jesse Neumeyer.
I need to see Tim
He's the editor. It's urgent
"Jesse-bear"?
Come on up
What's the occasion?
Aren't you supposed to be at school?
You know, some things are just
more important than school
Oh. You have to
tell me all about it
I need to know what happened
to Mandy Murphy's dog
'cause it doesn't say
You're right, it doesn't
Jesse:
Are dogs allowed at funerals?
JT: Yeah, he said
we should wait in here
- I hate doctors' offices.
- Um-hmm
In-state school doctor. Nice
- You must be Carl.
- Yeah, I must be
What about
Professor Neumeyer's blood?
Does it match the blood
on the bullet? We have a bet
Carl, I'd like you to meet
Dr. Fontaine
- Why?
- Hi, Carl
Carl, I had no choice
Professor Neumeyer has expressed
a great concern about you, Carl
- No, he hasn't.
- He explained your condition
and in my opinion,
a 72-hour observation period
would be most beneficial right now
How dare you?
How can you do this to us,
to the world, to your own daughter?
You lying, backstabbing,
son of a bitch!
- Fontaine: Put Mr. Axelrod in three.
- I felt sorry for you, but now
now you deserve
what's coming!
- You deserve it!
- Come on
You deserve
what's coming to you!
I owe you for this one
Well, that's good, JT, because now
I have something to ask of you
Anything you want
You want to admit me
for observation?
- I want you to admit yourself.
- Oh, no. No, no, no
This will be completely confidential.
The university will never know
Dan, I know that this whole thing
sounds very crazy--
I did not say "crazy," I didn't
say that. I think it's just stress
It's the anniversary
of Katherine's death
you've got pressure at work
and it's all coming out in this delusion
about a mysterious prophecy
of your murder from outer space
No, not outer space, Dan,
it's from the--
Oh, jeez.
All right, listen--
why don't you call Brad?
Ask Brad. He'll tell you
I talked to Brad. He doesn't know
what the hell you're talking about
Ah...
Now Dan, listen, you saw the bullet.
The bullet, it matches the blood
Jan and I will look after Jesse
You need to start
reducing the stress right now
Yeah, that's exactly
what I'm going to do
JT?
All those Christmases in Hawaii,
all those ski trips to Aspen
they were all my treat.
They didn't cost you and Jesse a dime
Because you refused my money.
You always had to play Daddy Warbucks
Oh, for God's sake,
spare me the lecture
You know what really
pisses you off, JT?
Not that I'm in trouble, no
What pisses you off
is that I'm ambitious
I tried to reach for the sky and got
slammed for it and you love that
You love it because you gave up
reaching a long time ago
If you needed money,
all you had to do was ask
You know what I need
The briefcase?
The briefcase is yours
As soon as I am done with it,
you can reverse-engineer it
sell the technology,
keep the profits. I don't care
You see, Brad, all I care about
is staying alive
Staying alive?
JT-- JT!
You don't really believe that
I would try and kill you over this?
Be careful, he's falling apart
We'll get everything back
and more
I promise
Sure we will
Recording:
"Leave a message."
This is the Professor calling.
I have something for Roy
You can reach me
at 425.555.145...
# All alone #
# Out at sea #
# Drifting for days #
# It's hard to believe #
# That help is on the way...#
- Hello?
- Professor Neumeyer?
This is Mrs. Strom,
the school secretary
Yes, yes, is Jesse okay?
Well, that's just it, we don't know.
She hasn't been in classes today
# Like the world #
# Circling the sun #
# Life goes on... #
Please...?
# Oh, life goes on... #
Yes!
- Yes?
- JT: Claudia, Jesse is missing
Claudia:
Jesse? How do you know?
JT: The school called, she
never went in. I need your help
She's such a smart kid, JT,
I'm sure she's fine
Just stay right there.
I'm on my way
Dad!
Dad, Dad!
- Dad!
- Why did you skip school?
It said in the newspaper clipping that
Mandy Murphy and her pet dog
were killed by the tree,
but then you saved them
Nobody could tell me if the dog died
like he was supposed to
Then it said in the newspaper about
the funeral, so I went to find out
And he is alive. Which means
that you can change things
Did you take care
of that business?
- Ongoing. Fill you in?
- Yeah
Okay
Are you mad at me
for ditching school?
No, Jess, I'm not. I'm actually
very proud of you. You were brave
You paid attention to detail,
you didn't take anything for granted
You checked everything
just like a good scientist
Yes?
This is Bremmer.
You've got something for me?
- Yes.
- Bring it
It's going to have to be
in a public place
It is. 1138 Grove.
Leave right now
- Okay, I have to go out.
- Why?
Aw, damn. Claudia parked me in.
Tell Claudia I'm taking her car
Here, can you give those
to her, please?
Just tell her
- Dad?
- Yeah?
I love you
Damn it, JT
Jesse: I'm changing
everything, every detail
Where is that blue parka?
Hah-- you are gone!
Ugh!
Grove Street
You know...
I grew up without a father
But I think it must be even harder
growing up without a mom
I've always had my dad
What would happen if he dies?
Would I ever see you again?
I don't know
Carl:
That's the mother lode, isn't it?
Hey, that's my case
you've got there
- No, it isn't.
- Brad: Hey, hold up
Hey, slow down! Hey!
You're JT's student.
You're Carl, right?
Professor Neumeyer gave that to me.
He wanted me to have it
- I don't care what he wants.
- Give me that case
- Give me the case.
- No!
Give me the case!
- Let it go
You lunatic, will you let it go?
Sikorski
There it is
# ... This is what it's all about #
# Everybody, let's shout,"Bomb
ticky.ticky, ticky.ticky bomb.bomb #
# Bomb ticky.ticky,
ticky.ticky bomb"#
# It's a bomb ticky.ticky,
ticky.ticky bomb.bomb #
#"Bomb ticky.ticky,
ticky.ticky bomb... #
Man:
Two more!
Two drink minimum
Scotch!
- 20 bucks.
- It's on me
Roy, I have something
to show you
No, no,
no, no, no
What's this?
This isn't real
- This is real.
- This isn't Angela
I gotta pee.
So do you
There's something else here,
you see...
this file came from a case whose
materials come 50 years in the future
Now, I know someone who can
reverse-engineer it for you
- That would be like having plastic--
- You think it's about the money?
Bremmer:
I know where she is
I can take her anytime I want,
but I'm not gonna do that
I want you to give her to me
I want you to betray her,
so she never thinks about you again
Look at you, look at you!
You say you're going to die
in this titty joint
sometime before what...
dawn tomorrow? Hmm?
You give Angela to me
before then
or I'm gonna make it
all come true
I'll be waiting for her,
Professor
You've got the wrong guy
Bremmer: Hey, hey, hey,
easy on the suit
- Cop #1 : Get him out of there.
- Cop #2: Let's go
I go to jail,
you go down, Officer
- Shut up, Roy.
- I mean it
- So do I.
- He's got a gun, arrest him
No, I don't have a gun,
you can search me
What about the club? The girls want to
know if they're still working tonight
Shut it down
Carl Axelrod escaped
from the hospital
Your brother-in-law
is down at the station
screaming his head off that Carl
stole his briefcase and assaulted him
And it gets worse--
I sent some men over to Carl's loft
and they went inside.
There's something you've got to see
All right, well,
I'm gonna go to the house first
because Bremmer
has someone watching it
No, I can post
a couple of men at your place
I need you to come with me
You're lucky Claudia called me
and warned me you were armed
Hello?
Hey, it's me,
I'm with Sikorski
Come home, please
No, I have one more stop to make
and then I'm going to come home
- No, Jesse is--
- Claudia, listen, they arrested Roy
Sikorski is gonna have
some men at the house
You'll be safe. I'll be safe
and then I'll come home
- JT...
- Kiss Jess good night, will you?
JT:
Hmm...
"Assuming... constant..."
Sikorski:
Look at this
See all this?
This is where Carl proves
that the universe will fall apart
if I am not dead by tomorrow
Today
www.tvsubtitles.net