Come on, put it...
Excuse me.
Out of the way, please.
Hey!
Chill out, mamacita.
What's with the, uh,
weekday vibe.
- It is a Tuesday, sir.
- Hey, hey.
You work on that show?
Yeah, I work on that show.
Just like your mom works
that street corner.
I'm sorry, that's too much.
No sweat.
My mom is a prostitute.
Hey! This chick knows
Jenna Maroney!
Hey! New drinking game!
Drink when
someone says something!
Whoo!
Who are you people?
We're "Crabcatchers."
You know, from Jenna's song
Catchin' crabs in paradise?
♪ I caught crabs in paradise
♪ and, yes, I mean
both kinds of crabs ♪
Oh, I thought that was
at least gonna be innuendo.
Jenna is playing the Tod show,
in a couple of days,
so we're just camping out
and "unwindulaxing."
Wait, so Jenna's
Jimmy Buffett rip-off
is actually a thing?
See, you people from New York,
you don't know all the stuff
that's going on
in the rest of the country.
Truck races, swamp parties,
mall fires.
I can't believe
she's pulling this off.
And I can't believe
I'm pulling this off!
Whoo!
Why do you have
a tattoo of a seatbelt?
So I don't get pulled over
when I'm driving shirtless!
Whoo!
You wanted to see me?
Have I mentioned marisol,
the Mexican sideline reporter
I've been seeing?
Well, since our weekend
in Aspen,
she's been put on pelvic rest.
Fast-forward noise.
Marisol was supposed
to attend a fundraiser luncheon
with me today.
It's $10,000 a plate.
And I'll have
to eat the ticket unless...
Unless I eat the ticket.
Fancy luncheon, seafood bar.
I'm thinking 75 cents a shrimp,
over three hours,
and split...
Carry 3.75...
By the time I'm done,
you'll be making money.
Good. I should warn you,
though,
that it's
a Republican fundraiser.
So if you're coming,
it won't be
as Liz Lemon, huffpo superuser
and gun-control lunatic.
You'll come as Liz Lemon,
my chum.
Chum.
Okay, I like that.
And you'll be able to keep
your opinions to yourself?
Oh, good Lord, Lemon.
You just locked your mouth
and then swallowed the key.
It makes no earthly sense.
Shrimp.
30 ROCK
S07 Ep04 - Unwindulax
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
♪ Sunburn's starting to scab ♪
Jenna's crab idiots
won't shut up.
Why couldn't she have died
when that rabid dog bit her?
Oh, it wasn't rabid.
I just said that
so they'd have to put it down,
and then I'd be the star
of that dog-food commercial.
I had to walk an extra block
to get around
your stupid crabcatchers.
My doctor's have been very clear
about this, Jenna.
If I get moderate exercise,
I'm gonna die!
And I'm mad at your success,
but pretending
it's something else!
Okay, speaking of me,
how many crabcatchers
fiesta crab hats
would each of you like to buy,
at the unbelievable price
of 49.95?
Please. I've had a crab
on my head for free!
I'm lying.
The claws hold your cigarette
while you uncork a "brew-skye."
"Uncork a 'brew-skye'"?
Yeah, you know.
Ka-zap.
Blinky, blinky, blinky, blinky.
Those aren't even
the right noises.
Everyone knows you hate stuff
like this.
You're maybe the most
high-maintenance bitch
in Hollywood.
Maybe? Who's more?
Who is she?
Okay, cut this crap out,
and get those sunburned "D" -bags
out of the plaza.
Hey, no can will, Pete.
But have
an unwindulaxing day...
You medical office
before-pictures.
I've never even seen a crab.
I'm sorry.
I don't need some
Kenyan-born college professor
telling m
i didn't build my company.
Because I earned my trust fund
by always being polite
to grandfather.
Now, Donaghy, still over at NBC,
with all those communists
and homosexuals?
Reginald, I believe you're
thinking of the White House.
But not for long.
In two weeks,
we take this country back.
And no bureaucrat can force me
to subsidize female promiscuity
in the name of health care.
Are you okay, chum?
Michelle Obama's on steroids.
And this is studio 6-H,
home to TGS,
starring Tracy Jordan.
Oh, my God, it's Jenna.
Visor lady,
get a picture of me.
What do I...
Press a button?
No, it's different from every
other camera in the world.
God, I can't escape you people.
Whoa, chill out, brother.
It's beer o'clock somewhere.
You're a fraud!
And you look like a condom
that's been dropped
on the floor of a barbershop.
Are you all unwindulaxing?
This guy looks like he could use
a little "latitude" adjustment.
Will you sign my Cesarean scar?
Oh, ahh!
You moron!
Hey, just a party foul.
Exactly.
That's why I said,
"you more on."
Like, "pour more on me!"
- Whoo!
- Oh, yeah.
Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, yeah!
She can't be herself
in front of these losers.
She has to be "Island Jenna,"
which means...
We can mess with her.
We should go
to a pumpkin patch?
Pranksmen, activate.
Obama's bailout
would never have worked
if big business hadn't
heroically taken it.
But where's our parade?
That's idiotic.
- Lemon!
- No, sir.
You don't have enough shrimp
to buy my silence.
Also, you are out of shrimp.
You know better, Jack.
You all know better.
Except for maybe
the really inbred wasps.
You thank for mention gordeau!
You're hypocrites.
You believe
in the death penalty,
but it's okay
to kill animals for food?
I don't know
where I'm going with this yet.
Hang on.
Hang on!
My boyfriend and I
aren't married.
But we might have
a baby together anyway.
And I hope it's gay...
Male gay.
Because with the ladies,
it's too much hiking.
But homosexuality is
unnatural, right?
Then why are there
gay dolphins, people?
You heard me.
They make love
to their husband's blowholes.
Let's see that
in some science textbooks.
Oh, that's right.
The whole Texas board
of education thing
that I don't fully remember.
Teachers should get paid
a million dollars a year.
If birth control pills
fixed boners,
you would get them free
with your driver's license.
How do we know
that God isn't a tree?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Elizabeth Lemon.
And, uh, this is
what we're up against.
Four more years of a president
chosen by people like her.
She has an iPad subscription
to The New Yorker.
She vehemently opposes
the Ivory Trade,
despite the jobs it creates.
And in her apartment there is
a black-and-white photograph
where you can
almost see a breast.
It's an original Leonard Nimoy.
If we do not defeat Obama,
then people
like my little friend here
will destroy this country.
So add a zero to whatever
you were planning to give.
For Romney, for America.
For anyone but her.
What the hell, Jack?
I thought you said
I was your chum.
You are my chum.
The bait I throw in the water
to attract the big fish.
Damn it!
Second meaning.
♪ Pour margaritas
sunburn's starting to scab... ♪
Yeah.
Whoa.
What are you douche-compadres
doing here?
Well, Jenna, everyone knows
how you're always so chill.
So, of course,
you won't freak out
when you see that Cerie is
wearing that exact same shirt
as a dress.
The belt is a baby's necktie.
Also, I found a bunch
of your pre-nosejob headshots.
You'll sign them so
I can sell them online, right?
Of course.
'Cause who cares
what you look like.
All that counts
is what's inside...
Your blender.
I'm glad you feel that way.
'Cause I've always wanted
to give you a haircut.
Mm.
Yeah!
You... virgins, have no idea
who you're messing with.
Whoa, Jenna.
Unwindulax.
Oh, I'm not just Jenna anymore.
I am a God
to those crabcatchers,
and they will do whatever I say.
So what?
Oh, I'll tell you so what.
For one thing,
if you cross me or my army,
you will never set foot
in Florida again.
Because that's our capital.
But I'm judging Spike TV's
Miss Nude divorcee
in Tampa on Christmas Eve.
Oh.
And I was gonna visit
MGM studios.
The rides there capture
the thrills and chills
of the movies.
And it doesn't end there,
because my people
are everywhere.
If you ever want
to pick your ball color
at a putt-putt course,
or have your alligator
euthanized humanely,
or fly on delta,
you will back off,
or the crabcatchers will come
for you.
Just as soon as it's cool
for them to drive.
It's a gray hoodie.
It say's "who farted?"
On the back.
It's got a bunch of tampons
in the pocket.
I don't know what else
to tell you.
Lemon, there you are.
Did your girlfriend
even cancel?
Or was this more
Karl Rove trickery?
Sorry, but I needed you
to come, Lemon.
This luncheon is a fundraiser
for my personal super pac
"Americans
for an American America."
I needed to unite the room
around a common enemy.
And Ed Begley Jr.
wasn't available,
because the sail
on his car broke.
See, this is why 50.1%
of Americans hate Republicans.
Because you're
sneaky and cynical.
Cynical? I think I'm
the very opposite of cynical.
I'm doing everything I can
for my beliefs.
And I truly believe
that one rich person
can make a difference
in this country,
and a roomful of rich people
can... change the world.
Well, I also believe that one
person can make a difference.
With ideas.
That really is wonderful.
Harold, you have to hear this.
Lemon, say that again.
Ideas are more powerful
than money.
So what are you gonna do
with all this money, Jack?
Buy ad time?
'Cause I'm already
on TV every night,
with a little something
called TGS.
And we just got nominated for
a stage managers' guild award.
So you may have millions
of dollars, sir,
but America will hear
my two cents.
That's not what people want,
Lemon.
Least of all,
from their televisions.
They want their honeys boo boo
and their Sunday night feetball,
which is the plural of football.
Americans don't want to think.
That's why they need
men like me
to pick their presidents
for them.
Wow. Okay.
So, I guess, it's my words
versus your money.
And we'll see who can really
make a difference
in this election.
It's on, Donaghy.
May the best
gender non-specific person win.
Just leave the amount blank,
Harold.
Those are tampons.
Deal with it.
For God's sake,
some of us have jobs!
I've got a pile
of 1020-Gs up he
with no travel times on them,
and if I don't...
Listen up, nerds!
Tonight, TGS is
about to get real.
We've got 38 minutes
of air time...
An hour, if the bowling
tournament ends early...
And we are gonna use it
to get the message out there.
I don't know.
I think we've been
hitting Romney pretty hard.
I guess that's why
they call me Mitt.
"Baseball Mitt Romney"
and "Barack a llama"
aren't saying anything.
I want to make a difference.
We got to do something big,
something that'll go viral.
Like that otter
that looked just like Tracy.
Look, we've got the greatest
resource in the world
American celebrity.
We get some hot young actor...
Oh, my grandnephew Kellan lutz,
from Twilight, is visiting me.
He's in my office.
I have tolerated
your pathological lying
for six years.
If you speak again,
I will kill you.
Great-uncle?
Momma's baby is
out of "marsh-mal-lows."
Sweet grandnephew,
I've been warming
more "marsh-mal-lows" for you
in the pocket of my dungarees.
Okay, good job, lutz.
Gentlemen, token silent lady,
we have to spend
all of our wonderful money,
and help my hair-mentor,
Mitt Romney,
become the 11th legitimate
President of the United States.
Garrett, what does
the campaign need?
Well, as you know,
with pacs like this,
we're not allowed
to have direct contact
with candidates.
I'm kidding.
I'm Garrett Romney,
Mitt's my dad.
But here's the thing, Jack.
My brother-dad,
which is mormon for "dad,"
has more money
than he knows what to do with.
With all due respect, Garrett,
I don't think that's a thing.
Well, it's just,
at this point in the campaign,
for us, it's more
about ideas than cash.
Garrett, I would slap you
if I didn't know you were going
to get your own planet
when you die.
And until your father has
100% of the vote,
I think we can still make
a difference.
I mean, look how poorly we're
polling with African-Americans.
Jack, there's no amount
of money that could...
How dare you talk that way
in front of the pile.
Aw, thanks, Jack.
There is no problem
in the world
that can't be solved
by throwing money at it.
Now, let's change
some black minds.
Look what Jenna's goons
have done.
Pete's going insane.
The pranksmen are neutered.
We can't let her get away
with this.
Well, what can we do?
We're just
three nerdy white guys,
and she's got a whole army.
But what if she didn't?
I know what we should do.
Pumpkin patch?
Hi, I'm Hollywood liberal
Don Cheadle,
and I supp...
I support Mitt Romney.
Good, continue.
Barack Obama would
have you believe
that African-Americans are
better off under his leadership.
But I just got $10 million
for appearing in an ad
for Mitt Romney.
So ask yourselves,
brothers and sisters,
who's really got your back?
'Cause from where I'm standing,
Mitt Romney is a...
Oh, my dear...
Mitt Romney is a layup.
But don't just take it from me.
Take it from my good friend
the black transformer, jazz.
What's crackin', my homies?
Jazz gets down
with the rom-nizzle.
Oh, my God, does he really
talk like that in the movie?
Paid for by Americans
for an American America.
"Dy-no-mite."
Oh, for heaven's sakes.
That is garbage.
What are you talking about?
That was don cheadle and jazz,
your heroes.
Do you know
how expensive that was?
Okay, I get it.
Let me do some,
uh, community organizing.
Sir, I am
a deputized election monitor,
and when my supervisor Barbara
gets out of her aquarobics class,
she will be hearing about this,
if she's found the hearing aid
she thinks her roommate stole.
In five, four, three, two.
Listen up, America.
Thomas Jefferson once wrote...
The greatest danger
to American freedom...
Shut up!
Listen to the words!
Is a government
that ignores the constitution.
Take it off!
No.
Whoo!
This is so demoralizing!
In the past 24 hours,
I've spent millions of dollars.
I got B.E.T.
to let Mike Huckabee present
"Best Club Banger"
at the Hip-Hop Awards.
And yet we're still polling
at 0% among African-Americans.
If my money can't make
a difference,
I'm moving to Monaco.
- Jack, don't say that.
- I'm serious.
Over there, they solve
all their problems with money.
They use it to put out fires.
Ce feu m'ennuie.
Why should I even bother
to vote?
New York will go for Obama
even if I voted a hundred times.
Instead of my usual five.
Maybe you can make a difference
in a battleground state.
Oh, what's the point, Garrett?
You know what?
I'll tell you exactly how this
election is going to play out.
Hey. I just came in
to see how my friend's doing,
but obviously he went back into
his mouse hole, so, uh...
How are you?
Jack was right.
People don't want
an idea bomb dropped on them.
Don't give up.
That is not
the Lisa Loeb I know.
Why do I even vote?
New York's gonna go
for Obama anyway.
Maybe if I lived in Ohio,
I could make a difference.
Actually, no.
Ohio's definitely going
for Romney.
Yeah, you don't know
which way Ohio's going.
But I do.
Liz Lemon,
I've done stand-up
in every state in this country.
I know the people of America.
I know how they think.
I can tell you exactly how
this election is gonna play out.
Everyone knows Romney has
a vacation home
in New Hampshire.
What they don't know
is that he hunts humans
on that property.
New Hampshire goes to Obama.
Now, North Carolina goes
to Romney.
I worked there this summer,
and they are not on board with
a black man lecturing them.
I don't care if it's Obama
talking about health care
or me
talking about white butts.
They are different
than black butts.
Pennsylvania is Obama's.
The voting machines there
have become sentient.
And, for some reason,
they are strongly in favor
of gay marriage.
But we're not gonna win
Wisconsin.
I don't know why.
Ever since Tracy set fire
to Lambeau Field,
Wisconsinites are coming around
on the death penalty.
Wisconsin goes for Romney.
That just leaves...
Florida, the penis of America!
Florida...
The penis of America.
Pete!
We have a scheme
to destroy Jenna
and her army of cretins.
For the past seven years,
I've been compiling a supercut
of all of Jenna Maroney's
worst moments.
Security footage,
cell phone videos, rehearsals...
All her biggest diva freak-outs
are on this DVD.
When we put this online,
the crabcatchers will see
what a fraud Jenna is.
Someone get a P.A.
to feed me baby food.
Or I will drop a "D"
in the greenroom.
No, Pete! Why?
Last night, after the show...
I went to give them
a piece of my mind.
Enjoy, bro.
But before I could...
♪ Slow down
they gave me peace.
♪ Way down
♪ go down to the water
there were no 1020-Gs
down there.
No neck pain.
No fear.
Just easy livin'.
Something you mainlanders
wouldn't understand.
Pete, come on.
Pete's dead.
I'm Panama, now.
Now, like any penis,
Florida is very complicated.
The Cubans in the South...
Very conservative.
I had a lot of expensive cigars
put out on me
in Miami comedy clubs.
But central Florida
is dominated
by Jewish retirees,
serial killers,
and secretly gay
Disney princes,
all of whom love Obama.
Meanwhile...
In Northern Florida...
Huh.
The only crowds
I could never figure out
were in Northern Florida.
One week they're laughing at me,
the next week,
they're laughing at me.
According to this,
the electorate there
is impossible to predict.
It's a combination
of elderly shut-ins,
beach bums...
Bus passengers
who ran out of money...
Swamp people and pirates.
These people don't like
to be told what to do.
They just want
to sit on the beach and drink.
There motto is "unwindulax."
Unwindulax.
Oh, my God.
Morning, Crabcatchers.
You all unwindulaxing?
One person can make
a difference.
And that person is Jenna!
The next president
of the United States
will be chosen by...
Jenna Maroney.
To be continued...
Mr. Spider.
Ew, web in my mouth!
Next week, on 30 Rock...
Will Jenna Maroney choose the
next leader of the free world?
Will Jack or Liz manipulate her
into doing the thing
we just said?
Will Cerie ever wear
a piece of clothing
for its intended use?
Will Pete drop
the whole "Panama" thing,
and have
a totally different story?
Spoiler alert...
Yes.
Is Tracy actually a wereotter?
Will Kellan Lutz fill his tummy
with "marsh-mal-lows"?
Will the invisible murderer
who's in every scene
finally strike?
Will NBC's head of promotions
ever get that mousetrap
off his penis?
Will Kenneth finally defeat
his Nemesis, Mr. Spider?
Will your DVR cut this pro...
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
www.tvsubtitles.net