Download the subtitle at - http://srtsub.blogspot.com
Come on, Sergeant
Come on
Well We are fine
Anbtahoa, Anbtahoa
We are fine -
We lost, we lost -
Silence -
Where is he? -
"He should leave," Stevens -
Shut up, Anbtahoa -
Come on
Well, get ready
I ended up ordered -
As long as we together we will be okay -
"Come on," Raines -
"Raines" -
Come on -
Oh my God, you see them? -
Calm -
Do you see them? -
Quietly, quietly, Haya -
What will we do, O "Smifi"?
"Smifi"
Prepared
Hey
"Smifi"
Damn -
Oh my God -
Well
My companion
Direction at 11-
Gtona -
At 11-
Must go -
Shut up Shut up, boy -
I just watched and
Look after him
There before us -
It will not -
Direction at 11
They are out there
Take notice to the left
Attention boys
Let's go from here
We will go
Let us
Come on, come on
"We are lost you," Raines
We can not escape
We are lost -
Shut up -
Raise your arm, lift your weapon -
Well, listen -
We are 10 miles away
The beach
And all Snstql
Return to ship
And must maintain a resolute
Guys will not lose it now
We have succeeded so far and should be
To stay alert and cautious
Will get through this situation okay? -
Well -
Well I will driving?
This is our chance
Look at me
Tomorrow we will be Balhanh
Nansa beer
Do you play on
Drum there?
Yes -
Really? -
You deftly
"O" Smifi
Let's -
Come on -
Stopped
Applied individually and carefully -
The apostles -
Wait a moment on the -
We do not shoot Englishmen -
We damn
Happy to see you
Tenuis cigar one of you -
Identify yourself -
"Corporal" Bob Raines -
Taatbasit not with me, and your unit? -
Secret two o'clock my Battalion
West Kent, Mr.
Where the company commander? -
Died, sir -
Sergeant, and Battalion? -
Matt -
If you have a supply of Men
Did not eat for several days
Both
But I have a job
You, young man
Peace yourself to Sgt.
Battalion Sntmrkz here
Perhaps we sign these
Villains in an ambush
Ambush?
Do you know what is coming?
You do not Tnaakecna Corporal -
Let's go to Dinkirk -
Both Staatmrkazhon here
My order is to maintain on-line
Defense, and we will keep it
Orders and commands I have my orders -
And I made you something -
Any type of
You are the soldiers?
I wish you luck, but we
Going to Dinkirk
This is the last orders of the Sergeant -
Stzlon here and Stqatlon -
Otherwise, I will
You arrested
Have we finished fighting
For the time being, Mr.
Come on, boys
Sergeant? -
Corporal -
Hey, hey -
What do you do? -
Okhvadwa your weapons -
We are on one side -
The apostles
"Oh," Bob
Enough, live to fight day
Last and this nonsense?
They will not stop
Bastards now
If we stay here would not survive Believe me -
You have escaped -
I will work for a coward named
To execute
No more of these
Men
Navy Intelligence
"White Hall, London"
"Ajebe O" Sophie
Major How is it?
Just like any other officer
Royal Navy
Strong and solid
And very handsome
That officer is
Normal, in fact
Strange that
Major still
But I attributed this to growing up
His father, a famous botanist
Gap and all
Around the world
And is a special forces officer
Good morning since 1939
"Emma"
And angered the leader
In some things
Seem this
Familiar?
Ebsbs
Sebsbas
What does it mean
This?
Major
Enter
Wonderful
Jack "I am pleased to see you" -
Sir -
"Steiner"
"Thank you," Lindsey
Oznkma Tareftma -
No -
This is strange -
"Major, sorry," Jones -
"Lt." Mortensen
U.S. Marines
"Of course knew," Holbrooke
Erjokma Agelsa
U.S.?
Znntekm not interested
This war
I moved Norwige U.S.
Boston Balrabah to ten
Roosevelt "knows he will remain"
Far from that war a long time
"Lt." Mortensen
Agreed to help us
Informally -
SMH personal position -
I suppose you want some adventure -
"Jack" -
I think your position as a coach
Delayed slightly
I'm going to do
Operations?
Process
Gerendil
What do you know about RDF -
RDF? -
Defend someone -
And mean follow-term trend -
Are the control points
Distributed Bashoatina
Radar is not it? -
Yes, it is a technique may Terbhana war -
And the problem is that
Germans also possess
German aviation draws
Objectives for wireless signals
While the pilots remain very
Working compass and the stars
Raid on the Royal Air
Alhelmzhafn and in December 39
Failed to radar spotted dimension
75 miles from the beach German
Will build towers fucking
From Norway to southern France
German radar
Called Freer
This research center
Freer here
In the mountains, and we believe that if
Them new techniques are here
Admiral allowed me to
The establishment of a commando unit
Small group
And the process
And what I want from you is the infiltration
To one of these stations
Tzbbwa and chaos and
Accustomed safety information
We have a unique opportunity
Chances
And is not formally
Ouhdtk to the presence of
And I want to know
Your position on this
How much will I get a man? -
Leader and eight men and a specialist -
This process will not be
Unfortunately stemmed from officially sanctioned
And we have six
Weeks
Deprive us any longer
Of landing at night
I want any maps or
Pictures or information you have
Mortenson know the area? -
I know it's tough area -
We used to camp out small mountains -
Good -
You can help
Training team
I want these
Men
Corporal "Brightlnj" prisoner -
I do I need -
I understand, I will
My contacts
Major
They together
Comrades
Perhaps they need to
To cease
How is
Grace "?"
About to
Situation
Wonderful
My mother will not Taiedk
This is to our advantage
I do not want in London -
Yes, this is for the common good -
And always for
Damn good
Produced by left or right?
I forgot
To the left
What about work
As a coach?
Grace "I did not say"
I will stop all operations
I said that you will become a coach -
Grace "Please" -
Tsobei does not matter -
Jack "Please" -
How will the number of orphans
At the end of this war?
I want your child to
That knows you
Prison Dashwood
Military, Kent
You are here
For you are scum
I Khzltm
All
Yourselves and your units
And your king and your country
And I'm here to correct this
Oaidkm to track
Will not understand until you leave
What it means to be a honest person
And not a coward, or on the run
Or a thief or rapist
See you -
What his command? -
"Soldier" Raines -
Sir -
"The soldier" Raines
Officer struck
Disobeying orders
Do you complete a coward?
You are a disgrace
This error must be
I go back Loest Kent
Save this for malicious prosecution
Will worsen our relationship, my son
Son why I joined the Army
Do you want to see the world?
This was my choice
Or imprisonment, Dad
"The death of" Raines -
Raines, "You are accused of" -
These are not orders
Sir, Are you okay?
Brightlnj "You"
Convicted
Sergeant rise of the hill
Ran for an hour Let's quickly
Come on, come on
O villains -
Are you okay? -
And would you let him worm -
I can not breathe -
He does not need
The assistant is a distinct
Are not you, "Brightlnj"?
It's Commando
Is not it "Brightlnj"? -
Yes -
Come on now
Come, come, moved -
Go up here -
Arfa this trunk
If you are a commando?
Nay, but you also -
And how was it? -
I have read about you
And did not really know your presence
I thought this kind
Of publicity
We can get out
From here
Escape, for I have
Something
I am gone we can be
Escape and change your name
And become a commando and kill
Some Nazi fucks
Trust me
Be brave
"Major" Jones -
Colonel -
I received a call from the Guard
I am at your service
Good
If
Is there anything important today? -
Just the usual -
I came to pick up a Men's -
"Yes," Brightlnj -
I think with the Sergeant Major
Lead some exercises
Let's have moved
Come on
What do you think
You're an actor?
Do you think Corporal
This encouragement?
Damn you -
Sergeant Major -
Sir
Damn
Water
What did you do it?
"I do not quite" Mr.
Are you?
There is nothing wrong now
The invitation was assisted by
O fools, let him
What is your name? -
Bob Raines, "from West Kent, Sir" -
Follow me and picked up his bag
"Come on," Mr.
Do you take him? -
Yes -
Do you have a place
To someone else?
What to do
Here?
It is a misunderstanding, Mr. -
I did not want excuses -
Hit the officer and cheese
But I'm not a coward
That the officer
Is why
Please get me out -
Unfortunately not -
Well, the "master" Enter -
Thank you, Mr. -
Lower your head
Major sorry
On your foot
Good luck -
"Go back to the class O" Raines -
Please, I want to Major
That Mr. Asir Commando
Sorry, not this time -
Raines, "Go back to the class" -
Back to the class, my son -
I disabled here -
Sergeant Major Hla dominated
On your men? Today the whole embarrassing
Yes sir
Commandos of the quality of
Especially when they will find us out
"Raines"
"Barlabs" -
Disposal, officer -
Retracted, retracted
Trajau
Taatgaby not my son -
I do not Otgaby -
And Major Sikhrzina immediately -
No -
I think I Sakhrjh
Sergeant Major
Why do not you calm down
All now?
And Sakhrjk -
Do not try any silly -
Ride car
Enter the car you Major
Go back to the ranks of O homosexuals
Damn you
Children
We will lead you
We will kill you
I came out and
Found you
I want to become
Commando
Thus, and as -
I said I go out -
I know what I said -
Do Stnl? -
No -
You said your man is Tdberon -
Ndber is?
If you Znnta
Suggested to do this?
Why?
O foolish
You stupid eye
Must Oaidk
For this reason
If prepared me
Die
Do you subscribed
Battles?
In France before
Battle Dinkirk
And what do you think I saw? -
Bloody massacre -
Can you climb mountains? -
Like a monkey -
"Well, take care of" Mr.
That he suffered a drought
A few sips of water and FAQ -
Yes, Thank you, Mr. -
You do not after the commando -
No, sir -
If I fail in any part
Of this test
Will return to prison, I understand? -
Yes, sir -
Do you settle the matter with the police? -
I do not know -
If you pulled a weapon
Ali will die again
You are going to hell
I learn that?
To Uccilort, Highlands
Scotland
Leave what you are doing
And gathered
Hurry
Moved
Gathered quickly
Attention
Good morning
Dear Sirs
Pleasure to see you
Here
Continue O
Sgt.
Good morning
My boys
"Sergeant on my right," Gray -
Good Morning Men -
"Sergeant, and I," McKinsey
"You invite me to" Mac
Most of you know me and those who do not
Know me before the big surprise
"I do not stare me" Giebel -
Yes, Sergeant -
Sharp What a wonderful young man -
Thank you, Sergeant -
Brightlnj "and" Raines "spent"
Time with the military police
Gentlemen, after
Emptied of you
Staatmnon if you were at
Military police
Do not misunderstand my appreciation
Do not mess with me and never
Am I clear? -
Yes, Sergeant -
Do not hear you -
Coming Hfeltena require
Level of fitness
Christsdna by
"Jesse Owens"
And it is vital that we move
Quickly and invisibly as a team
Look for those in your neighborhood -
Look at him -
Aarafoh Staklon with
And Tnbarzon and Taatpulon with
And Statmnnouna
On your life
Boys
Injury to try FIRST
Nubatna hearty
O band
Moved
Come on you guys
"Well done, O" Giebel
Harpk still great
Moved
Lined
Formed description
Timthon "Go back to the class"
Retracted
Abide
Back to the class
This knife
Commando
Designed from this
And put you in mind
Why?
Because we are fighting Nlthm
We continue to call and lead
But only when
Therefore, we have
Likes to Tatadoa
This
And kept her with you
All the time
"Sergeant" Mac
Deployed -
Sir -
"Dobson" -
Yes, Sergeant -
To the target area, come on
Today, please
"Riley"
To the shooting range
"Mortensen"
Giebel, "the field"
Shooting
Brightlnj "the field"
Come, my son is not
Front of me the whole day
Take Action -
Yes -
Come on
"Raines"
This is what must Ststkhaddmonh
To learn the use of these
Well we will start
Pistol
Lugar 9 ms
Automatic
Preferred by officers and
You will see why
Two bullets in the body and
One in the head, any questions?
No, well
Mr. "Mortensen" Be Dafa
Good
"Riley"
Correction a good son, and if
Were not ugly to kiss
Your knowledge of the shooting? -
You, Sergeant -
I? Never -
"Master" Raines
If we hit the door
The fold I'll call you
Sorry my sergeant
This was
Both sides of the weak
"Raines"
Where did you learn proficiency
Shooting?
Bmnazlat cowboy -
Mnazlat cowboy? -
"We have a" Jesse James
Here is not it?
Mr. "Raines" because you're a person
"Mr Popular" Raines
I think you deserve
Jogging is not it?
Sergeant is not it, "Gray"? -
Placed over your head, brown -
Over your head, son
Follow me, come on
Silence
Is this my painful, "Raines"? -
Yes, Sergeant -
Is this a painful, son? -
My pain, "Raines" is
Weakness leaving your body
Sir
Stop
What do you think you
You active?
System
Is something that is clear
You're put off by it
Sir -
Hist -
I speak, I mean what
Is your problem?
Nothing I'm sorry -
Sorry?, Sorry -
So it looks
Sad
What sermons you? Were not
Thpk your mother?
Is this the reason?
Is this a disappointment?
That's why I became a troublemaker? -
This will not happen again, Sir -
You're right
Will not be repeated
Because I Saaidk -
No -
No, sir -
Give me a reason not to get you back -
I -
Why you? -
Because you
I will learn and was done here
More than they have done in my life
Raines, "You did not complete"
Anything after
One more chance
Please
How your knowledge in
The next few days
Will determine what to do
The rest of your life
"It's my hand," Raines -
Thanks -
"Sergeant," Gray -
Thank you, Mr. -
Thank you, sir -
"Over my head," Raines -
Guys seems
Reload they
I lecture young
After five minutes
Come on
Let us
"O" Raines
Let us by
Mr. "Raines" out
If allowed
What's up my sergeant? -
Wait here, young man -
I fully Sergeant -
Come on -
Thread
Well guys finished
Of Sayakm to memorize
How are you doing
Dear soldier?
If
Are you a prisoner
Fugitive?
Can not you talk? -
Yes, sir -
I was, I did
That Mr.
I want you back
This chaos
The Leader in White Hall
Want your execution
Sorry Sir -
If we are in normal conditions -
Major, "Jones" was tried
And you would kill you
But at a time
Unusual
"And Major" Jones
An extraordinary leader
You are fortunate to have convinced me
Bbakaúk in this process
Thank you, Mr. -
Do not thank me -
I want to thank you -
No -
I prefer not to write
Notes
Gentlemen, we Sntgm
In our destiny
Or at least that's what
We must do
www.tvsubtitles.net