we stopped
oh. we're out of gas.
yeah. good idea.
what's up with this night? why is it so night?
mm-mm. what are you so excited about, the what?
the where?
oh. star circle.
circle of stars.
circle of uh...roundness.
oh. damn my head. i need some aspirin.
man this web sucks my ass! d'ya hear me? hey, hey you. whatever. hey. you know me don't ya? i know you do.
oh good, sqaure is here. hi square.
lick, it, oval.
what's your square pleasure?
you probably don't have it. but it's rusianik chyd. it's an old drink of kings of old.
haha.
kings of old richness old.
i got it, but can you afford it?
ah.
you stupid bobquart.
i'm sorry, did you just try to call me a bobquart?
you? did i? i did. i think you look like a purple wafer.
oh. really?
what i'm actually thinking, and please take this the wrong way as far up your hole as you can, is that your gunkookshlinger is the size of a fortmizer's reticulous. oooh kablamo!
wrong attitude partner.  it doesn't work too well when it's not real.
you shut up too.
what's up dudicon? ok letsa, i'm gonna leave, let's leave and we'll start this over ok, hold on.
yo dudicon! was it better that time? did you believe me?
and he's down.
he's a rather good shot don't you think?
yes he is.
he was the highest marksman in the class
well, i'll be.
i'll bet you he could probably hit a mite from 1000 yards out in high wind.
if uh...the wind is high then it wouldn't disrupt his shot would it? so what's the point of adding that kind of wind...to it?
i was refering to a poor wind that would be low, but high in speed and rich money...richness.
the kind of money speed that would richly affect a bullet's wealthy trajectory.
oh.
you got some uh... neat stuff here.
i know it's totally stolen, hahaha.
yeah but...
stole it, mm-hmm, hahaha
are they on the, on the way, on it, are they on the way, on the way?
on it. the way. hahaha.
uh...
uhh...
hahahaha, whoa.
did you bring the leg?
did you, what are you,am i, huh?  was i supposed to?
i'll be your krueger and you can be my nancy girl.
oh, hahaha.  what, he got it.
oh...i'll be your fred safford.
it was just like, muff dude, you better ditch that muzzle loader and get a damn ar, before that thing comes crashing through the woods.
yeah, but he wouldn't listen. son of a bitch ran off with muff in his damn mouth.
found him three days later down by the river. he seemed okay at first, but, he wasn't okay if you know what i mean.
man spider, then he went crazy. runnin around screaming how he was gonna quit Q109 and all that stuff, how they're out to get him.
like they were gonna come get him in the night or somethin weird like that.
okay. we're here.
m-eye leg hurts.
i know, we're gonna, we're gonna get you a new one.  this must be the leg shop.
w-eye would a hand cut off m-eye leg?
maybe so we would come here.  so, here we are...here.
ah fitz.  i see you brought the eye
i see, that you did see, that i brought the eye.
yo mouse, remember that drink you done owe me?
i am so in to doing whatever you're doing.
yeah yeah yeah, we both into drinkin man.  we drinkers.
what are we drinking?
man, pour out a little liquor.
everybody... gimme the drinks.
come with me.
to where?
to my hospital.  but first, you gotta look at this.
haha, what is it?
twin eyeballs.
they match.
i'm starving.
how do you like my car?
it's okay...if you're poor.
30,000 horsepower.  30k hp.
30,000-
i heard you the first time.
you will hear me every the time.
just because liquor's dead doesn't mean you can just roll this bitch all over town with the freedoms.
yes it does........i'm black now.
that is just like the poor.
uh, yeah. why don't you just uh...sink back into that leather, and hush. i would turn the stereo on but it would kill you.
oh...i love me some cookies.
mmm. just a small taste of my mighty blackness.
he's comin to.
hand me those things.
what, what should we do now?
these things?
no, no no.
what things?  these things?
give me that cold thing.
um...
give me that thing that makes everything cold.
why don't i, i don't i don't know what any of these things are, they're your things.
give me those things.
oh, those, those, these things
what's that, is that your blood?
come on man, what is this crap? thought we were gettin to know each other.
i...i'm tore up in this mother man. man, man don't.
trigga!
i am tore up.
oh... dude
who's, who's that? i, i...
okay.  you get it?
hey, you go get it man? better go get it before i crack.
uh, hold on. let's start over. you get it.
man, you go get it. don't make me put my finger on the trigger man.
no i'll get it, i'll get it, i'll get it, okay?...you got it?
man.
www.tvsubtitles.net