Out of my way, I'm drunk as hell, I'll blow your ass away like ringin' a bell, Pedal to the floor and the whiskey's flowin'
I gotta porn shoot, I gotta get goin', You don't understand. He don't give a damn, 12 oz. Mouse, 12 oz. Mouse
crankin' up the jams and singin' along, what's wrong is right, what's right is wrong, makin' out on ya at the end of the bar
blackin' out and pickin' up another scar, He don't give a damn, You don't understand, 12 oz. Mouse, 12 oz. Mouse
Jet car rollin' all night long, car full of bitches and a brand new bong, burgle crazy into the night, what's right is wrong, what's wrong is right
doin' all things and considering no one, i got a porn shoot, i gotta get goin', you don't understand, he don't give a damn, 12 oz. Mouse, 12 oz. Mouse
doin' all things and considering no one, i got a porn shoot, i gotta get goin', you don't understand, there's no effin' plan, 12 oz. Mouse, 12 oz. Mouse
skillet! here's the bowl, now fill it! whaddya mean shark's listening? far out.
You utter in a screaming tone, It's your pelagic right to roam, The entire worldy realm alone, Eyes cry a brackish brine
Another day, another doller, On terra firma I stand taller, Yet I remain in squamal squalor, Slipping down the bottom line
You stay in motion, My soul is your ocean, Forever will never concern me
Time is fleeting, Separating, meeting, Desperate isolation engulfs me
Amputation emulation lorenzini
Uuh... look at this one. That one looks nice too.
It feels like i'm staring at thousands of shoes.
Seriously, who's got some shoes?
Does anybody work here?  Do I... do I work here?  'Scuse me, me.  Could I get some hats?
No.
I am such a dick.
Seriously, could I, uh, could I try some shoes on? My head is freezing. Enough of this crap.
I said gimme the shoes, or this place is goin' up.
Ahh. Can I smoke this in here?
Too late!
What?
Wow.  Who did that, me? Nice! I wish the police would come, 'cause now I'm a fireman.
I don't have any water.
That doesn't seem to be working. Oh. God, I wish I could help.
It's been fun being a cop.
www.tvsubtitles.net