there's enough guns down here to take out a town about.... well about this size.
radio. clock radio. and a map. a map radio with a clock. what does that mean?
"he's my homin dog. got a sense of...radar and quasnit."
the music knows we're down here.
grab every gun. but leave those.
come on baby, come on baby. yeah. come on baby. crank it up. oh come on baby. why are you not doing it?
i think this piece overheated.
i think you should shut up.
keep trying, maybe you'll get it this time.
come on sweetheart
ha, oh look it didn't start again.
come on baby.
your car sucks. maybe if i throw money at it, it will start.
yeah uh...are you a mechanic? cuz i'm not. but still shut up.
i should have expected this from your poor ass.
i'm trying to start the car.
where are you going?
to buy a harmonica... a very rich harmonica.
so you're just gonna leave? not cool.
i just feel ever so inclined to buy a harmonica... made of gold... encrusted in diamonds... then dipped in gold... and rolled around in more diamonds.
it's deadly to vampires you know? or is it werewolves? i forget which, they're both poor.
you are not helping this situation.
alright okay, this is the one, this is the one. 50th times a charm.
would you please start car?
look at all those harmonicas. hmm. hmm.
come on, i know you want to. start for me, i'm touching your little button
I equate harmonicas to the blues.... and the blues to the poor, but I still want one.
i had no idea there would be this many harmonicas.
come on, come on. i know you want to. for the love of me turn on.
alright, now okay, now we're close. i can feel that. this is it. this is the one. you barely piece of suckass car.
i could afford to buy all these, but i just want one. the best one.
please start. you're making a fool of me. i don't even know what i'm hearing.
i don't even know how to play a harmonica.... but I want one
ah, okay, i'm just gonna barely touch the key, no no, not yet. just ease into it. just lightly rubbing the key with my fin. i'm just gonna barely touch the key, you won't even know i'm doing it. just lightly caressing the key, and start!
come on, why are you not doing it? come on. come on. perfect, that's great.
oh look, i'm back.
did you buy a harmonica?
did you get the car started?
did you get your harmonica started?
www.tvsubtitles.net