i have these...crazy dreams.
what are the dreams about?
they're about...the end. with fragments of the beginning. and there's meat.
am, am i in them?
they're crazy.
are they episodic or is it just one long...
what's that supposed to mean, episodic?
uh, are they segmented or-
why the hell would you think they're segmented?
i'm not saying they are. they're, they're your dreams
yes, they are my dreams. they're mine. for my head.
well then only you would know how to describe them.
that's what i'm tryin to do but it seems like you keep trying to do it for me.
do what?
describe the dreams
well...
then describe them
describe what?
the dreams.
what dreams?
uh, the dreams your having or not having them now..suddenly.
you trying to make me have them, for me?
i'm just here to help you. if you don't want my help, i'll seek other advice.
i think you should know when to stop helping me.
i'm never finished helping everybody.
I can't be finished.
look at this
beer.
we're runnin out of time.
you want some asprind?
do, i, do i need to have some asprind?
it's good asprind. it comes from asprindland.
where's that?
t's uh...it's over the hill.
which one, which hill?
that, that big one.
hand me that asprind.
hand me the asprind some more.
hand me that asprind to me, some more.
it's getting closer.
what do you want to do?
what did you say?
what, what'd i say?
you said kill em all.
i did?
yeah, with your own little mouth.
no way.
you did, you said kill them all. and somethin' about roostre.
wow.
with your own mouth.
how do i know that you know that my mouth is my own?
hey um...
take some asprind.
if i take, then i took it.
yeah, you make a good point.
how many did i have?
how many do you want?
some...enough.
enough for what?
enough to get home.
home for what?
dinner.
um...
this could be your dinner.
i said, what are we gonna do, they're coming!
you, chill out. i'm not gonna hurt him.
i'm saving him.
yah!
yeah man, you're right, you're right. it is crazy man i got this one hand and all that and i grow these corndogs and all that but, but listen. you know that q109 stuff, that stuff's real.
but q109 isn't a station.
oh, you don't say huh? then what, what do you think it is?
look, beer.
901q. that's line code for...xenomorphentation.
you're gettin it, very smart.
arachnid xenomorphentation.
and that's where the dog went.
it was added to the report chart but, but right before...
before what man?
before i...do this
watch.
and who added it to the report chart?
you told me it was comin bro. you told me to build the robots, and you told me how to do it. synthetic carbo-polymers got em through man. they got em through mouse. they got through, and we're gonna get out.
what do you mean, gonna get out?
the robots.
the what-bots?
you know what i'm talkin about. we made them
why would we make robots?
why are you climbing the clothes closet?
Now i'm a clothes climber.
if i didn't have this many clothes, i won't be able to climb up to this.
What is that there behind that thing there?
-Some kind of lock. -A what? -it's a lock -Is it? -A lock...
-Lock -It? ...
the hell was that?
um.. that... that was amalockh.
ama-what?
amalockhhh.
what's he do?
he...he kills us.... he kills us all.
well... let's kill him back.
keep thinking about all this beer.
www.tvsubtitles.net