whoa, hey there. now that, is a mean lookin pair of pants, if i've ever seen such a thing. hell yeah. i am on fire, sire. yah!!!!
hellll yeah!!!
oh that's nice. what is it? fake?
it's a one gauge.
what's the damage on that?
it'll blow your head into vapor, while it demoleculizes your bones, that's how fake it is.
yeah uh, that's great. what's that like a indian burn kind of thing?
my grandfather gave it to me after the meat wars. he was in em.
well then your grandfather was a grunt. and probably made zilch. i pity his family...i'd cease to care.
he did what he had to do, there's no shame in that.
i moved south. mummy told them i had, club foot.
mmm, well pusses say what pusses say. for pusses sake.
say what you will, money gets you everything. inculding happiness. but especially friends.
the one who says the most says the least.. especially the one next to me.
where are we now, the bible or something? the bible never made money. it's poor. it's full of poor people.
load me.
do you shoot your mother with that gun?
ka-kow
you promised you would quit.
i know, but i can't quit.
why not?
just because if i quit, they'll kill me. and then they'll come and kill you.
look the car is packed, let's leave here tonight. let's leave before they come back.
but they've already sent the tie, and i put it to my flesh.
we can be miles from here within the hour.
okay, you're right. let me go get...my skates.
i told you i smelled fuel. i'm big into oil. i own lots of it and i know what it smells like. it's rich smelling. the smell itself spawns property and mansions.
I'm gonna blow him away, all the way... away.
If you can find him... you barley find your ass to clean it.
Do it, be somebody.... be somebody for the great red one.
a b c d e...b b a...
what the guh?
i think they've lost it. their program that is. they're all going out of their minds.
make that not happen.
i'm tired of doing stuff for you. am i getting paid?
it...wasn't supposed to end this way.
this is getting out of hand...hand being the operative word here.
finger do, finger won't. finger will, finger don't.
what's that supposed to mean, that backward slow talk.
it means you'll never find him.
well i got the bug on it, so shut up and reload me.
ah it's just a bug. everybody go back to sleep. we need to rest for one more day.
we'll need more meat to sleep.
that's why i made these.
ah, we knew you were smart.
your dreams from the meat. uh, is that uh, is that happenin to you guys?
dreams, shut em out.
that's what's so interesting about them. i, i can't. i can't.
you tried little guy. you tried the hardest.
where does the firetruck go, go, go...where does the firetruck go, go, go...
and when does the hand know, know, know...and when does the hand know, know, know.
this is the best smelling flower that i have ever smelled. this is also the best smelling flower that i have ever picked.
eat the flower.
woman don't eat flowers.
eat it for him.
there is no him.
there's about to be. eat it.
straight a's on this one.
mmm, too late for you. i got this one.
what is that, fire? nobody cares about your fire. wow. don't do fire.
wow, now all we gotta do is wait boy. hand's out there somewhere. he's my homin hand.
i'm inside an elevator. buttons
...hahaha...buttons! muaaa!!!! ahhh, what a suck song! suck, suck, suck...!
yeah, down! excellent!
what kind...who drank all this liquor? um...me, haha. stupid question me.
haha, sorry bro.
damn cuz. is that your jibba libba hub-bub? cuz you know i don't need that man.
huh. i thought you were an alien.
damn bub, cool that smoke wagon before i shove it up your ass so far you'll be kissin that barrel til christmas.
christmas, uh...oh man christmas is cool.
well get a tinsel of this man.
i shot this on the street ten minutes ago, with my new camera man. check it out, it's got zoom, un-zoom, de-zoom, yo mama-zoom, zoom zoom in the boom boom, grandmama zoom, it's got it all man.
you know what that means?
it means my album done come out, and i need to go record for it.
haha, it means that the code is unstable. and it's cloning itself in a bad way. and that's never good.
what's that jimbo ka-nimbo mean man?
what, what's the jimbo, ka-nimbo? haha, golden joe! never... stop... drinking. ha...it's almost over.
liquor, hey, shh, get up. hey, get up. listen. someone's here.
i hear it. my ears told me. my brain listens to my ears.
shh, listen.
uhhh...uhhh!!! i don't know what to do man.
how am i gonna make the records? how am i gonna make the records?
it's getting closer.
all weapons cock!
www.tvsubtitles.net