Meep. Meep-mop. Meep. Meep-mop.
Meep. Meep-mop.
There he goes.
There... who goes?
He. Shark. He's blowing everything up.
Why would he blow everything up?
So it'll end in fire. Flames. Hot-heaty-hot. You know, fire?
What about my friends? They're out there.
Oh, those guys? He's probably eaten them all by now. It reads
and the Shark shall eat every creature who is friends of the green one. But there's Amalockh. He's a mean bitch.
Hey! Who's up there?
What else does it read?
I'll tell you, but we've got to get handbrain to Roostre, or we may never have a chance.
Meep. Meep-mop.
Meep. Meep.
Well, if it ain't the motley mots.
What's up, Roos-tre?
I remember you. You hit me in the head.
Yeah, but, you know, I had a reason.
Which one?
This one. This here one.
Meep. Meep-mop. Meep. Meep-mop. Meep. Meep-mop.
What the hell's this shibullet?
Mmm. Lose something?
Hey, man. Those are my X-rays.
No, not your X-rays. Look.
Meep. Meep-mop. Meep. Meep-mop.
Those are my X-rays.
What's wrong with him?
It's the language. It's giving out. And for reasons sooner on him. For today.
Linguas him out whole the other?
Ogelub renub the ghee?
Nix yurapict.
Produpt means artollah.
Newdmatschstam. Newdmatschstam.
Ow. Dude. You, my friend, have a totally cool car. But I've got a louder stereo. You know one that BMMM! Thumps.
What am I for here now? What did I talk? What here f-for now... Am I, what here? What, what here, heh, here for now what to...
Uncool. No one. Uncool. No one. Nobody. Uncool. Nobody controls me. Yeah.
One of the worst things that could possibly ever happen to someone is the inability to communicate.
Oh, oh help me. Help me, God. Help me.
EYE think that's mean.
Well, I think it's very funny. See that guy.
He's a teddy bear. But they won't ever know it. We have the time under control, don't we?
He always has the same time.
When he stands that still, then yes. It's exactly the same.
What if it were to move?
What if what moves, you sack?
What if it becomes 2:23? What if the tEYEme changes?
How much would you give to control a lifetime of time in a frozen segment of timelessness? Trillions of molecules, making up lifeforms in space.
I miss mEYE dad. He was coming to pick me up at school.
You have no idea how long you've been here. Your dad is long gone by now.
Not if tEYEme stands still. If tEYEme stands still, then EYE am still in line, waiting for him to pick me up. I have a lot of homework due the next day.
Not if I can help it.
What do you mean you're out of the gas? Well, I have armies coming, so this is uncool. Let's figure it out.
Clock shop.
That was easy.
Woah, I wonder what time it is. Uh, I think it's beer time. That's what methinks.
You... take care... of this.
Where... are you... going?
To save... my... friends.
They're... probably... dead... by now.
If that flower reaches the right person, we're all dead, and that'll be a great disappointment to me and all that me has become me.
Us. I know it's us, and that's what I meant to say. You know I meant to say that. You always know what I mean to say, cause you say it.
Nerg optima zopt rem.
Dodj beoj.
Nominye.
In here, dude!
Cordometze.
Woah bro, put these on.
What is this?
It's anti-anti-language gas. I made it from propane.
Well, right now we need to kill that Shark.
Right now bro him? It's pretty good gas.
We need to find a way in.
Dude, we're safe in here. Totally safe.
Not with those things outside.
Airvent.
Wait. Check this out.
They hate that. But I love it.
Oh, go on. You probably haven't had a good meal in who knows how long.
Now those are some good juices, aren't they?
How come we can talk right? Suddenly.
They must be outta gas. Let me see that hook.
Man, I sure have missed that hand.
You got a hacksaw or something? A biv knife?
Son of a bitch took it off in the middle of the night, right after I built this sucker.
I'll just have to use drunken karate. Hey, what's that over here?
What?
Heeya!
Holy crap!
Hold on...
Look at that. It works.
Oh yeah, that's right. That's what I'm talking about now, boy.
Now get 'er going. We're running out of no time.
Wake up now, boy. It be a killing time.
Wait!
What?
Oo. Nevermind.
www.tvsubtitles.net