The Americans have been
able to shut down
most of the reactors.
I'm going to have to manage
the override personally,
make sure those six
meltdown on schedule.
Is there anything I can do?
Take care of your mess.
I give you my word,
my wife and son will be dead
by the end of this day.
I'm not afraid of Father.
You should be.
He tried to kill me
and then he did this to you.
You're going to need to set
things up on your end.
All right, what do I do?
Divert suspicion.
Someone inside CTU
is leaking information
to someone
on the outside.
Ms. Driscoll, what's going on?
You're under arrest, Gavin.
For what?
Passing classified information.
Thousands of people's lives
are at stake.
Where are the people
who control the override?
I swear, I don't know anything.
Yeah?
DRISCOLL:
We've got a match, Jack.
His name is Henry Powell.
He's a computer consultant,
that used to work
for McLennen-Forster.
They're the defense contractors
that designed
the override devices
controlling the power plants.
You're going to fly
me out of here.
Drop the weapon now!
Now!
Put him in the back.
( gunshot )
He's dead, Jack.
Damn it!
You've got the wrong person.
Sarah's not guilty of anything.
It's Maryanne Taylor.
( alarm blaring )
( groans )
You're under arrest.
( car alarms blaring )
Excuse me, Curtis.
Not now.
Coordinate that with NRC
and copy me on 6-0-B. Bye.
I warned you about her.
What are you talking about?
Maryanne Taylor.
I told you she was trouble
and it was a mistake to
let her work here. No.
You told me that you weren't
comfortable working with her.
You didn't tell me
you were having a relationship
with a corporate spy.
How could I have possibly
known that, Erin?
Don't play that card with me.
Fine, then don't walk in here
with an I-told-you-so attitude.
Because now we both have
to deal with this.
You mean division?
That's right.
They're going to want
a complete timeline.
Everything from how Maryanne
got through the front door,
down to
the high-security files
that she was able to access
in a very short
period of time.
Can we have a conversation
off book?
Go ahead.
There's no point in either of us
compromising our authority
in the eyes of division.
Agree or disagree?
Agreed.
Maryanne did an excellent job
in establishing her credentials.
All we need to do
is leave out some of the details
in how she managed
to leverage
her way in here.
I don't like anyone
holding something over me.
Neither do I.
How long will it take you
to adjust the files?
Two minutes.
I'll call division at 5:00.
Explain to me how this mole-
Maryanne Taylor-
was able to infiltrate CTU.
We're still investigating,
Mr. President.
Who does she work for?
We don't know.
Find out.
We will, as soon as she
regains consciousness.
She's being treated
here in the clinic.
Treated for what?
An attempt on her life.
Who tried to kill her?
We don't know that either.
But whoever it was,
they're more than likely
connected
with the theft
of the override.
Jim, we need to find
that override now.
What's the latest
from the NRC?
They just reported
the San Gabriel Island reactor
is about to go critical.
What's the timeframe?
A meltdown within the hour.
We started evacuating
the San Gabriel zone.
The population affected
is less than 100,000.
Hopefully most of them
are already on the move.
All right.
Expedite the process
as much as you can.
Yes, sir.
( phone ringing )
DRISCOLL:
Jack?
Erin, Powell's dead.
He was hit by a sniper as soon
as we took him into custody.
Get anything from him
before he was killed?
No, but I managed
to get the last ten calls
he made off his cell phone.
He called two numbers
repeatedly.
Through caller ID,
we traced one of them
to Maryanne Taylor.
Powell was working
with Maryanne?
Apparently.
What about
this other number?
Hold on.
I'm going to need you
to trace it through CTU.
Okay, go ahead.
818-555-0539.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I've got an ID.
I'll be standing by.
Edgar, I need you to run
a locate on this number.
( keyboard keys clattering )
It's a cellular account.
Can you trace the location?
I need to ping the number.
How?
It needs to ring
at least four times
before I can triangulate
the coordinates.
Jameson can have me set up
in a couple of minutes.
WOMAN:
Who is it?
Navi.
Navi?
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for Dina.
Well, Dina's not here.
Why would she be?
She hasn't called you
in the last hour?
No. What's
going on, Navi?
Why are you blocking the door?
I'm not.
Let me in.
I told you,
she's not here.
You're lying.
You're hiding her.
No, I'm not. Navi, no.
You have no right to come
in here like this!
She is not here.
Go. Look.
That is my bedroom.
You can't go in there.
What the hell is going on here?
Nothing, it's okay.
Navi, please.
Please, go.
Look, pal, this is none
of your business, all right?
So why don't you hike it on out
of here? Please, don't interfere.
You can either walk
out of here
or I'm going
to throw you out.
I said, go!
( gun cocking )
No, Navi, please, no.
Navi, don't, please.
Get back inside.
Navi.
Don't tell my husband.
I beg of you.
You disgust me.
Navi.
( door slams )
Dina's not here.
What about the hospitals?
MAN:
Nothing so far.
Keep looking.
( phone rings )
Is it your father?
I can't tell.
Don't answer it.
( phone continues ringing )
We got it.
Where?
A hotel in Chatsworth.
Download the coordinates
to Jack's PDA.
Here's our backup.
( phone rings )
Yeah.
DRISCOLL:
We traced the call
to a fixed location.
We're sending it to you now.
Hold on a second.
Okay, I got it.
We're less than ten minutes out.
I'll have a tactical team
in place
by the time you get there.
Thank you.
The body is over there
by my car.
He was taken out by a sniper
from the north roof.
I want you to take
your photographs
and get the body back
to CTU as fast as possible.
Come on, Tony, we've got to go.
Wait, Jack.
Look, uh, I think
I'm done here today.
What are you talking about?
CTU backup's here.
You don't need me anymore.
I need you to see
this through with me.
I appreciate
the sentiment, Jack,
but you don't have
to prop up my ego.
Tony, this isn't about you.
If we don't find
the override device
within an hour,
we're going to have six
major nuclear disasters.
So please, get in
the car. Let's go.
Mom, we've got
to get you some help.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Your father shot me, not you.
Because you were trying
to stop him from killing me.
Everything that's
happening today,
what we've all been
fighting to achieve,
it's more important to him
than anything
or anyone.
But not to you.
M om?
I need to get you
something for the pain.
I'll be fine.
I just need to rest.
I can get it from Nasim.
No.
The hospital he works at
is right near here.
I'll be right back.
Nasim doesn't know why
we were really living here.
Mom, he's your brother.
I'll tell him you need it
and nothing else.
I promise.
I'll be right back.
Just hurry.
I will.
Mr. Secretary,
we have a meltdown.
The San Gabriel Island
reactor has just gone critical.
The core material
is now airborne.
I thought we had more time.
Ms. Driscoll, I have Derrick
Ross with the engineer
at San Gabriel Island
on with the NRC.
One of their generators
exploded,
it cooked their com lines,
so the feed is unstable.
We may only have a few seconds.
Patch us in.
What's going on?
We've had a meltdown
on San Gabriel Island.
( garbled transmission )
All attempts to contain
the core have failed.
Right now my men are trying
to bypass the reactor trip,
but that's not working either.
Mr. Rosner,
this is Erin Driscoll from CTU.
Can you hear me?
Yes, ma'am, I can.
I'm here with Secretary
of Defense James Heller.
What are your radiation levels?
We're at 500 rem right now.
That's 10,000 times
the dose of an X ray.
At this rem rate,
the radiation will continue
getting stronger and will spill
into the atmosphere
until the core
has exhausted itself.
Son, you've done
everything you can,
now get the hell
out of there.
Evacuating won't make
any difference, sir.
We've already been exposed.
We lost them.
Have we analyzed
the radiation
cloud's movement?
We're still waiting
for NGS
to get a weather
satellite for us.
Get on the phone
and have them expedite it.
I will, as soon
as I'm done rerouting these
evacuation instructions.
Can't someone
else do that?
No, sir, I'm short of manpower.
A government spokesman
has just confirmed
that the nuclear reactor
at San Gabriel Island
is in full meltdown.
Emergency personnel are on site
attempting to rescue workers
exposed to radiation.
Several people
have been taken...
You're not listening to me.
I've been trying
to get through to a number
in the San Gabriel
evacuation zone for ten minutes.
I need you to link me in to
access the emergency bandwidth,
and I need you to do it now.
All right, standby.
Thank you.
If you are on the road
or awaiting instructions...
( phone rings )
...here are some items
you and your family might need.
WOMAN:
Hello?
EDGAR:
Mom.
Oh, hello, Edgar.
Have you seen the news?
Yes, I'm watching
it now.
Then why haven't
you evacuated by now?
What are you still
doing home?
You know I don't
have a car.
Where's Margaret?
Well, I've tried
to get hold of her,
but the lines
are all busy.
I'm surprised you got through.
What about one
of your neighbors?
Can't you get a ride
from one of them?
No. By the time I got outside
they were all gone.
Mom, listen to me.
I'm going to make some calls.
I'm going to get someone there
to help you, okay?
I want you to sit by the phone
and wait for my call.
Can you do that?
Yes, I don't really have
a choice.
I'll call you back, okay?
Okay, honey. Bye.
No, we delegated
that whole situation
to Murphy's group, sir.
HELLER: I'm not interested
in who got it wrong.
We don't have the luxury
of miscommunications.
I'm assigning someone
from my office
to coordinate between the State
Police and the National Guard.
Set up the conference call
in ten minutes.
Thank you all.
Are you okay?
Yeah. How are you
holding up?
Considering the situation
we're in...
I'm doing fine.
The truth of the matter is,
we do not have the manpower
to handle this mess.
Tell me what I can do.
I've prioritized
evacuation protocol,
but I need someone
to keep the State Police
and the National Guard from
bumping in to each other.
All right.
I'll stop the Guard
at the 75th mile marker
and let the police
take over from there.
That'll maximize room
for civilian traffic.
I wish we had
some other way
to get those people
out of there.
There's nowhere else
to route them.
Jack has got to find
the override
before the rest of these
reactors go critical.
Hey, Jack.
Good to have you
in the field again.
Thanks, Lee.
You remember Tony Almeida?
Yeah.
I don't know
what he's doing here, though.
I want him here.
LEE: He's not authorized
to be in the field.
I'm going through
that door first.
I want him there
to back me up.
Fine.
Get another vest.
You got a visual on the suspect?
We've got a fiber optic
camera inside the room.
According to the manager,
we're grabbing a mid-40s
female and a teenage male.
Possibly mother and son,
both Middle-Eastern.
Okay, we need
the suspects alive.
They're no good to us dead.
I've been briefed.
Let's go.
Agent Castle, we've got
a visual on the woman.
What about the kid?
I haven't seen him yet.
We got to go, now.
You ready?
Go.
Don't move!
Drop the weapon!
( gunshot )
Where is the override?
Tell me who's got it!
Tell me!
( screams )
Now!
Agent Castle!
Agent Castle, stand down!
Agent Castle,
please stand down!
Get off her!
We've got to get
her to talk.
She's going to go
into shock
before she does.
Just relax!
Agent Castle, step outside now!
I want her prints
and photographs.
Send them over
to CTU immediately.
He has no right
to give me orders.
Hey, come here.
He did the right thing.
That woman was willing
to kill herself.
She'd die before she gave us
anything through force.
We need to get her
to talk
before the other
reactors go critical.
And we will.
What did you have in mind?
We need to find
some leverage.
( phone rings )
CTU, Barnes.
Yeah, it's Jack.
Put me through to Erin.
Come here. Come here.
Let me see your arm.
Driscoll.
Erin, we've got a suspect.
I'm sending you fingerprints
and photographs.
I need you
to run a profile
and send me all
relevant databases
and electronic
communications.
Got it.
Thank you.
Hey, I understand
your concerns about Almeida,
but for me, please,
just give him a break.
Okay, Jack.
TONY:
Jack!
Thanks.
JACK:
Yeah?
This is a bullet wound.
Probably a couple
hours old.
As the evacuation appears now
to be in full swing
with major delays
on all routes...
Excuse me.
A nuclear emergency team
has just emerged from the plant.
Uh, we can see them here
on our Sky-Cam.
They seem to be going through
some kind of decontamination...
( new report continues
in background )
Behrooz.
Uncle Nasim.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, it's a disaster
what's happening today.
Everyone's panicked
about radiation poisoning.
They all want iodine pills
and we're almost out.
Is that why you're here?
No.
I need pain medication.
It's for my mother.
She couldn't reach
her doctor by phone,
so she wanted me
to get it from you.
What's wrong with her?
It's her back.
She can barely walk.
She needs a prescription.
I told you.
She couldn't reach her doctor.
I'll see what I can do, okay?
Just have a seat.
( phone rings )
Yes?
Navi, it's Nasim.
Hello, Nasim, how are you?
I'm well, but Behrooz just
showed up at the hospital.
He seems disturbed.
Is Dina there too?
No, he says he needs
pain medication for her.
That there's something
wrong with her back,
but he's acting
very strange.
I'm sorry you have to be
involved in this, Nasim.
Involved in what?
What's going on?
Behrooz may be taking drugs.
He's been getting worse.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
What do you want
me to do?
Keep Behrooz there
until I can come for him.
How long will you be?
15 minutes.
I'll do my best, but...
Please, Nasim, don't let him
leave until I get there.
...congestion, the government
is asking people to remain calm
and exit in a quick
and safe manner.
Excuse me, Miss Raines.
I'm Edgar Stiles.
Sorry.
We've got a major
noncompliance problem.
I've got 25%
of the evacuees who aren't going
where they're being told to go,
and another 25%
that don't even know
that they're
in the evac zone.
However you need to do it,
make sure it gets done.
I'm sorry, what is it?
It's my mother.
Your mother?
She lives near
San Gabriel Island.
She's in a wheelchair.
She doesn't drive.
She missed her call to evacuate.
Now I don't know what to do.
Maybe someone from
the National Guard can get her.
I already spoke to
the area commander.
He said he couldn't
spare anyone.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure
what I can do.
Here's his number.
I thought maybe if you
called him yourself.
Look, I hate asking
for special treatment.
That's not something
I would normally do,
but she's my mother.
I can't make any promises.
Just promise me
you'll try, okay?
All right.
I want you to give
her something
for the pain,
but make sure
she stays lucid.
Understand?
Did you find out
who she is yet?
Yeah.
Her name is Dina Araz.
She immigrated
to the United States
five years ago,
became a citizen
two years ago.
Married to a Navi Araz.
He's also
a naturalized citizen.
Owns an electronics
store in Carson.
They have one son,
Behrooz, 17, a junior
at the local high school.
None of them
have criminal records.
They pop up on
any watch lists?
No, they must have
slipped under the radar.
Let's send some teams
over to the house
and the store, see
what we can find.
( phone rings )
Yeah?
Jack, it's Driscoll.
Homeland Security has...
Hold on, Erin.
I can barely hear you.
Go ahead.
After the attack this
morning, Homeland Security
has been archiving select
communications in the L.A. area.
They pulled up a call
that may explain
how Dina Araz got shot.
Erin, I'm going to put you on
speaker phone. Hold on a second.
You're on.
This conversation happened
about two hours ago
between the mother
and the son.
BEHROOZ: He wants me dead
because I messed up with Debbie.
DINA:
Behrooz, that's not possible.
Your father would
never want to hurt you.
BEHROOZ:
It's true.
Tariq told me everything.
DINA:
He was lying.
BEHROOZ:
No, he wasn't.
Mom, I don't know what to do.
You have to help me.
DINA:
Where are you now?
BEHROOZ: I'm near the Metrolink
station on Lassen in Chatsworth.
DINA:
Are you using Tariq's car?
BEHROOZ:
Yes.
DINA:
Hide it.
I'll pick you up there
in a half hour.
BEHROOZ:
Hurry.
That's it.
Let me know the minute
you get something from her.
Yeah.
We got our leverage.
( door opens )
JACK:
Lee.
( water running )
How long have you been
planning this operation?
Two years?
Five years?
Ten?
All this planning
for one day.
You do realize if all
the reactors melt down,
hundreds of thousands
of people will die.
Every war has casualties.
These people don't
know about your war.
These people
are innocent.
No one is innocent.
You really believe that?
As strongly as you believe
in what you believe.
But I won't waste
your time or mine,
trying to explain something
you can never understand.
Maybe I understand
more than you think.
I doubt it.
I know that something
happened today
to challenge
your commitment to your war.
You weren't willing to let
your son become a casualty.
That's why you were shot.
Protecting him
from his father.
I understand that.
I know what it's like
to watch your child
be threatened
and feel helpless
to do anything about it.
Right now Behrooz is
out there alone...
and you and I know he's
not gonna last very long.
His father
will find him...
...and kill him.
There is
another option.
If you were to help us find
the override device...
we will protect your son.
So he can spend the rest
of his life in prison?
No, so he can
walk away from all of this,
immune from prosecution.
How?
Mrs. Araz, your son is a minor.
He's 17 years old.
I can get him a legal
and binding pardon
signed by the president
of the United States.
You don't have the
authority to do this.
I can reach the president.
If you provide us
with the information
that allows us
to find the override
device- in time-
I am confident
that the president
will sign that pardon.
and this offer
expires the second
another reactor melts down.
Do you understand me?
You don't have a lot of time.
I would think about this.
Show me this document.
And I'll help you
find what you want.
Can we rule out
this boy's involvement
with the terrorist action?
No, sir. It's likely he knew
of his parents' plans.
He probably helped them.
Jack, you're asking me to
grant clemency to a terrorist.
Mr. President, I'm sorry,
but I don't think
we have a choice.
In all of my professional
experience, I believe that
we have to give in
to this woman's demands.
Have you tried
negotiating with her?
We don't have time.
In approximately two hours,
five nuclear reactors
are gonna go critical unless
we find the override device.
She is our only link.
Well, I'm uncomfortable with
this, but I trust your judgment.
I'll release the letter.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Make sure that document
is non-binding.
Yes, I understand.
I'll get back to you
on the redeployment figures.
Miss Raines?
Did you talk to them?
Yes.
Edgar, I'm sorry.
They can't get your mother.
Why not? They're
five miles off the highway.
It wouldn't take
that much time.
They know where she is.
Then what's the problem?
Thousands of people
are stuck
on the Interstate in traffic.
It's taking the combined efforts
of the police and
the National Guard
to get them moving.
So who cares
about one old woman.
They've got to throw their
resources into saving
the maximum
number of lives.
If my mother were rich
or a politician,
they'd find a way to save her.
Field Communications Desk.
This is Edgar Stiles.
I need another switching
station for that number.
Do you need it again?
No, I've got it logged.
Hold the line.
Thank you.
Go ahead, please.
Mom.
Hello, honey.
Mom, I've been
trying everything.
I can't get anyone
out there to help you.
I've done everything
I could. I did.
I'm sure you did, honey.
It's okay.
It's not okay.
The fallout's
coming toward you.
It's 15 miles away.
I know.
I'm watching it
on the news and...
I know what to do.
Ma, there's nothing you can do.
You can't stuff towels
under the door.
That's not what I'm talking
about doing, Edgar.
What do you mean?
They've been talking
about radiation poisoning
on the news.
That's not something
I want to go through,
especially since there's
only one way it can end.
Honey, I want
to end things on my terms
as opposed to all
that pain and suffering.
Mom.
It's the right thing to do.
It's the only thing-
you know that.
No, I don't.
You have been
a wonderful son, Edgar.
You've been a gift
to me and your father.
It's okay. I'm going
to a better place, and...
I'll see you there,
but not for a long time.
You've got a lot ahead
of you. Great things.
Maybe I can get someone to you.
I'll keep trying.
You've got a very important
job to do there.
A lot of people
are counting on you.
So...
I'm going
to hang up now,
and I want
you to know
how very, very much
I love you.
Mom.
Ma?
Edgar, where
are you going?
Edgar!
I have to get
out of here.
What are you
talking about?
My mother. She lives next to the
San Gabriel Island nuclear plant.
She wasn't able to
evacuate in time.
We still have five
other nuclear reactors
that are on the verge
of melting down.
I need you
at your station.
I don't care what you need.
You better start caring.
You have
a choice right now.
Obey orders or end up
in a jail cell.
You're going to arrest me for
trying to save my mother's life?
Edgar, if what
you're saying is true,
there's nothing you
can do for your mother,
but there are thousands
of other people
whose lives you can save.
Suppose your mother
were here right now.
What would make her proud?
What do you think
she'd want you to do?
She'd want me to help.
Then don't you think you should?
MAN:
We're ready to go.
We're just setting up
the comm line.
This is a pardon for your son
signed by the president.
This is acceptable.
Where is he?
He's at Lindower
Memorial Hospital.
It's not far.
Set up a perimeter
around Lindower Memorial.
I want you to call him
and tell him we're coming
to pick him up.
Give her the phone.
We have
to record the call.
( phone rings )
Hello?
It's me. Where are you?
Waiting for Nasim.
I don't know why
he's taking so long.
Don't worry about that now.
Things have changed.
What do you mean?
Listen carefully,
Behrooz.
Government agents
found me.
I'm with them now.
Behrooz,
they know everything.
Behrooz, just a few
more minutes, okay?
But it's all right.
Everything is going
to be all right.
I made a deal.
What are
you talking about?
You're going
to be okay.
You won't be arrested-
or even named-
in any of this.
I don't understand.
I'm going to help them
stop your father.
You are?
Yes.
You said that I would be okay.
But what about you?
We'll talk about that later.
Right now, these men
are coming
to pick you up.
I want you to go with them.
Are they making you say this?
No.
I don't know
who these people are.
I want to be sure
that they're not
forcing you to say this.
I'll come with them.
You'll know
when you see me.
Okay?
I'll meet you outside.
No. Tell him to go
to the emergency room.
I want him to stay
where it's crowded.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
I'll see you in a few minutes,
Behrooz.
Okay.
We're transferring
the suspect.
I want to set up a
protective cordon right away.
Copy that.
Let's go.
Uncle Nasim.
I have to go.
What about the pain medication?
My mom's getting it
from somewhere else,
but thanks for trying.
Behrooz!
Hey.
What are you doing?
I can't let you go.
Why not?
I spoke to your father.
What?
He told me
you need help.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I gave your father
my word.
My father is a terrorist.
He's involved
in what's happened today.
Stop talking, Behrooz.
I swear, it's true.
You're talking nonsense.
No, I'm not!
He's behind the kidnapping
this morning,
and the reactors melting down.
We're all involved-
my mother and me.
We've killed people.
Your father will be furious
when he hears this.
My father is coming here?
No!
Behrooz!
I tried to stop him.
You broke my heart,
Behrooz.
You broke my heart.
If you kill me, Mother
will tell them everything.
Tell who?
The police.
She's with them.
I don't believe you.
It's the truth.
She wants me to be safe
and, if you kill me,
she will ruin
everything you're doing.
Liar!
If you don't
believe me,
look outside.
They're coming to
pick me up.
Help!
Shut up!
Tony, did you
notify Security?
No.
Something is wrong.
Set up a Level Three
cordon
around the hospital.
I'm going with you.
No, you're not!
What's going on here?
There's been
a shooting.
Who? One of the pharmacists.
Who are you?
My name is Jack Bauer.
I work with the
Counterterrorist Unit.
We've been tracking the man
who did the shooting.
Where is he? Someone just
radioed in from C wing.
Saw a Middle Eastern man
running. He has a hostage.
A 17-year-old boy?
I think so.
What are the possible
exits from that wing?
>From where
he was spotted,
he's pretty much
got to end up
in the east parking garage.
We've got men
heading there now.
You tell your supervisor
to tell his men to back off.
No one makes
contact with him.
Do you understand me?
All right.
( phone rings )
Hang on a sec.
Yeah?
Tony, it's Jack.
Navi Araz is here.
He's already killed
his wife's brother.
What about the boy?
I don't know.
We're going to have
to lock down
all the exits.
I think he's headed
for the parking garage.
I need you to meet me
on the east side of the
building with backup.
Copy that. We're going to
the east side of the building.
We need backup teams there
right away.
What happened?
We're still looking
for your son.
There is more. Tell me.
Mrs. Araz, we're going
to find your son, all right?
I hate you.
I've always
hated you.
The only reason
I never said so
was because
I was afraid of you.
But I'm not afraid
of you anymore.
Get in.
Go to hell.
Get in!
Jack, we're in the garage now.
We've secured the exit.
I'm almost there.
Can you get an ID?
No. Nothing yet.
Let me see your hands!
Put your hands where
I can see them! Now!
Careful!
Drop the gun!
You'll hit the boy!
Let the boy go!
We can work this out.
I will put my gun down
if you give me the boy.
All I want is the boy.
Stay back!
Put the g-
Tony, stop the car!
Behrooz!
Mom!
Keep her in the car!
That stairwell leads
to the basement.
He's got nowhere to go
but down.
Set up a link with CTU now!
Copy that. Call CTU.
We need backup here.
Mrs. Araz, calm down, we'll get
your son, all right? Calm down.
DRISCOLL: We've uploaded the plans
to you from the building department.
There are only three exits
from the hospital's basement.
We've got all entrances
and exits covered.
He's trapped down there.
Let's try to open up
a negotiation.
My husband
won't negotiate.
Why is that?
He doesn't need to.
He has to assume
I have agreed to help you
in return
for my son's safety.
Well, he can't stay down there
with him forever.
He won't. In two hours,
all the reactors will have gone
critical. After that,
it won't matter
what I tell you,
and he can kill my son.
I am only helping you
to save his life.
I believe in our cause,
and if you can't
save my son,
I am happy to see
the reactors melt down.
Did you get that?
Subtitles by Jaxdahl
Corrections by ResDog
www.tvsubtitles.net