The Chinese are continuing to press the case
that we were involved in the assault on their consulate.
Have they managed to find evidence
beyond the surveillance video of me?
No... and we have to make sure they don't.
You were part of the covert team
that mounted the assault on our consulate.
If you're not going to tell us who was ultimately responsible,
that leaves you.
If it's Stealth,we can't track it by radar.
Those missiles travel at a speed of 600 miles an hour,
which means it could hit a target on either coast in under three hours.
That's assuming it's headed for the coast.
If it's not,it could hit its target at any time.
What is CTU going to do now to find the missile?
At this point,CTU no longer has any reasonable expectation
of finding the missile before it reaches its target.
I gave you the responsibility to stop this.
You failed me,David.
And you failed your country.
Drop the gun!
It's over. -TONY: Do it,Jack.
Do you really have what it takes to let me kill him
while you're looking him in the eye? -Yes.
JACK: Tony...
I have the power to give you a deal
signed by the President of the United States.
In exchange,you're going to help me find Marwan
and stop this warhead from hitting its target.
Show me the deal.
Bill,this is Jack.
Has the President signed the pardon yet?
Any minute now.
I don't like that we're cutting this woman a deal,Jack.
We can't verify she's telling the truth until it's too late.
We don't have a choice.
Right now,she's the only person that can lead us to Marwan,
and Marwan's controlling the missile.
Has the Attorney General reviewed this immunity agreement?
Yes,sir.
We should be getting his final approval any minute now.
PIERCE: Mr. President,I'm sorry to interrupt,
but there's something you might want to see.
It may affect the immunity agreement.
What is it,Aaron?
The woman you're about to pardon...
I'm pretty certain you've met her before.
Explain.
May I?
Absolutely.
On the right
is the hostile we have in custody.
On the left,
this is news footage from four-and-a-half years ago in Los Angeles
moments before the attempt on your life.
You're telling me the woman
we're about to cut a deal with
tried to assassinate me?
Yes,sir.
Novick.
All right. Thank you.
Mr. President,the Attorney General says
the immunity agreement is in order,
ready to be signed.
LOGAN: If I read this document right,
it grants immunity not only for what this woman has done today,
but for any crimes she's ever committed in the past.
NOVICK: That is correct,sir.
Sign it.
We're trying to get you the deal,
but we will pull it if the missile hits first.
I will talk when my representatives confirm my immunity.
Not before.
Manning.
Yeah.
She's right here.
I'm listening...
Is the paperwork in order?
Good.
Where is Marwan?
The Global Center.
A helicopter is waiting for him on the roof
that will be taking him to a ship.
If he flies low enough,he'll evade radar.
When is he leaving?
Now.
Get the chopper ready.
Alpha Four,it's Manning.
She stays here until we verify this.
Simmons,this is Bernhardt. What's your 20?
Capturing Marwan alive
is our only chance of stopping this warhead
from hitting its target.
We are not to use lethal force even in self-defense.
Am I clear?
Got it,Jack
Let's go!
She's not answering her phone.
She should have been here already.
She said she was delayed.
We're not waiting.
How long before we get to the ship and international waters?
Ten minutes.
Something's wrong.
Edgar,it's Jack.
We're almost there.
Have you got confirmation on the target?
We just repositioned the satellite.
The images are coming through now.
There,on top of the Global Center
I see a chopper.
Southeast corner.
Copy that.
I want you to take a southeast approach.
Stay below the building.
Missile still on target.
We've got to get out of here.
Just a few minutes until we're up to speed.
Okay,come up over the building now!
Don't let him take off!
Stay above him!
Go! Go!
I can't! He's right on top of me.
Go!
PILOT: The engine's out!
Put me in a position to bail.
JACK: There he is!
I got you covered.
Clear!
No!
Tell me where the missile is.
Tell me where it is.
No!
I don't understand. Bauer had orders to take Marwan alive.
I'm sure Jack did whatever he could.
That's not good enough,David.
CTU is searching Marwan's helicopter,
trying to find something that will help them locate the missile.
We're out of time.
Not yet.
Mr. President...
I'm sorry to add to an already difficult situation,
but the acting Chinese consul,Su Ming,is on teleconference.
He says it's urgent.
Put him through.
Gentlemen...
as we discussed earlier,
our consulate in Los Angeles
was attacked three hours ago.
A Chinese citizen was abducted,
and our consul killed.
We've already given you our assurance
that we had no knowledge of this reprehensible attack.
Which is strange,
since one of your agents has confessed his direct involvement
and implicated his superior,as well.
What are you talking about?
My name is Howard Bern.
I'm a federal agent with the Counter-Terrorist Unit in Los Angeles,
speaking of my own free will,under no duress.
I participated in an unlawful assault
on the Chinese consulate in Los Angeles.
I was acting under the orders of Special Advisor
to the Secretary of Defense...
Jack Bauer.
SU: Mr. Bern provided details which leave no doubt
that he is telling the truth.
The full tape will be forwarded to you immediately.
Putting aside the question of
how this so-called confession was obtained,
what does your government expect us to do?
Mr. Bauer committed a crime at our consulate,
which is Chinese territory.
If he was acting without your approval,
he should be turned over to our government
to be tried and sentenced according to our laws.
Mr. Su,we'll get back to you.
Damn it,David,you said this would be handled.
I'm sure the Chinese don't want war.
No. But they do want to embarrass us,
take the moral high ground
in the court of world opinion.
Well,we need to take the least-damaging course of action.
Unfortunately,then,there's only one option.
Which is?
We hand Bauer over to the Chinese.
Unacceptable.
Besides,if we turn him over,
he'll implicate this administration.
The Chinese made Bern talk.
They'll do the same with Bauer,eventually.
Jack Bauer would never compromise national security.
As much as I'd like to believe that,everyone breaks.
What you believe is irrelevant.
There is another option,Mr. President.
Go on.
Suppose something happens to Bauer?
Suppose he has an accident?
That's an obscene suggestion.
It solves a lot of problems.
PALMER: Mr. President!
This administration does not condone murder.
And it never will.
Is that clear?
Yes,sir.
I'm sorry,sir.
Did you find anything on Marwan's body?
We're still looking. Are you okay?
I'll be a lot better once we take this missile down.
MacALLAN: Sir,we might have found something in here.
What is it? It's been shot up pretty badly,
but one of the drive platforms is intact.
It's some kind of tracking or navigation program with a GPS node.
Adams is uplinking whatever's left to CTU.
Okay,thanks.
Buchanan.
Bill,it's Jack. Forensics found something.
They sent it over... Chloe's got it.
She and Edgar are trying to download the interface.
How close are they?
I'll put you on speaker.
You're on,Jack.
Chloe,have you got anything on that program?
Nothing yet.
Give us a second,Jack.
It's totally random. I can't make any sense of it.
Maybe try a correlation matrix.
What's that going to do?
Just do it,Edgar.
I told you it wasn't going to work.
That's because you didn't expand the parameter.
See?
What have you got?
Two parallel columns,
but the data points are badly damaged.
What do you mean,parallel columns?
They could be a flight path.
I'll try plotting them over the USGS map.
It's working.
If that's a flight path,it's headed due west,over Nevada.
It's Los Angeles.
It's gotta be. It's coming towards Los Angeles.
Chloe,run a time analysis.
Assuming the missile travels at 600 miles per hour,
it puts it within this 30-mile segment.
I'll get those coordinates to the Air Force.
Captain Clarke,Bill Buchanan,CTU.
The missile's heading for Los Angeles.
We've narrowed the possible coordinates.
We're uploading them to you now.
Okay,thanks.
They have planes ready in the air now.
If our projections are correct,
they should be able to find it quickly.
They'd better,since the casualty figures of an L.A. air strike
would be over a million lives lost,
including ours.
Put the military channel on speaker.
Delta One,I'm approaching the designated segment.
Roger that,Delta One.
Still no joy target. Searching.
Jack,if the missile gets shot down,
could the warhead detonate?
No,the warhead is specifically designed
not to blow up until it hits its designated target.
But the force of the impact could trigger the arming mechanism,right?
It's unlikely.
But it is possible,right,Jack?
Yes,it's possible,but we don't have a choice;
we're out of time here.
This is Air Control.
I've got a blip at 40.38 south by 30.16 west. Respond.
Closing in on those coordinates.
Possible contact. Breaking left.
Delta One,I've got tally on the target,12:00.
I'm arming.
I'm in range,sir. Request clearance to engage.
Delta 2,target is confirmed.
I've got good tone. Fox two. Missile away.
Splash one.
That's a direct hit,Delta One. The target is down.
I repeat,the target is down.
Here's the report so far.
No nuclear radiation
was emitted when the missile was destroyed.
Debris hit the ground and,uh...
there was some damage and several injuries,
but no loss of life as far as we know.
We'll pick this up later.
When they told me you were dead...
It's all right.
Oh,I love you.
I didn't realize how much until I thought I lost you.
What is it?
When that woman called and she told me...
Hey,listen... you did what you had to do.
But I didn't do what you did.
You chose me,and I chose...
Look,we did the best we could,all right?
Now it's over.
No,commercial flights are still grounded. I'm...
I'm trying to get Paul back on a military transport.
Yeah,I haven't taken care of his funeral arrangements yet.
I still need to call his mother.
Listen,I-I'm gonna,I'm gonna have to get back to you.
There's something I need to deal with.
Your father said you're going to Washington tomorrow.
Yeah,I have to take care of Paul's funeral.
And after that?
I'm sorry,I...
I know this isn't the right time
to talk about everything.
Maybe tomorrow before you catch your flight,
we could,we could get together.
Jack,I don't think that's a good idea.
I thought we agreed that we...
wouldn't make those kinds of decisions today.
I know,but,just...
Audrey...
I love you.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
That's all I want.
We both know that you belong here,Jack.
At CTU,
doing what you do best.
And thank God
there are people like you
who can deal with that world...
But I can't.
Please don't say that.
Oh,Jack.
I love you.
But after today,it's just...
It won't work.
I'm sorry.
This is Bauer.
Jack,it's David Palmer.
Yes,Mr. President.
Words cannot express the debt this country owes you.
Thank you,sir.
Jack,this is hard for me,
but I don't seem to have a choice.
The Chinese have proof
that you led the assault on their consulate.
What kind of proof?
Howard Bern made a full confession.
He identified you as the agent in charge.
And now the Chinese want me.
That's right. And we have no choice but to comply.
I see.
But what they really want is for you to implicate the government.
Mr. President,that will never happen.
I know that.
They'll put you on trial,
propagandize about American arrogance...
then put you in prison.
I understand.
Jack,this is unfair,to say the least,
and I'm ashamed of my part in it.
But I promise you this:
I will make it my life's purpose to bring you back
to American soil as soon as humanly possible.
I know you'll do what you can,sir.
The Secret Service is sending over an agent to CTU.
He'll place you under house arrest,
but you'll have some time to put your affairs in order.
Jack,my friend,I wish there was something else I could say.
Mr. President,you're doing what has to be done.
So will I.
I know you will.
Thank you,Jack.
Thank you,sir
This is a messy situation.
Even if Bauer doesn't implicate the President
in the attack on the consulate,
there are other problems.
Bauer is Special Advisor to the Secretary of Defense,
which makes him a high-value prisoner.
A gold mine of information.
The Chinese could squeeze him dry.
You're right.
Plus,the Chinese could share the information
with any intelligence agency in the world.
Eventually,what they get out of Bauer
could find its way into the hands of terrorists.
This could set us back years.
So the bottom line is...
I don't think you need me to spell that out for you.
I assume this isn't coming from President Logan.
Absolutely not.
He's expressly forbidden it.
But that doesn't mean he'd be sorry if it happened.
So any investigation into Bauer's death...
Will be brief and superficial.
I'll see to it personally.
Fine. I'll take care of it.
Good.
The President ordered Jack be extradited,not murdered.
Cummings wants Bauer dead so the Chinese can't question him.
President Logan shut him down.
We were both there.
It was a weak rebuke,at best.
This is still conjecture on your part,
based on one side of a conversation.
I know what I heard,and I know Cummings. You don't.
You really think he's capable of doing something like this?
He's been doing Logan's dirty work for the last 15 years.
Logan's gotten used to looking the other way.
I'd tell the President myself,
but he won't listen to me.
If you don't intervene now,it may be too late.
...and the Prime Minister is offering
to host a conference in London
for improving the flow of intelligence information among nations.
Tell him I accept his gracious offer.
Maybe you should tell him yourself,sir.
I think he wants to congratulate you personally
for steering the country so effectively
in its time of crisis.
Set up a call.
Yes. sir.
David.
I have been overwhelmed
by the outpouring of goodwill from heads of state
around the world.
Well-deserved,Mr. President.
You played a role,David.
You played a role.
Thank you,sir.
So what can I do for you?
Would you excuse us?
I'd like a moment alone with the President.
Sir,I have reason to believe
that your security chief may be preempting your decision
to hand Jack Bauer over to the Chinese.
Preempting me how?
By killing him before they can take custody.
Oh,for God's sake,David,
Cummings was just speaking hypothetically.
You can't take that at face value.
Besides which,I told him it wasn't an option.
All I'm asking you to do,sir,
is to talk to Cummings,
and make sure he understands your order.
David,I can't indulge some half-baked conspiracy...
I think I've earned the privilege
of having my concerns taken seriously.
You have.
But it's also no secret that your presidency
was infected with a certain level of paranoia
and scandal.
I won't allow that in my administration.
Questioning my security chief
would not only undermine his authority-
it would compromise mine,as well.
Hear no evil...
I beg your pardon?
You heard me.
David,thank you again for your assistance today,
but it's time for you to go back to civilian life
and let me do my job.
Hi,Jack.
Hey.
I just found out that Logan's going to make you take the fall
for everything that happened at the Chinese consulate.
No one's making me do anything.
The President didn't have a choice.
Yeah? Well,that doesn't make it fair,does it?
It is what it is.
This is Bauer.
Jack,are you still at CTU?
Yes,sir. Tony Almeida's just about to debrief me.
Listen to me very carefully.
Do not turn yourself in.
The man they sent to take you into custody
has orders to kill you.
Orders from who?
Someone in Logan's camp.
They think the Chinese will break you.
Logan authorize this?
Not directly,but he won't do anything to stop it.
Now,listen to me.
Get out of there now.
Thank you,sir.
Bill Buchanan,Regional Director of Division,Los Angeles.
Dale Spaulding,Secret Service.
You'll have to sign this before I take Bauer.
What is it?
Chain of custody authorization.
I'm not signing anything until Bauer's been debriefed.
When that happens,he's all yours.
Fair enough.
We'd be burying a million Americans right now
if it wasn't for Jack Bauer.
He's a hero.
I'm sure he is.
I'm just following orders.
I want him treated with the respect he deserves.
Of course.
Tony's on line one. He says it's urgent.
Something to do with Jack.
Buchanan.
Bill,it's Tony.
Jack escaped.
Escaped?
He took me by surprise. There was nothing I could do.
Damn it.
Look,he's still inside the building,
somewhere in Section C.
I'm the one who ordered the lockdown.
I'll be right there.
All right.
Bauer's trying to get away.
Jack disabled the surveillance feed a minute ago.
Were you able to make visual contact before that?
Yes,he's still in Section C.
Jack was willing to turn himself over to the Chinese.
What happened?
I can't say for sure,
but he did get a phone call.
Who from?
I don't know. I was waiting for him to finish up.
Next thing I know,I'm on the ground.
He cold-cocked me.
Does Bauer have a weapon? Yeah.
How many entrances and exits?
Four. They're all blocked off.
We'll try to punch through 'em.
Yeah,but I have two guards posted at each point.
I'm not taking any chances.
What are you doing? Going after him.
BUCHANAN: Wait a second.
I've got orders to take Jack Bauer into custody.
I intend to execute those orders.
This building is my jurisdiction.
SPAULDING: You lost jurisdiction when you lost Bauer.
If you want me to stand down,call the President.
Otherwise,stay out of my way.
But I'm going with you.
No,you're not. I'm doing this alone.
Either you take Tony,
or you're not going in.
Follow me.
Jack,it's Tony. Are you in here?
Let me talk to you! There's got to be a way out of this!
Jack,give it up!
Stay out of my way.
This is over!
I'm going to go bring Jack out.
You want to stop me,you can shoot me in the back.
Jack,I'm putting my weapon down.
I'm coming in.
Jack?
Jack!
He's dead.
You killed him.
He was shooting at us. He was aiming wide.
He was laying down cover fire.
If he wanted to hit us,he'd have hit us.
Oh,my God,Jack.
You killed him,you son of a bitch! You killed him!
Get him out of here! Take him to the Situation Room.
I'm sorry.
God,Jack.
Give me the epinephrine.
I hope it's not too late.
He really looks dead.
MICHELLE: That was the idea,Chloe.
How fast is it supposed to take effect?
Come on,Jack!
Damn!
Tony...
Come on,Jack! Damn it!
Can you hear me?
You know where you are?
Yeah.
All right,Chloe,
I need you to run interference with the local coroner
until we can switch bodies.
Make sure their database synchs up with Jack's information.
That won't cover the autopsy.
There's not going to be an autopsy.
They wanted Jack dead. Now he's dead.
AUDREY: Bill...
I just talked to my father.
He said that Jack was being handed over
to the Chinese government?
He was supposed to be...
but he tried to escape.
I don't understand.
Neither do I.
No.
Audrey...
No,don't say it.
No.
I'm sorry.
All right,we're clear.
You sure you're okay,Jack?
Yeah,I'm fine.
You both need to get back to CTU
before anyone gets suspicious.
Tony,you can drop me off anywhere up there.
All right.
We've secured your new identity.
It should help you get across the border.
Okay.
Did you get me a clean phone?
Yeah. Here's a scramble filter.
You can talk up to one minute undetected.
I can't thank you both enough for everything.
You got to get going.
Jack...
Be careful.
Yeah.
You,too.
Thank you both for everything.
Palmer.
Mr. President,this is Jack Bauer.
You threaded the eye of the needle.
I had some help,sir.
I wanted to thank you
for advising me of the situation.
Mr. President,you saved my life.
I'm only sorry it came to this.
Me,too,sir.
I just wanted to let you know that I was out.
I'm glad.
This is probably the last time we'll ever speak.
Jack,you do understand,when you hang up,
for all intents and purposes,Jack Bauer's dead.
I understand that,sir.
Mr. President,it's been an honor.
Same for me,my friend.
www.tvsubtitles.net