Previously on 24.
We have a problem. If the information on that hard drive is discovered by the Americans,
it'll jeopardize the next phase of our plan.
Well, it's not here.
Keep looking.
Agent Drake?
Drop the weapon! Drop the weapon now!
Jack's on the line.
Jack, what is it?
I pulled some data off a hard drive that we found hidden in Anderson's apartment.
I believe Mitch Anderson's trying to steal a stealth fighter.
Mr. President, we have reason to believe that a stealth fighter has been stolen by a terrorist.
- He's in your airspace as we speak.
- Just how sure are we about this?
It's a near-certainty, Mr. President.
This is a stealth aircraft.
If he finds you,
he may be on you before your fighter escort can react.
Mitch Anderson, we know who you are.
We know what you're trying to do.
Captain Anderson? Captain Anderson? Chloe, I think we've been cut off.
Is there an override channel?
He's cut off all communication circuits.
I don't think there's anything we can do.
Dad. I'm scared.
Air Force One has been fired on.
I repeat, Air Force One has been fired on.
Oh, my God.
Was Air Force One just hit?
Was Air Force One just hit?!
Escort pilots report Air Force One has suffered an indirect hit by an air-to-air missile. Pieces are falling to the ground over the desert.
The following takes place between 11:00 P.M. and 12:00 A.M.
This is Air Force One. We are declaring an emergency. Repeat, Air Force One is declaring an emergency.
Copy, Air Force One. What is your condition? Over.
Extensive damage to the port side wing and fuse lines. We've lost our pressurization, losing fuel pressure. Low hydraulics.
Chloe, are those the coordinates?
Yeah. They're 20 knot of the miles northeast to the city of Indio.
Edgar. Contact local PD and EMS. Alert them of the situation with Air Force One.
On it.
Tony, do we have any CTU support teams in the area?
The Las Vegas office has two satellites search and rescue teams available.
I'm gonna dispatch Air Force One's coordinates to all of the search and rescue teams over in LA and Vegas so they can start for the landing site now.
Edgar, pull up satellite on the National Park. Pinpoint any possible landing scenarios.
Chloe, what's happening?
We've lost the signal. They're still moving fast and losing altitude.
Change the frequency.
OK, I've got it.
Reaching 6 knots.
Going through 7500 and 210 knots.
Roger, 210 knots.
Chloe, are you still waiting coordinates?
Yeah, they're making a turn.
Roger, I'm close to a stall. Yeah, I'm putting you down now. Don't get redeployed, we are still hard and fast.
Air Traffic Control, This is CTU. We are sending EMS, Police and rescue teams to the site ASAP.
Copy that, CTU.
This is Air Force One, descending through 5500, 169¡­
Chloe, what's showing on radar?
Air Force One is down.
Air Force One? Air Force One, do you read? Air Force One is down.
I just got a confirm of scattered ground flashes from DOD satellite.
Edgar, bring that up.
What's the status of Air Force One?
It's down.
What's its crash signature like?
It was a rough landing, radio's down. We don't know if there are any survivors.
Match your coordinates to the satellite. Send it to all agencies.
Got it.
Anybody tried sub-channel com-sat?
No.
Secret Service has at least five personnel on board; all of them have private channels.
Com-sat 3 operator.
This is Jack Bauer. Log in password: F-H-Ralfie-4.
Go ahead.
I want you to flood all AF1 channels with an acknowledge signal.
Copy. This is com-sat 3 operator, calling AF1 channels 1 through 5, please acknowledge. AF1 channels 1 through 5, please acknowledge.
This is channel 3.
Who's this?
Peterson. We're down.
What is the status of the President?
I don't know. I can't move yet.
Agent Peterson, my name is Jack Bauer. I'm with CTU. Rescue units are on route. What else can you tell me?
I see some bodies. I¡­ I think we have some survivors.
Mr. Vice President, I just received confirmation.
Air Force One sustained an indirect hit from an air-to-air missile fired from a stolen stealth fighter.
Is the President alive?
We don't know at this time.
When will we know?
Hopefully within the next few minutes.
Charles, we've known each other for 15 years. If I can offer some advice?
Of course.
We all hope President Keeler is alive, but even if he is,
it's very likely he won't be in any shape to run the country.
You need to make arrangements to be sworn into office as soon as possible,
and the media should provide live coverage.
The American people need to be reassured that their leadership is intact.
It's good advice, Mike. I'll take it under consideration, but I don't wanna act prematurely.
I understand.
Well, we have to get to the White House. I've arranged for a security briefing with the Pentagon.
That's great.
By now, you all know that Air Force One has been shot down. The escort pilots following Air Force One managed to get a visual of the stealth fighter used to commit the act,
pilot engaged, then shot down the stealth. The status of the President is unclear at this time. Rescue teams are minutes away. We'll know very soon.
The man responsible for what has transpired today, Habib Marwan, is still out there,
and most likely planning further attacks. I want every one of you to rededicate yourselves to finding Marwan.
I don't want a single lead ignored or a shred of evidence missed.
Let's get back to work.
Michelle, let me talk to you.
I want you to uplink all curtainlies to a station, so you and I can start working on a priority list.
We might not know exactly where Marwan is, but he has to be within a 15 mile radius¡­
J ack.
Jack. I'm sorry to interrupt you, but I just got off the phone with the Secretary of Defense, and right now there's a higher priority than finding Marwan.
What is it?
Recovering the Nuclear Football.
Didn't it go down with Air Force One?
Not exactly. The missile inflicted enough damage that the plane left a trail of debris as it went down.
A lot of things were sucked out, including the Football. There's a transponder embedded in the casing, so we know its exact location.
Well, good, then the retrieval team should have no problem recovering it.
The Secretary wants you to head up that team, Jack.
Why?
It's his top priority.
That case contains the codes and locations of out entire nuclear arsenal.
Nothing is more critical than getting it back, and as quickly as possible.
Fine.
I'll organize your team, mobilize the units.
Thanks.
What's the location of the Football?
Forty miles northeast of here, in the middle of the desert.
Hey. Hey.
What's wrong?
What else is happening?
Paul may have to go back into surgery. Apparently the bullet did more damage than they thought.
I'm sorry.
I keep thinking if I had handled things differently, if I had trusted him more, that¡­
Audrey, you are not responsible for this.
I, and I alone, made the decision on how to handle Paul.
If you wanna remain affective,
be able to do your job, you have to let it go.
Jack, that's your gift.
You're able to block things out. I can't do that.
Jack, the chopper's waiting.
I have to change and get ready.
All right.
Honey.
What's wrong?
I don't know. Something woke me up. It sounded like some kind of an explosion or something.
Explosion? Nearby?
I'm not sure.
It was probably just a bad dream.
Yeah.
You're still stressed, aren't you? I want you to try and forget about work, OK?
Just focus on what we came out here for ¨C to relax,
and to make a baby.
Look.
What?
Watch your step.
Oh, my God.
Kelly.
What is it?
If the President is unable to fulfill his duties, Vice President Logan will have to assume office, at least on temporary basis.
Cabinet members will need to be briefed on the circumstances surrounding the crash.
Yeah, I'll take care of it.
Not all Cabinet members are equal. State and Defense need more detail than say, Aviculture and Treasury.
Yeah, I can handle it.
I just wanna make sure that the transition is smooth.
I understand,
but uh¡­ I do know what to do.
All right.
Tony.
I've noticed a little hostility on your part. If it's because of me and Michelle¡­
It's none of my business.
As far as the hostility goes, I can promise you ¨C it's over with.
Whatever you say.
One more thing; I think the world of Michelle, love working with her.
Outside work, we never got off the ground,
she never said why but it didn't take a genius to figure it out ¨C she cared about you.
If you ask me, she still does.
Mr. Buchanan, rescue teams are inside Air Force One.
We're picking up the live feed now.
Go ahead. Check to see if he's alive.
She's dead too.
Copy that. They said he was in the conference room.
We got a survivor.
I'm going in.
Looks like the President's son. He's dead.
Where's the President? This may be him. Wait, hold on. This may be him.
Mr. President? He's still alive.
I repeat, the President is alive.
We need medivac teams in here ASAP. Did you read that? We need medivac teams in here.
I have Agent Buchanan for the Vice President.
Yes, he's right here. Bill Buchanan.
Bill.
Mr. Vice President. I'm in direct contact with the rescue teams at the crash site of Air Force One. President Keeler is alive.
Thank God!
Yes, Sir.
But he's in critical condition. He is unconscious, he's lost a lot of blood,
there's no chance he's going to be able to lead this country, certainly not for a few days, and probably much longer.
Mr. Vice President?
Yes, I'm here.
This is all confirmed?
The President is being medivaced to the nearest emergency center as we speak.
Sir, I recommend you invoke the 25th amendment, and take control of things as soon as possible.
I understand. Thank you, Bill.
President Keeler is alive but he's incapacitated.
We should, uh¡­ we should probably contact the Cabinet members.
Actually, sir, I've already put that in motion. Most of the Cabinet members are standing-by. The others will be very soon.
You did without my permission?
I¡­ You had enough to worry about, sir. I thought it'd be best to be prepared.
Yes. All right.
Thank you.
Shall I begin the process of collecting votes?
Yes, go ahead.
I can't get a signal.
Try up here.
Got it.
Kelly. Look at this.
what is it?
I'm not sure, but if it's what I think it is¡­
I read this article once; I think it's got a funny name, umm¡­ I can't remember
but it's got our nuclear codes. It goes everywhere the President goes, and he can launch an attack from it.
We gotta call somebody.
Who are you gonna call?
I'll start with the police, I guess. They'll put us through to the right people.
The Football transponder's signal's still strong.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Look, when I walked away from you at CTU, I felt like you didn't understand what I was trying to say.
I'm not telling you that you shouldn't care. I care. I care about you. I care about what happened to Paul, I feel completely responsible for it.
But right now this country is under attack, and I've got a job to do, and I don't have a choice.
Jack, I understand. What you have to do is very important.
I just didn't want us to leave things like that.
I'm glad. Me neither.
Audrey, hold on a second. I gotta take this call.
Wait, Jack. Take the call. Stay focused on what you have to do.
Yeah, I'll talk to you in a little while.
- OK.
- Bye.
This is Bauer.
Jack, it's Tony.
I got a guy on the line the police put through. He's in the desert, says he found a case.
Jack, this guy found the Football.
OK. Let me speak to him.
All right. His name's Jason Gerard. We're running a background check as we speak.
I'm patching him through right now.
OK. Tony, stay on the other line.
Mr. Gerard?
Yeah. Hey, call me Jason. I'm with my wife Kelly. Who's this?
Jason, my name is Jack Bauer. I'm a Federal Agent with the Department of Defense.
My colleague Agent Almeida says you found what we refer to as ¡°the Football¡±.
Yeah, it sure looks that way.
I mean, I don't know very much about this sort of thing. My wife and I are just out here on a camping trip.
OK, fine. Why don't you just describe to me what you found?
Sure. It's a black-leather briefcase; it's got a number paneling over by the handle.
It was in a protective case that had the Presidential seal on it.
Well, that sounds like it.
Right now I'm in a helicopter. I'm about 20 minutes away from you. Look, I just want you to hang out there and wait for me.
I think someone beat you to the punch. I see headlights.
How far away?
Uh, it's hard to tell. A few miles?
OK, just hold on a second, Jason.
Tony. This kid Jason says he's got headlights headed towards him. Do we have any ground units in his vicinity?
No.
How about patrol park rangers, anything?
No, nobody.
How can that be?
We're spread thin, Jack. All state agencies are still assisting with the evacuation.
Jason, are the headlights headed straight for you?
Yeah. They're pretty much coming this way.
Dammit. This situation just got a lot more complicated than we thought.
What do you mean?
The Football has a transponder. It's a tracking device that allows anyone to pinpoint its exact location, as long as they've got the right frequency.
Do you think someone got a hold of the frequency, who's not supposed to have it?
Right now we're gonna have to make that assumption.
Well, who do you think it is?
The terrorists who carried out today's attacks.
Listen, if I'm right we don't have a lot of time.
I need you to remove the transponder and take the Football, and get away from there as far as you can.
Uh¡­ All right.
Flashlight. Get your light.
OK, uh¡­ Go ahead.
The transponder's tiny, and it's hidden in the surface of the case. It's designed not to be found.
Then how am I supposed to find it?
Do you have a compass and a flashlight?
Uh, yeah. Get the compass.
OK, I want you to move the compass over the surface of the case slowly.
The transponder puts out an electromagnetic field.
It's not very strong, but it should move the needle.
Just move the compass over the surface of the case slowly,
and watch the needle.
Here, here, here. Get the beam of the compass.
I think I got it. I found it. I found it.
OK, good. Take a knife or a sharp rock, and start scratching the surface hard.
Hurry.
- Dammit.
- Jason, they're coming.
Come on, Jason, talk to me.
I'm working on it.
OK, I think I got it.
OK, I want you to take the compass, put it over the scraped area and tell me, is the needle moving?
No, no, it's not.
OK, you've disabled it. Good work. How far away is the vehicle?
Not far!
OK, I need you to take the Football and start moving. I don't care which direction, just start moving now. I'll get back to you.
We gotta go. We gotta go now.
Tony, I'm gonna need surveillance of the entire area put up to my screen.
Why are we stopping?
We've lost the signal.
How is that possible?
I don't know. Maybe it was damaged on impact
And it just happens to malfunction now that we're getting closer?
Scan the area for cell phones, active and passive signals.
Yeah?
Jason. OK, we found a reserve power station about a half a mile north of you.
Yeah, that's right. I remember it from the map.
OK, I want you to go there now.
It's OK. Yeah. Yeah, we'll get there.
The station's a large unmanned facility. I want you to break in and find a place to hide. I want you to avoid using your flashlight, and as soon as you hang up,
I want you to take your cell batteries out.
The batteries?
Yeah, to prevent something called passive triangulation. In other words, it'll stop you from being followed.
What if I need to contact you?
If you need to contact me, put the batteries back in, but only if you have to.
Now, I'm gonna give you my direct line. Have you got a pen?
Yeah. Hold on.
Go ahead.
3-1-0-5-9-7-3-7-8-1
OK, yeah, I got it.
Start moving now.
OK.
He said to take the battery out of the cell phone. Come on.
I had a cell phone signal for a few seconds. It's moving, but it's gone now.
Did it move enough to yield a vector?
Wait. Yes, it was headed a few degrees west of north, just before we cut off.
Check the map. See if there's anything near there.
There's a reserve power plant. A kilometer away, maybe less.
Whoever has the Football, that's where they're heading.
This is it.
Stay back.
We're not in any danger, right?
I mean, how can anyone even know that we're here?
We're just being safe.
Not a relaxing weekend in the desert, just like I said¡­
They're here. I gotta call Jack.
Come on.
This is Bauer.
It's Jason. These terrorists you talked about? They're here.
How many?
I just saw two jeeps.
Where are you?
Just inside the power plant. When are you going to get here?
Soon, just stand-by.
Go, Kelly, go, go.
Tony, it's Jack. We're out of time. We need the schematics for the power plant now.
Yeah, it should be on your screen in a few seconds.
OK, I got it. Thanks.
Jason, you're still with me?
Yeah, I'm with you.
Which side of the building did you enter?
Uh¡­ The, the south side.
This is a large facility.
I want you to go to the lower level, southeast corner.
I'll find you there as soon as we land.
Ok.
Hey, hey, Agent Bauer? Please hurry.
We are.
Find them.
There's got to be stairs somewhere.
Here they are, here they are.
Wait. What if it's a dead end?
There's a man and a woman.
Where are they?
This way.
They were down here.
Follow them and flush them out.
Go around and cut off the exits.
Go up there, go up there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ok.
Anything?
Nothing.
Helicopter.
Intercept it.
Ok.
Jason.
Where are you?
We just landed. We're approaching the building. Where are you?
We're inside the plant, on the lower level.
Jack! Jack!
Jason, you're still there?
I'm here. They're inside the building. We cannot keep hiding. They are gonna find us.
I know. You gotta keep moving. I'll get back right back to you.
Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, it's Jack. I need to speak to Audrey Raines now.
Ms. Raines, Jack's on line one.
Jack.
Audrey, I'm taking fire. The other agent's been killed.
I need the latch code for the Football now.
All right. Hang on.
Take the Football, take the Football! Come on.
Jack. *76114.
I got it.
Hey.
Jason, I need you to open the case. The combination is *76114.
Why? Where does that plant us?
Just do it. *76114.
He wants us to open the briefcase. *76114.
OK, it's open.
OK. Inside should be a phone, a control board and a book with colored pages. It's called the Playbook.
I want you to remove the Playbook. Give the case with the control board back to your wife. The two items need to stay separated.
Why?
Because the control board is useless without the Playbook.
I need you and your wife to split up.
He wants us to split up.
I can hear him.
I am not leaving my wife.
You have to.
Forget it.
Jason, please listen to me. I know how scared you are
but if this man gets what he wants, he's gonna kill both of you.
Right now the only chance you have to survive is to separate, do you understand me?
It's OK, Jason. He's kept us alive this far. Let's just do what he says.
Just get here as fast as you can.
I will.
I love you.
Give me the Playbook.
Here, you take the phone.
I want you to go to that top wile over there, all right? I'm gonna stay down here. You just find a place to hide, all right?
Go, go, go, go. Go. Hide, hide.
I've got him!
He's clean.
Where's the control board?
I¡­ I don't know what you're talking about.
Tell me what I want to know.
I swear, I don't know what you're talking about. Please.
It doesn't have to be this painful.
This is Bauer.
They've got my husband. They're hurting him.
Where are you? I'm on the lower level.
We had to leave. We're on the second floor. I don't know where.
OK, I'm on my way.
They're gonna kill him.
Kelly, stay on the phone. Keep talking to me.
I can't.
Kelly!
Please...
Where is the control board?
Stop.
I have what you want.
Give it to me.
First, you let my husband go.
No!
OK. OK.
I'll give it to you if you promise not to kill us.
I won't kill you. I promise.
It's over there.
It's behind the pillar.
It's locked.
What is the code?
It's uh¡­ *76114.
It's here.
Let's go.
Kill them.
This is Jack Bauer. I need a medic. Second level, north end of the building.
It's all right. He's gonna be OK. Help is on the way.
Where is the Football?
They have it. They went out that door.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. You did great. Thank you.
Air support, two hostiles just left the building.
I do not have possession of the Football. I repeat, I do not have possession of the Football.
Air support, the Football is in the lead jeep headed north. Take it out.
I repeat, take it out.
Put your hands where I can see them!
Air support, I cannot see the Football in the vehicle. Shine your spotlight on me
and follow.
Air support, I'm in possession of the Football. Go after the other jeep.
Almeida.
Tony, it's Jack.
I'm in possession of the Football. Three hostiles are down, one escaped.
I'm not positive, but I think it was Marwan.
I'm sorry, but I had to make a choice.
Marwan gave us the Football to buy his freedom?
Yeah, that doesn't sound right to me either.
What are you thinking?
I don't know.
Let me ask you something; Is anything missing?
No. All the components are here.
Hold on one second.
Tony, I was wrong.
There are some pages missing.
All right, look, Jack, the sections are color-coded. What's missing?
Red Chapter, Section Three.
Get Audrey.
All right. We'll call you right back.
You're worried about him.
I am. He seems unsure of himself.
No, Mike, trust me.
He spent his whole life preparing for this. He's just being cautious, feeling his way along. He'll be fine.
Yeah?
Well, the vote was unanimous. The 25th amendment's been officially invoked.
Tell the press we're ready. Let's get this done.
Mr. Vice President
the 25th amendment is in effect
Any descending votes?
None, sir.
Well, we should proceed with the sworning then.
Yes, sir. The sworning will only take a minute, and then we'll take a short break and you can address the nation.
I'm still not entirely certain that a live address makes much sense this time of night.
After what's happened today, sir, an awful lot of people are wide awake. I'm sure they'd like to hear from you directly.
Yes, of course.
We're ready, sir.
Please. Please. Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
Yeah?
Jack, it's Tony.
Is Audrey there?
Jack, I'm here.
Tell me what the contents are of the missing pages.
Jack, it's the Red Section which contains warhead locations and activation codes.
But we started canceling all the activation codes as soon as Air Force One went down.
Yes, but there are thousands of warheads. It's gonna take an hour to clear the slate.
Jack, in the meantime, if they get a hold of a warhead and a matching activation code, we will not be able to stop them.
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
Mr. Novick's office.
Let me speak to Mike Novick.
Yes, sir, right away.
I soundly swear that I will faithfully execute the office of the President of the United States, and will, in the best of my ability,
preserve, protect and defend the constitution of the United States.
Mr. President, I appreciate it.
Ladies and gentlemen, I appreciate you coming at this late hour.
Novick.
Mike, it's Jack. We got a problem.
¡­to take this oath under tragic circumstances. Words cannot express the sense of sadness¡­
Part of the Football's been compromised.
Yes, I'll tell him.
Mr. President.
I just received a phone call from CTU.
I'm sorry to tell you, sir, but it appears that part of the Nuclear Football has fallen into the hands of terrorists.
Transcript: Nina Myers @inside-24.com/forum/
Synchronization: Tintinxm www. forom. com
www.tvsubtitles.net