Caption By Dean From F6
Rearranged By allanmauwx From TLF
Perviously on 24.
Who is this?
Andrew, my name is Jack Bauer.
I work for Secretary
of Defense Heller.
Secretary Heller was kidnapped
less than half an hour ago.
I believe the same people
that kidnapped him
are the ones
that are chasing you now.
The safest thing for you to do
right now is
let me bring you in.
I found the person
who stumbled
onto our server.
Is he with you now?
No, I'll have him shortly.
Find out who he's talked to.
Who are you?
I'm the man
that's going to kill you
if you don't follow
my instructions.
This is a simple task, Behrooz,
but these are the ones
where mistakes can be made.
Debbie, what are
you doing here?
I followed you.
Omar saw you
with someone
outside the compound.
She didn't
see anything.
I made sure of it.
We've spent years
planning for this,
waiting for
this day to come.
Now it's here and you've
compromised everything.
It's a simple
job, Ronnie.
You pick up the subject
and you bring him in.
Bauer has not been in the field
for a year and half, okay?
Which is why I need you
to keep him on a tight leash.
For the record, Jack,
I think Driscoll
made a mistake
letting you
come along.
You get the gate.
I'll get the kid
out of the car.
My father's
the Secretary of Defense.
Richard,
right now you're
the only witness
to your father
and your sister's kidnapping.
We need your help.
You don't have anything to hide, do you?
HELLER: We'll be fine, Audie.
We're still on U.S. soil.
What are they going to
do to us? I don't know,
but if they wanted me dead
they would have killed
me at Richard's house.
Our soldiers have taken
the terrorist James Heller
into custody.
In three hours, Heller
will be tried for
war crimes against humanity.
If he is proven guilty,
he will be executed,
in accordance with our laws.
As you are all aware,
the Secretary of Defense
and his daughter have been
kidnapped by a terrorist cell.
The terrorists have announced
that they will put Jim on trial
for war crimes,
then execute him.
All of it broadcast
for the world.
Make no mistake, this
country is under attack.
Foreign terrorists
are operating on our soil.
And intelligence indicates
that the kidnapping
may be some kind of trigger,
the first step
in a series of larger attacks.
Mark, what kind
of protective
actions are
being taken?
We've changed all
the codes and protocols
the Secretary
has knowledge of.
Also, the other
Cabinet members
have been sequestered.
All right.
Melissa?
Where are we with
trying to keep
these people from
broadcasting?
The media outlets will all
cooperate and not air it.
But the terrorists
have announced
that they will use the Internet,
and we cannot control that.
They're using technology that
makes their feed untraceable,
and we can't
shut down the Internet
without disabling
the command
and control functions
of the government
and the economy.
Mr. President, the only way
to stop this is at the source.
We have to find the terrorists,
and rescue
Secretary Heller.
Erin, where is CTU on this?
We have search teams
out in force
and we're working
a few active leads, sir.
Anything promising?
We'll know very shortly,
Mr. President.
Keep us closely posted.
Ladies and gentlemen,
nothing takes priority
over finding the people
who have Jim Heller
and stopping them.
Thank you.
Where are we
with Heller's son?
We're still trying
to find out what he knows.
If he had anything to do
with his father's abduction,
we need to know.
Get on it.
Then try
his emergency frequency.
What's going on?
Where's Ronnie and Bauer
with the witness?
We don't know.
What?
I just got off
the phone
with transit. A hostile
intercepted Andrew Paige
at the station. We
can't reach Ronnie
or Jack. What do you mean you can't
reach them? They're not answering
their phones and there's
been a report of a shooting
at the station. I'm checking
for an update right now.
Get recent pictures
of Andrew Paige
and get them
to our people
on the ground.
Also set up a security
grid around the station.
My system's already
logged on
to the station.
I can get it faster.
All right. Fine.
You do tactical with me.
Let's go, Edgar.
Edgar Stiles.
Miss Driscoll.
Jack Bauer's on line one.
Where are you? Why have you
and Ronnie not been in contact?
Erin, Ronnie's been killed.
What are you talking about?
He was shot by a hostile
who kidnapped Andrew Paige.
Where are you now?
I'm in transit. I'm tracking
them, but he doesn't know it.
Give me your location, and I'll
send backup to apprehend him.
Erin, I don't think
that's the right call.
I believe if I follow them,
they're going to lead me
to Secretary Heller and
the men who kidnapped him.
Listen to me.
Terrorists have
just announced that
they are going to try
and execute Heller
in less than
three hours. Bring
the man in now.
Right now this is our best
chance of finding him by then.
Jack, we had a deal.
Erin, you're breaking up.
Listen, have SWAT
and rescue teams
standing by.
I'll call you as soon as the
hostile reaches his destination.
That call-
do you have
a location?
No, it had a block on it.
I've just been informed
that Ronnie Lobell
has been killed
in the line of duty.
The killer was a hostile
connected to Heller's abduction.
At this point,
Jack Bauer is
no longer cooperating
with this investigation.
All departments need to be
working on the location
and capture of Jack
Bauer and the hostile
that he's tracking now.
Sarah, I need you
to reconfigure the grid
and to include routes
away from the station.
I want all ground teams on this.
MTA Downtown.
This is Chloe O'Brian from CTU.
Do you have any new information
about the kid who was
abducted from your station?
No, we told you
everything we had
a few minutes ago.
What about surveillance cams?
I can access them
if you give me the port codes.
We're looking at them
right now, Miss O'Brian.
There's nothing.
Thanks.
Yes?
What are you doing there?
I need you to help me
with this grid.
What kind of help do you need?
The northeast quadrant
is pass-coded and I don't...
Pilot L-1.
What?
That's the log in.
Chloe could you
just get back here?
My friend Andrew,
who I promised would be
okay, do you mind
if I try to find him?
Get down!
Yes?
I have the programmer.
Good. We need to know
what he told CTU
as soon as possible.
Proceed as planned.
Understood.
There was a problem
at the train station.
What happened?
A federal agent
interfered,
I killed him.
Are you being pursued?
No, anyone that left
the station after me
would have caught up
to me by now.
Unless they don't want you
to know they're there.
Take precautions.
Make sure that you are
not being followed. Go.
Move!
Dad.
You okay?
Did they hurt you?
No.
They just
wanted me present
while they broadcast
an announcement.
They're going
to put me on trial.
For what?
Crimes against humanity.
That's ridiculous. When?
Less than three hours.
Dad, I'm sure that
Jack and the President
are doing everything
they can to find us.
Maybe they'll get
here before then.
I can deal
with anything
these bastards
have got for me.
I wish you hadn't
come this morning, that's all.
This is a list of the offenses
you are being
charged with.
Sign it.
I'm a senior member of the
United States government.
I'm not signing it.
Then you will die,
Mr. Secretary.
Pick up the document
and sign it.
No!
Let her go.
Leave her alone, you son
of a bitch. Come on!
Leave her alone.
Kill her!
All right.
All right! I'll sign it!
Pick up the document.
Pick it up.
Where are we on finding
Bauer? So far nowhere.
That's unacceptable. There are
a lot of places he could be.
We're working up
everything we can.
What else are you
doing to find Heller?
After I'm done here
I'm going to find out
what his son Richard knows.
Sarah's working on the
forensics from the kidnapping.
Have you gotten anything new yet? No.
Great, what else?
Sarah Gavin.
We're trying to trace the origin
of the terrorist web cast. And?
The code's been braided, and I
can't get into the system file.
In other words, nothing.
Ms. Driscoll,
it's the President.
Make something happen.
Yes, Mr. President.
I understand you lost
one of your field operatives.
Yes, we did.
Did the engagement yield
any witnesses or prisoners?
Not yet, but
there's some hope.
Tell me.
Jack Bauer, who as you
know used to work here,
is currently in the field
trailing a suspect.
Trailing him?
Why doesn't he bring him in?
We're in the process
of doing that, sir.
Erin,
are we going to be able
to save Jim and his daughter
before this... trial starts?
I certainly hope so, sir.
Mr. President,
I have to ask you something now
because we may not
have time later.
What is it?
We may find ourselves
in a situation
where we have Heller's location
but can't extract him safely.
If that's the case,
would you authorize,
in advance,
an all-out assault?
The assumption being that
the Secretary would not survive?
Correct.
We'll cross that bridge
if the scenario presents itself.
Yes, sir.
Good-bye, Erin.
Manning.
Hey, Curtis.
It's Maryanne.
Look, I know you're busy
with the Heller kidnapping.
Yes, I am.
My friend Aileen said
you're calling in
level-five consultants today
because you're overloaded there.
We added some personnel
because of the crisis.
She said you struck
my name from the list.
Why?
You don't meet
the criteria, Maryanne.
Don't give me that,
Curtis.
I have the qualifications
and I have the clearance.
Why'd you exclude me?
All right, you want it straight?
I don't think we'd work
very well together.
Why? Because we slept together
a few times
and you stopped calling me?
I stopped calling you
because I realized
you were using me
to get ahead
in your career.
That's your
interpretation, Curtis.
And you didn't seem to have
a problem with it at the time.
I'm not going to have
this conversation.
Fine, I'll have it
with Erin Driscoll.
Maryanne... Consulting with
CTU would be a huge opportunity
for me, Curtis.
And I'm not going to let you
get in the way
because you're uncomfortable.
Where should I post
those FBI bulletins?
At two-three.
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's me.
Can you talk?
Jack, what the hell happened
with Andrew?
Someone got to him
before we could
pick him up.
Did you tell
anyone at CTU
where we were supposed to meet him? No.
What are you doing,
Jack?
Driscoll just announced
you're operating
outside her authority.
I don't have a choice,
she's not handling this
the right way.
What if you're wrong?
I'm not.
This is the best chance we have
of finding Secretary Heller.
Jack, if anything happens
to Andrew...
Chloe, I'm doing the best I can,
but right now our first priority
is to find these terrorists.
So why are you calling me?
The hostile's headed
towards the canyons.
I'm going to need
satellite surveillance
to help me track them
without being seen.
You want me to steal
satellite bandwidth from CTU,
without anyone knowing?
Yes.
Where are you?
I'm on Orchard Road
just north of the 14
about four miles east
of Valencia.
Okay, Caltrans has traffic cams
in the area,
but you will need
satellite coverage
once he gets
closer to the canyons.
Call me back as soon as
you've got the coverage.
I'll keep a private
channel open. I will.
Who was that?
It was personal.
Something wrong?
I'm not sure.
Chloe's acting kind of strange.
That's nothing new.
Hey, what do you need?
I just got off the phone
with Maryanne Taylor.
Erin, whatever she told you,
it's coming from
a very disturbed place.
That may be.
But she's as qualified
as any of the others
you brought in today.
I'm not comfortable
working with her.
That should be
enough for you.
Normally it would be.
However, she mentioned
that your pillow talk
included a synopsis of
the new data mining protocols.
That's a lie.
If she got
that information,
it was from
someone else.
Now she's using it
against me.
She knows details
about the new UVX system.
That's classified
information.
She could force us into
a section one security reboot
and drag us through
a six-month investigation.
I don't believe this.
I asked her to come in.
Deal with it.
Do you have the results
on Secretary Heller's son yet?
Yeah.
The polygraph makes
clear he didn't have any
knowing involvement
in his father's kidnapping.
But...?
He's still insisting
he didn't tell anyone
his father was coming
to his house this morning.
The polygraph was
inconclusive on that claim.
You think he's lying?
It's possible.
Richard was the
only one who knew
where his father
would be this morning.
And he may have told
someone about it.
Why would Richard protect
somebody who's betrayed him?
Because he's too arrogant to
believe that's what's happened.
It'll take days to go through
his phone records.
I want you to see
if you can get the name
out of him another way.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Erin, we're not even sure
if he's guilty of anything.
This is how we'll find out.
Get started.
Did Father talk to you
about Debbie?
What about her?
When Dad told me to take
the briefcase to Omar...
Debbie followed me.
She didn't know
where I was going.
She just wanted to talk.
Debbie saw the warehouse
where we're holding Heller?
Yes.
But there wasn't anything
I could do about it.
You could have broken up
with her months ago
like your father and I
told you to.
I know I made a mistake,
but Father found out
she was with me
and now he wants me
to get her over here.
You know
what that means.
If he thinks
there's the slightest chance
she could expose
what we're doing...
I didn't realize you felt
so strongly about her.
She's not going
to mess anything up,
I swear to you.
What do you want me to do?
Talk to him.
He'll listen to you.
Please.
Okay.
Your father's
on his way to a meeting.
I'll try to reach him.
Thanks, Mom.
When can I
get out of here?
Secure him.
What the hell are you doing?!
Get your hands off me!
Who else knew your father
would be at your house
this morning?
I told you, no one.
What, are you crazy?
CURTIS: This works on the
neurotransmitter level.
It makes every nerve
ending in your body
feel like it's on fire.
You're bluffing.
You know you can't
get away with this.
And by the time
you're released,
the mark on your arm
will be gone.
It'll just be your word
against mine.
My father is the Secretary
of Defense, for God's sake.
I thought you hated him.
Now he's dear old dad?
Help me!
Somebody!
Please!
Help me!
Stop.
I can't do it, Erin.
I'm not going to let Eric
work on Richard Heller.
Why not? Maybe he's protecting a friend,
but he wasn't knowingly
involved with the terrorist.
It's an inappropriate
use of force.
I gave you an order.
Then give it to me
in writing, Erin.
What are you
suggesting, Curtis,
that we release him?
No.
I've seen good results
with sensory disorientation.
Cut off his sight,
saturate his auditory.
It's noninvasive.
Fine.
Try it.
Yes?
DINA:
I just spoke with Behrooz.
He told me about the problem
with his girlfriend.
He's very upset, Navi.
That's what concerns me.
He has feelings for this girl,
despite what he tells us.
Now she's seen the warehouse.
I know.
It's very troubling.
I told him to get
her over to the house
so we can question her.
Did he make the call?
No, he asked me
to talk to you instead.
Hmm.
Go upstairs.
What are we going to do?
Are you talking
to Father?
I'll talk to you soon.
You'll take care of this?
Yes.
Thank you.
What did he say?
Do I still have to call
Debbie and get her over here?
No.
Thank you, Mom.
I'm going to pull over soon,
and we're going to talk,
okay?
Good.
There's some things
I need you to know.
Today is not about me or you.
It's about something bigger.
What I need to know
with certainty,
is that whatever you saw
on the Internet
will not interfere
with what we have planned.
You have to convince me of that.
Yeah?
It's going to be a while
on the satellite.
Ever since Heller was taken,
the load is through the roof.
How much longer?
I'm not sure yet.
What is your current
position exactly?
I need it to
update the request.
Suspect pulled over
just past mile marker 31.
What did he get off for?
There's nothing there.
I don't know, Chloe.
I've got to go!
Get back to me as soon as you've
got the satellite coverage.
Jack, I'm watching this.
How?
On Caltrans' traffic cam.
You've got to stop this.
If I intercede right now,
we lose our opportunity
to find Secretary Heller.
What did you
tell CTU?
That someone was
preparing to distribute
some kind of positioning
code on the Internet.
What else?
I tried to dig deeper,
but everything was in
some kind of Arabic.
I couldn't read it.
That's all you told CTU?
Yes. I promise.
Ah!
Are you sure?
Jack, stop them, just stop them.
That's all I know.
I swear, I promise.
Please, just don't
hit me anymore.
Please.
I talked to the programmer.
I don't think there's a problem.
He didn't tell CTU enough
for them to be able to stop us.
Are you sure?
Yes. He only got a brief
glimpse of the code.
He was never logged on
to our server.
I need you here.
Get back on the road.
Have them see what else
they can find out,
and then get rid
of the body.
I will see you soon.
Chloe, how do you open
a secure pipe to Division?
Ask Edgar.
I did. He's busy.
Well, I'm busy, too.
Why are you always so
impatient with everybody?
Not everybody, just you.
Now please go away.
Bitch.
Jack, what's happening?
The hostile's moving.
I've got to follow him.
Jack, you can't leave
Andrew there;
they'll kill him.
Jack?
Jack, please.
Jack.
Jack?
Yeah.
Is Andrew alive?
Yes. Dispatch an ambulance
to this location.
Get me the damn
satellite coverage!
That's right, just off the road
next to the 31-mile marker.
Please get there
as fast as you can.
What's wrong?
When the trial begins,
you may have
an opportunity to escape.
You have to take it,
even if it's dangerous.
Maybe we'll have
a chance before then.
They're never going to take
their eyes off of me.
It has to be
when their attention
is on the trial.
I don't want to get
out of here without...
Forget about me.
You have to take every chance.
Promise me.
Dad, I-I... I ca...
Yes, you can. You can.
I want you to live
your life, a full life.
I want you to have a family.
That's all
I care about.
You're my baby.
I can't do it.
Yes, you can.
You can do it.
Come on now.
Chloe, you want me
to get that?
No.
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's me.
I was just looking
at the C.H.P. dispatch report.
Andrew is in really bad shape.
I will never forgive you.
Do you hear me?
Chloe, I understand
how you feel, but you've
got to think
through this clearly.
We have terrorists on U.S. soil.
They've bombed a train,
and they've kidnapped
the Secretary of Defense.
Right now our only chance is
to follow this hostile and hope
that he leads us
to Secretary Heller.
No, I'm not listening
to you anymore. This is over.
I'm going to Driscoll. No, you won't,
Chloe, because you know I'm right.
No, I don't.
Chloe, if you didn't
believe in what I was doing,
you'd have turned
me in already.
I hate that this
is happening.
So do I.
Chloe, I can't do
this without you.
I need your help to stop them.
Chloe.
What?
Are you with me?
Yeah.
I'll call you as soon
as I have the satellite.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Miss Driscoll,
this is Maryanne Taylor.
Thank you.
Hi, Miss Taylor.
I'm very excited to have this
opportunity to help you here.
Hello, Curtis.
Maryanne.
Curtis, take Maryanne
to an empty station,
and get her started
on the data sorts.
Let's go.
You'll be working
over here.
You know, Curtis,
I didn't want
to go over your head,
but you left me no choice.
Is that so?
I'll let it go
if you will.
Get to work,
Maryanne.
Is there a problem?
No. Why?
What are you working on?
Division protocol manifest.
I need you to build a firewall
around station four.
Who's that?
Her name
is Maryanne.
I just want to make sure
she doesn't stray outside
the area of her
assignment.
Fine.
Chloe, what's going on?
O'Brian.
I don't think
I can do this, Jack.
Why, what's
the matter?
Curtis has me
spread too thin,
and I've got to get you a satellite
on an overloaded
system.
I need more time. We
don't have more time.
In five minutes we're
going to be coming up
on Route 11.
It's a two-lane road.
We'll be
the only cars for miles.
There's no way I can follow him
without being seen.
All right.
I think I know
a way I can speed this up.
I'll get back to you.
Chloe, the satellite subsystem
tanked
and Driscoll wants these
updates, like, now.
Okay, I'll be right there.
I hope Driscoll
doesn't get too upset.
She really overreacts
sometimes.
Oh, this happened
to me a few days ago.
You can retrieve
all your files
from the auto backups
in the server room.
Good idea.
Yeah?
All right, I managed
to steal you a block of time,
but there's no
continuous coverage
in the area you're in.
I'll have to order
a reposition.
Fine, then do it.
Hold on.
Looks like
we're catching a break.
He's pulling into a gas station.
I hope he stays there a while,
'cause this is going
to take some time.
Get back to me
as soon as you got it.
Okay, I will.
You're Edgar, right?
Yeah.
Hi, I'm Maryanne Taylor.
Erin Driscoll asked me
to come in
and help on
data logistics.
Yeah, I heard something
about that. Hi.
Hi. So, um, can you do me
a favor?
A favor?
Yeah, you know,
everyone's really busy
and I just feel like
I'd be more useful
if I had an overall
on what's going on today.
The Secretary of Defense
has been kidnapped.
I know that.
I mean tactically.
I really don't have time
for this. I'm a little busy.
Why don't you
just give me
the main points, okay?
All right,
we think Jack Bauer
is following one
of the terrorists.
We think? Yeah, it's a
little loose right now.
He's off on his own doing
this, and we can't find him.
I thought Bauer didn't
even work here anymore.
He doesn't.
Driscoll gave him the
authority to do this one thing.
All right.
Thanks, Edgar.
Richard...
how long do you think it's been?
What?
How long do you think you've
been sitting here like this?
Three, four hours.
It's been less
than 30 minutes.
Time is the first thing
you lose track of
with sensory
disorientation.
And it only gets worse.
This is illegal!
You can't keep me here.
You'll be here until you tell me
what I need to know.
I told you everything I know!
Your father was kidnapped
by terrorists.
Our polygraph analysis tells us
that you're hiding something
that might help us find him.
Just tell me
what it is
and all this stops.
You're not going to do this.
If you don't care enough
about your father
to tell me what
I need to know,
I'll get it out of you this way.
You're not going
to do this!
Please!
No!
You're not going
to do this!
Stop it! Stop it!
O'Brian.
What's your time frame
on the reposition?
Suspect's going to be headed
back out on the road
any minute.
My request's still in the queue.
Chloe, we've got to get that
satellite coverage up and running now.
There's nothing I can do.
You're going to have to find
a way to keep him from
getting back on the road.
It's going to take as long
as it takes. Just hurry.
Okay, I will.
Why is Debbie here?
What did you do?
I called her and asked her to come over.
You said that
you would help me.
That you talked
to Father.
Your father's right.
We need to find out who
she told about this morning.
I told you
she didn't see anything!
Then there shouldn't be
any problem.
What did you say
to her?
I told her
that I was concerned
about the two of you
and that I wanted to help.
Mom...
Behrooz,
you know what's at stake.
You do as you're told,
understand?
Debbie, thank you
for coming.
Sure.
Hi.
Come in.
Debbie, please.
Make yourself comfortable
in the living room.
I'll make tea.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm glad
your mom called.
If she and your dad
have problems
with us being together,
we should talk about it.
Debbie...
What's wrong?
You don't understand.
You shouldn't have come here.
Why do you always
say things like that?
Damn it.
O'Brian.
Chloe, what's your bottom line?
Am I going to have
satellite coverage
in the next minute or two?
I'm sorry, Jack.
It's going to take
at least another five.
That's too long. That's
the best I can do.
Damn it. I'm going to have to figure
out a way to keep this guy here.
Keep working on it.
Okay, I will.
Everybody put your hands up now!
You, Don't move!
www.tvsubtitles.net