Previously On 24
David, what have you done?
Excuse me, sir?
I just got a call from the secretary of state telling me about
a covert action against the Chinese consulate in Los Angeles.
That's correct. I sanctioned it.
You authorized an attack on their consulate! That's a military engagement.
It was a covert operation,
We marched onto Chinese soil,
we kidnapped one of their nationals, and in the process the
Chinese consul was killed.
Mr. President
if we don't find that warhead before it's deployed,
ten million americans could face annihilation.
And we could be at war
with a Billion Chinese.
Is he going to make it?
We're going to do the best we can.
I just need him coherent long
enough to get the information about Marwan and the missing warhead.
I know, Jack. You already made me aware of that when you
forced me to sacrifice Paul Raines's life.
I'm so sorry.
You made a choice that killed Paul,
and I'm trying to deal with it.
We both have a job, let's just do it.
I know that he worked
with Marwan on the warhead. Now he needs to tell us where it is.
He doesn't konw. But he knows where Marwan might be.
A factory on sixth.
They're looking for the
warhead in their cities.
They have no idea that it's
going to be delivered by missile.
Start the sequence.
We're done here.
They can't stop us now.
I've been waiting for this.
You're too late.
Kill me.
That won't stop the missile.
Tony, can you see this?
Yeah.
Can you get a source of the transmission?
No, Jack- it's on
an encrypted uplink.
There's no way to trace it.
The following takes place
between 4:00 A.M. and 5:00 A.M.
Tony,it\'s Jack,have you got a lock on the missle?
No,we\'re still trying to find it,Jack,what\'re you gonna do with Marwan?
-We\'re gonna scan the building one more time, then I\'m gonna
bring him in to the CTU, I want you to prep a holding room.
Tony I\'m going out for comm,if you need me,get me on my cell.
Alright,you got it!
I want you to try to decode his files,
I\'m gonna go prep the teams to look at the building.
Unbelievable,
how the hell did they manage to assemble a missle capable of carrying a nuclear warhead.
S-series cruise missle,
,steath technology,
they must\'ve smuggled it in piece by piece and then assembled it downside.
If it\'s stealth,we can\'t track it by radar,
what about the targets?
Pull it up.
An S-series has a range of 1800 miles
which means the warhead could be delieverd from the midwest anywhere in the continent to the U.S.
This missle traveling up speed 600 miles an hour
which means it can hit the target in either coast under three hours
Let\'s assume that it\'s heading for the coast,
it\'s not there,could be here,start at any time.
There are no files on this,
he just received what\'s scrambled down alike.
What else did you find?
Nothing,it was clean,
just the laptop and the cell phone.
-Ok,take this (encrypted) outta the phone,
upload it to CTU,see if any other traces.
You got it
This is Bauer.
Jack,
this is president Logan.
I\'m just been told a cruise missle,has just been launched containing the nuclear warhead.
Yes,sir,that\'s correct
Our millitary tracking devices are doing everything they can to find the trajectory of the missle
,but we don\'t have a lot to go on.
What about Marwan,Jack?
You think that he will break?
That won\'t be easy,sir.
He\'s planned and organized everything that\'s happened today,
he\'s committed to his cult,he\'s prepared to die.
I know that you are doing your best,keep me posted.
Yes,sir. I will.
-Let the Joint Chiefs know the situation,
but tell him that this should be eliminated to the intelligence community only.
Sir,
if the nuclear missle has been launched,we have to assume the washington is its target.
What are our options?
We don\'t have many.
Our first priority is to establish a continuity government
and start a quiet evacuation of government personnel in the city.
Bring the cabinet members and the speaker of the house to the bunker,
the congress and Pentagon should be taking to the mountain safe facility.
Right.
Mike,
let them know that this is category one emergency,
tell them nothing more,
we can\'t afford the information leak.
David,
public needs to be warned,cities need to be evacuated.
Not yet,
let\'s see what Bauer comes up at first.
He will die before he talks to us.
I know.
Stand down.
You and I both know that all I wanna do right now is kill you.
But I have my orders.
We\'re running outta time. You win. I\'ve been instructed to ask you what you want?
What I want is already happening.
-The death and destruction of the innocent life is means to the end.
Why don\'t we just skip to the end.
To the end?
Everything that you did today,
you (defer) a reason for your people,what do you want to change?
I have no interest having a political discussion with you.
-I\'m on an unique position to make things happen,
I have the ears of the president of the U.S. right now.
You have the power to make any kind of the deal that you want.
And I promise you,
you will do more for you and your people if you cooperate with me than if you let that missle hit its target
You tell me where the missle is headed,
you help me to stop it,
then I guarantee you that you will talk to the president,
and he will listen to you,he has no choice.
Right here,right now,
you have the chance to get what you want.
I\'ve already had,agent Bauer.
Of till this day
every elected official
and citizen of America
will know that america can not intervene our lives nor countries
with impunity.
Besides,your presidency means only one to mention-
evil.
That\'s you see us?
Yes,
and vulnerable.
Chloe,
come here.
What?
You\'re never gonna believe what I just found,
I got names of some calls received on Marwan\'s cellphone
take a look.
Richard Heler
That\'s right secetary of denfence Heler's son
called Marwan a week ago.
Did you tell anyone yet?
No.
Just you.
I'll let Buchanan know.
With every minute that passes, the missile's target zone widens.
We need to get updates from regional teams.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but you need to hear this.
Edgar just pulled a name off Marwan's cell phone.
It was from a call he received last week.
Who called him?
Richard Heller.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
We ran the number and it came up as originating from Richard Heller's cell phone.
That must be how Marwan knew where secretary Heller was going to be yesterday morning.
You think Richard helped to plan his own dad's kidnapping?
I don't know.
Where is he now?
Well, it's 4:00 A.M.
He's at home asLeep, I guess.
Where does he live, Chloe?
Van nuys.
We have field teams in the area?
I don't know.
I'll pull it up on the ip phone.
Yes, we do.
Dispatch them.
I'll call secretary Heller, tell him his son's being brought back in.
Chloe, does Audrey know about this?
No.
It's more of a management conversation, don't you think?
This is o'brian.
Your team has been issued new orders.
You are to dispatch immediately to van nuys.
Audrey, you got a minute?
Yeah, sure.
What is it?
It's about your brother, Richard.
Is he all right?
I assume he is, yeah.
What do you mean?
We just found out that Habib Marwan got a call from Richard's cell phone a week ago.
I'm sorry, but that's absurd.
We don't know what it means yet,
but Buchanan is sending a team over to pick Richard up right now.
Tony, my brother was already brought in once today and he was cleared.
Yeah, I know.
But this call definitely connects him to Marwan and the missile.
Look, I don't know how he got mixed up in this, but my brother is not a terrorist.
Audrey,
Richard's phone number was found in the received registry of Marwan's sim card.
Does my father know about this?
Buchanan's calling him right now.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell him, yeah.
Jack, we got something.
W hat?
Richard Heller called Marwan a week ago.
We're sure about this?
Yeah, they're bringing him to CTU.
I want to question this kid myself.
We need to get back there now.
Put the suspect in the vehicle.
We're headed back to CTU now.
It doesn't matter where you take me.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
This is Bauer.
Jack, were you able to get anything out of Marwan?
No, we're going to bring him back to CTU.
We think we got a better chance of breaking him there.
We're about ten minutes out.
Curtis, you okay?
Yeah!
Can you see the shooters?
They're on the roof behind us.
Go!
Notify the perimeter we no longer have Marwan in custody!
Perimeter teams, Marwan's escaped!
He's headed towards the southwest sector.
Chloe, what have you got on Marwan?
Nothing-
he already ditched the transpo vehicle and we can't find him on satellite.
How did his people get into that area?
They didn't-they must have been there before us.
Marwan secured the location.
All right,
have perimeter teams comb the nearby buildings for remaining hostiles,
then shift personnel to tracking the missile.
We lost him, Jack.
Damn it, Tony, how?
They dumped their vehicle on the freeway.
In the chaos, Marwan must have gotten into another car and driven off.
We're trying to analyze the satellite right now,
but the images are too noisy.
How does Buchanan want to handle this?
I'm here, Jack.
Finding Marwan is becoming less likely.
With that missile in the air,
we have to follow primary leads only.
Right now that's Richard Heller.
Has he arrived yet?
No, our team's on the way to get him.
He'll be back here momentarily.
Bill, I want to interrogate this kid myself.
I understand.
I'll have him ready for you.
Okay, we're on our way in.
Curtis, we need to back to CTU.
They lost Marwan.
We're going to have to track him from there.
What did Buchanan say?
Richard Heller's in first position.
We're going to interrogate him.
Mr. President.
Please, everybody, be seated.
I would like to apologize for the abruptness of your removal from your homes and your offices.
Please know that every precaution had to be taken to ensure the secrecy of your arrival.
The U.S. Has been thrown into a category one emergency.
A cruise missile containing a nuclear warhead has been launched and is now headed for,
we believe, a major U.S. City.
Very possibly washington D.C.
Now,
all branches of the military have been alerted and they're doing everything in their power to locate the missile and to intercept it.
Excuse me, sir.
You're saying that not only do we not know what the missile's target is,
but you don't even know
where the missile is?
That's correct.
When do you plan to inform the public?
As of this time,
we feel that informing the public wouldn't be in the country's best interest.
"We" meaning who, Mr. President?
I feel that way, Mr. Speaker.
Doesn't the public have a right to know the truth?
That's all I have for now.
When I know more, an update will be given.
Thank you.
Mr. President.
Yes, Don.
S ir,
I do not wish to question your decision in front of the cabinet,
but I think that you're making a grave mistake in not alerting the public.
Look, I've thought a lot about this and...
I'm certain it's the right course.
Well, if I may say so, sir, you do not seem certain.
It's a difficult day for all of us, Don.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Mike,
what's going on here?
Meaning what?
Logan was sworn in a few hours ago,
we're under a massive terrorist attack-he needs all the help he can get.
He understands that and he's seeking advice from everywhere.
Not from his cabinet.
Or the congressional leadership.
Give it time, Don.
Give it time.
Tactical's at Richard's house,
they're going through his things right now.
What about Jack?
Jack and Curtis are on their way back.
Someone has to tell Audrey that Jack's going to be interrogating her brother.
Audrey's not going to want to let Jack near her brother.
It can't be helped.
If Richard knows something about that missile...
it's funny, this morning Jack and Audrey were planning their future.
Now he's responsible for her husband's death,
and he may have to torture her brother.
And yet...
every move he's made has been the right one.
Not if he wanted to be with her.
Look, Michelle...
everything that's happened here today,
it's been hard going through it with you again.
It's been hard for me, too.
And I...
look at what this job does the people in our positions,
and I realize...
I want us to be together again,
but it's go to be away from all this.
You want us to leave our jobs?
We've spent the last 12 years of our lives doing this.
Where would we go?
What would we do?
I don't care.
People start over every day, if it's important to them.
You're asking me to leave the only thing I've ever done.
Yes...
I am.
This is beyond belief!
I cannot be brought here!
Audrey, you got to get me out of here.
These guys broke into my house.
This is so illegal.
All right, Richard, listen.
Just calm down, okay?
Listen to me.
Your phone number came up on the cell phone of a terrorist, all right?
That's what they said.
That's insane.
You know that.
Audrey.
Now listen, ok, just right...
Yes.
They have to get him into holding now.
Audrey!
Audrey, don't let them do this!
Don't let them do this to me!
Who's interrogating him?
Jack.
What?
You are not going to do this.
You are not going to torture my brother.
I'll be right in there.
I don't want to hurt Richard, but we're out of time-
he knows something, and I'm going to find out what it is.
And what if he doesn't?
You're aware that he called Marwan.
It came up on his cell phone.
There has got to be an explanation for that.
Let me talk to him.
You honestly believe that you can interrogate your own brother?
It's because he's my brother,
maybe I can get something out of him that you can't, Jack.
Please, just give me five minutes.
Please.
Take five minutes.
Thank you.
Mike.
Don.
How's, uh, President Logan managing?
Given the circumstances, he's doing very well.
I noticed that ex-President Palmer is here with him.
Yes, he brought the former President in to advise.
Yeah, well, that's probably a good idea.
Palmer's been at the helm in this kind of crisis before.
He knows how to lead.
President Logan doesn't have any problem leading,
if that's what you're getting at.
Oh, no, not at all.
It's just that if he's not going to ask his cabinet for help,
the leadership, it comforts me, somewhat, that he's in good hands.
Is there something else you wanted to say, Don?
Yeah, yeah, there is.
The people elected john Keeler to run this country.
In his absence, Logan is expected to take over.
But if he's not up to the task,
mike, it is I, speaker of the house, and not David Palmer, who steps up.
Understood.
And let me assure you, that's not the case.
Logan is in complete control.
Excuse me, Don, I got to get back.
Sure.
Excuse me, Mr. President.
We may have a problem.
What is it?
Don Ashton.
He's been asking a number of questions and raising concerns as to President Palmer's role here.
That's too bad.
We have more important things to worry about at the moment.
Sir, as the speaker of the house,
he can create problems which you don't need right now.
Mike's right, sir.
Don's very ambitious.
Now that he's next in line to the presidency,
he'll look to exploit any angle he can.
He won't put his ambition in front of national security.
No, he won't see it in those terms, sir.
In his eyes, national security and his personal ambition are one and the same.
What do we do?
Show him who's in charge.
everything set up?
Yeah, he's ready.
Let's do this.
Audrey!
Get me out of here.
Please, tell them I didn't do anything.
Richard, I want you to listen to me very carefully, okay?
A missile carrying a nuclear warhead was launched by this man: Habib Marwan.
Tell me what you know about him.
Look, I don't know what you're talking about.
CTU has proof that you called him last week, tuesday at 4:00 A.M.
I don't know any Habib Marwan or anything about a missile.
You have got to believe me, Audrey.
Richard, that missile is in the air right now, heading toward a city.
Please, Richard, just tell me what you know.
I told you, I don't know anything.
Why'd you make that phone call last week?
I didn't make a phone call, Audrey.
What's happened with my son so far?
We decided to let Audrey talk to him first.
They just got started.
Has he confessed to anything yet?
No, sir.
Richard, it's not making sense.
That call was made.
Look, I don't know where you get your information,
Audrey, but it's all bull.
His readings are spiking.
He's holding something back.
Richard...
Richard, I am begging you to talk to me, all right?
If you don't,
there is a man who will come in here and he will get the information from you.
I saw him torture someone today.
It's what he's trained to do.
He won't stop hurting you until you tell him the truth.
Please.
Don't let them do this to me.
Tell me what you know and they won'T.
I don't know what you want from me.
I don'T.
Richard, look at me, look at me.
We have a chance to fix this.
This is not working.
We don't have time to coddle him.
Open up.
I don't care if he is my son, he's playing games now.
All right, Richard, this has gone far enough.
Either you tell us what we want to know or I will let them use every piece of equipment they have to drag it out of you.
You understand that?
Dad, don'T...
Audrey, leave the room.
Dad, please...
now!
I mean it.
Richard, I want you to tell them everything you know, please.
Now what's it going to be, Richard?
Go to hell.
I didn't do anything wrong, I don't have to tell you anything.
There's a nuclear warhead going to detonate somewhere over this country.
Those lost lives will be on your head.
You will be a murderer.
I didn't mean to do anything wrong.
I swear.
What did you do, Richard?
Tell me what you did.
A week ago, I was...
I was at a bar and...
there was this girl and her boyfriend...
okay?
Right.
What were their names?
I don't know.
They wanted to party and I...
we...
we went back to my place.
We got high...
then...
I guess there was time for one of them to make a call on my phone.
How?
When we were in bed.
So while you were in bed with her,
he used your phone in the other room.
He wasn't the one in the other room, dad.
I was with him.
She must have been the one that made the call.
So, you were set up?
Yeah.
I guess so, dad.
Did they leave you with a number or an address?
No.
What kind of a car were they driving?
They didn't have one.
I drove.
Where did you drop them off afterwards?
I didn'T.
They took a cab.
Do you remember the name of the cab company?
No, dad, I don'T.
Get in touch with every cab company that works in the area.
I want their log books.
Get me a sketch artist now.
I'll run it.
Take over.
So now you know.
I suppose you're even more disgusted with me, huh, dad?
This is not about how you choose to live your life, son.
This is about how you've put this country in jeopardy.
If you had told us this information yesterday,
maybe these terrorist attacks would not have occurred.
No, don't you put that on me, dad.
'Cause yesterday I didn't know that that night had anything to do with these attacks.
You should have told us everything.
I'll wait outside.
You made a profound mistake today, Richard.
Based on this information here,
we can start to develop a contingency plan.
You got the cab company?
Better than that.
We got the cab driver.
He dropped the couple off at an apartment complex in panorama city called the mercerwood.
Did you talk to the apartment manager?
Yes, we gave him a description of the guy and the girl.
He says he knows what unit they're in.
Okay, Jack, you take this.
I'm gonna need our best field ops.
I want Curtis and castle.
I'm going to need Curtis here with me.
Then you got to give me Tony.
All right.
What about the phone call to Marwan?
I used our digital comm software to analyze Richard's phone.
The phone call to Marwan activated a listen-in.
He was able to hear all of Richard's calls after that night.
That's why Marwan knew that secretary Heller was visiting Richard off book yesterday.
Anything on the missile?
We've been running military protocols, but so far nothing.
Do we know if President Logan is going to make an announcement?
As of now, the President still thinks that would do more harm than good.
Please, as you were, everybody.
Be seated.
Gentlemen and ladies,
considering the crisis that we face today,
I felt it prudent to enlist the assistance of ex-President Palmer.
In what capacity, sir?
Excuse me.
Sir, everybody in this room has a title and specific function.
Exactly what position will President Palmer be occupying?
I'm here solely as an advisor.
Not only to the President, but to anyone here who requests my counsel.
President Palmer's outside the chain of command,
if that's what you're asking me, Don.
Asking for a clarification, sir.
The missile carrying the nuclear warhead was launched from a location in central iowa.
It's becoming more and more likely that the target is on or near one of the coasts.
It's clearly going to be new york or D.C.
Why aren't we evacuating those two cities?
I disagree, jennie.
It's not clear.
And if you start to evacuate these two cities,
then you may have an unauthorized mass exoduses of boston, philadelphia, baltimore, atlanta...
that's a situation I don't think the President should be dealing with.
Maybe the President should be telling us that himself.
Please, Mr. Speaker,
I've discussed this option with a number of domestic experts including President Palmer,
and that's my assessment as well.
What about air defense?
We going to stand by and let the airspace over these cities remain undefended?
We have a limited number of f-18 interceptor jets at our disposal.
They need to be augmenting the search for this missile,
and not deployed in a wait-and-see mode.
Mr. Palmer, I'm sure that we all appreciate your desire to help,
but the constitution has determined who the decision makers should be at this time.
I think you're overstepping your bounds.
In the first place, it's Mr. President, Don.
And it is the content of my statements you should be addressing.
David.
It's true, you are to be addressed as President.
It's an expression of respect,
but not a functional title.
I understand that, sir.
But you have to understand, I've been through this crisis before.
Yes, but we are here now.
The appointed and the lawful representatives of the people of the united states.
Mr. President...
David, there will be no more discussion on this matter.
Your point has been taken.
However, Ashton has made a good point, and I want to address his concerns.
Perhaps it's best if I excused myself.
Perhaps.
Ladies, gentlemen...
Mr. Speaker, I think you're right.
We'll put those jets over D.C.
And new york.
Did you see it on the inside feed?
Yes.
It went exactly as you'd hoped.
We won't have any more problems with Don Ashton today.
I hope you're right.
We'll be monitoring everything on three.
All right.
Make sure LAPD's there when we land.
We're going to need transport to the site.
They've already been called.
ok
Tony, wait.
I-I can'T...
I can't spend another day without you.
I'm ready...
to leave here.
I'm ready to go with you.
Tony.
Be careful.
Right.
They're setting up a remote feed.
Richard's going to help Jack identify the suspects when they get onsite.
Then what?
Then they'll let him go.
His motives certainly weren't seditious.
Dad, I feel so lost.
I know, sweetheart.
Ms. Raines?
Yes.
Jack Bauer's on line two for you.
Thank you.
You take it, sweetheart.
I'll be on the floor.
Hello.
Audrey, it's Jack.
I know you don't want to talk to me right now,
but there are a few things I need to say.
All right.
Look, I know with everything that's happened today,
you've seen me do things that...
before now, you thought were unimaginable.
I would have been happy to skip today.
Yeah, me, too.
But the truth of it is,Audrey,
I never believed you could ever really love me if you'd known about everything I've done.
Jack, I-I can'T...
Audrey, please, let me finish.
These were the things that I was running away from.
That's why I moved to D.C.
That's why I stopped doing field work.
That's why i don't work at CTU.
All I know is that you're back in it, and it's too much for me, Jack.
I know.
I know...
the last thing i ever wanted to do was push you away from me.
God, Audrey, I love you,
but this is how the job has to be done.
I just want you to know how sorry I am that it had to involve you and the people you care about.
Look, you don't have to say anything now.
Please, just promise me, as soon as this is over...
we can talk about everything that's happened.
Audrey, please.
Jack.
I gotta call you back later, okay?
All right.
Yeah.
Jack, tactical's just got the schematics ready.
What are the approach parameters?
They want us to go in from the west.
Edgar.
This is the composite the sketch artist made based on Richard Heller's description.
Get it to Jack and Tony.
Will do.
Now can we go?
We still have plenty of time to get to Marwan.
I don't like cutting it this close.
This is a sketch of the guy that Richard Heller described.
He and the girl are our only leads to finding Marwan,
so once we identify the suspects, it is vital that we take them alive.
Manning.
Curtis, it's Jack.
We're getting ready to land.
Is everyone set?
Yeah.
We're all set.
Richard's ready to make a positive I.D.
Copy that.
I want you to stay on this channel.
You got it.
We're a go!.
I need you to make sure that no LAPD units go inside our established perimeter!
Am I clear?!
Yes sir!
Okay, let's go!
Are you ready?
They found us.
What are you talking about?
A helicopter just landed a block away.
So what?
So- they found us.
Damn it!
Hey, we can't go together.
Why not?
Because one of us has to stay here in the apartment.
Why?
Because if they think that we're still here,
then it gives the other a chance to escape.
You've got to be joking.
One of us is going to get caught to save the other?
Exactly.
It's gonna be you.
Jack, what do you want to do?
Move in on the apartment immediately?
No, I want you and castle to take up positions here on the roof of the main building in the center of the complex.
Team A, B and C, acknowledge when you're in position.
Team A on site (B C in position)
Copy that.
Let's go.
Okay.
Lapd, I need the entry code for the south gate.
I'm in.
Okay, I've got a visual on the apartment.
There's activity inside.
Macallan, meet me at the front door of the apartment.
Have your people cover us.
On my way.
Go.
Pick it.
It's ready.
Put your hands where I can see them!
Put your hands where I can see them now!
He's dead.
Get a picture of him.
Send it back to CTU.
Got it.
Tony, this is Jack.
Has anybody reported any outside movement?
No. Why?
The man is dead.
The girl is no longer in the apartment.
She couldn't have gotten past the perimeter teams.
I know, but there are plenty of other places to hide.
I want all teams to maintain their positions until we have time to search the other apartments.
Roger that.
All teams, hold position.
Drop your gun.
All right!
All right.
Kick it away.
Look, he's injured.
Why don't you let him go?
You can take me instead.
Your two-way.
Turn around.
On your knees, hands on your head.
Cuff him.
Get up.
Curtis, you should have it.
Whoa.
Is that him?
Is that him?!
Yeah.
Jack, that's him.
We have a positive id on the picture.
Okay, thank you, Curtis.
Tactical, this is Bauer.
I need five teams of two to initiate a search of the complex.
Start with the outer buildings along the perimeter, move your way in.
Copy that, they're being deployed now.
Tony, this is Jack.
We're initiating the search.
Tony, do you copy?
Castle, why is Almeida not on comm?
Tony you copy? Tony come in!
All teams, this is Bauer.
Castle is down Almeida is missing.
I repeat: Almeida is missing and possibly a hostage.
Our communications have been compromised.
Move over to secondary frequency.
CTU, I need more tactical personnel now.
CTU, do you read?
Michelle.
You heard him, people.
Shift profiles.
We may have a hostage situation.
Move.
Now!
www.tvsubtitles.net