Whatever you've planned next
is going to fail.
Just like everything else
you've tried today.
Almost 40 dead in a train crash,
many more near the San Gabriel
Island Nuclear Plant.
We managed to stop the other 103
power plants from melting down.
That's what America will remember -
that we stopped you.
No, this country will forever be afraid
to let their leaders appear in public.
For all the hatred that you have
for this country,
you don't understand it
very well.
Marwan...
The police report file
has been distributed.
In the next few minutes,
CTU will be alerted that
the military pilot
and his family
are missing.
What do you think
we should do?
We have to make sure CTU
is too busy to realize
its significance.
Jack Bauer is alive
and in my custody.
I will return him to you unharmed
in exchange for Behrooz Araz.
He'll be overseeing the operation.
BILL:
Let's talk about
what happens if we don't
agree to the exchange.
We don't get Jack Bauer back,
for one thing.
That can't be
the deciding factor here.
Well, most importantly,
if we don't
go through
with this exchange,
we may lose an oportunity
to trap Marwan.
Is my mother
in the van?
She was working with
you. Where is she?
- I don't know.
- I don't want to die.
( gunshot )
I got their sniper.
Let's move out.
Why'd you give them the kid?!
It's okay, he's been
double tagged.
We'll be tracking him.
BAUER: I managed to
short-circuit the phone lines
in the building
that I was being held.
If you can find
two service obstructions
at the same coordinates,
we can get to Marwan.
( beeping )
We have a location where
Marwan was holding Jack.
( ringing )
Yes?
There'a problem.
Just as I was about
to do a preflight check,
they grounded the plane.
Resolve this now.
Did you make your report to
the chief mechanical officer?
I was just about to head
over there right now.
Don't let me hold you up.
( silenced gunshot )
It was just a false alarm.
All right.
I'll clear it for takeoff.
We placed multiple
trackers on Behrooz Araz,
but those
are no longer transmitting,
which means that Marwan's men
found and destroyed them.
Are you close to finding Marwan?
We may be, sir.
Jack Bauer managed
to tag the location
where he was being held.
We're preparing to mount a raid
on that location as we speak.
I want Marwan found... now.
I've asked Secret Service
to secure a landing site
so I can be on the ground
to address the nation
before the 11:00 news.
Sir, we believe that you're
safer in the air right now.
I have been flying for 20 hours.
The American people need to hear
from me now, not tomorrow.
Then may I like to suggest you
do it from Air Force One?
It may not be optimal,
but at least you'll
get your message across.
I appreciate your concerns,
but I'm going to give my speech
when I get to Los Angeles.
I'll inform the press corp,
give them enough time
to notify their outlets.
Yes, Mr. President.
Just make sure I'm briefed
on Bauer's progress
before I go on the air.
Of course.
What's Jack's status?
His team just arrived
at Marwan's location.
They should be in place
in a few minutes.
CHLOE ( over phone ):
CTU Com.
This is Bauer.
Strike teams are moving
into final positions.
We're about five minutes out.
How are you on your end?
We're coordinating backup teams,
we have building plans on line.
- Chloe?
- Yeah, it's me.
- Michelle brought me back in.
- Good.
Are the satellites
in position?
Yes. We've been
monitoring the area
for the past five minutes,
but there's been no activity.
How's Paul Raines doing?
Is he still in surgery?
Uh, no, he just got out.
Chloe, I'm glad
to have you back.
We're going to need your help.
Look, is Audrey there?
I think so.
Let me speak to her.
Hold on.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello.
Audrey, I have Jack on the line.
Are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Hold for Jack.
O kay.
JACK:
Audrey?
Jack... you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
How's Paul doing?
They just finished operating,
but they said
that he's going to make it.
I'm waiting
to talk to the doctors.
Good. I'm glad.
Look, Audrey, I know we
have to talk about how
I handled everything
with Paul.
Yeah, we do.
It's just...
It's really hard right now.
Yeah, I-I understand.
Are you still out in the field?
Yeah. We're getting ready
to move on Marwan.
Be careful.
Yeah, I'll call you
as soon as it's done.
Yeah... right.
I just got off
the phone with DOD.
They want to know
what our status is.
Jack's team has been deployed
to Marwan's location.
He should begin
the assault any minute.
Did you get a read
on how many
hostiles are inside?
Based on the infrared scan,
we counted eight.
BILL: Did we pick up voice transmission
that could indicate
that one of them is Marwan?
No, but we know he was
there 25 minutes ago
when Jack left the building.
If the information
on that hard drive
is discovered by the Americans,
it will jeopardize
the next phase of our plan.
Well, it's not here.
No, you haven't
looked hard enough.
I've been searching
for almost an hour.
Aziz told one of his men
he hid a backup copy
of those files in his apartment.
Well, why didn't Aziz
tell you where he hid it?
Because he was killed
before he could tell me.
Look, Anderson shared
this apartment with Aziz
Maybe Anderson knows
where the hard drive is.
Keep looking.
I'll try to contact him.
Bravo three-niner in the air,
heading 55-2.
AIR TRAFFIC:
Roger, Bravo three-niner,
you are cleared
for 3-5 thousand feet.
Bravo three-niner,
ascending to 3-5 thousand feet.
( beeping )
I'm in the air.
I should reach the target
in 45 minutes.
We have a problem.
What kind of problem?
Aziz, he hid a backup
copy of his files
in your apartment
on hard drive.
We haven't been
able to find it.
Ask Aziz.
Aziz is dead.
I don't know about a hard drive.
You have no idea where
he might have kept it?
If I knew where it was,
I'd tell you.
( fizzing )
I'm not trying
to get myself killed.
I'll get back to you.
Okay, in order
to flush Marwan out,
I want you to lead your men
down the main corridor.
He'll try and escape
through the left flank.
That's where I'll find him.
Tac team's ready
to go in on your word.
Have they set
the charges on the door?
Yes.
Gentlemen, we are a go.
We've got a green light.
Teams A and B,
move into position.
All teams, move
in on target.
Prepare to ignite
charges on my mark.
JACK:
Three, two, one.
Blow the door!
( gunfire )
Go! Go! Move! Move! Move!
Delete the files!
Delete everything!
( rapid gunfire )
( two gunshots )
( grunting )
( gunfire over speakers )
( rapid gunfire )
Hold your fire!
Clear!
Marwan's not here.
Notify the perimeter.
Team One and
Team Two, come in.
Marwan is not in the building.
Maintain your perimeter.
Come on!
I can't stop this thing from deleting.
This doesn't make sense.
This room's hot. Get your
men out of here!
Get your men out of here now!
Jack, what's happening?
What's going on over there?
- You OK?
- Yeah, I think so.
Check your men!
Jack, if you can hear me, respond!
Michelle, Marwan's escaped.
He just blew up the hard drives
to all his computers.
He's trying to cover his tracks.
I'm going off comm
If you want me I'm going
to be on my cell.
Chloe
Get data forensics in there now
and start a hard target
search for Marwan.
Get me a medic!
Medic!
You can't stop it
Stop what?
The course you'll be on
What's going to happen
within the hour?
Mrs. Raines?
Yes.
Your husband is in Recovery.
How is he?
He's stable, but
one of the bullets
did some damage
to his spine.
Right now he's paralyzed
from the waist down.
Is it permanent...?
It's too early to tell.
That'll take weeks,
maybe months,
before we fully
understand the extent
of damage to his spine.
So it's possible he could regain
the use of his legs.
It's possible, yes.
But not likely.
Again, it's
too early to tell.
We could go over
the details later,
but I'd be lying to you if
I told you I was optimistic.
A lot depends
on his attitude,
his support system-
emotional as well as medical.
Does he know?
Yes. I just told him.
I'm sure he'd like
to see you.
Excuse me, can you
give us a minute?
Oh, no, don't even think
of feeling sorry for me.
Whatever they say,
I'm going to walk again.
I know you will.
So, where's Jack?
He's still out in the field.
He called
a little while ago,
wanted to know
how you're doing.
He knows that bullet
was meant for him.
I was just trying to
push him out of the way,
I didn't expect
to get shot myself.
What you did was very,
very brave, Paul.
LAPD's widening their
search perimeter,
but so far they're
coming up empty.
Jack said something might
happen within the hour.
If we don't find Marwan...
We're going to find him.
Did you secure Marwan yet?
No. He must've slipped
through the perimeter.
How the hell could you
let that happen?
Doesn't matter
how it happened.
What matters
is that he's gone
and we're doing everything
we can to find him.
What exactly are you
doing to find him?
We've widened the perimeter,
set up a search grid.
State police
and LAPD are conducting a sweep.
Jack's on line two.
He says he's got something.
Put him on the speaker.
Jack, it's Michelle.
You're also on with Tony
and Bill Buchanan
from Division.
Okay, look, Marwan had an area
set up for forging documents.
Some of them made it
through the explosion.
We managed to secure a number
of names and faces.
Agent Castle is uploading
them to your server now.
I want you to cross-reference
them with the watch lists.
We'll get on it right away.
Okay, get back to me
if you've got a match.
Edgar...
I'm initializing the facial
recognition software now.
Good.
BUCHANAN:
Michelle...
Listen, I'm sorry
if I snapped.
It's okay.
We're all under
a lot of pressure.
You holding up?
Fine.
Edgar, how's that uplink?
Coming up.
Chloe...
how long has Buchanan been
at Division? I don't know.
It took them a while to fill
Chapelle's position. 6 months?
Where he was
before that?
Seattle, I think.
Seattle?
Yeah, that's where
Michelle was posted
while you were in jail, right?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Got a match.
( cell phone ringing )
This is Bauer.
MICHELLE: Jack, we have got a
match on one of those photos.
He's on the FBI's watch list.
His name is Mitch Anderson.
What do we got on him?
Ex-military,
arrested for drug possession.
Served time in military prison,
was dishonorably
discharged four years ago.
Since then he's been
hired as a mercenary
in a number of conflicts
around the world,
came back to the U.S.
about a year ago.
Is he under active
investigation?
He was moved up the list
when we raised the alert,
but he wasn't made
a priority.
The Bureau sent an agent over
to check out his apartment.
Has the agent
checked back in yet?
They may still be in transit.
Okay, I want you to get me
an address on Anderson.
Start digging up as much
information as you can.
And get me a contact number
for the FBI agent.
I'm on it.
FBI.
I'm looking for Mitch Anderson.
( knocking on door )
This FBI Agent Drake.
Please open the door.
( gunshot through silencer )
( body thuds )
( cell phone rings )
Agent Drake.
Hi, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm working with CTU.
I'm looking for a man
named Mitch Anderson.
Your office said
you were investigating him.
I just got to his apartment
a few minutes ago.
What do you mean,
he's not there?
No. Why is CTU involved?
Is there new information
about Anderson?
We have evidence connecting him
to a man named Habib Marwan.
Marwan's been responsible
for all the terrorist activity
earlier today.
We also have reason
to believe
he's planning
another attack.
Well, how is
Anderson involved?
I'll advise you
when I get there.
How far away are you?
About ten minutes out.
I'll be here.
Thank you.
MAN ( over phone ):
Yes?
We had a slight delay.
I'm heading over there now.
What about Anderson?
He's in the air,
on his way to the target.
Everything's on schedule.
Are your people in place?
Yes. We're ready to deploy.
Good. I'll see you
when we arrive.
Sorry, but this
just isn't cutting it.
The tone is all wrong.
Sir, maybe I
could give the
speechwriters
a clearer idea
of what you want.
This is one
of the most traumatic days
in the history of this country.
What I want...
is a speech that is equal
to the occasion.
( sighs )
Give me a few minutes,
will you, Robert?
Let me... think about this
a little while longer.
Of course,
Mr. President.
Oh, and, Robert, ask my son
to step in, will you?
Yes, sir.
Dad?
Well, a quick trip to Mexico,
a low-key state visit,
and then we'd finally have
some time to spend together.
It's okay. The, uh, press corp's
been keeping me entertained.
You know,
ever since your mother died,
I promised myself
I'd be there for you.
You've been doing
what you had to do.
I could, uh, use your help
right about now.
I'm going to be
addressing the nation
in about one hour,
and I still don't have
a speech that
I'm happy with.
( chuckles ):
I'm no speechwriter.
No, I know.
But you've got a level head,
and you're about
the most decent person
I know.
As far as I'm concerned,
you represent the very best
this country has to offer.
So...
what do you want to hear
the president say
when he addresses you tonight?
The truth.
We've been attacked
by terrorists.
Americans are dead.
The man responsible
is still at large,
and we are
by no means certain
that we can catch him
before he strikes again.
What happened earlier...
may be nothing compared
to what happens next.
That's the truth, Kevin.
Is that what you think
I should say?
I don't know.
Neither do I.
But the fact remains...
...I have to say something.
Y-You want me to help you
figure it out?
Absolutely.
Agent Drake?
Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon now!
Are you Agent Bauer?
Yes!
Now, holster your weapon!
- I need to se your I.D.
- I don't have
identification-
I'm working with CTU
on a provisional basis.
I talked to you ten minutes ago.
Call Division
and confirm.
Agent Drake,
just take it easy.
He's with me.
Agent Hart, CTU.
Now, I'm gonna
holster my gun.
I'm gonna show you
my credentials.
I'm sorry.
With everything
that happened today,
you can't be too careful.
I understand.
Agent Bauer, we just
intercepted a call
indicating that Anderson
was in possession
of computer files that could
tell us Marwan's next target.
What's the source
of the intercepted call?
I'm still waiting
for the details.
Did you find the apartment
in this condition?
No. My ASAC thinks
that Anderson
may have hidden a backup copy
of the files here.
I was trying to find it.
Right now Anderson's
our only lead.
We're gonna stay here and help you
finish the job.
Do a canvass.
We'll take upstairs.
( phone ringing )
Where are you?
I'm almost in position.
What's the problem?
Is my cover in place?
I've told you before-
yes.
You'll be 100% safe.
Marwan, they have
to believe I'm dead.
They will. My people
have taken care of this.
They better.
Because once this is done,
the entire world is gonna be
looking for me.
Mm-hmm. I understand.
Yeah, I'll tell him.
Thanks, Ruben.
( sighs )
- Edgar.
- Yeah?
I have some bad news.
Do you want me to tell you here
or somewhere private?
- What?
- I just got off the phone with Ruben Weiss
from OSHA, and he said
they're not gonna be able
to get in the area
where your mother died.
for a few weeks, maybe months.
Why not?
Think about it.
Half-life? Radiation?
What does that mean?
Well, he didn't spell it out,
but I think that means
you're gonna have to have
your funeral without the body
Of your mother
I can't deal with this
right now, Chloe.
Michelle needs prioritized lists
for Marwan's pursuit plan.
Oh.
Okay, good.
Do you want me
to do that for you?
No.
LAPD's locked down the area
where Marwan was last seen.
I need you to review
the search grid.
All right.
Okay, thanks.
Michelle.
When were you planning
on telling me?
About what?
TONY:
About you and Buchanan.
Never. Because it's none
of your business.
Michelle.
Before you worked with him at Division,
you worked with him
in Seattle on Homeland Security
restructuring, right?
- Yeah.
- We were still married then.
Legally, yes.
Did you sleep with him
while we were married?
No.
I didn't.
But you are now.
Like I said,
it's none of your business.
Edgar, where are those updates?
Coming right up.
( quietly ):
Edgar, what are you doing?
- Miss Dessler.
- Edgar, wait.
- What?
- Wait, before you turn that in,
I made a mistake-
I used Row-Major format
instead of Column-Major.
Why would you do that, Chloe?
You know Row-Major isn't compatible
with our software.
- It'll bring all our processors to a crawl.
- I know. It was a mistake.
I thought it was going
to Division.
Well, fix it.
Chloe, that was
my mistake- why'd
you cover for me?
- You're welcome.
- You'd have had your job back
if you would've let me
hand her the disk.
I thought you had
a lot on your mind.
Agent Bauer?
Yeah?
I checked with the neighbors-
nobody's seen
- Mitch Anderson today.
- Did you talk to the manager?
Yeah, Anderson
kept to himself.
Paid his rent on time-
the ideal tenant.
Okay, thanks.
Agent Drake?
Yes?
Anderson was ex-military,
dishonorably discharged.
This bag is from Vanguard Mills.
They manufacture medals
for the armed forces.
There's a date stamp on it,
three months old.
Anderson left the military
four years ago.
You think he's currently posing
as military.
It's a distinct possibility-
I want you to let
your people know;
we'll do the same.
Have this scanned and send
it over to Chloe at CTU.
You got it.
This is Special Agent Drake.
Can you put me through
to Dawson, please?
Thank you.
( line ringing )
CTU. Almeida.
Tony, it's Jack.
We just found some evidence
that indicates
that Anderson might be posing
as military.
I want you to update
the profiles,
- see if anything comes back.
- All right, I'm on it.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah, this is Drake.
Listen, we just found
credible evidence suggesting
that Anderson is disguised
as military.
That's right.
Yes.
Fine.
No, that's not a problem.
Good.
All right.
Well, thanks.
I'll let you know
if we find anything else.
Hey.
I found something.
It's an external hard drive-
this is exactly
what we're looking for.
That's good work.
Drop the weapon!
( typing )
( whispers ):
Come on.
( phone rings )
Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, it's Jack.
Where's Chloe?
She's busy doing
a systems update.
Okay. I need you to tell
Michelle and Tony
that the FBI agent that I met
at Anderson's apartment
was an impostor working
for Marwan.
I killed her, but not before
she took out my backup.
CTU needs to send out
a team, lock down the apartment
and initiate an investigation.
Do you want to tell them
yourself?
No, you can tell them
in a second.
Right now, I need you to help me
pull some data off a hard drive.
The directory's locked.
Hold on one second;
I'm going to put you on
speakerphone.
Okay, go ahead.
Can you get into the root?
Yeah, but I can't
open the files.
Okay, hold down tab and arrow
until the manufacturer's
code appears.
Okay, I got it.
What are the last three digits
on the part code?
R-Two-Five.
Escape out and enter pass
code C-I-S-Eight-Three-R.
That should backdoor
you into the files.
( whisper ):
Oh, my God.
Jack, did it work?
Yeah, I'm in. I need to speak
to Michelle and Tony now.
I'll get 'em.
Jack's on the line.
Jack, what is it?
I pulled some data
off a hard drive
that we found hidden
in Anderson's apartment.
On it is a flight simulator
and full schematics
to an F-117A Stealth fighter.
Anderson's an experienced pilot.
I know. I also think
he's posing as military.
I believe Mitch Anderson's
trying to steal
a Stealth fighter.
Tony, I'm on my way in.
What's the holdup?
- Have you gotten anything from the airport?
- Hang on, it's coming through.
Central Air Command reports
that an F-117A Stealth fighter
took off on a scheduled mission
about 40 minutes ago.
Now, the pilot did not call in
on schedule.
That was about six minutes ago.
All attempts to contact
that pilot have failed.
Okay, that's it.
We have to assume
Anderson's flying
that plane.
Yeah, I agree.
Is the aircraft armed?
Yeah, standard
non-nuclear ordinance.
We're going to have to work up
a list
of obvious possible targets.
Yeah. Right. I'm working
that up right now.
Wait.
Air Force One is headed to L.A.
Jack, did you hear that?
Yeah, what's the ETA?
11:00 p. m.
Oh, my God.
They're going after
the President.
I'll call Air Force One.
Tony, we don't have a lot of time.
I need you to get me
the recall frequency
for that plane's squadron.
And send Anderson's bio
over to my screen.
Yeah, I'm on it.
- Where's Buchanan?
- He's in Tactical,
talking directly
with the military.
Tell him he's going to have to
tell the Joint Chiefs of Staff
that we believe the likely
target is President Keeler
aboard Air Force One.
You really have been
helpful, Kevin.
I think this speech strikes
just the right note.
Mr. President,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's Michelle Dessler at CTU.
She says it's urgent.
Yes, what is it, Ms. Dessler?
Mr. President, we have reason to
believe that a Stealth fighter
has been stolen by a terrorist...
and is in your airspace
as we speak.
This plane is due
to land shortly,
and I'm about to
address the country.
Just how sure are
we about this?
It's a near certainty,
Mr. President.
We've informed your pilot,
and he's preparing
to combine evasive action
with immediate descent.
You're cleared to land
in Palm Springs.
I'm sure my escort fighters
are perfectly capable
of protecting Air Force One.
Mr. President, this
is a Stealth aircraft,
invisible to radar.
If he finds you,
he may be on you
before your fighter
escort can react.
What are the chances
he'll find us?
We can't be sure, Mr. President.
But the radar signature
of a 747 and four fighter planes
is unmistakable.
You're telling me that this
stolen Stealth plane
will attempt
to shoot me down?
It looks that way,
Mr. President.
I see.
Dad...
It's going to be okay.
It seems our plane
may come under attack.
We're going to take
some precautions.
Get me the Vice President
on the phone.
Yes, sir.
All right, Jack, it should be
coming through right now.
Yeah, I've got it.
Not much to go on.
Parents deceased.
He has a sister named Alicia.
Looks like they might
have lived together
at the same address
for a number of years,
so they might be close.
Any recent contact information?
No. Let me see if I
can find that for you.
No, we don't have any time.
Have you got
- the recall frequency?
- Yeah.
Get ready to patch me through
to Anderson.
Copy that.
Air Force One is descending
through 20,000 feet.
The fighters have formed
a protective shield.
How long before it touches down?
Nine minutes.
And the fighters report
no sign of Stealth aircraft?
Not yet.
Maybe it's not there.
It's there,
we just can't see it.
We're being beaten
by our own technology.
Jack, you're set.
When you hit
your intercom button,
you'll be patched through
to the Stealth fighter.
Copy that.
( beeping )
JACK:
Mitch Anderson, can you hear me?
Captain Anderson,
do you read me?
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm a federal agent.
We know who you are, we know
what you're trying to do.
Sir, I know you can hear me.
Nothing you've done so far
can't be undone.
All you have to do is
change your vector
to heading one-one-
five-southeast.
That'll put you on a fast track
to Andrews Air Force Base.
Once you touch down, then we can
discuss how you want to handle his.
Please just talk to me.
Explain to me
what you're trying to do,
what you're trying
to accomplish.
Why?
I've been going over
your service record.
It's very impressive.
Graduated top of your class,
Air Force Academy.
Highly decorated for your
service in Desert Storm,
including Air Force
Silver Star.
What happened to you?
Explain it to me.
Because what you're trying
to do right now...
I don't think
that's who you are.
I don't think that's how
you want to be remembered.
If I go down,
you have to stay the course.
Do you understand?
Mr. President, I'm... I'm sure
it won't come to that.
KEELER: Charles, you're
the Vice President.
The nation will be
relying on you.
If the worst happens,
think of me
as a casualty of war.
Don't waste time.
Just pick up the torch
and move forward.
Yes, sir, Mr. President.
Mr. President, we think CTU
is in communication
with the pilot of
the stolen aircraft.
Patch it through.
JACK: I've just been notified
by the FBI that they've contacted
your sister, Alicia.
They've advised her
of what's happening.
She's scared.
She wants to talk to you.
All you have to do,
Captain Anderson,
is respond to me, and I'll put her
right through.
( static crackles )
Captain Anderson?
Captain Anderson?!
Chloe, I think
we've been cut off.
Is there an override channel?
He's cut off all
communication circuits.
I don't think there's
anything we can do.
Damn it!
Dad...
I'm scared.
( beeping )
( indistinct pilot chatter )
( radio static crackles )
Was Air Force One just hit?
Was Air Force One just hit?!
( Woman speaking indistinctly
over radio )
Escort pilots report...
Air Force One has suffered
an indirect hit
by an air-to-air missile.
Pieces are falling to
the ground over the desert...
Subtitles by Jaxdahl
Corrections by AKB and ResDog
www.tvsubtitles.net