You killed Tariq?
You can't let Father know.
He wants me dead, because
I messed up with Debbie.
You were determined to kill him,
to kill our own son.
Nothing will stand
in the way of what
needs to be done-
not him, not you.
Your father's
following us.
What?
It was the only way
I could save you.
( gunshot )
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I think I got it.
This is really it.
I can turn off the override
and stop the remaining plants
from melting down.
Did the best I could, sir.
I hope it works.
So do I.
Edgar, what's going on?
Why are some of the reactors
still not shutting down?
Six of the reactors were immune
to the kill sequence.
Contact Bauer. Either he
finds the people responsible
for planning
the override,
or we're looking
at a nuclear holocaust.
Bauer and Audrey Raines left
here about five minutes ago.
Where'd they go?
Falstead Security.
You're going to need to set
things up on your end.
When Jack Bauer
and Audrey Raines
are killed, CTU is going
to know that someone inside
leaked their location.
Divert suspicion.
Fine.
The override device
maintains heat levels
within the reactor.
They can melt down
every one of
those power plants.
The man you saw when you
were being held captive,
right now he's
our only lead.
Stop there.
I think that's him.
They're trying
to seal us off.
Well, shouldn't we call CTU?
No. CTU's gotta
be compromised.
That's the only way
they'd know we were here.
Then who are you calling?
The only person
I can trust right now.
I'm empty.
( screams )
Jack.
JACK:
Tony!
Is there any chance
this is a mistake?
For the remaining six
nuclear reactors,
Arch is taking longer
to shut down.
No. I can recheck it.
Those plants are firmly
in the grip of the override,
which has been sealed off.
We can't get at it.
Did you send a
list of the six
affected cities to the
President? Yes, sir.
What about evacuation
procedures?
We've already alerted
the National Guard.
We're just
waiting to see
how the President
wants us to proceed.
Miss Driscoll,
President's ready.
Okay, put him on.
Mr. President.
I understand we've
been able to shut down
98 nuclear power plants.
Yes, sir,
but as of now, it appears
that our shutdown order will not
be effective with the
six remaining reactors.
Not going to be effective?
What exactly does that mean?
I'm afraid it means
that we could have
six nuclear disasters
on our hands.
What are the casualty
projections if all six plants...
melt down?
450,000 deaths in
the first 24 hours.
The long-range estimate's
in the low millions,
and that's not
taking into account
the resulting cancers
and birth defects.
Why were we able to shut down
the other power plants,
but not these six?
It's because they're still
being controlled
by the terrorists, sir.
You mean because
of the override device
that they stole today?
Exactly.
We have to find
the override device itself.
It's a prototype,
and the terrorists
have the only
one in the world.
All right,
then let's find it.
I'm going to order the
evacuation of those six cities.
Jim, keep me posted.
Yes, Mr. President.
( phone ringing )
All right, let's
get back to work.
Yeah.
Mr. Secretary, it's Jack.
Don't let anyone know
you're talking to me.
We got a problem.
I understand, Marcy.
Let me see what I can do.
I have to take this call.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
First off, sir,
I want you
to know
that Audrey and I
are safe, but there was an
attempt made on our life
at Falstead Security.
What?
A group of assassins, well
armed, well trained, took out
our entire
security detail.
You're gonna need to
send a forensic unit
over to identify the
bodies, but I don't
want anyone at
CTU to know.
Why not?
Because I think someone
over at CTU
is complicit in the attack.
How do you know that?
Sir, CTU is the only agency
that knew where we were.
No one else
had that information.
Is one of Erin's people
working with the terrorists?
Yes, I think so.
I just don't know who,
but it's clear
that they didn't want Audrey
to make the I.D.
of the man she saw
when you guys
were both being held.
I'm sending a Secret Service
detail to pick you two up.
Sir, please
don't do that.
That's not the right
thing to do here.
Why not?
I don't want
anyone to know
where we are.
That way,
I know we'll be safe.
How do you want me
to handle this?
Remember the sequence
we developed
for the Melbourne situation?
Yes.
Try that. I think it'll work.
Okay.
Sir, I've got to go.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I know we're safe.
Jack, take care of Audrey.
Yes, sir, I will.
You okay?
I'm almost
getting used to this.
Yeah.
Tony, is it possible
that we could
have been followed?
No. We're clear.
Where are we going?
We need to lay low for a while.
What kind of communication
do you need?
A wi-fi and a hard line.
All right,
we'll go back to my place.
Okay.
Thank you, Tony.
Wait till you see it
before you thank me.
No, I mean for picking us up,
saving our lives.
I'm sure you're wondering
what's going on.
Not really, no.
Something wrong?
What could be wrong?
I'm not in
the federal prison anymore,
thanks to you
and President Palmer.
Michelle left me.
I...
( sighs )
You know what? Never mind.
Why don't you tell me
what this is all about?
You heard about Audrey and
her father this morning.
Yeah.
We were at Falstead Security
so Audrey
could make an I.D.
of a man she saw
during the kidnapping.
I don't get it. Why?
The secretary's kidnapping
was just a cover.
The terrorists' main objective
is to gain control
of American power plants
from coast to coast.
The man that Audrey saw
is our only lead.
I thought you weren't in
the field anymore, Jack.
I'm not.
The secretary is
my responsibility.
I got caught up in it.
Yeah, well, listen
to me very carefully.
I don't want
to get caught up in it.
So you do whatever
you need to do at my place.
I'm staying out
of it, all right?
Understood.
Today continues to be
a challenge to the strength
of the American spirit.
We have a condition in six
cities across the United States
in which nuclear power
facilities may become unstable.
While we work to regain control
over these facilities,
I am also asking
our National Guard to assist
local authorities to affect
an immediate evacuation
of those six cities.
This evacuation is only
being issued for all persons
living or working...
The President didn't
mention the fact
that there isn't
enough time left
for a complete
evacuation.
If those reactors
melt down,
there are gonna be at least
50,000 dead per city.
We still have time
to try and find
a way to prevent that.
I can tell
you now, Erin,
the chances of doing that
from here are very low.
We have to find
the people who have
the override device.
What about the hospitals
north of there?
All right. Keep checking.
Called Dina's sister.
There's no answer.
All right, I'll take care of it.
You and Rafi go check
the station again.
Okay.
The Americans have been able to
shut down most of the reactors.
How many are under our control?
Six.
More than enough
to break their will,
but I'm gonna have to manage
the override personally,
make sure those six
melt down on schedule.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes.
Take care of your mess.
Don't worry, Madwan.
I give you my word.
My wife and son will be dead
by the end of this day.
( groaning )
We have to get you
to a hospital.
No. Your father knows
I've been shot.
He'll be looking for us
in all the hospitals.
Well, we're going
to have to take a chance.
Mom, you're hurt.
I'll be okay.
You won't.
You need to
get to a doctor.
I'm not afraid of Father.
You should be.
He tried to kill me,
and then he did this to you.
He is not my father anymore.
( groaning )
Mom, please.
All right.
Drop me off
at an emergency room,
but then you have
to drive away.
No. Whatever happens,
we're staying together.
Jackie, I'm running
a filter for Driscoll.
Could you baby-sit
it for a sec?
I'll be right back.
Sure.
Yes, Marianne.
I couldn't take your call.
I was in a meeting.
Jack Bauer and Audrey Raines
are still alive.
My information was accurate.
Yes. The location was correct,
but they survived the attack.
Are they headed back to CTU?
I haven't heard anything.
Bauer didn't call in?
Not that I'm aware of.
That doesn't make sense.
( sighs ) Actually,
it makes perfect sense.
Bauer knows there's
been a security breach,
and you can bet
he's told someone here.
I gotta get out.
No, you are to stay in
until we take care
of Bauer and the woman.
What about me? I
am not gonna spend
the rest of my
life in jail.
You'll be taken care of.
You know that. Now go.
There you are.
What do you need?
Division is waiting
for those projections.
Well, they're ready to be sent.
Well, then, send them.
( knocking )
Yeah.
Sir, your assistant,
Scott Borman, just arrived.
Should I sent him in? Yeah.
Thanks.
Mr. Secretary, it's good to see
you safe and sound, sir.
Thanks, Scott. Sit down.
Is there a problem, sir?
There's a big problem.
Someone inside CTU
is leaking information
to someone
on the outside.
What do you
need me to do?
I need you
to go to Erin Driscoll.
Tell her that Jack Bauer
is no longer
at Falstead Security,
that he's watching
the surveillance videos
at an old CTU substation
in Torrance.
Anything about
when Jack will call in?
When they identify
the man that Audrey saw.
I take it Jack and Audrey are
nowhere near the CTU substation.
Right. I'm trying
to flush out the mole.
Then you'll need me to put
a DOD Comsat envelope
around this place.
And if anyone sends out
a communication
containing the information
you planted, that's the spy.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
The dog next door
likes our yard.
( rooster crows in distance )
Well, here we are,
home sweet home.
Just stay here.
Oh, God!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, Jack, it's okay.
This is my friend Jen.
Tell him to play
with his guns outside.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here,
anyways?
I thought
you were working.
I'm going in late.
This is Jack
and his friend Audrey.
This is Jen.
Hi.
I-I saw you on TV today.
You're the daughter
of the Secretary of Defense.
You and your old man were
kidnapped this morning.
Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm helping them out
with something.
Could you be
a little more
specific?
We need to use Tony's computer.
What, they don't have
computers where you work?
Listen, babe,
we have a situation here,
all right?
They need to lie low
for a little bit.
We can't let anybody know
they're here, all right?
Whatever.
I'm leaving anyway.
Tony...
Jen, you can't go anywhere.
Why not?
We can't leave
until Jack
and Audrey take off.
We can't take
a chance.
What kind of chance?
I work at a bar.
I'm sorry, Jen.
We're not gonna be long.
Look, stay as long
as you want.
I have a job.
He doesn't.
Jen, can I talk to you
for a second?
Please?
Sorry.
No, she seems real sweet.
Look, we were fighting
for our lives a few minutes ago,
and if it hadn't been for Tony,
we would have been dead.
Now, I've been
through a lot today,
and I'm sure when
this is all over,
your boss will understand.
And if he doesn't?
I can have him killed.
Knock yourself out.
Thank you.
How are you guys making out
with that?
Good. I just have convert this
so I can read it.
And then, hopefully,
you can make an I.D.
from the surveillance video.
I have some software for that.
Let me dig it out.
Thanks.
( quietly ):
You told me about Tony,
but I didn't know
that Michelle left him.
Yeah, a few months
after he got out of prison.
I thought he went to prison
because of her.
He saved her life,
and she paid him
back by leaving him?
That's the way
Tony sees it, too.
Didn't happen
exactly like that.
When Tony got out of prison,
he was angry.
He couldn't get a job.
Personally, I don't think
he wanted one.
He started drinking.
He pushed her away.
What is she doing now?
Deputy director
over at Division.
I hope he can help us.
If he can, he will.
All right, here we go.
You got it, Tony?
Yeah, I got it
right here.
Thanks.
We're in.
Start the ball rolling
with Driscoll?
Yep. Headed into
her briefing now.
She's not gonna be happy
when she finds out
we're using her
to flush out the mole.
I am surprised
you felt the need
to keep her in the dark
about this one.
As long as there's
a leak in CTU,
we keep everyone
in the dark.
Make sure
that you're online
and that your databases
are unlocked.
As soon as Jack
sends in the image,
I need you to be able
to move as quickly as possible
to make this I.D., okay?
I don't understand
why Jack's doing this
at the old substation.
Well, apparently there's
technical reasons.
I didn't speak
with him directly.
Who did?
I did.
He also asked
that his whereabouts
be kept strictly internal
until he contacts us.
All right, let's go.
Old CTU substation in Torrance.
I remember this lady.
We saw him around here.
There he is.
You sure that's him?
Yes.
I'm gonna route this
through the D.C. office.
Tony, she's on the phone.
We can't have her
making calls.
We need the phone.
Go to hell.
I can't go to work.
I can't talk
on the phone?
Just give me
the phone.
Go to hell!
Give me the
damn phone!
( thud )
( screams )
( typing,
computer blipping )
Go ahead.
Thanks.
This is Marcie.
Marcie, it's Jack.
I'm sending you the image
we need I.D.'d.
We're ready to receive.
Okay.
You positive this came
from her system?
Yeah.
The voices were digitized
and scrambled,
but we were able
to clean it up enough
to make out the words
"CTU substation. "
Where's security?
They're on the way.
Thanks, Scott.
Yes, Mr. Secretary?
Erin, I'm sorry
to report
there's been a breach
in CTU.
What?
The information Scott gave you
about Jack is false.
What do you mean false?
Jack and Audrey were ambushed
at Falstead Security.
They survived
the attack,
but it's clear that someone
in this office
gave them up.
With all due respect, sir,
you knew about this
and you didn't tell me?
Being left out
of the loop
is not something you
should be concerned about.
I assume you're telling me now
because your sting operation
yielded a result.
Yes, it did.
Read that.
Where is she?
She's being taken
into custody.
Join me.
Miss Driscoll, what's going on?
Go with these men.
What for?
You're under arrest, Gavin.
DRISCOLL: You've been passing
classified information.
What?
What are you talking about?
Take her to Holding.
Miss Driscoll,
what are you doing?
I haven't done anything.
Miss Driscoll,
this is a mistake.
What is happening?
Can someone please tell me
what is going on?
I didn't do anything, please!
Get back to work.
I don't care how
you divide up her files.
I just want everything off
her system and then sent to me.
And enter new pass codes.
We can't just do this
on your authority.
Edgar...
it's okay.
But he works for DOD,
not CTU.
Yeah, well, he's the one
that found the mole, right?
And Heller wants him
to have joint authority.
Finish up here and get
back to station two.
The program we set up
for the reactor
is almost finished compiling.
Can I see this?
Sure.
What makes you so sure
Sarah's the mole?
She was sending out encoded
information about Jack Bauer.
I don't think she would compromise
Bauer or the investigation.
That's how she was able
to fool everybody, Edgar.
She's the last person
you'd expect to do it.
All right,
just get me those files.
It's right here.
2:22 p. m. Message sent:
"Old CTU substation
in Torrance. "
This doesn't seem
weird to you that she
would leave it
on her system like this?
She didn't just leave it;
it was encrypted.
Yeah, with
a Bainbridge algorithm.
Come on, it's so old school,
it's like saying,
"Please decode me. "
Let's face it,
Sarah wasn't the sharpest knife
in the drawer.
( sighs )
( door opens )
Please, Miss Driscoll...
I promise you, there's been
some kind of mistake.
How could there
be a mistake?
Your system was isolated-
the message was sent from it
while you were there.
Somebody set me up.
That's the only explanation
I can think of.
Tell me how that's possible.
Someone backed into my system
through a subnet,
planted something.
That's the first thing
we checked.
None of them were compromised.
Let's stop playing games.
Thousands of people's
lives are at stake!
Where are the people
who control the override?
I don't know.
That's what I was working on.
Who did you send the
message about Jack to?
I didn't.
Miss Driscoll... ( sighs )
I would never betray our country
or endanger people's lives.
You know that.
Was it the same contact
who coordinated the attempt
on Jack and Audrey's life
at Falstead Security?
I don't know. It wasn't me.
I learned my
lesson today
with Sherrick, and I am
no longer going to err
on the side of caution
in these interrogations.
Do you get my meaning?
I don't know what to say.
Eric, no.
Please don't do this.
Eric... Miss Driscoll...
( zapping )
( gasping )
Please stop.
If you want it to stop,
you tell me
where the Dobson override is
and who has it.
( crying ):
I swear, I don't know anything.
Wait.
( crying )
There's got to be
an explanation for this.
You got to give me
some time to think.
( zapping )
Talk to me, Sarah.
Talk to me.
Miss Driscoll...
I'm not a spy.
I'm not.
Please believe me.
Driscoll,
please.
I'm concerned.
Do you think you can
break her in time?
I can break her in time,
if she's guilty.
According to Scott,
there is no way
that this could be
a mistake.
I agree it's
hard evidence,
but I've known Sarah for eight months,
and she doesn't fit the profile.
How do you want
to handle it?
I'll watch for
a few more minutes,
then I'll go back in.
I'll brief Jack.
( crying ):
Eric, please...
please.
Eric!
What are you doing?
Just checking the surveillance
from later that night
to see who he's talking to.
Did you find anything?
No, not yet.
Anybody want a beer?
I could use one.
( phone rings )
This is Bauer.
HELLER: We found our mole. Who is it?
Sarah Gavin, works in Comm.
Is she working alone?
As far as we know.
Okay, I'll call Marcie, tell
her the CTU channels are open.
We'll start sharing data.
How's Audrey doing?
She's good, she's resting.
Sir, I think now
would be a good time
to send someone to
have her picked up.
We're at 21408 Kipling,
North Hollywood.
What's there?
A friend.
I'll send
the Secret Service.
Thank you, sir.
Your father's sending
someone over to pick you up,
take you back to CTU.
( quietly ):
Okay.
Don't you think you've made me
miss enough TV today, Jack?
( sighs )
Why didn't you
ever call me?
( scoffs softly )
For what?
I've been there.
I could help.
( laughs )
I'm considered a traitor
to this country.
My wife left me.
So how are you gonna help me,
huh, Jack?
Yeah.
( sighs )
Look...
I owed you
for getting me out of prison.
But today, I
repaid that debt.
And to tell you the truth,
all you do is remind me
of a past I'm trying to forget.
So why don't you
do me a favor.
Do what you need to do here,
and let's leave it at that,
All right?
Yep.
So, how did this happen?
I was working in the yard
and... backed into a nail
that sticks out of our gate.
( groans ):
Oh.
This looks like a gunshot wound.
I'm afraid it was nothing
that exciting, Doctor.
It was my fault.
I was supposed to fix
that gate last week.
All right, you're gonna need
a tetanus shot,
then I'll stitch it up.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll be right back.
Go watch him.
DINA:
What's going on?
He said something
to the nurse.
Did he make a phone call?
Not that I could see.
Did she?
No.
Good.
Maybe it wouldn't be so bad
if they called the police.
At least the police
could protect us from Father.
It would be bad
to go to jail for the
rest of our lives.
That's what would happen.
So where are we going to go
after we leave here?
If we can get out
of the city
and stay somewhere
for a couple of days,
I can arrange for us
to get out of the country.
( sighs )
( crying softly )
( phone rings )
Yeah?
Jack, it's Marcie.
We got a match.
Who is it?
Name is Henry Powell.
I posted everything
on that secure site.
Hold on a second.
( typing )
Okay, I got it.
He's a computer consultant.
He used to work
for McLennen-Forster.
Wait a second, McLennen-Forster.
They're the defense contractors
that designed
the override devices
controlling the power plants.
Yeah, well, he's
not there anymore,
but he freelances
for them,
and he's definitely
still in L.A.
How do you know that? Because
he's trying to leave the city.
We just found out he
scheduled a chopper
to meet him in
Van Nuys in 15 minutes.
I thought all air traffic
had been grounded.
It is. He must have
some well-connected friends.
He got a special clearance.
Son of a bitch.
Where in Van Nuys?
The helipad at the Larchmont
Building. Okay, I'm gonna
want you to ground his flight
but not until I get there.
I don't want him
to see me coming.
Jack, they're here.
Can you make it in time?
I'm gonna try.
Audrey, get your things.
We got to go.
Agent Davis, Secret Service. Jack Bauer.
You're gonna take the secretary's
daughter straight back to CTU.
Those are our orders.
Okay.
You got a car for me?
It's right over there.
Thank you.
Audrey, they're ready.
This is Agent Davis. He's
gonna take care of you. Okay.
Be careful.
I will. You, too.
CTU, Patterson.
This is Jack.
Let me speak to Erin Driscoll.
Jack, I just got the file
on Henry Powell.
I'm going through it now.
He's trying to leave the city.
I've got to get over
to Van Nuys.
You want air backup?
No, I want to keep
a low profile.
I don't want to spook him.
The soonest I can get you a
ground package is 30 minutes.
That's gonna be too long.
When is his flight due
to take off?
Less than 15 minutes.
What do you want to do, Jack?
He's most likely
on his own.
I'm gonna have to try
and handle this myself.
All right.
I'll send a team anyway.
I'll be in touch.
What are you gonna try
and handle by yourself?
Don't worry about it.
It's covered.
Jack, it'd be
pretty stupid of me
to let you die right after I
risked my life trying to save you.
Could you use my help?
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Curtis.
Yeah, Edgar?
Has Sarah confessed to anything yet? No.
What are they doing to her?
Don't worry about it.
Just get back to
work, all right?
Curtis?
What did Edgar want?
Why do you care?
Well, you should let him know
we need his full attention-
Get back to your station.
What's that?
Just something to numb the arm
so that I can close the wound.
Okay.
I really wish
you'd let me admit you.
This wound is serious.
There's a chance of
an infection here.
No, Doctor, please.
Do whatever you can,
and we'll leave.
Behrooz,
where are you going?
I'll be right back, Mom.
WOMAN ( over P.A. ):
Dr. Travis,
you have a visitor
in the main lobby.
Dr. Travis...
Mom, the police are here.
Did you call the police?
This is a gunshot wound.
I told you it wasn't.
DOCTOR: Then why are
you acting so strangely?
Let's go.
You shouldn't leave-
you need to be treated.
Wait!
Let's go!
Come on...
Come on!
( tires screech )
Marianne.
( sighs )
What is it, Edgar?
About an hour ago,
you asked me to bump up
your security clearance.
I was a little busy
with the override,
but I finally got it for you.
Great. Thank you.
What?
You'll need
to pick a password.
I set up the screen
on server five.
( sighs )
There you go.
You need to use
the same password
as the one that unlocks
your system files.
Okay.
Edgar.
Why do you keep looking at me?
I don't keep looking at you.
Let's
go outside.
I want to talk
to you in private.
I don't want to talk
I have a lot of work to do.
It is getting
incredibly tedious, Edgar,
to have to remind
you repeatedly
that I could step into
Driscoll's office any moment
and have you fired.
Curtis, I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I need you to walk with me
to Driscoll's office.
Walk with you?
Please, Curtis.
Sorry
to interrupt.
What is it?
You got the wrong person.
Sarah's not guilty of anything.
How do you know?
Because I just sneaked
into Marianne's system.
She used Sarah's to communicate
outside of CTU,
made it look like
Sarah was the one.
That's not
possible.
Sarah's workstation
was isolated from the subnet.
She didn't use the subnet.
How'd she get through?
She used a plain old
AC power line.
What?
That's the last place
anybody would ever look.
Plus it has plenty of bandwidth
to carry
the signal.
Where is she?
She's trying to leave
the building.
Lock down
the exits.
( alarm buzzing )
( grunting )
You're under arrest.
Examine the contents.
Impound the car.
Strip it and search it.
I got her.
( car alarms blaring )
Mr. Powell?
Yeah, let's go.
Uh, sorry, sir, we can't.
What?
Uh, flight's
been grounded.
No. McLennan-Forster
has special ordinance.
The paperwork was sent.
I know, but the order
was superseded.
By who?
Department
of Defense.
You're going
to fly me out of here.
Please, sir.
Now! Get in.
All right, where we going?
Just get us in the air
and fly east.
There it is.
Do not take off!
Do not
take off!
Go! Go!
Hold on!
Shut it down!
Come on, go.
Drop the weapon
now. now!
Shut it down.
Get out of
the helicopter now.
Move!
Get up!
Put your hands on
the roof of the truck.
Some people I know,
they'll pay you.
Shut up.
I got his
cell phone.
Bring me the bag.
Put your hands behind your back.
( panting )
Who are you guys?
Police? FBI?
Actually, I'm currently
unemployed.
I'll make it worth your while.
Put him in the back.
Come on.
( gunshot )
He's dead, Jack.
Damn it!
Subtitles by Jaxdahl (with Electron and ResDog)
www.tvsubtitles.net