24 SO4E20
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
CC: Johnsonh
Timeline: Guozi
Translator: lijingsisu Requiem
Supervisor: Requiem
Previously On 24
I want Bauer arrested.
Bauer is heading the field operation.
Jack Bauer is not the only
man who can do the job!
Put someone else in charge!
Jack, we've got a problem.
Secret service is on their way
over there now to arrest you.
Bill, they can't interrupt this mission.
You got to stall 'em.
There's nothing I can do from here.
You have to get Marean before
secret service gets there.
People of america, you wake
up today to a different world.
I have a visual on Marean.
He is in the building.
Damn it. They know we're here.
Everybody move on the doors.
Our cover's blown!
Everyone go, go, go, go, go!
President Logan realized this was a mistake.
You're free to go.
We had Marean.
Damn it! We had him!
This man Marean has a nuclear warhead,
and I allowed him to escape.
Mr. President...
Stop!
I don't even know if I
deserve to be called that.
There's someone who can
advise you better than I can.
I'm not sure what you're asking me to do.
President Logan is requesting you
run the effort to recover the stolen
weapon and be in place to make
whatever decisions need to be made.
Is it compatible?
I'll need to reconfigure
the trigger mechanism.
Has the warhead been reconfigured?
Yes, we, uh... may have a
potential security breach here.
Who?
The technician, sabir.
His girlfriend's getting suspicious.
I think sabir may have become
involved with radical groups.
You mean terrorists?
Yes.
The woman with the phone tip who was
suspicious about her boyfriend panned out.
She sent us a schematic
of a microchip that was
used exclusively in the
legacy nuclear warhead.
Take a team with you.
Let's get on this.
what was that?
he's going to ram us!
The following takes place
between 2:00 A.M. and 3:00 A.M.
It's good to have you back, Mr. President.
Thank you, aaron.
This way, sir.
President Logan's not
working out of the west wing?
No, sir.
Since the strike on air force one,
he's been in the bunker.
How's your son?
Very well, sir.
Thank you for asking.
Still in the service?
Yes. In fact, he, uh,
just re-upped.
Good for him.
We're mighty proud.
Mr. President, thank you for coming.
Mike. Is there an update on
president Keeler's condition?
No, he's still comatose.
And the long
- term prognosis is still unclear?
Yes.
How's president Logan?
Looking forward to seeing you.
Thank you, aaron.
President Logan.
David.
I appreciate you coming so quickly.
Tell me how I can help you.
David... I wasn't prepared to have
all of this thrust upon me so suddenly.
What I'm trying to say
is I-I made mistakes.
This crisis could've ended an hour
ago if I hadn't interfered with
a CTU operation that would've...
would've captured Habib Marean.
Punishing yourself for a mistake is
something you can't afford right now.
What I can't afford and what this
country can't afford is another mistake.
Every decision I make affects the
lives of millions of americans.
I understand the pressure you're under.
I know you do.
When you were in office, you dealt with
this kind of situation more than once.
That's why i want you here.
I still don't understand what
it is I can do to help you.
Sit.
The warhead that was stolen is an s-series.
That's one of the most powerful
nuclear weapons in the arsenal.
Wherever it's detonated,
it will wreak... unthinkable devastation.
Help me find it.
I will give you full authority to act as
my proxy whenever you think it's necessary.
Charles, how do you want this to work?
I'll call Bill Buchanan at CTU,
and I'll let him know that...
he'll be dealing directly with you.
All right.
Thank you, david.
Mike'll fill you in.
We will get through this, Mr. President.
Um, I'll be, uh, in
conference room b working
on the morning statement for the press.
I'll keep you apprised
of any developments, sir.
Thank you, mike.
Mr. President...
I know you believe my
actions during your term in
office amounted to a personal
and political betrayal...
it's not something I believe.
It's a fact.
Get to your point.
If my presence here makes
it more difficult for you,
say the word, and I'll leave.
Mike... you're wired
into this administration,
and I have no doubt that you have
this country's best interests at heart,
so for now, let's let bygones
be bygones and get to work.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I appreciate that.
I reviewed the briefing
materials on the way here.
Have army reserve supplement the search
teams looking for the warhead in iowa
and have D.O.E. And D.O.D. Coordinating
on crisis response in case it's detonated.
Yes, sir.
CTU is heading up the search for this
man who stole the warhead, Habib Marean?
Yes. They recovered a damaged videotape
from Marean's last known location.
They're in the process of restoring it.
But Marean is not CTU's
only lead on the warhead now.
What else do we have?
A CTU analyst named Chloe
o'brian secured a hard
drive belonging to one
of Marean's associates.
This hard drive may contain information
that could lead us to the warhead.
I told you I'm not hurt.
I did the shooting. Now please
leave me alone so I can do this.
Okay. The hard drive is unlocked.
Chloe, the hard drive
belonged to someone who
had no previous experience
with nuclear weapons.
He had to get that information from someone.
The emails I'm decrypting
look like exactly that:
Weapons schematics, designs of nuclear
triggers- all from the same person.
Who?
The e-mail address itself is
shielded under a false domain name.
What is it?
Mem4xp.
Okay. Chloe, I want you to
forward all the emails to us.
Edgar?
I'll run a trace to
find the point of origin.
These emails came from a domestic server.
Whoever sent this is in this country.
Okay, Chloe, thank you.
Hold on.
Hey. How you holding up?
I'm not used to the idea that I just killed
someone, if that's what you're asking,
but I'm doing my job.
Fair enough.
Get back as soon as you can, okay?
Okay.
I got a hit.
The man who sent the
emails name is lee jong.
Is he in our database?
He's a chinese national:
A research scientist who worked on
china's nuclear weapon's program.
He was accused of falsifying research
data and fired by their government in 2001.
Is it possible china's providing
Marean with support for this attack?
No, the chinese wouldn't use someone that
could be traced back to them so easily.
He's selling his services
as a freelance operator.
If lee's helping Marean
reconfigure or redeploy the warhead,
most likely he'll know how to find it.
Check with the I.N.S.,
See if lee's entered the
country in the last week.
Excuse me.
This is Bauer.
Jack, dr. Besson.
You wanted me to give you
an update on Paul Raines.
He's still in recovery,
but you can see him now.
Just limit your visit to a few minutes.
Thank you, doctor.
Get back to me if you find anything.
Where can I find you?
I'll be in medical.
Okay.
Yeah, I understand.
Hey.
Dr. Besson wants to move you to
amherst general's spinal program,
but the faa still has a ban on air travel.
I am trying to get you an exemption.
Well, if anyone can get
an exemption... you can.
Listen... I've thought a lot about this,
and... I want to go with
you to massachusetts.
"With me"?
Yeah.
You need to get better, and you
shouldn't have to do that alone.
No, I can take care of myself.
I don't need your charity.
It's not about charity, Paul.
It's what I want to do.
What about Jack?
You said you were in love with him.
I know.
Sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt.
I'll come back later.
No, it's all right.
Come in.
Thought you'd be at the dod briefing.
Yeah, it ended early.
Oh. I just wanted to come
down and see how you're doing.
I've been trying to get down
here since you got out of surgery.
Listen, Paul...
please, you don't have to say anything.
Yeah, I do.
You saved my life.
I was in the wrong place at the wrong time,
so... you pushed me out of the way.
Honestly, I wasn't even
thinking. It just happened...
Paul? You all right?
I'll check back on you later.
Does he know that you want to come with me?
Not yet.
What is it?
We found lee jong.
Where is he?
Chinese consulate.
Damn it, he must have known
we were coming for him.
He took refuge.
He got there about an hour ago.
Consulate's sovereign territory.
It's the one place we can't get to him.
But we're going to try.
David palmer for you.
David palmer?
Frankly, president Logan's been a little
overwhelmed by what's been happening.
He enlisted palmer to help us directly.
Good.
This is Bauer.
Hold for the president.
Sir.
Thank you, mike.
It's nice to talk to you again, Jack.
It's nice to talk to
you, too, Mr. President.
L assume Bill told you about lee jong.
Yes, sir.
I'm about to call the chinese
consul and explain the situation.
I'd like it if you personally
took lee into custody
and brought him back to
CTU for interrogation.
And you think the consul
will be cooperative?
He's a reasonable man.
And what if the political
approach doesn't work?
I'll leave it to you to make
the necessary preparations.
Whatever it takes, we need
this man lee in custody.
I understand, Mr. President.
Thank you, Jack.
You have a chinese interpreter?
Melissa rabb. She's very good.
Okay, I need her,
curtis and one of his agents,ready
to move on the consulate now.
Edgar stiles.
Okay, I'm opening a window
now, send it through.
Ms. Dessler.
Division just called.
That videotape they
were trying to restore-
they were only able to
reconstruct part of it.
They're sending it to my
work station as we speak.
Bill.
People of america, you wake
up today to a different world.
One of your own nuclear weapons
has been used against you.
It'll be days and weeks before you
can measure the damage we have caused.
But as you count your dead, remember...
you wake up today to a different world.
Do we take that literally?
That he'll set off the warhead before dawn?
We have to look at the worse case scenario.
What time is sunrise on the east coast?
7:02. Less than two hours from now.
Unless you renounce your policies of
imperialism and interventionist activities
this attack will be followed by
another and another after that.
The chinese consul in los
angeles, a man named koo yin.
Mr. Koo, this is david palmer.
It's an honor to speak
with you, Mr. President.
I'm calling on behalf of president Logan.
The situation today has forced him to direct
his attention to
other,equally urgent matters.
I understand.
And my government extends its sympathy
for these terrible attacks on your country.
We stand ready to help in any way we can.
Thank you.
The fact is, you can help us.
There's a man in your consulate
by the name of lee jong.
Yes, he arrived here earlier tonight.
We have evidence connecting him to
the terrorists behind today's attacks.
We need to take Mr. Lee into
custody immediately for questioning.
Mr. Lee expected suspicion to fall on him.
He says there's been a mistake, he
has no connections with terrorists.
We believe he's helping the terrorists
detonate a nuclear device on our soil.
Many lives are at stake, Mr. Koo.
President palmer
I would very much like to help,
but Mr. Lee is a chinese citizen and
the consulate is chinese territory.
I can't just hand him over to you
without going through channels.
Then I urge you to contact the premier
immediately and explain the situation.
Tell him speed is of the essence.
Tell him cooperation will be regarded as an
extraordinary act of friendship
on the part of his nation,
and our nation will respond in kind.
Mr. President, I'll do my best.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
Thank you, Mr. Koo.
Consul's going to try
to make something happen.
How long will it take?
I don't know.
Anything new?
Yeah, white house just authorized adding
iowa army reserve units
to the ground search.
Have they widened the perimeter?
Yeah, they locked down a 60-mile radius
around the area where
the warhead was stolen,
but I'm concerned Marean's people might have
managed to sneak it outside that perimeter.
Well, we closed all major roads
and air traffic immediately,
but there is a chance they got it through.
Homeland security's faxing over casualty
projections based on that possibility.
That's probably them right now.
Yeah, I'll get it.
CTU.
Woman: I'm calling for Tony Almeida.
Who is this?
This is Michelle Dessler,
a colleague of his.
May I ask who's calling?
The woman he happens to be
living with. Is he there?
Yeah, hold on.
It's for you.
Who is it?
The woman you're living with
Jen.
I've been calling everyone we
know going crazy looking for you.
Then finally I thought maybe
Jack Bauer took you back there.
Do you have any idea how worried I've been?
Yeah, I'm sorry,
I should have called earlier,
but I've been very busy.
Oh, really? Busy with Michelle Dessler?
I'm working, jen.
Oh, for CTU.
On a provisional basis, yeah.
I thought you hated that place.
Things have changed a little.
Yeah, I guess they have.
Look, jen, we can talk about this later.
Right now I got to go, all right?
Tony, what's your ex-wife doing there?
Jen, I'm sorry, but I got to go.
Michelle, um...
I'm sorry you had to find out like that.
It's really none of my business.
Yeah, it is.
I should have told you I was
living with somebody else.
I don't want to talk about this right now.
Yeah, well, I do. Listen to me.
When you left, everything fell apart
and jen happened to be there for me.
You don't have to make
excuses for your relationship.
I'm not making excuses.
I'm just telling you how it is.
Do you love her?
No.
Ms. Dessler, the new protocols
from dod just came in.
Should I send them to your screen?
Send them to station 16.
Thank you, Edgar.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Is there anything I can do?
I said I'm fine.
I'm trying not to think about what happened.
I'm going to process it later, okay?
Sure, fine.
Edgar, I appreciate your
concern, I really do.
It's just that when I shot that guy,
I thought I'd go all fetal position,
but the truth is I didn't feel anything.
At all. I hope I'm not
some kind of a psychopath.
Well, he was trying to kill you.
Yeah, but still.
Maybe it's a delayed reaction kind of thing.
Maybe you'll freak out
about it in a few days.
I hope so.
Sir.
Sir. Bill Buchanan.
thank you.
Yes, Bill?
Mr. President, we've just seen
a tape recorded by Habib Marean.
On it, he says we'll be, quote
"waking up to a different world. "
We can't be sure what that means,
but it may indicate that the warhead will
be detonated before dawn on the east coast.
Thank you, Bill.
CTU thinks that the warhead
may be detonated before dawn.
Get me Mr. Koo.
This is koo yin.
Please hold for president palmer, sir.
Mr. Koo.
President palmer, I didn't expect
to hear from you quite so soon.
Has the premier been made
aware of the situation?
Yes, Mr. President, he's
considering it very carefully.
There's no time for that.
I've just learned that
the terrorists may detonate
a nuclear device within the next two hours.
Mr. Palmer, I understand
the urgency of the situation.
And without making any promises,
I have every expectation of
giving you a favorable answer.
When?
I know I'll be speaking with
him again in two to three hours.
I told you, that's not soon enough.
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
It's the best I can do.
Thank you, Mr. Koo, for your efforts.
Please keep me informed.
Of course, Mr. President.
he thinks Mr. Lee will be handed over
to us, but not before two or three hours.
Now, from their point of view, that's
moving very fast for something like this.
From ours- not
nearly fast enough.
what do we do?
this is Bauer.
Jack, are you at the consulate yet?
Yes, sir, we've taken up
position across the street.
Have they agreed to release lee?
Not quickly enough.
And I just learned that the nuclear
device may be set off at any moment.
Now, Jack, is there any doubt in your
mind that lee is working with Marean?
No, sir- the e-mails he
sent left no room for doubt.
Then we have to get lee out
now and find out what he knows.
Yes, sir.
No one connected with the government
can admit to knowing anything about this
ever. If you're caught, you'll be tried
in a chinese court under chinese law.
I understand.
Now, Jack, if it was anyone else,
I'd ask if you were sure about this.
With you, I already know the answer.
God bless you.
Good luck.
Thank you, Mr. President.
We're on. We're going in to get him.
All right.
Almeida.
Tony, this is Jack.
I'm at the consulate.
I need you to get me real-time
infrared satellite coverage.
All right, I'm on it.
What's going on, Jack?
The consul's not going
to release lee in time.
We have to go in and get him.
Who knows about this?
We have authorization from the white house.
Tony, this is a covert operation.
You're the only person at CTU who can know.
I need you to spoof the
satellite logs and make sure
that the mainframes aren't
monitoring your station.
Tony, there can't be any record that
this ever took place, you understand?
Yeah.
Okay, thanks.
Let's suit up.
Tony, it's Jack.
I'm on com.
All right, Jack, I'm uploading a
picture of lee to you right now.
Also, I just got a hold
of the building schematic.
Can you overlay the infrared?
Coming now.
Looks like the bulk of the people are
on the first floor residential area,
most of them not moving, probably asleep.
Try the second floor offices.
Grabbing data on the second floor.
All right, we got people moving.
Okay, by the way they're gathering around
that third room, that's
probably where lee is.
I think you're right.
I'll get back to you as soon as I'm moving.
How do you want to deploy?
I want agent rabb to stay in the
van until I need her to translate.
You both can cover the perimeter.
I'm going in alone.
Jack...
my orders are to make this
mission completely deniable.
If I get caught, I have to be
able to say I was acting alone.
All right, what do you want us to do?
Stay here.
If I need you, you both can reengage
as soon as I leave the consulate,
but only on a covert basis- masks
on, non-lethal force, you understand?
We'll be here.
Tony, I'm going in. Any change on infrared?
Negative.
We'll continue monitoring in real time.
Alarm's a cambia model three.
I'm jumping the relays at the door now.
Roger that.
All right, Jack, stop.
We have somebody approaching
from your west side.
I repeat, your west side.
Okay, he's moving away.
Give me the status on the other four guards.
Jack, you're right on top of them.
We have someone approaching
from your north side.
Okay, you're clear.
I've got him.
Roger that.
People moving toward you on both floors.
I'm heading out. Hostiles
in pursuit. Bring up the van.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
let's go!
He's hit.
Pass me the medical bag.
Now!
We're in.
Go! Go!
Jack, give me a status.
We're away, lee's in custody.
He's been shot in the back, no exit wound.
How bad is it?
I can't tell yet.
The bleeding doesn't look too severe.
We're on our way to you.
We're about 15 minutes out.
I'll have medical ready.
he says not to touch him.
He doesn't want you to touch him.
Tell him I'm just trying to help him.
I need to check his wound.
hold him down!
Hold him down now!
We need to calm him down
so that I can talk to him.
Tell him we got medical
assistance waiting for him
and that this shot is only
to help him ease the pain.
Does he understand?
Yes
Mm-hmm.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Hey, the faa's cleared us to leave
at 8:00 on a medical transport plane.
Dr. Besson's agreed to accompany us.
That's great news.
As soon as you settle in, I'll
start looking for an apartment.
I don't know what to say.
I'm going to get through this.
I know you will.
Raines.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, so you're going to
take care of the transportation...
I got to call you back
Paul?
Paul, what is it?
Dr. Besson!
Please, someone come quickly!
Okay, okay, it's okay.
He's right here.
10 milligrams vasopressin.
What's going on?
I can barely hear his heart.
We need to do an ultrasound, but all
signs point to a cardiac tamponade.
What does that mean?
The sac around his heart
is filling up with blood.
Drain off some of the fluid, but we
got to get him back in surgery now.
If we don't stop the bleeding, his
heart will not be able to function.
Get me the pericardiocentesis tray, now.
Okay...
...roll on his back.
there.
Tell him we know that he helped
Habib Marean with the missing warhead,
and now we need him to help us find Marean
and stop him before he can detonate it.
If he denies involvement, tell him
we can prove it with his e-mails.
he doesn't deny it.
He says he knows where Marean is, and he
will tell you if you agree to his terms.
What are they?
he says he went to the consulate seeking
protection from our
government as well as Marean.
He believes Marean wants to kill
him to prevent him from talking.
He wants our guarantee of protection.
Tell him if the information that he
provides us leads us to the warhead in time,
he will be immune from prosecution
in this country and I will
take him back to the chinese
consulate or wherever he wants to go.
he says this is acceptable, but he wants a
guarantee of this in
writing from the president.
Tell him I understand that
and I will get that for him.
I give him my word, but I
need the information now.
He says he must have this
guarantee before he will tell you.
No, that's not good enough.
this is bau... this is Bauer.
President palmer's on the line.
Put him through.
Jack, Buchanan told me you've got lee
jong in custody, and that he was wounded.
Yes, sir.
Is he talking?
He wants to help us, but he
won't till he has a written
guarantee that he won't be
prosecuted in this country.
We also have to provide safe travel
to a destination of his choosing.
This guarantee has to be
signed by the president.
Jack, CTU believes the detonation
of this warhead is imminent.
Can you force him to talk immediately?
I don't think so.
I think the fastest way to make
this happen- give him what he wants.
Okay. I'll get the guarantee from Logan
and have it waiting for you at CTU.
Thank you, sir.
What is it?
Su ming, the deputy chinese consul.
They didn't waste any time.
I can't blame them.
They have to know we're behind the attack.
What shall I tell him?
I'll take the call.
We have to start fencing
with them sooner or later.
Might as well be now.
Mr. Lee won't talk unless he has a
guarantee of immunity and safe transport.
Get that from Logan, will you?
Mr. Su. Yes.
¶÷
Is this president palmer?
Yes. Has the premier
responded to the consul's
request to have Mr. Lee turned over to us?
Mr. President... the consul is dead.
What?
He was shot when armed men broke into this
building and took Mr.
Lee with them by force.
I'm shocked and deeply
saddened. Please convey
that to your government on behalf of mine.
Mr. President... is it your position that
you have no knowledge of this operation?
That the timing of your call and this
abduction is entirely coincidental?
The consulate is a sovereign territory
of the people's republic of china.
I can't believe anyone connected
with this country had a hand in it.
I'm sure you understand the political
ramifications if you are incorrect.
And I'm sure you understand the
ramifications of unproven accusations.
No accusations have been
made, Mr. President, but
I can assure you there
will be an investigation.
Your government will have
my complete cooperation.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I'm sure you'll be hearing
from us again... very soon.
President Logan will provide lee with a
written guarantee, as
long as it remains covert.
Sir? What's wrong?
Koo yin was killed in the
course of the abduction.
my god.
By one of our own people?
No. It must have been friendly
fire, but it really doesn't matter.
If they're able to find
proof that we were involved,
in the long run, the
repercussions will be as
serious as those we're
facing from the terrorists.
Tony.
I just heard that lee jong is on
his way here and he's been shot.
How did this happen?
The chinese weren't going to give lee up in
time, so Jack and his
team had to extract him.
Jack went into the
consulate? On whose authority?
The white house.
Why is this the first
I'm hearing about this?
This operation needed to be kept off
the books to make it was deniable.
But you knew about it.
Yes, I did. I ran tactical from here.
It is absolutely unacceptable. I
was kept out of the loop on this.
That's the way Jack wanted to play it.
You don't work for Jack! You work for me!
A situation, frankly, I wish I had
been consulted on in the first place.
Meaning?
Meaning, I thought it was a mistake to
reinstate you, and now I'm certain of it.
Look, I understand you don't
appreciate being kept in the dark...
but I think this is about something else.
Well, you're wrong about that,
too, and you are way out of line!
Thank you.
Tell him we're almost there.
The medical assistance that we promised
him and the guarantee are waiting for him.
I can't understand him.
Ask him if he's in pain.
He says he's cold, very cold.
What's going on, Jack?
He must have severe internal bleeding.
Damn it. His lungs are
filling up with fluid.
I'll alert CTU.
Mr. Lee. Mr. Lee.
Tell me where Habib Marean is.
Please, tell me where he is now.
Damn it, we're losing him.
All right, stand by with a gurney.
We're coming in hot.
Jack
Jack, what's going on?
You can't come in here.
He's dying.
So is he. Get out of here.
I just started this operation.
This man is our only connection
to a stolen nuclear warhead.
You've got to save him now.
I'll get to him as soon as I can.
He's not gonna make it.
I already have a patient.
Curtis.
You have a new one.
Are you crazy?
Maybe you didn't understand me.
This is the only man
that can help us find the
missing warhead and stop
it from being detonated.
If you don't save him,
millions of people will die.
Do you understand that? Millions of people.
Start working on him now!
Jack, what are you doing?
If I walk away from Mr.
Raines now, he will die.
You don't know that for sure.
Jack
Do it. Now!
Give him more volume.
Jack,please,please don't do this.
His lungs are damaged.
He's lost a lot of blood.
All I need you to do is stabilize him
so I can talk to him. Can you do that?
Maybe.
Then do it.
Deborah, I need you over here.
What about Mr. Raines?
Have one of the agents give chest
compressions if the pressure drops.
I got it.
Put some gloves on.
Jack
I have my orders! I'm doing my job!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?! You're letting him die!
Get her away now!
Stop it, Jack!
Jack, stop!He saved your life!
There's a tension pneumo. We have
to relieve the pressure immediately.
Get me a chest tube!
Get him on a monitor.
Jack, please, stop this.
Pulse is weakening. Pressure dropping.
I'm begging you,Jack,stop it!
Hey, let go of me!
Please!
Let go of me!
Jack, Paul's crashing.
What can we do for him?
He's in v-fib. Use the defibrillator!
Charging.
Clear!
Hit him again, Jack!
Charging!
Clear!
He's still flatlining.
Give him a shot of epinephrine.
Where is it?
On the tray, second syringe from the left.
Got it.
Inject it in the iv.
It's in.
Come on...
Jack.
Jack. He's dead.
no!
Jack!
No!
He's gone.
oh, my god.
You son of a bitch, Jack!
You son of a bitch! You killed him!
He saved your life!
Get her out
of here- now.
You killed him! I hate you, Jack!
You killed him! How could you do this?!
You killed him, Jack.
You killed him!
Let go of me!
Suture.
Is he gonna make it?
I'm doing the best I can.
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
www.tvsubtitles.net