Caption By Dean From F6
Rearranged By allanmauwx From TLF
In three hours,
Heller will be tried
for war crimes against humanity.
If he is proven guilty,
he will be executed
in accordance with our laws.
When the trial begins,
you may have
an opportunity to escape.
You have to take it,
even if it's dangerous.
When Dad told me to take
the briefcase to Omar,
Debbie followed me.
Debbie saw the warehouse
where we're holding Heller?
Yes. But father found out
she was with me,
and now he wants me
to get her over here.
You know what that means.
Debbie,
thank you for coming.
Sure.
I need you to build a fire wall
around Station Four.
Who's that?
Her name's Maryanne.
I just want
to make sure
she doesn't stray outside
the area of her assignment. Fine.
Listen to me. The terrorists
have just announced
that they are going to try
and execute Heller
in less than four hours.
Bring the man in now.
I don't think
that's the right call.
I believe that if I follow them,
they're going to lead me
to Secretary Heller
and the men who kidnapped him.
Jack Bauer
is no longer cooperating
with this investigation.
All departments need to be
working on the location
and capture of Jack Bauer
and the hostile that
he's tracking now.
Right now, our first priority
is to find these terrorists.
I'm going to need
satellite surveillance
to help me track them
without being seen.
You want me to steal
satellite bandwidth from CTU
without anyone knowing?
Yes.
Am I going to have
satellite coverage
in the next minute or two?
I'm sorry, Jack.
It's going to take
at least another five.
I'm going to have to figure out
a way to keep this guy here.
Keep working on it.
Everybody put your hands up now
You- don't move!
Slowly, move back
to the corner.
Everybody just stay calm.
You'll be out of here
before you know it.
You...
hop up on the counter,
black out
that camera.
Anybody else working
in the back?
Put your hands up.
Move over there with the others.
Now!
You have any IDs
on the other two?
I don't know yet.
If I did, I'd tell you.
I'll keep you updated.
Thank you.
Yeah, please do.
Briefing in five minutes.
County just reported
that Andrew Paige
was taken into their ER
in critical condition.
Paige? The programmer Jack
went to pick up?
That's not all.
The bodies of two unidentified
Middle Eastern men
were found at the site-
gunshot wounds.
Bauer must have done that
to save the kid.
Where did they find all this?
Moore Park.
It's getting out of control.
We lose an agent,
now one of our only witnesses
has been disabled.
What about
the hostile and Bauer?
Still at large.
All right.
We have less than three hours
before Heller is executed
in front of the country.
Maybe we shouldn't concentrate
everything on Bauer,
and pursue other leads.
Except for Heller's son,
we have
no other leads.
I want all tactical teams
working on finding Bauer
and the hostile.
You got it.
Keep moving back
towards the corner.
Move!
Everybody get down
on the ground.
Lady, get down
on the floor!
Take it easy.
Shut up!
You want to get
through this, lady,
you listen to me.
You understand?
Get down on
the floor now!
I want your wallets
and your cell phones.
Make it quick.
Where's your cell phone?
I don't have one.
What's this?
You some kind of cop?
No.
What do you need this for?
Protection.
I get my money,
no one gets hurt.
Do I make myself clear?
You, in the cap.
What's your name?
Doug.
Doug, give me your keys.
Which one of these
opens the front door?
Which one!?
The brass one.
Hi. I'm sorry. We've
got an electrical problem
with the store.
We're closed right now.
I just need
a pack of cigarettes.
I'm sorry. You're going
to have to go
to the gas station
across the street.
Thank you.
O'Brian.
The satellite up yet?
No. I have to reposition
without Driscoll noticing.
Where are you?
I'm at a Mercury
Mart in Solmas.
I had to
stage a robbery
to keep the hostile in place. What?
It was the only way
I could stop him
from getting back
on the road.
How much longer?
It's going
to take ten minutes.
Son of a bitch.
Chloe, please hurry.
I'll get back to you.
Chloe?
Driscoll's
called a briefing.
I'll be there
in a couple minutes.
Chloe, now.
Where you going?
To a briefing.
Should I be in there?
No.
Hi. I'm Maryanne.
I'm helping out today.
Okay.
And you are?
This is
Chloe O'Brian,
our senior sys tech.
She doesn't have time
to chat either, Maryanne.
It's nice to meet you, Chloe.
As some of you know,
about an hour ago,
a hostile abducted a witness
in this case-
Andrew Paige.
Do we have any idea
where this hostile is now?
No, but we have general
direction of travel.
County Emergency Services
just called this in.
His best route of escape
is the freeway.
He'll likely
dump his vehicle
and try to
hijack another one.
This is Andrew Paige.
He was apparently tortured-
and about to be killed-
when, it seems,
Jack Bauer intervened.
Assuming this took place
in the last half hour,
and that the hostile was
continuing east, he's somewhere
in the northeastern corridor
of Ventura County.
We'll coordinate
with Caltrans,
CHP and Ventura Sheriff
to set up watch points.
I want every available
resource on this. Edgar,
take the lead
in satellite positioning.
Sara, you'll
coordinate with NSA.
That's all, thank you.
Chloe?
I'm sorry
about Andrew.
I know he was
a friend of yours.
They said
there's a good chance
that he'll pull through.
Thanks.
And, Chloe,
there's nothing
you could have done.
I want you to put a
pipeline on Chloe's system.
What for?
She knew about Andrew Paige.
How do
you know that?
Her reactions.
Which means she's been
in touch with Jack Bauer.
Well, I'll need
her access code.
Doug!
Get over here now!
Open the safe.
That's it?
Yeah.
Why don't you
take it and leave?
I won't say anything
to the.
When does your armored truck
make its pickup?
About 12:30.
What, you want to rob
the armored truck, too?
Shut up.
Get back in the corner.
Move!
Is he going to keep us here
another two hours?
We have to do something
to stop him.
Damn it.
Something is wrong.
Kaleel is not
answering his phone.
Maybe he's out of range.
No. Not for this long.
Check with our people
in the area.
Find out if anything
has happened to him.
Kaleel may not
be here in time.
We'll have to start booting
up the routers without him.
Take care of it.
Let my daughter go.
You don't need her.
She has already
been useful.
Please.
I'll do whatever you want.
I know you will.
That's why we are keeping her.
I don't care if you kill me.
But if you kill her,
even your own people
will see you as a barbaric pig.
Is this what your religion
teaches you?
Dad. Dad.
Calm down.
You all right?
I'm fine.
Where's your medication?
Your nitroglycerin.
Where is it?
I left it in the car.
My father has a heart condition.
He needs his medication.
Any indication Chloe's
been in contact with Bauer?
No.
Keep watching.
This is Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, it's Chloe.
Why are you calling me?
I need to talk
to you in private.
Meet me in Archives.
When?
Now.
Why are we meeting like this?
I'm busy.
Edgar, I need you to help me.
Help you with what?
Sara piped in to my system.
Why would she do that?
Driscoll must have
asked her to,
otherwise she wouldn't
even have access.
Well, if Driscoll's
spying on ya,
I'm sure she's
got a good reason.
I'm not getting involved.
I've been in contact
with Jack Bauer.
What?!
That's right,
now you're involved.
So you're either going to
help me or you're going
to turn me in.
I'm turning you in.
Jack can find Heller
if he's allowed
to follow the hostile,
but Driscoll won't let him.
That's her call.
She's wrong.
That's your opinion.
These decisions
are not ours to make.
How about if you do
it as a favor to me?
How many times
have I helped you
since you started here?
A lot.
What about the
first two weeks
when I had to do
all your work
for you because
you were too nervous?
You owe me.
You're asking me to do something
that can get me fired.
Not if I say
I ordered you to do it.
Remember, I outrank you.
I'd take the heat.
What do I have to do?
I need to reposition
the satellite for Jack,
and I need to do it now.
Since Sarah's piping my system,
we have to use yours.
Okay.
Send it to Archives Three.
Transfer my calls there.
I want to know
who's in charge here.
I want to speak
to the man who was just in here.
You'll speak to him later.
No, now!
I am the Secretary
of Defense
of the United States
of America.
You will listen to me!
Dad, don't make it worse.
What do you mean, worse?!
What could be worse than
waiting around here
to be murdered by a bunch
of lawless, Godless thugs?
Dad, calm down.
I don't want to calm down!
Don't tell me to calm down!
What's the point?
We're here, okay? The best thing
we could do
is keep our heads, and hope
that someone comes along...
Hope?
Hope that we
get rescued?
We have to do something!
We have to take...
Dad, what is it?
What's happening?
Okay, try to take a deep breath.
I need help.
Look, help me, please.
I... I think he's
having a heart attack.
Dad, look, you've
got to lie down.
Lie down.
You've got to...
Dad, are you
listening to me?
It's okay, he's coming.
Step back.
Hurry.
Move away from him.
You need to lie him down,
please!
Hurry. Look...
Step away.
Go on, get out of here!
Still with me?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Go back, go back.
Put your weapon down, slowly.
Both of you,
hands on your head.
If another one of my men dies,
your daughter will be killed.
When the armored truck pulls up,
how many men come inside?
Two. One stays by the door
and one picks up the money.
They park in the front
or the back?
In the front,
by the street.
Come on, let's go.
Everybody up!
We're moving to the back
of the store! Now!
Stand over there.
Look, the longer
you keep us here...
Shut up!
Let's go!
You try that again
and I will kill you.
You understand me?
Get up.
Now!
Move to the back of the store.
Damn it.
Everybody in the freezer now!
Not you.
Move.
Anybody makes a sound,
I kill all of you.
Doug, you in there?
Make him go away.
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
I was in the back room.
How come
you're closed?
I'm taking inventory.
In the middle of the day?
Yeah.
Okay, um...
Sure everything's all right?
Yeah, fine.
You don't
look fine, Doug.
I'm just
a little tired.
Thanks, Bill.
You mind if I use the head?
It's... broken.
Something's
wrong here.
Now you going to
tell me what it is,
or do I have to come in
and see for myself?
Don't even
think about it.
Step inside now.
Move.
Grab that counter.
Doug, lock the door.
JACK:
Give me the keys.
I want you
to go over there,
give me his gun and his radio.
Move, come on!
Take out his cuffs.
Officer, put your hands
behind your back.
Cuff him.
Go back to the freezer.
Let's go.
At this time, we have
no more information
regarding the kidnapping
of Secretary of Defense
James Heller
and his daughter Audrey
other than the image
you are now seeing, which was...
My husband and I realize
we've been unfair to you.
We've treated
you as badly
as we have been
treated ourselves,
by certain ignorant people.
Well, it was pretty obvious
you didn't approve
of us going out.
Is that okay to say?
Yeah, it's okay.
Well, we hope you'll
accept our apology.
That means a lot to me.
That said,
there's something else
I want to discuss with you.
What's that?
This morning,
you followed Behrooz
to his father's warehouse.
Oh.
Um... I thought Behrooz
was seeing someone else.
I got jealous.
Oh, I understand.
But Mr. Araz moved
his inventory there
because he's been
robbed a few times.
And we've been trying to keep
that place secret
so it doesn't
happen again.
I promise I won't tell
anyone where it is.
Good.
And you haven't told anyone yet?
No.
I haven't talked to anyone
but Behrooz today.
Well, then that's settled.
Thank you for inviting me
here, Mrs. Araz.
It's my pleasure.
Has Behrooz ever
shown you pictures
from when he was a child?
No.
Show her, Behrooz.
Have a look
at these.
I'll be right back.
Oh, my God.
That's not you.
It is.
You were so cute.
Thank you, Hannah.
You're welcome.
Have you been following this,
Mr. Araz?
Yes, it's horrible.
It makes it so difficult
for the rest of us
when people from home
do these unspeakable things.
I agree.
Yes.
The girl didn't tell anyone.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Good. It'll be taken
care of, then?
Soon.
Have Behrooz do it.
He created this problem.
He should be responsible
for solving it himself.
I agree.
I'll call you when it's done.
Thank you.
2-Charles-Nine.
This is Station Four.
There's a 2-11 in progress
at 2221 Mill Road,
cross street Cedar.
Two males seen
leaving bank with shotguns.
Respond Code Three.
Two-Charles-Nine.
Do you copy?
Stand back from the door!
Step back!
Two-Charles-Nine.
Do you copy?
You...
Are you Unit Nine?
Yeah.
You tell them
you're on your way.
One wrong word
and I will kill you.
Now.
Two-Charles-Nine...
Help! We're being robbed!
Two-Charles-Nine.
We have help on the way.
Get up, now.
Now's your time to let us go
before the cops get here.
Shut up.
These people are
your responsibility.
You'd better start
talking to them.
Sara,
has Chloe had any
contact with Bauer yet?
No.
What about the work she's doing?
Could it be on his behalf?
No. I've been watching
her system.
Chloe is not stupid.
Assume she's taking measures
to protect herself.
Maybe she's co-opted the help
of someone else inside.
I'm not quite sure
how much of my time
you want me to devote
to this, Miss Driscoll.
I expect you to be able
to walk and chew gum
at the same time, Sara.
Chloe's loyal to Bauer.
There's a good chance
that she's helping him.
Find out how.
What are you doing?
That looks like
a satellite screen.
It was.
I mean, it is.
A satellite for what?
We're trying to find
Bauer, remember?
Division's already doing that.
I'm just going over
what they're doing.
Sometimes they miss data.
Do they know
that you're doing that?
Yeah, they know what I'm doing.
Here, call them if
you don't believe me.
Relax, Edgar.
I don't have to call anybody.
Do what you have to do.
I will.
Do me a favor?
There's a chance that Jack
might try to contact Chloe.
If you see or hear anything,
call me, okay?
Why would Jack try
to contact Chloe?
He just might.
Let me know.
Sure.
Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, what did she want?
She wants to nail you
to the wall
and take a piece out of me, too.
Remember our deal.
If you get caught,
you don't take me with you.
And if I get caught,
you say you ordered me
to do this.
You don't have
to repeat the deal.
I'm the one who
came up with it.
Did you reposition
the satellite yet?
I'm working on it.
Leave me alone.
No, let them stay in the field.
We'll use our
own people for that.
Hang on, Ed.
Yes, what is it?
Miss Driscoll,
your daughter's on line two.
I'm busy.
Tell her I'll call her back.
She says it's important.
Fine.
Ed, I'm going to have
to get back to you.
All right.
Okay, bye.
Maya?
I need you to come home.
What's wrong?
I'm having a bad day.
Sweetheart, have you been taking
your medication?
No.
If you don't take it,
you're going
to feel bad.
Now, you know that.
It numbs me.
I don't like it.
Do you like feeling
like this better?
Come home.
I can't, Maya.
Why not?
Listen to me.
I want you to take the pills
and I'll call you back
as soon as I can, all right?
You promise?
Of course, I promise.
What are you going to do?
I'll take my pills.
Good.
Do you love me?
You know I do.
Then why don't you say it?
I love you,
Maya. Okay?
Okay.
All right, bye.
Behrooz, can I
see you for a moment?
Yes.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
I talked
to your father.
We both agree you have
to be the one
who'll take care of this.
But she didn't tell anyone.
And we're fortunate
that's the case.
But she still
saw the warehouse
and she could tell
the authorities about it,
if she's ever
brought in for questioning.
This is riskier
than letting her live.
If she disappears,
her mother will call the.
By the time
this day is over,
the will be too busy
to look for a runaway girl.
Now take it.
Don't make me bring
your father into this.
Just take her
to the basement and do it.
Don't think about it.
Get it over
Behrooz.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I want to make
a copy of this one.
Can I take it home
and scan it?
Sure.
We need to get out of here.
What?
You're in danger.
Are you kidding?
From who?
Don't ask questions,
just come with me.
What? Behrooz...
Trust me, Debbie.
We're okay. Come on.
I can't.
Why not?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Debbie?
Debbie,
what's wrong?
Answer me, Debbie,
Come on, Debbie,
what's wrong?
Get up, Debbie,
we need to go, Come on.
Please help me!
Come on, Deb!
What's wrong, Debbie?
Come on, Debbie!
Come on.
Debbie, what's wrong?
What did you do to her?
I didn't expect you
to be able to do it.
Debbie?
Come on, Debbie!
Debbie!
Give me the gun.
Hey!
I am so disappointed in you.
Yeah.
This is Sergeant Dennis McGrath.
You know you're surrounded.
You should know that I've got
hostages and I will kill them,
if you try to use tear gas
and send your men in.
Let's not go there
yet, okay?
Who do you have
in there?
The owner, two
men and a woman.
What about Officer Datson?
Yeah, I've got him, too.
You only need one hostage
to protect yourself.
Keep Officer Datson
and let the others go.
I need to think about that.
Yeah?
I've got satellite coverage.
Okay, good.
The suspect will be free
in about five minutes.
He'll be traveling
on foot on Route 11.
I'll find him.
One of you is coming with me.
You.
Come here.
Put your hands up
against the rack. Now!
Everybody else,
to the back of the cooler.
Move!
Open the door.
Lock the door
with the chain.
Now, I will let you go
as soon as we are clear.
But if you try and be a hero
again, I will kill you.
Do you understand me?
I understand.
Good.
Let's go.
Which car is yours?
The blue Lexus.
Unlock the door.
Move.
Tell those officers
to put their weapons down
and take five steps back!
Okay, calm down.
We're going to try
and help you through this.
Tell them to do it now!
Okay, drop your weapons
and move back!
JACK:
Stand back!
Do what he says. Step back.
Step back.
Come on. Come on.
Open the door.
Come on, open the driver's door.
You try and follow me,
I will shoot him!
On my count, get in.
One, two, three, move.
Go! Go!
Call in a roadblock.
Suspect driving east
on Route 11.
One hostage.
Move the rearview mirror to the
right so I can see out the back.
There.
When do you let me go?
When I feel like it.
Who are you?
What do you mean?
You don't seem like
the kind of guy
that needs to rob
a Mercury Mart.
That Mercury Mart
was a money drop.
There was supposed to be
18 grand in that safe.
How do you know that?
We're done sharing.
I'm not gonna forget your face,
and I've got
your driver's license.
You talk to the,
it's not gonna be hard
to find you,
do you understand me?
I won't tell them a thing.
Okay, pull over here.
Now!
Get out of the car.
Move!
Start running.
Now!
O'Brian.
You got him?
Yeah.
Good work. Now download
his position on my PDA.
And stay reachable.
I will.
I'm sorry,
could you repeat that?
Hold on a second.
Miss Driscoll?
Yes, Sara, what is it?
You have a phone call
from a man who says
he's your neighbor-
a George Cliocove?
He says it's about
your daughter.
What line?
Six.
George, it's Erin.
Erin, there's been
another incident with Maya.
What's happened?
She came into the backyard
where Evan was playing,
and she started
screaming at him again.
Is Evan okay?
Yes. Fortunately,
I was home.
But this is the end, Erin.
I've got to
protect my boy.
Did you call
the, George?
Yes, I did.
They're on their way.
Where's Maya now?
She went back to your house.
I'm very sorry, George.
This will not happen again.
It can't, Erin.
Miss Driscoll,
is everything all right?
No, it's not.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
Yes.
I need you to call LAPD
Westside and find out
who they dispatched
to pick up my daughter.
She has a medical condition.
She suffers from
schizophrenia.
There was an incident
with one of my neighbors.
What would you like me to do
once I find out
who they dispatched?
Tell the officers
to cancel the call.
I'll take care
of it personally.
Yeah, I don't think
that's possible.
Once a call's in progress, don't
they have to follow through?
CTU has preemptive
privilege over local.
Yes, but that's only in
a national security situation.
Sara, I'm asking you
to do something.
Should I ask someone else?
No.
I'll do it.
Send a unit over
to my house.
One medic,
one field agent.
Bring Maya back
to our clinic.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Yeah, I got it.
Thanks.
I found Jack Bauer.
Where is he?
In Solmas. He's still
tracking the hostile,
only now he's
using satellite.
How do you know that?
DOD just called
to complain that
someone over here was
stealing bandwidth.
I took a look at the
imagery and found him.
All right,
bring them both in.
Who logged on
to that satellite?
Chloe.
Chloe, why are
you logged on
to an active DOD satellite?
All right,
you're done here.
Whatever,
I was gonna quit anyway.
You're not being fired.
You're being arrested.
Call security.
Edgar,
lock up her systems
and take control
of all her files.
Yes, ma'am.
I want you
to call Jack Bauer now.
Yeah.
Driscoll wants to talk to you.
What are you talking about?
Hello, Jack.
Erin... look, I've got
some information for you.
The hostile's name
is Kaleel Hassein.
Stand down, Jack. It's over.
Erin, right now Hassein is free.
He's looking for
a car and a phone.
Once he has those things,
he's gonna lead us
straight to Secretary
Heller, I promise.
You can't know that
for sure.
What have you
got to lose?
You've got him
on satellite.
Just bombard the area
with a receptor beacon.
Send a team to pick
up the hostile.
Damn it, Erin, if you do that,
everything I've done over
the last two hours
will mean nothing!
I'm glad you finally
figured that out.
Erin!
Take Ms. O'Brian into holding.
ERIN: Edgar... you
have it up on satellite?
EDGAR:
Yeah.
The hostile's
flagging down a car.
You need some help?
Yeah.
I just, uh...
Give me the feed down here.
Sara, what's the load
on the cell tower
in that area?
About 40 to 50 calls.
Put personnel on every call.
Record every call.
Let's see
if he contacts someone.
Yes?
Omar, it's me.
Where have you been?
We've been worried.
Everything's fine.
I'll explain later.
Where are you?
I'll be there
within the hour.
Is the broadcast
on schedule?
Yes.
We're about to prepare Heller.
Hurry.
Edgar.
Not now.
Yes,
now.
How do you feel about
what's happening
to Chloe?
What do you mean?
She's not just
gonna lose her job,
she might go to prison.
What do you care about all this?
I overheard the conversation
you had earlier.
I know you were working with her
behind Driscoll's back.
What do you want?
I want to make sure
I have your attention
whenever I need it.
Thanks, Robin.
Miss Driscoll,
we got the call.
ERIN:
Put it on speaker.
Cue it from the
top of the call.
Omar, it's me.
Where have you been?
We've been worried.
Everything's fine.
I'll explain later.
Where are you?
I'll be there
within the hour.
Is the broadcast on schedule? Yes.
We're about
to prepare Heller.
Hurry.
Looks like
Jack was right.
Tell the teams to stand down
for the time being.
Keep tracking Hassein
by satellite.
Son of a bitch.
Damn it!
Get out of the car!
Put your hands in the air!
OFFICER:
Step behind the vehicle now!
Come on! Come on!
Get out of the car!
Get your hands up Now!
and step out of
the vehicle!
Suspect is armed...
Step away
from the car!
Take two
steps forward!
On your knees!
Put your palms down!
Put your chest flat
on the ground!
Keep your hands down!
All the way down!
www.tvsubtitles.net