The San Gabriel Island
reactor has just gone critical.
The core material
is now airborne.
HELLER:
I thought we had more time.
At this rem rate, the radiation
will continue getting stronger
and will spill
into the atmosphere
until the core
has exhausted itself.
Son, you've done
everything you can.
Now get the hell out of there.
Evacuating won't make
any difference, sir.
We've already been exposed.
Jack has got to
find the override
before the rest of these
reactors go critical.
I know about
you and him
and I am not
okay with it.
Look, you and I
aren't together anymore.
PAUL: I thought we were
trying to work things out.
Yeah, I tried.
But you kept putting it off.
What did you say to Paul?
That I'm filing for divorce.
Somebody set me up.
ERIN: Thousands of
people's lives are at stake.
Where are the people
who control the override?
Talk to me, Sarah.
I'm not a spy.
( gunshot )
Erin, Powell's dead.
He was hit by a sniper
as soon as we took him
into custody.
Did you find out anything
from him before he was killed?
No, but I managed to get
the last ten calls
he made off his cell phone.
He called two numbers
repeatedly.
We traced one of them
to Maryanne Taylor.
You're under arrest.
Don't move!
Drop the weapon!
( gunshot )
Listen carefully, Behrooz.
Government agents found me.
I made a deal.
BEHROOZ:
I don't understand.
DINA:
You're going to be okay.
I'm going to help them
stop your father.
You broke my heart.
If you kill me,
Mother will tell
them everything.
If you don't believe me,
look outside.
They're coming
to pick me up.
Drop the gun!
You'll hit the boy!
Behrooz!
Mom!
That stairway leads
to the basement!
He's got nowhere to go but down!
Set up a link with CTU now!
If you can't save my son,
I am happy to see
the reactors melt down.
Did you get that?
( phone ringing )
Driscoll.
Erin, it's Jack.
Araz is on the move.
We're getting ready
to move into the hospital now.
Daddy, you're choking me.
Jack, it's Jim.
Bring us up to speed.
We have a hostage situation
involving one of the men
that was involved in
the terrorist attacks
this morning.
ERIN:
I'm pulling up his I.D. now.
His name is Navi Araz.
The sleeper?
ERIN: He was granted American
citizenship five years ago.
Who's the hostage?
His 17-year-old
son, Behrooz.
He broke ranks and now his
father sees him as a liability.
Araz knows we have
his wife in custody.
He's worried that
if he kills
the boy, she'll betray him
by cooperating with us.
AUDREY:
What does she say?
ERIN: She's agreed to
help us find the override
and stop the nuclear meltdowns,
if we rescue her son.
So, the father will stall,
keep the kid alive
until the reactors blow.
That's right, sir.
We've already lost one
in California, Jack.
Can we trust
this woman to help us?
I think right now she'll
do everything she can
to protect her son.
Okay, Jack. Whatever
you need, you've got.
Just get that kid.
Yes, sir.
Erin, I'm going to need
a thermal satellite scan
of the building.
We're looking for two heat
sources in close proximity,
in remote areas of the basement.
I'll call you back
as soon as we have something.
Yep.
You're running out of time.
Save my son.
Bring her with us.
We're gonna need her.
I said
get on the floor!
You're not my son.
Why?
Because I don't want
to kill innocent people?
Because you're weak
and you stand for nothing!
I always saw you
as something more
and now...
I don't even
recognize you.
Will that make it easier
for you to kill me?
( phone rings )
MAN:
Navi?
Yes, it's me.
Did you find your son?
Yes.
Is he dead?
Not yet.
Is there a problem,
Navi?
Government agents
have arrested Dina
and surrounded the building that I'm in.
I need the boy
for leverage,
but I'm not sure
how much longer
I can hold them off.
Has Dina
told them anything?
I don't think so.
And she won't,
as long
as I don't kill the boy.
How much more time do you need
to melt down
the remaining
nuclear power plants?
One hour, maybe two.
Why?
Why so long?
The Americans
have programmers
trying to prevent
the meltdown.
That means we have to manipulate
each plant individually,
and that takes time.
I'll hold them off
as long as I can.
I know you will.
( phone beeps )
Yeah?
ERIN: Jack, I think we
found Araz and his son.
Where?
We have two thermal readings
in the north wing
of the basement.
What's there?
Laundry room.
How many ways in?
Just one, but according
to the blueprints,
there's a laundry chute.
Is it accessible?
>From the third floor.
It looks big enough
to get a man in.
Okay, we're on our way.
We got him.
Where are they?
Laundry room.
This is Bauer.
I need two teams
to the north wing.
Set up a hard perimeter.
We're moving to
the third floor.
I need a fast line
and a rappelling harness.
Got it.
Lee, get me Dina Araz.
We're putting her into play.
Where are the latest timing
estimates on the remaining
nuclear plants?
Right here.
These are from
40 minutes ago.
They update
every 15 minutes.
I'm sorry, Miss Driscoll.
I've been little upset
about my mother.
You have to put your emotions
on hold a little longer, Edgar.
We're in the middle
of a crisis.
My mother just died,
Miss Driscoll.
I can't put that on hold.
I'm sorry;
that was callous of me.
But I'm really depending
on you now, Edgar.
Please come through for me.
I'll get you those figures
as soon as we're done here.
Thank you.
HELLER:
All right,
bring me up to speed.
We're trying to hold off
the meltdown process
on five nuclear power plants.
How's that going?
Our programmers are trying
to fight off the override.
They can slow it down, but
they won't be able to stop it.
Which means we still have
to find the override.
EDGAR:
Yes.
Jack has a suspect cornered
at a local medical facility,
and we're fairly certain
this man he's pursuing
is one of the key architects
in today's events.
Can we take him alive?
Unknown.
What about
Maryanne Taylor?
I sent Curtis
to interrogate her.
I want to call my lawyer.
Really?
I do have rights.
Yeah?
Henry Powell
had rights, too.
I don't know any Henry Powell.
The one who helped the
terrorists obtain the override.
He's right here.
Want to say hello?
Bring him in.
You sick... sick bastard.
CTU didn't kill him.
Well, then who did?
The same people who planted
the bomb under your car.
Whoever they are,
they've caught up with you.
Even if we let you go,
you'd be dead in 15 minutes.
Get him out of here.
Your only chance to survive
is to tell us what you know.
I want a deal.
You get to live.
That's your deal.
All right.
Who did you and Powell work for?
I don't know.
I only dealt with him.
Why did he send you into CTU?
To cover his tracks in
case he became a suspect.
And after Audrey Raines
saw him at the warehouse,
it became necessary?
Y es.
Did Powell work directly
for the terrorists,
or for someone else
associated with the terrorists?
I told you- I don't know.
I need names!
People who can get us
to the override.
I don't have any names!
But I-I can get them for you.
How?
Powell kept a file
on his computer
at his office downtown.
It was a... an insurance policy
in case either of us ever needed
a bargaining chip.
Give me the address
and the access code.
It can't be accessed externally.
It requires a thumbprint
identification-
either his or mine.
Since he's dead...
it'll have to be mine.
All right, you set?
TONY:
Yeah.
We think we found them.
Where? The basement,
in the laundry room.
Our satellite picked up
two thermal images.
Then Behrooz is still alive.
Yes.
I'm going to need you
to distract your husband.
I'm going to take you
down to the basement.
In one minute, we're going
to have you call your husband.
We need you to keep him on the
line as long as possible. All right.
Let's go.
Okay.
You ready?
Ready.
Okay, keep going.
Six feet...
four feet...
three feet...
Stop.
All right, come here.
Okay, make the call.
Remember, keep him on
as long as you can.
( phone rings )
Yes?
It's Dina.
Where are you?
Still in the hospital.
What have you told them?!
Nothing.
And I'll keep my mouth shut
if you release our son.
You know I can't do that.
Then at least promise me
you won't kill him.
Is he still alive?
Yes...
and he'll remain alive,
as long as you remain silent.
I have a visual on the suspect.
The boy is still alive.
I'm ready to proceed.
Go.
Slowly retract the rig.
I'm in position.
( metal clanging )
Don't... move.
Get up slowly.
Put your hands
on your head!
Stay with her.
Put your hands on your...
( grunts )
Hostile's engaged!
( grunting )
I don't want to have
to kill you, but I will.
Now get up... slowly.
Interlock your fingers.
( silenced gunshot )
It's okay, son.
Just put the gun down.
It's over.
TONY:
Drop the gun!
Tony, don't shoot!
Please, son, put the gun down.
TONY: Put your hands on your head.
Hands on your head!
Turn around.
Behrooz, are you all right?
I killed him!
Your son is safe.
He's alive.
We did what you asked.
Now, where is the
override device?
I don't know that,
but I can give you an address
where much of the work
behind today's attacks was done.
That's not the deal we made.
That's all I know.
I can only tell you
what I know.
What's the address?
24878 Alvert Street.
What's there?
It was a drop-off.
The place we used
to get our final assignment.
It was the last place
I saw the men
who were going to take
possession of the override.
When was that?
Yesterday.
Send in an advance team.
Tell them to set up
a hard perimeter.
No one goes in there
until we get there.
You got it.
What about these two?
Until we know she's not lying,
they come with us.
So this Maryanne Taylor claims
she has to access
the file personally.
Yes, she does.
And do you believe her?
I'm not sure.
The polygraph indicates
that she's telling the truth.
But in my opinion,
she may be a sociopath.
Are you a psychologist?
No, but I have had dealings
with her before.
Dealings that might
affect your judgment?
No.
Well, we have
to check it out.
The question is how.
I can spare
an operative
from the cyber unit
and a security team.
What do you think?
I think Curtis should go.
I need Curtis here.
AUDREY: The information in the
computer file may be important.
Someone with experience needs
to examine it firsthand.
HELLER:
I agree.
Send Curtis with a security team
and you'll have
to figure out
how to do without him
till he gets back.
Yes, sir.
I don't like this.
Either do I,
but those are our orders.
Get it done and get back
here as quickly as you can.
Okay.
You okay?
Anything you need?
I'm fine.
You understand,
Sarah, I had no choice.
You were identified
as a threat to security
and I acted accordingly.
I would have hoped
you had more faith in me.
Personally, I do.
But the evidence
was brought to me
by the Secretary of Defense,
and I couldn't
very well ignore it.
So what happens now?
You can go home and rest.
No one would blame you
if you did.
But if you're up to it,
I could use you on the floor.
The San Gabriel Island
reactor went into meltdown
less than an hour ago.
The five remaining
plants are critical.
I need my best people
in play.
I'll go back to work.
Thank you, Sarah.
It shouldn't
be too complicated.
Building security is light.
I have a keycard
that'll get us
into Powell's office.
How long is it going to take?
Five minutes to get up
to his office,
another five
to download the data.
We're looking at a 15-minute
operation time?
Approximately.
If I think you're stalling,
taking longer
than you should,
I will take action.
You got that?
Raise your leg.
Don't make me do it for you.
Curtis, I'm not going to run.
Then you won't mind
wearing it.
Can I put
my foot down now?
Yes.
Look, I realize
that after today,
you have a hard time
trusting me,
but if we're going to pull this
off, you're going to have to...
I don't have to do anything
except retrieve the data
your boyfriend had
and put you in jail for treason.
Is that what
you really want?
Without a doubt.
Curtis...
Get your hand off me.
I spoke with Mike
at the local D.O.D. office.
He wants to know who you want
to bring in to help manage
with their load.
Things are too unstable
for me to leave here.
I have to keep my eye
on tactical.
Well, I checked with their logs,
and they're going to need
someone pretty soon.
How are you holding up?
I can handle it,
if that's what you mean.
Dad, it'll be fine.
Why don't you head over there,
then?
I'll call you from there.
Sarah, you're back.
Yeah.
I heard some rumors about
what they were doing...
I'll be all right.
Just bring me up to speed.
Sure.
We're still trying
to find the override.
It's the only way
we're going to stop
the remaining plants
from melting down.
What have you gotten
out of Maryanne so far?
She claims she has access
to a computer
that has data on it
about the override.
And which computer is this?
She's taking Curtis
over to it now.
They let her out
of the building?
Yeah. He's got a security team
with him.
And we trust her because...?
She's trying
to cut a deal.
Agent Bauer.
Agent Salars.
Agent Almeida.
Did you set
your perimeter yet?
Anything inside four blocks
is not going anywhere.
Any activity?
Not that we've seen.
Okay, I want to keep this
as surgical as possible.
You, me, and Almeida will be
the insertion team.
Your men will maintain backup.
You ready?
Yeah.
Go.
We're clear!
Dina must have been lying.
I don't think so.
She wants to save her son.
Well, then they must have
cleared this place out.
Bring in
a forensics team now.
I want this place
torn apart
for fingerprints.
Yes, sir.
Tony.
What is it?
Go.
It's clear.
That's the train
they attacked this morning.
So that's how the terrorists
got ahold of the override.
Jack?
They planned
the kidnapping here.
Yeah.
Edgar, the location
Jack is searching
didn't show up
on any agency watch list.
Yeah, well, I'm having
a hell of a time here.
Why?
The building is owned
by a company
that's owned
by another company,
that's owned by an LLC.
( typing )
Galaxy Financial?
I've heard that name before.
No, Hal, I want you to put
that in a separate file.
We'll handle the kidnapping and
the train bombing another day.
Right now, I only want
things that are pertinent
to helping us find
the override device.
Okay, I'll have it up on the system
when you get here. Okay, thanks.
( phone rings ) Tony,
look, I need to talk to you.
I'm sorry.
Just give me a minute.
Yeah.
Jack, this is Sarah from CTU.
Listen, I got something on
that address you gave to Edgar.
What is it?
The ownership of the
building is complicated,
but I recognize one of the shell
corporations on the ladder.
Which one?
Galaxy Financial.
I never heard of it.
Neither did I
until this afternoon.
When Paul Raines came in,
I was the one
who ran his clearance.
Paul Raines? What does he have
to do with the company?
He's a general partner
in Galaxy Financial.
You're telling me that Audrey's
husband owns the building
that was used by the terrorists
to plan this morning's attacks?
According to this, yes.
Where's Audrey now?
She's on her way over to D.O.D.
Patch her through to me.
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
Miss Raines, this
is Sarah from CTU.
I've got Jack.
Hold please.
All right.
Jack, I've got
Audrey on the line.
Audrey, it's me.
Hey, did you find
anything at the address?
Yeah, the building was used
by the terrorists
to plan this morning's attacks.
Jack, that's a great find.
Yeah, there's something else.
What?
The company
that owns the building,
it's called
Galaxy Financial Services.
Have you ever heard of them?
No. Should I have?
Your husband is
the chief financial officer.
What?
Audrey, the information is true.
CTU just verified it.
I need to find Paul.
I need to speak to him now.
Paul had nothing to do
with the kidnapping.
Maybe, maybe not.
But his name is all over
the paperwork for the building.
Because of his relationship
to you and your father,
he's going to have
to explain that.
Jack, I don't
know where he is.
He left CTU without
saying anything.
Can you reach him?
What? Yeah, I have
his cell phone number.
Okay, I want you
to call him.
I want you to
keep it personal.
I don't want you to
tell him what I know.
I just want you
to tell me where he is.
Audrey, five power plants
could still melt down.
If Paul has any information
that can help us stop that
from happening, we have
to follow through with it.
You know that.
All right.
Please get back to me
as soon as you can.
Okay, I will.
( phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
Hello.
Hey... Paul, it's Audrey.
I wasn't expecting
to hear from you.
I know, I was just...
Look, Paul, I-I didn't like the
way we left things between us.
I didn't care
for it much either.
Look, uh, I'm glad
you called, but, uh,
I'm about to check out.
Where you going?
What difference does it make?
Look, Paul, I was thinking
about what you said,
about how... we've got
so much going on for us.
I thought
you wanted a divorce.
Yeah, I thought so, too,
but...
You know, Paul,
today was the first time
that we've seen each other
in months, and...
I don't know, maybe it took
a while for it to sink in.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe there is something there.
Audrey, you know this is what
I want, more than anything.
Then let me come over.
I don't want to have
the most important conversation
of my life over the phone.
All right, I'm at
the Westmore, Room 408.
All right, I'll be there soon.
I'll wait for you.
( grunts )
Okay, no one goes
back down there
until the forensic team
gets here.
When they do,
I want the place torn apart.
I want fingerprints,
trace DNA samples,
fiber samples, everything,
you understand?
I understand.
Okay.
Hey, I need to follow up
on my own.
I need you to do me a favor.
I need you to take Dina Araz
and her son back to CTU
and head up the interrogation.
Wait a second, Jack.
They'll never let me step foot
in CTU, even if I wanted to.
Tony, listen.
You're the only one
I can trust to do this.
Over the last two hours,
I watched
my friend
come back to life.
It's not that simple, Jack.
If I press hard enough,
I can get you reinstated.
But I need to know now,
is that what you want?
I don't know.
Maybe I was wrong.
You saved the life
of the daughter
of the Secretary of Defense
who happens to be my boss.
You do know that, right?
TONY:
Jack...
Thanks.
I'll do it.
Lee.
Agent Almeida will
be driving your car.
( phone rings )
Yeah.
All right, Jack.
I spoke with Paul.
He's at the Westmore downtown,
Room 408. I'm heading
over there now.
No, Audrey! You need
to let us handle this.
We don't know Paul's
connections to the attack yet.
He could be dangerous.
Jack, I don't think
we have a choice.
He was on his way
out the door.
I had to make something up
just to keep him there.
Fine, I can get
there instead.
Jack, I'm only a couple minutes
away and he knows that.
He's not going to stick
around if I don't show up.
Audrey, I know you're trying
to help, but
I don't feel comfortable with
you going in that room alone.
Jack, it's the only thing
that he won't suspect.
He's been wanting to talk
about the marriage all day long.
Look, I'll keep him there
until you get there.
No, it's not an option.
Jack, just get there
as soon as you can, please.
Audrey. Audrey!
Erin, I just
got off the
phone with Jack.
He wants me
to approve
Tony Almeida's reinstatement.
Do you have a problem with that?
Considering what Almeida
has done for us today,
I do not have
a problem with that.
Good.
Sir, you said
you spoke with Jack.
How long ago was that?
Ten, fifteen minutes ago. Why?
We have some new information
I'd like to share with you.
We found a curious
connection to the terrorists.
What kind of connection?
Paul Raines.
My daughter's husband?
One of his companies
is listed as the owner of the
building Jack just searched.
The building the terrorists
planned the attack from today?
That's the one.
Has anybody gone to pick him up?
We have teams on the way
to the hotel where he's staying,
but he was about to leave,
and the only way
to keep him there
was under a false pretense.
False pretense.
What's that supposed to mean?
Jack called to tell us
that Audrey's meeting Paul
in his room. Jack's
on his way over there.
What?!
She's going to try
and keep him there
until our backup teams
can take over.
Unacceptable.
How could you
let this happen?!
This wasn't
my decision.
This was her choice.
Jack did everything
he could to stop her.
When did you
find out about this?
About five minutes ago.
That's when you
should have told me.
Yeah.
Find out.
Tell me everything you know
about Paul Raines.
Why?
What's his connection
to all this?
How should I know?
Look, Curtis,
I wish I knew
something that
you could use.
Believe me,
I'm quite clear
it's my only
way out of this,
but I don't
know any more
about Paul Raines
than you do.
How much longer?
We're about five minutes out.
Raines's part in all this is
being investigated as we speak.
If your name turns up linked to
the kidnapping in any way...
It won't.
I am going to do
everything I can
to find something in Powell's
computer that will help you.
Maybe something about Paul
Raines will be on there.
( phone rings )
Yeah.
What's this I hear about you
going to see Paul by yourself?
It's the only way
to keep him here.
If Paul was involved
in our kidnapping...
Look, Paul would never hurt me.
There is strong evidence
to suggest that he was involved,
which means he is dangerous.
Look, I don't believe he is.
You don't know
what he is, Audrey.
I've lived with him
for eight years.
I know him.
Yeah, I thought I knew him, too.
Audrey, I forbid you to do this.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm already here.
Mr. Almeida.
That's right.
Erin Driscoll,
Director of CTU.
How are you?
Uh, this is Mrs. Araz
and her son, Behrooz.
Mrs. Araz is in need of
medical attention right away.
Have her taken care of and
prepare them for interrogation.
We've told you
everything we know.
We'll see.
You're going
to need these?
( sighs )
Miss Driscoll,
I'm sure you're aware
of my history here.
Not an issue.
Jack Bauer and Secretary Heller
both vouch for you.
That's enough for me.
Thank you.
Uh, Jack thought
it'd be a good idea
if I headed up
the interrogation.
That makes sense.
You've had the chance
to observe them firsthand.
If there's anything
you need, let me know.
That man I was
just talking to
is Tony Almeida.
I want you to keep
an eye on him.
Let me know if he
goes off protocol.
I'm particularly
interested in...
...in any communication
between him and Jack Bauer
or Secretary Heller.
That's right.
I'm beginning to see how
things work around here,
Miss Driscoll.
How do things work around here?
You can care less
about me being
falsely accused
and tortured.
You're beginning
to feel squeezed out
and you need allies.
That's why you were
so nice to me before.
We're facing a
crisis today, Sarah,
and our first priority is to
deal with it successfully.
Is that a problem for you?
Not at all,
but after what I
went through today,
if you want my help,
I need something, too.
And what's that?
I want my arrest expunged.
Not explained
by an official letter
in my file- expunged,
and I want a promotion,
two pay grades.
Done.
( knocking at door )
Come on in.
I'm glad you came.
Can I get you
something?
Sure.
I had them send up
your favorite champagne.
To tell you the truth,
I, uh...
wasn't sure you'd really come.
Why wouldn't I?
You were so adamant
before about ending things.
Your turnaround
was just
a little surprising, that's all.
How about you?
I hardly hear from you
for about six months
and then you see me
with another man
and suddenly
you're pouring Don Perignon.
It shows what a fool I am
for not realizing what I had.
It also shows
that I still have
feelings for you,
and you must have some
for me, too-
otherwise you wouldn't
be here, right?
I would hate to think
you are playing
some kind of game with me.
I don't play games, Paul.
Okay.
To new beginnings?
New beginnings.
Miss Driscoll,
it's Jack on line three.
Jack.
Are the backup teams
at the Westmore yet?
No. They were
caught up in traffic.
I'm still a couple
miles out.
If your teams
get there first,
tell them not
to waste time
coordinating
with hotel security.
I want them in that room
as soon as possible.
Why not put some fiber
optics in place first,
get a better
position on Raines?
Because, if Paul's involved,
he's gonna be nervous.
I don't want anything
to possibly tip him off
before we're ready
to enter that room.
I don't want Audrey
in any more danger
than she already is.
Okay, I'll pass that
along to Tactical.
Has Curtis had
a chance to question
Maryanne about Paul yet?
She says she doesn't know
anything about him,
but they're about
to get into the computer files.
That might help us
find the override.
Okay, thanks, Erin.
It's right down this
hall and to the left.
Stay alert.
This place may not be
as empty as it seems.
What, you think
this is some kind of trap?
Yes, I do.
Like you said, Curtis.
This is my only chance
to stay alive.
I'm not going
to blow it, so relax.
Okay?
All clear, Curtis.
This will only take one minute.
Here it is.
All I have to do
is reformat
and then we can download
the data and get out of here.
Paul.
What?
The file has a second
password encryption.
Do you know it?
I think so...
but it's strange.
( gunshot )
Take your hand
away from the gun.
Take it away.
The files are still secure.
I-I didn't give
them anything. I...
Now put the gun down.
Put it down.
Your name is Curtis Manning.
You work for CTU.
You're going to tell me
how far along you are
in your investigation.
What investigation?
Of the override.
Have they discovered
where it is yet?
You're an American
and you're working
with the terrorists.
Who are you?
I'm going to ask you
one more time.
What does CTU know
about the override?
Fine.
Or...
I could move
to Washington.
I could turn West
Coast operations
over to Ben Simon.
Audrey.
Yes, I-I heard you.
Turn West Coast operations
over to Ben Simon.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I-I guess you'd have to decide
whether or not you thought
he was capable of running...
Not what do you think
of Ben Simon.
Wh-What do you think
of me moving back east?
Oh, um...
Well, I-I, I don't know.
I feel like I'm
doing all the work here.
You said you
wanted to talk.
You're not talking.
These things take time, Paul.
Well, maybe...
talking isn't what
we should be doing.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
You're my wife,
for God's sake.
You can't believe that I came
over here to sleep with you.
Okay, you didn't
come over here to sleep with me.
You didn't come over to talk
with me. Why did you come?
I just... I thought that
maybe we could spend
a little time together.
It would be nice.
On-on a day like this?
All hell's breaking loose.
You thought it
would be nice
for us to spend
some time together?
Well, I guess I really wasn't
thinking when you called, was I?
What are you doing here?
What's really going on?
Are you spying on me?
Are you doing something
worth spying on?
What is that supposed to mean?!
I just...
Maybe I should go.
I think you should stay!
Please, just let me go.
No!
Let go of my cell phone.
Take your hands off of her!
You set me up!
Audrey, get behind me.
Put your hands
on your head now!
Now!
What do you want?
I want answers.
Well, I'm not
talking to you.
Subtitles by Jaxdahl
www.tvsubtitles.net