Here are all the access codes for CTU and Division.
Thanks.
I'm probably gonna be gone a while.
If you need anything,you can always call me at home.
Excuse me,sir.
Driscoll's replacement's arrived.
Tony,I want to thank you for filling in.
I'd like you to stick around and assist Miss Dessler.
Who?
Michelle Dessler, do you know her?
I used to be married to her.
I have to go to McLennan-Forster.
Why there?
It turns out the man we're looking for works there.
Need to get into their computer system?
Yeah.
Okay,I'll go with you.
So how can I help CTU?
One of your employees,a Harris Barnes,
is actually Habib Marwan,
one of the terrorists responsible for today's attack
and the theft of the override device.
We need you to take your I.T. systems off-line
so Paul can look into his directory.
CTU will subpoena those files.
They will find out the truth.
Damn it.
what you doing
He's trying to rebuild the files I deleted.
Look at this.
,...
that's it.. Print it out,now! Now!
He's going to find evidence we sold arms to terrorists.
The pulse bomb, we have to use it,now.
We're dealing with an EMP.
Once it goes off,everything
within its radius that has an electrical component gets fried.
I'm going to try and stop it. If I don't,
I want you to take the hard copy
and try to meet me in the front of the building.
A CTU agent is heading down near you.
Don't let him anywhere near it!
Oh,my God.
the following takes place...
are any elect
only the...
How many square miles were affected by the blackout?
Approximately,eight.
The southeast quadrant of downtown.
Okay,hold your position until the readings stabilize.
Any word from Jack or Paul?
No. Once the pulse bomb went off,
we lost all communication with them.
What was the last word we heard from them?
Well,Jack and Paul found something.
It seems it must have been incriminating to McLennan-Forster.
So that's why they set off the EMP,to destroy the evidence.
That'd be my guess.
The fact that McLennan-Forster is taking aggressive action,
is evidence against them.
Yeah,but it's not proof.
Curtis,could Jack or Paul been injured from the detonation?
No,an EMP only damages electronics.
But it doesn't mean they're safe.
We know you printed a document before the EMP detonated.
Where is it?
It's up to you.
You decide when the pain stops.
Call me when he talks.
no
Drop the gun or I'll kill him!
I said drop it!
Paul?
Where's the data printout?
I hid it...
in an office down the hallway.
I know you're hurt,
but we've got to get it and get out of here. Let's go.
It's here.
Take a seat.
Where is it?
Bottom drawer, under some folders.
I hid it because I thought I might be captured.
Is this it?
Yeah,it's in code.
I couldn't make any sense out of it.
We need to get it back to CTU.
I don't think I could have held out much longer.
You did great.
Let's go.
For those of you who don't know, this is Michelle Dessler.
She'll be taking over
as acting director of CTU, effective immediately.
Tony,I appreciate you carrying the ball
until Michelle got here.
Why don't you bring her and everyone else up to speed?
Yes,sir.
Less than an hour ago, we discovered that the man
responsible for planning today's attacks,Habib Marwan,
has been a long-term employee of McLennan-Forster,
the third largest defense contractor in the country.
Now we know that Marwan's been using the alias Harris Barnes.
What we don't know yet,
is how he managed to evade their security checks.
Marwan knows we're looking for him,so he's probably gone dark.
But his association with McLennan-Forster
has become our primary focus.
Jack Bauer and Paul Raines went to the company
to inspect his computer files.
But as they were doing so,
an electromagnetic pulse bomb was detonated,
wiping out the company's entire database.
It also fried every electrical device
within an eight-mile radius.
Streetlights,computers,cars, cell phones,everything.
Were Jack and Paul able to find anything before detonation?
Yes,but we haven't been able to contact them since the blast.
We have to assume whoever detonated the EMP
thinks Jack and Paul found something and wants them eliminated.
Have rescue teams been sent into the area?
Not yet. Once we've confirmed that the affects have subsided,
we'll send two teams in with fully-functional electronics.
The only problem is,until we find Jack and Paul,
they're not going to be able to do much.
We want to do everything we can
to find Jack Bauer and Paul Raines.
But the priority is to retrieve any information
they found at McLennan-Forster.
That's all.
Tony?
I need the access codes for CTU and Division.
Thank you.
Division is sending over a supplemental list
of terrorists that supposedly had contacts with Habib Marwan.
I want you to check any names
that have been flagged by other agencies,including overseas.
Given what's happening right now,
it doesn't seem like the best use of my time.
It has to be done.
And I'd like youto do it.
Michelle,Jack and Paul
have information that could be vital
in helping us end this crisis.
I should be helping us find them.
Michelle...
The last time I saw you,
you couldn't stay sober long enough to keep a job.
That was six months ago.
This is what I need you to do.
If you don't like it, you can resign.
I'm gonna need a security clearance.
I'll make sure you get a level three.
A level three?
I used to have a six.
Right now,all you need is three.
Is there a problem with Agent Almeida?
Not at all.
It's just that Secretary Heller is very sensitive to personal conflictson the job.
I know your history.
I know that you guys were married
and that he sacrificed his career to save your life.
But if this is going to be a problem...
His being here will not affect my work.
I won't let it.
Now,if Secretary Heller wants to speak to me about it,
I'll be more than glad to.
We are receiving preliminary reports from LAPD,
indicating that there is widespread looting going on
in the blacked out zone.
A number of cars have been set on fire,
stores have been ransacked, shots were heard.
There may even be casualties.
We just don't know at this time.
Shots were heard? That could be
the same people that are after Jack. I don't get it.
What information could Jack have found
that would be worth setting off a pulse bomb?
Something that implicates McLennan-Forster.
Anything they're doing now is insignificant
if there's proof that they helped Marwanwith today's attacks.
This is Anderson.
It is time for you to go.
Marwan,your face is all over the news.
Don't worry about it.
Things will proceed as planned.
Are you ready?
Yes,of course.
How long will it take you to get there?
Less than 30 minutes.
I'll inform the others.
The helicopter's heading to McLennan-Forster,
and it's not responding to any of our ID requests.
You sure?
Yeah,I'm positive.
Michelle.
exuse me
There's a chopper flying through the dead zone,
not one of ours.
Police?
No. Not one of theirs either,I checked.
A chopper that size carries 20 menfully armed.
Who would have sent it?
Whoever set off the EMP.
They're going in after Jack and Paul.
McLennan-Forster's been training mercenaries for years.
Contact our field teams in the air.
Let them know about the intruding chopper.
Jack,I can't do this.
Don't have a choice. Come on.
You got it.
Give me that chopper back on the northwest corner.
Let's move!
Come on,this way.
This way.
Where do we go now?
Weapons and ammunition.
Get away from me! Get down!
Get out of here, or the next one won't miss!
I'm a federal agent.
Yeah,sure you are!
Get away from here!
Look,we need your help!
go! now!
Okay,just relax.
I'm leaving!
Okay,I'm leaving.
Drop the weapon. Now!
Kick the gun over to me.
Paul!
Get in here.
Pick up that gun.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I am a federal agent.
Well,you should have been here to help us to stop the looting.
You still have any rifles or they get them,too?
Behind the counter
Show me.
We're the first to be hit because everybody knows we're Arab Americans.
And we're good citizens.
We had nothing to do with what happened today!
Be quiet,Safah. He doesn't care.
take what you need, but leave us two guns.
We've chased the looters off once,but they'll be back.
Just stay there.
Give me the keys.
What are you guys doing here?
We needed to take cover.
What do you mean?
Who's after you?
It has to do with the terrorist attacks.
I have critical evidence that I need to get
to the authorities.
The men that are chasing us are responsible for this blackout.
They detonated a device called an electromagnetic pulse bomb.
It destroys all electrical activity
within an eight-mile radius.
So everything that's happened to us tonight- the looting,
the blackout- it's all because of the terrorists?
Yes,and the evidence that I have
can help prevent further attacks from happening.
Jack, the commandos will be here any minute.
Commandos?
He's right.
You both need to leave this store.
Right now,we're their target.
You're not safe here with us.
Why don't you leave? This is our store.
If I had a choice,I would!
You have weapons and shelter.
Right now,there is no other place for us to be.
Can I talk to my brother for a second?
Stay where I can see you.
What's the plan?
CTU knows we're in trouble.
They also know we can't contact them.
They can view this area with satellite and infrared.
McLennan-Forster's commandos arrived
in a military helicopter.
CTU had to see that on satellite.
If we can initiate a large enough fire fight,
we can force their commandos to use radio frequency
to communicate their positions.
And CTU will pick up the signal?
yes
So you want to engage
the McLennan-Forster army,
just the two of us?
We have a positional advantage,
and we only have to hold out until CTU gets here.
My brother and I talked about this.
We're staying.
I can't force you to leave your own property.
But this is not just a bunch of looters.
This is a very dangerous situation.
You don't understand.
For years,we've been blamed for the attacks by these terrorists.
We grew up in this neighborhood.
This country is our home.
If you're fighting the people who caused today's bloodshed,
then we'll help you.
I agree. The President should stay in the air
at least another hour, if not longer.
If he wants to speak to the nation,
he should do it from Air Force One.
Keep me informed.
I have an update on the damage
from the San Gabriel Island meltdown.
It's not quite as bad as we had feared.
How are you doing?
sit down
Any word from Jack or Paul?
no
I can't imagine how hard this must be for you.
There's something else, isn't there?
A couple of hours ago,
when we thought that Paulwas somehow involved with the attacks,
Jack questioned him.
And Paul has his pride, so he resisted,but...
Jack was pretty rough?
Very.
That's his job.
He had to make sure.
You have to believe that Jack had no choice.
I know,I guess it was just a shock to see it.
Somehow he seemed like a different person.
We need people like that, Audrey.
Jack is an incredible man. Just...
But you're not sure you feel the same way as you did before,is that it?
Something like that.
Could I speak to you for a moment?
It's important.
Okay. Um...
I don't have much time.
You're aware I was falsely accused
of leaking information earlier today.
I need people whose minds are on their jobs. Yours isn't.
Is the back entrance locked?
Yeah.
Okay.
Put one of these in each window.
Have extra ammunition standing by.
Then I want you to get two hunting vests,
fill all the pockets with empty clips. Go.
Ms. Gavin won't be workingwith us anymore.
...her workload.
We're stretched pretty thin as it is.
Everyone on the floor is up to their necks already
or not qualified to replace her.
You may want to reconsider.
No,I don't trust her.
yeah
You'll be working with Agent Stiles
and Manning for the rest of the day.
Edgar,I need you to call up Sarah's protocols.
Check the configuration, make sure they're accurate.
okay
I'll advise internal stations of the personnel changes.
Give me an update first.
The zone is still pretty quiet,except for emergency vehicle chatter.
There's no sign of Jack or Paul.
CTU's tact teams are standing by.
But the best we can do
is spread them around the perimeter, and wait for some sign of Jack.
When they do, we can follow the signal straight to where he is.
He's going to deliberately engage an entire team of commandos?
It's the most efficient way to be found.
If we send all our teams to one location and you're wrong,
Jack and Paul won't survive an attack.
If we cover the perimeter,
we may have a chance to save them.
Do it.
There's one of them.
It's time.
No one fires until I give the order.
ok
Team leader,this is Specter.
I was just shot at.
I'm on the northwest corner of Stringer,between Flower and Third.
Audrey?
yes?
Could you let DOD know that we've piggybacked
onto local law enforcement channels in the blackout zone?
I told them earlier we might need to use their feeds.
So you don't need them any more? -No.
All right,no problem.
Um,look,I didn't mean to be confrontational before.
Just... when you walk into a hailstorm,
you have to be decisive.
I think that you should re-evaluate your professional opinion of Tony.
Why's that?
This morning Jack had nowhere to turn.
And he went to the one person that he knew
would come through for him and that was Tony.
Tony saved our lives.
I didn't know that.
After that,we just spent a couple hours with him.
It's true,Tony does have a lot of issues,
but he is good at what he does,
and I think that we could use him on a day like today.
Thanks.
Tony,look,I just want you to know that...
just because I overruled you a few minutes ago
doesn't mean that I don't value your input.
Anything that you have to say, I will consider seriously.
Good.
guys
You sure you both want to do this?
Yeah.
My brother and I,
we're more angry about these attacks
today than you are.
But if he were here right now,
he'd be standing next to you just as we are.
Just stay low and do what I tell you.
Thank you...
for saving my life.
yeah
They're here.
Tony,Michelle just said that you were doing a search
on possible ties to Marwan. May I help?
Do you have a sign-on for the Zeitgeist server?
In Washington?
Yeah,it would save me time
if I could use it on this search.
Yeah.
There you go.
Thanks.
Anything else?
It should kick off a few names. You can help me
run them down once it's done searching.
Okay,great.
So,um...
did you tell Michelle what happened today?
I said that Jack called you.
Anything else?
Well,I didn't say you that were living with anyone, if that's what you mean.
She probably already knows that
A lot different than Washington.
Yeah,it is different.
Are you talking about Jack...
or yourself?
I think we found them!
See those signals underground?
Each one's a radio, all using the same frequency.
That's because they're planning an attack.
They converged on a location on Flower and Third,
about a quarter mile from McLennan-Forster.
You were right, he's actually drawing them in.
Sporting goods store, across the street.
Let's move.
Bravo One,move in.
Infrared is picking up automatic weapon fire
at the site of the radio transmission.
How much longer before our teams get there?
The ground teams are closest. They'll get there first.
When?
At least five or six minutes.
Who's helping him?
I don't know.
They've got to be civilians.
We need to end this quickly and get that document.
Is that understood?
Yeah. I understand.
Let's go.
Raji!
Hey,Raji!
You okay? Raji?
Fall back!
Okay,because of
the night vision goggles, if they get within ten feet of you,
shine your flashlight in their eyes,it'll blind them.
ok
Jack!
The gunfire stopped.
The teams on site?
Not yet.
Without enforce the commandos could have taken over the location.
Which means they might have taken the information back from Jack and Paul.
Get in touch with the teams.
I'll update Division.
If McLennan-Forster win the firefight,
what about Jack and Paul?
there is no way to tell
CTU personnel are approaching the location.
CTU,this is Castle, we're about to engage.
How many hostiles have been sighted?
Six down outside,unknown number inside.
Lee,it's Tony.
Are Jack and Paul still alive?
Unknown at this point.
All right,look,the hostiles cannot be allowed
to leave the area with the information Jack took from McLennan-Forster.
Do you understand?
We'll do the best we can.
No,Lee,listen to me.
Failure is not an option.
That information is what this whole thing is about.
Roger that.
Jack!
Yeah? I'm here!
You and Raines safe? -Yeah.
All hostiles are down. We're clear.
Copy.
Yeah,Dan.
No,no,my people will take care of that
when we sift through the data.
Yeah.
Okay.
Jack and Paul are okay.
What about the information?
We don't know if Jack has it yet.
But even if he does, we don't know that he's going
to bring us any closer to finding Marwan.
Well,we know that McLennan-Forster is involved.
That should yield some leads.
Well,it's going to have to be worked up here,
because McLennan-Forster's computers were all knocked out by the EMP.
You want to head that up?
all right
I'm going to make sure you get some help putting the store back together.
I need you to get this to CTU.
Nothing happens to this store, do you understand me?
Jack! Look out!
Paul?
Paul? Paul?
Medic!
Come on,stay with me.
Come on,Paul. Stay with me.
No,no,Paul.
Paul,stay with me. Come on,look at me.
Look at me. There you go.
Look at me.
I owed you.
You don't owe me anything. Just stay with me,okay
Jack,let the medic do the work.
Any problems?
What about you?
I'm leaving now.
The President of the United States is on a tight schedule.
We can't be late.
Ê± ¼ä£ºf1_ralf
www.tvsubtitles.net