English subtitles by PoneyTeam
Caption: Dean@F6- Resync: Noz
Previously on 24.
For God's sake, pull
yourself together.
You didn't have to kill her.
Yes, I did,
because you didn't have the
courage to kill her yourself.
Courage? To poison a girl
who did no harm to you at all?
This is my husband Navi.
This is Debbie's mother.
Is she here?
We haven't seen
her since yesterday.
Get in the car, follow her.
Make sure she doesn't
go to the police.
Chloé, you're out of here.
Chloe.
Don't worry, Edgar. Driscoll
doesn't know you were helping me.
She doesn't?
I'm the one who
got you into this,
I'm not going to sell you out.
We'll be here until you
tell me what I need to know.
Richard, your father was
kidnapped by terrorists.
Our polygraph analysis tells us
you're hiding something
that might help us find him.
There are people on the
outside looking for us.
You cannot give up.
I have to do something
while I still can.
This trial is going
to be a spectacle,
broadcast all over the world,
designed to humiliate
and degrade this country.
There's a gas pipe.
Did you check
out the briefcase?
Mm. It's fine.
I was afraid it might be
damaged in the train crash.
The case is very strong.
Come on! Get them out!
Now! Come on!
Hurry, open the door! Now!
I know you.
She recognized me.
She has to be killed.
Erin, I'm on sight.
Jack, stand down.
What are you talking about?
The Marines won't
get there on time.
The President wants to
take out the building
with a missile strike.
With the secretary
and his daughter inside?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're going to have
to clear the area.
Jack, don't go in there alone.
Jack, clear the area! The
building is going to be destroyed!
The following takes places
between 12:00 P.M. and 01:00 P.M.
James Heller, you have been
brought before this court of law
to stand trial
as a war criminal.
We will prove to the
people of the world
that these crimes against
humanity are the direct result
of the polices initiated
by you in your capacity.
Since the true extent of your
evil legacy is immeasurable,
we have done our best
to document those acts
which have been
witnessed directly
by the chosen followers.
Under your orders, the
death squads of America,
continue their imperious crusade
against the true believers
and pure followers.
How much longer
until the fighter
is ready to launch the missile?
Command and control is
locking on target now.
Mr. President, I have Erin
Driscoll on line three.
Mr. President, I'm calling
to ask you to consider
aborting the missile strike.
Based on what?
We are attempting
a rescue operation.
I was told that the
Marine Strike Force
was still 10 to
20 minutes away.
They are, sir.
Jack Bauer went in by himself.
The terrorist group is
moments away from executing
the Secretary of Defense
in front of the world.
And I cannot allow
that to happen.
I understand, sir.
But if Jack can effect a
rescue before that happens...
In that case, I'll
abort the missile strike.
But he's running out of time.
How long does he have, sir?
Seven minutes.
Try and make a sound,
I'll blow your head off.
This is a map of the complex.
Where are they holding
the Secretary of Defense?
I am either going
to kill you now,
or you're going to
tell me where they are
staging the trial!
Point... now. Where is the secretary?
There is no place in this world
where your evil has not scoured
the sacred land of the true word.
Your imperialistic
legacy has devoured
the lives of the innocent.
- Jack?
- Yeah?
The President won't call
off the missile strike.
How much time do I have?
Less than six minutes.
Did you get a read from
the thermal scan on
how many hostiles inside?
We estimate 16.
Jack?
I'm not turning back, Erin.
Understood.
Good luck.
...the injustices that
you have committed...
Stop this, please.
...on behalf of...
Just stop this, please.
You've got to stop this.
My father hasn't done
anything to hurt you.
He's an innocent man. Please!
Please. He's innocent.
Please.
Listen to me.
Please, no, no,
no, wait, wait, no.
You've got to stop it! Listen.
Audrey?
Behind you.
Oh, my God.
Jack!
Are you all right?
Did they hurt you?
No, I'm okay.
You've got to stop them.
I will.
Get my father first.
Go.
Take this.
Press the button on the handle.
You use that if you have to.
I'll be back for you, I promise.
Jack.
Finally, we hold you
responsible for blasphemy.
For desecrating holy
lands and shrines,
and for spilling the
blood of our brothers.
James Heller, your
guilt on these charges
is not a matter of dispute.
I have, here, a full
confession that you have signed.
And so, now, it is time
for your sentence to be read
and for the execution of that
sentence to be carried out.
James Heller,
before the eyes of God,
I sentence you to death...
to be carried out... immediately.
Call off the missile. Call it off!
Abort. Abort. Please confirm.
He's doing it.
There's one in the pipe, safety's off.
We've got to get Audrey.
Down the hall.
It's been aborted.
The strike's been called off.
Where are the Marines?
They haven't crossed
the perimeter.
I'll get an updated E.T.A.
We're clear.
She was here.
We got to go. Move!
Take the two shooters at your 11:00.
You ready? Go!
Give me a clip.
Jack!
It went off my vest.
It's all right. Keep firing.
I'm out.
I'm out, too.
It's the Marines. Stay down!
Mr. Secretary, stay down.
Just stay down until
this area is secure.
Jack!
Jack! Jack!
Put the gun down!
Step back or I'll kill her!
Step back! I will kill her!
Step back!
I will kill her!
Do it!
Okay. Okay, just relax.
Now just stay calm.
Just relax.
This is over.
You're surrounded.
You're right.
First, you'll watch her die.
Yes, sir.
The President sends along his gratitude.
I'm just glad you both are all right.
It's been a while since you've been
in the field, Jack.
Looks like you haven't skipped a beat.
Audrey and I owe you our lives.
Thank you, sir.
I've arranged transportation
for us back to CTU.
I'd like you and Audrey
to be debriefed there.
Just as long as we don't lose
any time in finding out
who these terrorists are
and where they're coming from.
As soon as we get back there,
I'll set up a live feed
with the office in Washington.
You won't miss a step.
Those soldiers there are
waiting to take us back
- to CTU.
- Thanks.
How's she doing?
The doctor needs to check out
some of these contusions
and she's dehydrated.
Thank you.
- You should go.
- Where?
I'm taking you and
your father back to CTU
Jack, when I was inside, I-I
recognized one of the men.
Who?
I don't know.
I-I can't place him, but I know
that I saw him before today.
They're going to correlate
a photo file of all the casualties.
As soon as they've got
that, you can make your I.D.
Excuse me. Bauer.
Agent Bauer, this is CTU.
I've got Paul Raines, on the line.
He'd like to speak to his wife.
Is she with you?
Hold on one second.
It's Paul.
He wants to speak with you.
Paul.
Audrey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm-I'm fine.
Thank God.
Where are you?
As soon as I heard about you
and your father, I got on a plane.
You're in L.A.?
Yeah. I'm at CTU.
Audrey?
Yeah.
See you soon.
I'll see you soon.
We need to go.
You all right?
Mm-hmm.
Make sure Edgar gets this.
Find anything?
I'm still trying to connect up
with the feed from the rescue site.
Division is using up
most of our bandwidth.
Call over there and tell them
to multiplex. We need to start
going through the debris.
Yeah, now that Heller is safe,
we're no longer in first position.
Miss Driscoll.
I took care of it.
What's that?
Our list of passcodes
for the FBI fiber.
You can use their feed.
How did you get that?
I used to consult there.
I still have friends.
As soon as I saw the load
on the routing table,
I knew we'd run
into a traffic jam.
Good. Install it.
Start cataloging whatever's
there. Anything that flags,
promote it up to me.
You know... if
you let me, Curtis,
I can help you a whole lot more.
Honestly, I don't even know why
you have a problem with me.
Because I'm ambitious?
Okay, I'm ambitious. Aren't you?
I don't sleep with people
to get ahead in my career.
Neither do I.
I slept with you because
I was attracted to you.
I still am.
Deal with it.
A White House spokesman
has just confirmed
that the interrupted
video transmission
was caused by a raid
mounted by the Marines
and the counter-terrorist
unit, who rescued
Secretary of Defense
James Heller moments ago.
Yes, I'm watching.
Of course I'm watching.
God willing, our good fortune
will continue for the rest of the day.
Thank you.
What are you talking about?
It's over.
They found Omar.
The government
stopped the trial.
Yes, I know.
Then how can you say this
is all good fortune?
Everything we've
worked for is ruined.
You made me kill someone
I cared about,
all for nothing.
No, not for nothing, Behrooz.
The trial was only
our first step.
I don't understand.
There were certain things
that your mother and I decided
to keep from you.
What things?
Please, I'm busy.
You forced me to
kill my girlfriend
because of this trial.
You owe me an explanation.
I don't owe you anything!
See who it is.
See who it is!
It's Terrick.
Why is he here?
Terrick.
Behrooz, you remember Terrick.
Of course he does.
I just spoke with Madwan.
He assured me that everything
is still on schedule.
- That's right.
- What are you doing here?
Your mother told Madwan
you took care of
the American girl?
Yeah?
Then you'll need help
getting rid of the body.
I don't need any help.
I can do it myself.
I'm sure you can, Behrooz,
but we can't afford
any more mistakes.
Show Terrick where the body is.
Go.
Okay, Agent Manning, this
is the last of the bodies.
- You shoud see them now.
- All right. Got it.
What's next?
Here's some more of
the terrorist gear
we collected out
of the warehouse.
Wait a second.
top. Go back.
You need me to retransmit?
No. On the ground
in front of you. Can you give
me a shot of that briefcase?
This?
Yeah. Can you open it?
It's empty.
Are there any
identifying marks on it?
Some kind of logo
engraved near the lock.
Let me see. Zoom in.
Zoom in.
Make sure that gets on the
next transport back here.
Will do.
Sarah. I need you
to do a corporate logo
search. I may have found
a link between the train
crash and Heller's abduction.
I'm sending it to you now.
Okay. We'll pick this up later.
The man I recognized
at the warehouse-
I want to make that ID.
As soon as you've been
checked out by the clinic.
I'll get the photos ready.
Excuse me, Ms. Raines.
This way, please.
It's all right. Go ahead.
Okay good.
Excuse us.
I'm going to need
to use your station.
Have Driscoll send me over a
passcode for the onsite feed.
Okay.
Thanks.
Does he know?
About you and Jack.
How long have you known?
Not until today.
Although I'm surprised
that I hadn't figured
it out till now.
But it's not what you think.
Paul and I were over before Jack
and I started seeing each other.
Except Paul doesn't
think it's over.
Last time I spoke with him,
he thought he had
a second chance.
Yeah, well, that's more
about fixing his wounded pride
than fixing this relationship.
So he doesn't know about it.
Not yet.
I'll take care of it.
This way, please.
Yeah.
No, not till I get back to DC.
Sarah said you may
have found a thread
connecting the train bombing
to Heller's abduction.
Yeah. About an hour ago, NTSB
reported that a passenger was killed,
but not as a
result of the crash.
He was shot at close range.
Who is he?
We're still trying
to find out.
He had no I.D.
His face and prints
don't show up on any database.
But whoever killed him
stole something he had
chained to his wrist.
I think it may have been this.
A witness on the train
saw a man with a
briefcase handcuffed to him.
Take a look at the damage.
It could have been
sustained during the crash.
We just recovered this
where Heller was being held.
What are you telling me?
That the train
bombing was a cover
for the theft of this briefcase?
What was in it?
It was empty.
We traced the corporate
logo on the briefcase
to McLennen-Forster.
- The defense contractor?
- Yeah.
Have you contacted them?
Just got off the
phone with their CEO.
He stonewalled.
Said before he
disclosed anything,
we'd need special clearance
from the Department
of Defense.
The Secretary should be able
to get us whatever
clearances we need from DOD.
Let's get a
printout of all this.
Yeah.
...story, only moments ago, a second
broadcast showing secretary of defense
James Heller was put on the internet. This
image was captured from that broadcast.
At this time, we have no confirmed
report on why the broadcast...
The girl's mother went home.
Even if she calls the police,
it will be too late.
I heard the news in the car.
Everything was accomplished?
Yes.
The trial was cut short,
but it served its purpose.
When they search
the warehouse,
will they figure
out what we're doing?
It doesn't matter.
It's too late for
them to stop it.
If everything is
working on schedule,
why do you look so troubled?
Where is Behrooz?
He went to bury the girl.
But his car is
still in the driveway.
He didn't take the car.
I don't understand.
He went with Tariq.
Tariq was here?
Oh, my God.
He's going to kill my son.
He's going to kill our son.
Yes.
I told Madwan that Behrooz
took care of the girl.
Madwan must not
have been satisfied.
He must have decided that
Behrooz was a liability.
How could you let this happen?
How could you let
them kill our son?
What could I do?
What could I do?!
He's our son!
Our flesh and blood!
Dina, listen to me.
How could you let
them kill our son!
Behrooz stopped being
our son a long time ago.
How can you say that?
Because it's true.
Living here has changed him.
He's been like
a stranger to us.
He proved it to me today
that he no longer
believes in our cause.
Maybe...
he never did.
Behrooz...
Behrooz... Behrooz...
Oh, my God.
Secretary Heller would
like to say a few words.
I'm incredibly privileged
to have the finest people
in the world behind me.
All of you.
It's going to take a
lot more than a few words
to express my
feelings, but for now,
from the bottom of
my heart, thank you.
Secretary Heller, Curtis
Manning, head of Tactical.
Curtis.
An honor, sir.
Please, sit down.
Erin, my daughter and
I owe you our lives.
It sounds like you had
to make some tough calls,
but you made the right ones.
I'll see to it that you get
full recognition for a job
exceptionally well done.
Thank you, sir.
Now, before we
start the debriefing,
I'd like to visit with my son.
Where is he?
We're actually holding
Richard here, sir.
Why is that?
When we brought Richard
in, we gave him a polygraph.
It indicated that
he was possibly
withholding
information from us.
About my kidnapping?
My son and I have
wildly different political views,
but I can't believe
that he was involved.
We don't think he had
knowing participation,
but we believe he
shared knowledge
of your whereabouts this
morning with someone,
and he refuses to
divulge their information
or their identity.
And what are you
doing about that?
We discussed a
number of options.
You have to understand
the circumstances.
Stop BS'ing me. What
did you do to him?
There's a technique
that's noninvasive
called sensory disorientation.
You subjected my son to SDT?
Yes, sir, we did.
But it was stopped the moment
- you were rescued.
- Jack, did you know about this?
No, sir.
I want to see my son now.
Of course.
Curtis.
Erin, I realize
you've been under a lot of
pressure these past few hours,
but you better have
cause for this.
Jack?
I appreciate you not
involving the Secretary
in the differences you and I had
on this operation.
We both did what we
thought was right, Erin.
I'd like to put the
past behind us, Jack.
I could use your help.
What do you need?
I'd like you to function
in Ronnie's position
as head of Field Ops
until we avert this crisis.
Whatever I can do to help.
Let me make one thing clear.
Ronnie was under my command,
and you will be, too.
Understood.
The photos from
the warehouse-
are they ready for
Audrey Raines to see?
I believe so.
I'll have Edgar
port them to a workstation.
Okay. Thank you.
Dad.
They said you were okay.
Audrey, too. Thank God.
I said some awf...
awful things before.
I was afraid I'd never
get a chance to apologize.
I said some pretty
harsh things myself.
But, no matter what was
said, you're still my son,
and I will always love you.
Me, too, Dad.
They said they were
using some interrogation
techniques.
They were totally out of line.
I am going to sue them blind.
I think it'll be a little more
effective if you
let me deal with it.
I promise you, if they were
out of line, heads will roll.
What do you mean, "if"?
Why did they think
you were holding
something back from them?
I don't know.
Richard, if you know something
that would shed some light
on what happened to me...
What, you don't think
I would tell them
if I thought it was relevant?
So there is something?
Now you're giving
me the third degree?
Son, do you have any idea what
your sister just went through?
If you know anything
that would help us find
the people behind this,
tell me now.
Dad...
I'm glad you're alive.
I... I really am.
But I am not going
to tell these people
things about my private life
that they don't need to know.
That you don't think
they need to know.
Richard, these people
were trying to save
our lives!
These people can't be trusted!
What they did to me is proof.
Agent Manning, could
you come in here, please?
Agent Manning,
I am authorizing
you to do whatever
you feel is necessary
to get this information
out of my son. Dad...
I love you, son,
but I have a duty
to my country.
You can't be serious.
Dad!
Bring the shovels from the back.
Come on. Help me.
They said it was
okay to come in.
Hi, Paul.
My God, I was so worried.
Are you hurt?
No, just some
cuts and scrapes,
nothing serious.
Sure?
Yeah, really. I'm okay, Paul.
They've okayed me
for my debriefing.
On the flight over,
I couldn't stop
thinking about us.
How when we
separated we said that
we'd both take
time to figure out
what we wanted and...
now I know.
Paul.
I want us to be together again.
I'm ready to work at it.
I'll make our marriage
first priority.
Just give us a chance.
I'm sorry, Paul.
That's not what I want.
Audrey, I...
I am a fool for
bringing this up now.
You can't make decisions
about our relationship
when you're in
this state. Paul.
I'm seeing someone.
Well, how long has
this been going on?
Six months.
You love him, or...?
Yes.
Audrey?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I'll come back later.
No. Um...
Paul, this is Jack Bauer.
Nice to meet you.
You're the one that
saved Audrey's life.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Those photos are ready
for you to look at.
Okay.
Um, Paul, we'll talk later?
Yeah.
You all right?
You ready to go?
Not yet.
Now i am.
No.
- No.
- You're absolutely certain you saw
this guy before the compound.
Positive, and I could
- tell that he recognized me.
- Okay.
No.
That's all of them.
He must have gotten
out before the rescue.
Okay, we should go
through the pictures again
just to make sure.
I will, but there
are only two men here
who aren't Middle Eastern,
and neither one of them are him.
What?
I just remembered
where I saw him before.
Where?
There was a Heritage
Foundation dinner
about two months ago,
at the Hyatt downtown, here.
Do you remember his name?
No, but I know someone
at the foundation.
Maybe I can get the guest list.
- Okay, good.
- Agent Bauer?
Driscoll wants you in
a conference call that's
starting in a few minutes.
Okay, fine. I need
you to get ahold
of the Hyatt hotel
security department.
Get access to their
archival video surveillance.
Audrey will give you
a time and a date.
Set a parameter, keep
Driscoll informed.
I'll be right back.
It's hot.
You brought me here
to kill me! Why?!
Why are you doing this?!
I did everything
they told me to do.
You know why.
I took care of the
girl. Madwan knows!
It's not Madwan
that wants you dead.
Who wants me dead?
Who?!
I want to know! Tell me!
Your father.
No!
It's not true!
No! No!
Please!
No!
Mr. Reese,
I'm Erin Driscoll, Director
of CTU Los Angeles.
My colleagues Curtis
Manning and Sarah Gavin
are also present.
Also, Jack Bauer who's Special
Advisor to Secretary Heller.
Ms. Driscoll, I
hope you understand.
We at McLennen-Forster
couldn't give you details about
that case until we received
the appropriate
permission from DOD.
Understood, Mr. Reese.
May we please begin?
What was your
courier transporting?
It's a device we developed
under the Nuclear
Regulatory Commission's
Emergency Management Program.
It's a Dobson-type override.
What exactly does
this override do?
It's a combination of
hardware and software
that can remotely take control
of a nuclear power facility.
Under what circumstances
would the override be used?
The government wanted
to be able to control
a plant's nuclear pile
in the event of a disaster
that necessitated evacuation.
And the person
in possession of this program,
could they do the opposite
with it, create a disaster
at a plant, a meltdown?
Theoretically, yes.
But merely having
possession of the override
wouldn't be enough. There
are safeguards in place.
What kind of safeguards?
Anyone who's trying
to use the override
would have to hack through
the reactor's firewall.
That would take
massive computer power,
which NRC could see
coming a mile away.
Is it possible that
NRC could miss this
due to unusually heavy
traffic on the Internet?
I don't follow.
Well, less than an hour ago,
millions of computers
around the world
were streaming the trial
of the Secretary of Defense.
Is it possible that this trial
was just some kind
of a Trojan horse
to disguise a massive attack
on nuclear power
plants' firewalls?
That might be possible.
How many nuclear power
plants in this country
would be vulnerable?
All of them.
How many is that?
At this time,
the United States has 104
nuclear power plants online.
We have to assume that
they've used this override
to take over these plants.
Get me NRC now
and find Secretary Heller.
Thank you, Mr. Reese.
Set up an all-department briefing.
Get me NRC, now.
Pipe it through here.
I want all personnel
in the conference area.
Edgar...
can you monitor my
allocation tables
for a few minutes?
Sure.
Yes?
It's me.
You're on a secure line?
Yes.
I would've checked in sooner.
This was the first chance I got.
All right. Go on.
They find out about the override.
www.tvsubtitles.net