24 SO4E19
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
CC: Johnsonh
Timeline: Mars
Translator: sHiN3
Supervisor: Requiem
Previously On 24
There's a convoy missing.
It was headed from Illinois
to Jefferson City, Iowa.
It disappeared just inside the border.
Disappeared?
They were due to call in at
that checkpoint every 20 minutes.
They didn't.
I tried to reach them
through comsat.
There was no reply.
What was on the trucks?
A nuclear warhead.
They found us.
Where are you?
It doesn't matter.
It's over.
They already got us.
You have to kill Prado.
He knows too much.
Drop the gun!
Drop the gun now!
Put the gun down!
Who are you?
My name's Joe Prado.
I'm innocent.
Mr. Prado's rights will not be violated.
Take me to him now.
We have no choice, Curtis.
Do what he says.
There's a nuclear warhead missing.
This is our only lead, Bill.
What the hell's going on here?
You've got a key witness
on a missing warhead.
We should be pressing this
guy with everything we've got.
Jack, it's Mike Novick.
Mike, if we want to procure
any information from the
suspect, we're going to have
to do it behind closed doors.
You're talking about torturing this man?
I'm talking about doing what is necessary to
stop this warhead from
being used against us.
All right, gentlemen, I'll have
an answer for you in 20 minutes.
Mr. President, this thing
could be over in 20 minutes.
What if I could find another way to handle
this that wouldn't
implicate anyone else but me?
I'm not going to authorize that, Jack.
You don't have to.
What do you mean?
Accept my resignation.
And if I do that, what then?
Release the suspect.
Now you're throwing me out?
That's right.
Make a sound and I will blow your
brains out all over the windshield.
Where is he?!
I don't know!
Where is he now?!
Where's Marwan?!
Okay, okay, okay.
Marwan's...
Marwan's going to be at a place
called the hub club tonight.
Where is it?
It's...
Where is it?!
It's just east of downtown!
This will help you with the pain.
The following takes place
between 1:00 A.M. and 2:00 A.M.
Put me through to the White House.
President Logan?
No, not the president.
Mike Novick.
One Moment Please.
I'm sorry we're trying to locate Mr. Novick.
Call me when you've got him on the line.
Yes sir.
What happened?
Prado talked.
Who did this?
Audrey...
I'm a representative of DOD.
I have a right to know, Bill.
Did Jack do this?
Yes, he did.
It was the only way to get him
to give up Marwan's location.
So President Logan gave Jack
the authority to use force?
No, Audrey, the president didn't.
Where's Jack now?
He's prepping a team to apprehend Marwan.
Curtis, Castle told me
you want to utilize LAPD?
I'm having them lock down
a ten-block perimeter.
I don't think that's the right call.
Marwan's people are coming and going.
We lock down that area, we
just give them a heads up.
All right.
We'll stay invisible.
Excuse me for one sec.
What is it?
I just came from the clinic where they're
treating Prado for a multiple injuries?
Audrey, what do you expect me to do?
Marwan has a nuclear warhead and he's
going to use it, unless we find him first.
I understand the situation, Jack.
Then you know what I did
was absolutely necessary.
At least now we know where he is.
Logan gave you a direct
order not to use extreme
interrogation measures
without his authorization.
Jack, you are acting against the president.
I know.
Jack, we're set.
I'll be right there.
All right, everyone, let's move out!
I've got to go.
Jack, you can't keep working outside
the line and not expect consequences.
Trust me.
No one understands the
consequences better than me.
No one.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Why?
Just asking.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Look, for whatever it's worth,
you did the right thing with Prado.
Thanks.
Authorizing the torture of a
foreign national is one thing, but
torturing a U.S.Citizen... I can't...
Sir,
this man Prado has information on
the whereabouts of a nuclear warhead.
We don't know that for sure, Mike.
No, sir, we don't.
Because you're not letting
CTU do what they need to do.
I want to wait till the attorney
general gets back to me with an opinion.
Mr. President, we are running out of time.
Walt, you were the first one
to raise an objection to this.
What do you think now?
I think you need to make a decision, sir.
And sooner rather than later.
Mr. Novick, Bill Buchanan's
on the phone from CTU.
He's called twice. It's urgent.
I'll be right there.
Yes.
What should I tell him?
Mr. President...?
Stop pressing me for an
answer I'm not ready to give!
I need more time.
I'm sorry for the delay, Bill, but the
president is still working
through his decision.
The president won't have
to make that call, Mike.
What are you talking about?
Prado gave up Marwan's location.
I thought Prado claimed
he didn't know anything.
He did.
He changed his mind.
You mean Bauer physically coerced him.
Tell me what happened, chapter and verse.
Mike, Bauer got the information we needed.
I think it's best if I
insulate you from the details.
The president gave explicit orders.
You should have restrained Bauer.
With all due respect, restraint is
a luxury we can't afford right now.
What am I supposed to tell the president?
Convince him to sign off on
the extreme interrogation,
and we'll cheat the timeline
in the official record.
I made the mistake of deceiving one
president; I won't make
the same mistake twice.
Even though we both know Bauer was right?
Mike...
Someone out there has one
of our nuclear warheads.
May I speak off the record?
Go ahead.
I'm worried about President Logan.
Worried?
Why?
His behavior over the last few hours..
I'm concerned about his ability
to lead us through this crisis.
I understand.
Yes?
Where are you?
At the Iowa location.
We just arrived with the package.
Has Sabir done the compatibility check?
Not yet.
Call me as soon as he's finished, and I'll
have the next payment wired to your account.
Is it compatible?
I'll need to reconfigure
the trigger mechanism.
Is it compatible?
Yes.
How long will that take?
An hour.
Maybe less.
Then you should start.
My girlfriend.
She'll leave a message.
She's already left three messages.
I don't want her calling around for me.
Take the call, but hurry up.
Nabila?
Where are you, Sabir?
It's the middle of the night.
I asked you where you are.
At the hotel.
Stop lying to me.
I called.
You never checked in.
Tell me what you're doing.
Nabila, I can't talk about this now.
Get some sleep, and I'll
explain everything tomorrow.
You mean after you've had time
to come up with another lie?
I found something on your computer, Sabir.
A bookmark.
Do you have something to do
with what's been happening today?
How can you ask that?
Are you working with these terrorists?
Of course not.
You know I'm not a violent man.
I know your politics.
Nabila, enough.
Stop talking nonsense.
Is it nonsense?
Like I said, I'll explain things tomorrow.
Sabir, listen to me.
She's fine.
Don't worry.
I want schematics on the
nightclub, options for a
staging area, and let county
know we need traffic control.
Thank you.
Bill, how could you let Jack torture Prado?
Audrey, it had to be done.
The president made it very clear that
he didn't want Prado's rights violated.
That's right, he did make
it clear, and he was wrong.
We can't just break protocol
because we think it's
right at the time and
expect to get away with it.
Normally, I'd agree with
you, but in this case,
I'd rather ask for
forgiveness than permission.
What kind of answer is that?
The answer is it worked.
We got Marwan's location.
Audrey, will all due respect,
this is not Washington, D.C.
Policy and politics do not always work on
the front line, which is where we are today.
Yes, well, Charles Logan is a politician,
and he is not going to give you forgiveness.
I hope this does not come
back to haunt you or Jack.
If what we did gets us to
Marwan, we'll live with it.
What is it?
CTU located Marwan.
They've sent a tactical team to grab him.
That's good news.
But I'm curious how they
obtained Marwan's location.
Did they use force?
Yes, sir, I believe force was
used, but I'm sure I don't need
to remind you that this is an
extremely time-sensitive situation.
Who's responsible, Mike?
I'm asking you a question, Mike.
Who did this?
Jack Bauer.
I'm the President of the United States!
I can't allow this kind
of insubordination to
go unanswered, especially
in a time of crisis!
I want Bauer arrested.
I agree that that should
happen, sir, but I think
we should wait until we
have Marwan in custody.
No, I want him arrested now.
Sir, Bauer is heading the field operation.
Jack Bauer is not the only
man that can do the job!
Put someone else in charge!
Mr. President...
Get me secret service!
Yes, Mr. President.
Has Jack set the robotic camera in position?
It should be ready in a few minutes.
We're set to receive.
Thanks, Curtis.
Get this to Audrey Raines and
have her stream it to DOD, please.
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Mike Novick.
I just got out of a room
with president Logan.
He knows how we got the
information from Prado.
How did he find that out?
He's not a stupid man, Bill,
and I'm not going to lie to him.
Well, you'll just have to convince
him to leave it alone then.
I tried.
He's not going to leave it alone.
Fine.
Tomorrow he can bring charges against me.
Right now, I have to get back to
the business of finding Marwan.
It's not tomorrow and it's not you.
What does that mean?
He wants Jack Bauer arrested.
Arrested?!
Mike...
Jack is heading up the team
that's trying to bring in Marwan.
We're aware of that.
Logan's adamant.
He wants this dealt with immediately.
Anything less he will take as a
personal repudiation of his presidency.
Okay, what's more important, the
president's feelings or capturing
the man who's responsible for
everything that's happened today?!
I hear what you're saying, Bill, but
Logan's already called the secret service.
They're on their way to
take Jack into custody.
I suggest you warn him immediately.
Before we move in, we need
confirmation Marwan's inside.
I'll send in the remote camera,
see if we can get a visual.
What's your point of entry?
Ventilation shaft.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Can you get the schematics
for the AC configuration
for the building, send it over to my pda?
I'm on it, Jack.
I'll send it to you as soon as I can.
Okay
The camera's working.
O'Brian.
We've got a Los Angeles woman
reporting suspicious activities.
First Tier wants it kicked up to you.
Cross reference and I.D.Match?
She seems to be who she says she is.
Okay, send her information to
my screen and put her through.
Here you go.
This is Chloe O'Brian, how can I help you?
I was just telling the man on the phone, I'm
not sure who exactly I should be talking to.
I'm an analyst at CTU Los Angeles.
Why don't you start at the beginning?
I'm calling about my boyfriend.
What's his name?
You need to understand, I'm
not sure if this means anything.
You were about to tell me his name.
Sabir Ardakani.
We've been going out since grad school.
Can you spell that?
S-a-b-i-r A-r-d-a-k-a-n-i.
Where'd you go to grad school?
Berkeley Tech.
We were both studying engineering.
He's been traveling a lot
lately, "business trips," he said.
I'm not sure why I looked, probably because
of everything that's been going on today,
but I found something on his computer.
Tell me.
I think Sabir may have
become involved with...
radical groups.
You mean terrorists?
Yes.
Where is Sabir now?
He said he was going to Arizona for a client
meeting, but the hotel has no record of him.
When you looked through his computer
files, tell me what you found specifically.
Most of his files are encrypted,
but there was one document
in the recycle bin that's a
schematic for a microchip-
A type I've never seen before.
Jack, do you copy?
Yeah.
Buchanan wants to talk to you.
Now?
He says it's urgent.
Fine.
Go ahead, Bill.
Jack, we've got a problem.
Secret service is on their way
over there now to arrest you.
What are you talking about?
Logan knows we violated his
order when you after Prado.
Bill, they can't interrupt this mission.
You got to stall them.
Jack, I've been on the phone
for the last ten minutes.
There's nothing I can do from here.
You have to get Marwan before
secret service gets there.
Curtis, did you copy that?
Yeah.
I'll run interference.
Give me a couple minutes.
I'll be ready to transmit.
Yes, we're ready.
Excuse me, Marwan.
I just talked to Abat in New York.
As soon as you're done,
I'll upload the tape.
Good.
I want this delivered to television
stations by dawn on the east coast.
That won't be a problem.
Do you want to cover your face?
No.
I want the american people
to know who did this.
Ready.
People of america, you wake
up today to a different world.
One of your own nuclear weapons
has been used against you.
It'll be days and weeks before you
can measure the damage we have caused.
But as you count your dead, remember
why this has happened to you.
You have no understanding
for the causes of the
people you strike down or
the nations you conquer.
You choose to meddle in
their affairs without respect.
You follow your government,
unquestioning, toward your own slaughter.
Today you'll pay the
price for that ignorance.
I have camera in the vent.
I've got a visual on the main room.
Approximately 50 civilians.
Marwan won't be here, he's going
to want to stay out of sight.
Hold on, I've got a possible sentry...
and a second possible sentry at the
window, looking down on the street.
Michelle, can you get a frame grab?
We're working on an I.D.
Sending a freeze frame to the
facial recognition software.
Jack, we have a match.
He's a known associate of Marwan.
That confirms that Prado
gave us a legitimate address.
But not that Marwan is in the building.
We can't risk exposing ourselves
till we know he's in there.
Castle.
Secret service is approaching your position.
Jack, secret service has arrived.
Did Marwan's people see them approach?
No.
They came up through the rear alley.
Moving on to the next room.
Unless you renounce your policies of
imperialism and interventionist activities,
this attack will be followed by another,
and another after that..
I've got a visual on
people in the storage room.
How many?
Five.
But they're talking to
someone outside my sight line.
I got it.
All right, stand by, Jack.
What's going on?
Secret service.
I'm Agent Greg Merfield,
this is Agent Frank Wells.
We know this is a highly
irregular situation, but
we have orders to take
Jack Bauer into custody.
Curtis, let me talk to them.
Go ahead, Jack.
This is Jack Bauer.
Right now we are trying to confirm
that Habib Marwan is in this building.
He is a terrorist in possession
of a stolen nuclear warhead.
I cannot impress upon you
how sensitive this mission is.
The president was specific, sir.
We need to pull you off this now.
I don't think you understand.
I am in a concealed position.
You pull me out now, you put
this whole operation in jeopardy.
As soon as this is over, I give
you my word I will go with you.
I'm sorry, agent, if you don't come out,
we're going to have to come in and get you.
Local secret service command
has confirmed the order, Jack.
There's nothing I can do about it here.
Jack, we don't have a choice.
We're going to need to replace you.
Jack, this is Castle.
I'm heading out to you.
Fine.
Approach the south side of the building.
Got it.
Curtis, we're on the move.
All right, be careful.
Marwan, the police are here.
Nasir saw an officer outside.
Start packing.
Hold on, I got a visual on Marwan.
I have a visual on Marwan.
He is in the building.
Damn it, they know we're here.
Everybody move on the building.
Our cover's blown!
Everyone, go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!...
Down!
Down!Down!Down!...
Everybody, get down!
Down! Down! Down!...
Freeze!
Hostile down.
I got him, Jack.
Marwan and his men have escaped through
a hole in the outer basement wall.
Set up a two-mile perimeter,
cover all utility access points.
Bomb!
Bomb! Go!
Jack, what happened?
Curtis!
Jack, do you read me?
Jack, you okay?
Yeah.
Check on the men.
Michelle, it's Jack.
We can't pursue, they blew
the tunnel up behind them.
It's completely blocked.
Have LAPD tighten up the perimeter.
Get them to tell us what
this tunnel feeds into now.
Yeah.
Jack...
Agent Bauer...
Agent Merfield.
Secret service.
I'm sorry, but I'm here
to take you into custody
Hand over your weapon.
You blew this mission.
I'm sorry, sir, I'm just following orders.
has anyone asked President Logan
what the hell he was thinking, arresting
Jack in the middle of the operation?
Look, Curtis, we still have
to focus on finding Marwan.
We pulled up city records.
The building is directly
adjacent to a sewer line.
How many street-level
egress points are there?
At least 30.
Which means Marwan's probably
gotten past our perimeters already.
Yeah, well, we still have to keep looking.
LAPD and FBI will set
down a grid down there.
I want you to coordinate your men with them.
We just found a videotape
on the man we shot.
It's been damaged, but we should be
able to recover most of what's on it.
Well, have one of your men come
back here with the videotape.
Edgar's repositioned the satellite.
We'll let you know if we find anything.
You got it.
How did Marwan get past your men?
They had to move in before they were ready.
Why?
Secret service showed up to take Bauer into
custody, which compromised
one of our positions.
I didn't mean...
that's not what i meant to have happen.
With respect, sir...
your orders were explicit.
What other search protocols are you running?
None, Mr. Novick.
We're essentially without a lead.
Bill, give us a few minutes.
We'll get right back to you.
Standing by.
This is not my fault.
None of this would have
happened if Jack Bauer
hadn't disobeyed my
orders in the first place.
Sorry, sir, but if you're asking me
to agree with that assessment, I can't.
If it wasn't for Jack,
we won't locate Marwan.
CTU is waiting for us to call
them back with a directive.
What would you like me to
tell them, Mr. President?
I have no idea.
And that's the problem, isn't it?
It is my fault we lost him.
This man, Marwan, has a nuclear
warhead, and I allowed him to escape.
Mr. President...
Stop.
I don't even know if I
deserve to be called that.
Whatever I call you won't change the fact-
you are president of the united states.
I shouldn't be.
For the good of this
country, I should resign.
That's not an option, sir.
Not without destroying the public's
confidence, which is already at its limits.
Three presidents in as many
hours would be devastating.
Then what should I do, Mike?
Tell me what to do.
There's someone who can
advise you better than I can.
You should consider bringing him
in here to help you through this.
Who?
President Keeler is in
critical condition after Air
Force One crashed in the
Mojave desert a few hours ago.
A white house spokesperson
reports that the president was
taken to an undisclosed military
hospital following the crash.
Sir, there's a secure call
coming through for you.
Thank you, Adam.
Hello.
Mr. President...
Mike?
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry to disturb you so late.
I've been up all night following the news.
This is a tragic day for our country.
Yes.
May I ask when you received
your last intelligence briefing?
Three hours ago, why?
Since then, the terrorist behind
today's events, Habib Marwan,
has taken possession of a nuclear warhead.
My god.
How?
Well, he recovered the football
from the wreckage of Air Force One,
and he used it to track
and steal the warhead.
President Logan feels he needs help.
What kind of help?
Substantial.
I'm not sure what you're asking me to do.
President Logan is requesting that you
run the effort to recover the stolen weapon
and be in place to make whatever
decisions need to be made.
A crisis is looming.
Hard choices may need to be made, and
by the president's own admission...
he feels he may not be up to the task.
This country is very possibly about to
face the worst terrorist act in its history.
We need your leadership.
Before I do anything,
I want to speak to
President Logan face-to-face.
Fair enough.
We'll notify your secret service
detail to bring you to the White House.
All right, Mike.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Please step out of the car, Agent Bauer.
What's going on?
President Logan realized this was a mistake.
You're free to go.
I am genuinely sorry about all this.
Doesn't really help us
with our situation, does it?
We had Marwan.
Any sign of him?
We have people all over the tunnels.
So far, nothing.
We had him.
Damn it!
They're not finished searching the tunnels.
If you haven't found him
yet, you're not going to.
Too many ways in, too many ways out.
CTU have any new leads
on Marwan or the warhead?
No.
Great.
Load everybody up.
We're going back to CTU now.
All right, everyone, let's go.
Edgar...
I'm busy, Chloe.
I need you to release your system.
Why?
It's the only one with a random sequencer.
You're gonna have to wait.
I can't wait- someone called a lead in.
And now that Marwan's
escaped, I need to pursue this.
This is more important.
I have agents out there looking for Marwan.
I need to reconfigure
the perimeter for them.
You don't need your system to do that.
Just tell them to use the profiles
we loaded onto their panels.
That won't be good enough.
Things are changing every minute.
They're field agents, they have guns.
They don't need you to coddle them.
You know, that's a pretty rude attitude.
I need your system.
No.
Tony.
What?
A woman called in, and she
thinks her boyfriend may
have had something to do with
today's terrorist attacks.
Did you verify it?
No, that's the problem.
I need to use Edgar's system.
Why?
Her evidence involves data that she
got from her boyfriend's computer.
It's in proprietary format.
Well, what's Edgar doing?
He's screwing around, moving agents
that Jack and Curtis don't need.
Edgar.
Yeah?
Let Chloe into your system.
What about tactical I'm running?
I still got guys out there.
Marwan's long gone.
Most of those agents you can call back in.
Excuse me.
Yes?
This is Morrison.
Is there a problem?
I haven't heard from you.
CTU found the club.
How'd they know you were there?
Must have been Prado.
Has the warhead been reconfigured?
Yes.
Then our timetable remains unchanged.
Marwan...
we, uh, may have a potential
security breach here.
Who?
The technician, Sabir.
His girlfriend's getting suspicious.
But it's being taken care of?
Of course.
It's been handled.
Let me know when it's done.
Tony.
Yeah?
The woman with the phone tip who was
suspicious about her boyfriend panned out.
What'd you find?
She sent us a schematic of a
microchip that we did analysis on.
It's used exclusively in
legacy nuclear warheads.
Does this include the
warhead Marwan has control of?
Yes, this is the design of the chip that
controls the trigger on the stolen warhead.
What do we know about the man
whose computer we found this on?
His name is Sabir Ardakani.
According to his girlfriend,
he's recently become radicalized.
I want his picture and I.D.
On an all-agency distribution
list, highest priority.
She thinks he's out of state,
but she has no idea where.
Well, if he's in this
with Marwan, he's probably
somewhere in the Iowa
region, with the warhead.
This woman who gave you
the tip, is she local?
Yes.
Los Feliz.
She says that the rest of the
files on his hard drive are locked.
If that's the case, we're
going to need a specialist.
We're going to need to send
a team over there as soon
as possible and see what
else we can dig up on him.
All right.
Chloe, I want you over there.
What?
Take a team with you, let's get on this.
Oh, I'm not a field agent.
I don't do that.
Chloe?
We need a specialist on this.
You're the only one who can get
those files off that hard drive.
I want to know what Ardakani's
doing and where he is.
Chloe...
I'm giving you an order- go.
Does my panel have a live
link to the tactical network?
Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
We don't do that until the agent's on site.
I'm not an agent.
I know that, but you're
attached to a mobile unit, Chloe.
I'm just trying to do things by the book.
Isn't always what you tell me to do?
Why do you have to be so contrary?
I'm just not comfortable out here.
I want to make sure you
have everything covered.
Fine, you have your live link.
What else?
Trunk my audio in with Bergen and White.
I want to make sure that I can
monitor two-way between them and CTU.
Done.
Okay, I can't think of
anything else right now,
but if I do, I'm going to call you,
and I really hope you don't give
me so much resistance next time.
Chloe, I know you're scared, and I'll make
sure everything is covered on this end.
Why did they ask me to do this?
I really hate it.
While you were prepping, I asked
Buchanan if I can go instead of you.
He wouldn't let me.
He said you were the best analyst we have.
He's right.
I know.
I'll call you if I can
think of anything else.
Okay.
Hi.
I'm Agent O'Brian, these
are agents Bergen and White.
You're Nabila Al-Jamil?
Yes.
Where's the computer?
Please, come in.
These men need to search the house.
Did Mr. Ardakani keep records
other than on his computer?
There are some papers in the bedroom.
This is the computer you
found the chip schematic on?
Yes, but like I told your people on the
phone, the rest of his files are encrypted.
Are you sure?
Yes, I ran a check sum and
built a subroutine to confirm.
I have a doctorate in computer sciences.
Okay, let's see...
You're right.
They used blowfish algorithm.
How can you tell?
By the tab on the file headers.
Can you decrypt it?
CTU has a proprietary algorithm.
It shouldn't take that long.
We'll start by trying to hack the password.
Let's start with the basics.
Write down nicknames, birthdays, pets-
anything you think he might have used.
Okay.
What was that?
I don't know
Go!
In here.
Your men are dead.
Open the door.
Don't you have a gun?
I work with computers.
Open the door.
Edgar Stiles.
Edgar, it's Chloe.
This is an emergency.
We're being shot at!
Where are you?
The Los Feliz location.
We need help!
Okay, all right...
Jack, Curtis, Chloe's in the field.
She's under fire.
What's her location?
1482 Franklin, Los Feliz.
Curtis, how far out are
the closest tac teams?
I'm on it.
Chloe, it's Jack.
What's your situation.
I barricaded us in the laundry room.
Who are you with?
Our informant.
Bergen and White were with me.
Bergen's down, I don't know where White is.
I'll call you back.
Chloe, don't hang up the phone.
Get her back on the line now.
Hurry.
This is Jack Bauer.
I need an LAPD response at 1482 Franklin.
We have two agents down, one under fire.
Where are the tac teams?
About 15 minutes.
That's too long.
Be open, be open...
where are the keys?
Jack, it's her!
Put her on speaker.
Jack, how far away is help?
At least ten minutes.
Ten minutes is too long.
Chloe, just try to stay calm.
Tell me where you are now.
He's shooting at us!
The glass is bulletproof.
Chloe, I need you to tell me where you are.
We're in a CTU car.
He's shooting at us from outside.
I don't have the keys. Can I hot-wire this?
No, it's secured.
But there should be weapons
stored inside the vehicle.
There's a rifle in the back.
It's locked.
I need the combination.
I'm on it.
Chloe?
Where's going?
Wait, I think he's leaving.
We got the combination?
Not yet.
He's going to ram us!
Oh, god!
What's taking so long, Jack?!
I've got it!
It's three-one-four-three!
Chloe, did you get that?!
Three-one...
What's going on here?
What's doing?!
Go, get out!
Get out, get out!
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
www.tvsubtitles.net