24 SO4E18
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
CC: Johnsonh
Timeline: Mars
Translator: sHiN3 Requiem
Supervisor: rustyapple sHiN3
Previously On 24
This is air force one
declaring an emergency.
We're not gonna make it.
I have to put it down now.
Chloe, what's happening?
Chloe!
Air force one is down.
This may be him.
It's the president.
He's still alive.
I repeat, the president is alive.
Marwan has to be within a 50-mile radius...
Jack.
There's a higher priority
than finding Marwan.
What is it?
Recovering the nuclear football.
Didn't it go down with air force one?
The missile inflicted enough damage that the
plane left a trail of
debris as it went down.
A lot of things were sucked
out, including the football.
That case contains the codes and
locations of our entire nuclear arsenal.
What's the location of the football?
40 miles northeast of here
in the middle of the desert.
Air support!
Football is in the lead jeep headed north.
Take it out!
I'm in possession
of the football.
Three hostiles are down,
one escaped.
I'm not positive,
but I think it was Marwan.
There's some pages missing.
Tell me what the contents
are of the missing pages.
Jack, it's the red section which contains
warhead locations and activation codes.
If they get ahold of a
warhead and a matching
activation code, we will
not be able to stop them.
Mr. vice president...
President Keeler is alive.
But he's in critical condition.
Sir, I recommend you
invoke the 25th amendment
and take control of things
as soon as possible.
You're worried about him?
I am.
He seems unsure of himself.
I do solemnly swear that
I will faithfully execute
the office of the president
of the united states,
preserve, protect and defend the
constitution of the united states.
Mr. President, I have just
received a phone call from CTU.
Part of the nuclear football has
fallen into the hands of terrorists.
The following takes place
between 12:00 A.M. and 1:00 A.M.
Vice president Logan has
been sworn into office.
He's now president of the united states.
His office called, they want
an update from us in 15 minutes.
We're working on several protocols
related to the plane crash.
What is he going to want to focus on?
He's going to want to know
how a stealth fighter was
stolen from one of our air
bases and, more to the point,
how it was able to take down air
force one with one of our own missiles.
Has he been briefed on Marwan?
He knows Marwan is the mastermind
behind today's events, yes.
But he's going to want more
specifics on the football.
Where are we on that?
Jack's at the debris field outside of indio.
He's trying to reconstruct the red chapter
of the playbook that was stolen by Marwan.
How's he doing that?
He's working with fred laughton
from the department of defense.
He wrote the codes, so
he'll know what's missing.
Good.
Who's going to run point on this update?
You and Tony.
All right, everyone, we don't have a lot of
time, so we're going to
have to fast-track this.
Double source all intel through
homeland security and CIA.
Skip the usual request procedures,
tie into their data directly.
yes?
Ms. Dessler, I've got
Jack Bauer on the line.
Put him through.
Go ahead, Jack.
Michelle, are you still in briefing?
Yes, Jack, you're on speaker.
What have you found?
Fred Laughton and I just
finished a rough reconstruction
of the red chapter- we're
getting that over to you now.
Jack, it's Bill Buchanan.
Summarize our exposure.
What information exactly does
Marwan now have in his possession?
Well, the red chapter lays out the
location of our domestic nuclear arsenal.
The inventory is in the thousands.
Many of the weapons are in transit as
part of our standard shift operations.
Why can't DOD just secure these weapons?
Because a number of the weapons
are in between checkpoints.
It would take over an hour
to account for all of them.
Listen, everyone, we've got to
remember, Marwan only needs one.
All right, Jack, we'll
get on this immediately.
Get back here as soon as you can
and help Audrey liaison with dod.
We need to account for every single
weapon documented in that chapter.
I'm on my way.
The coordinates for the third one
are latitude 37 degrees, 14 minutes.
Longitude 115 degrees, 21 minutes.
There it is.
Jefferson city, Iowa.
When is the warhead due to arrive?
7:00 A.M., Local time.
Five hours from now.
That puts it somewhere 200 miles east.
It's still in illinois.
We can intercept it anywhere
from this point to here.
All right.
Let's put our people in place.
The warheads that are in
transit because of the daily
shift-and-hide operations
pose the biggest problem.
We can verify military traffic
in the coastal areas from here.
Why don't we find out what
DOD has in the midwest.
Yeah, that's already underway.
Audrey said she should
have it in a few minutes.
Look, Tony...
am I interrupting something?
No, Chloe.
What is it?
Are you logged on to division three?
Yeah.
Look at this:
15 minutes ago, the
credit card of Eric Murphy
was used at the western
gas station in torrance.
Who's eric murphy?
His real name is yosik khatami.
He's a terrorist affiliated with Marwan.
How do we know that?
Through a watch list.
We put out a net asking for anybody
connected to the name Habib Marwan.
We didn't expect to get any hits so soon.
Why was he so careless?
Maybe he wasn'T.
Maybe it's some sort of decoy.
Well, it wouldn't be much
of a decoy because we don't
know where he is or what
direction they're traveling in.
This was a mistake.
Did the gas station have
a surveillance camera?
Yes.
He's driving a black lexus 300.
Are we hooked into satellite?
Yes, we're monitoring them now.
If this guy's still on
the road, we'll find him.
Who do we have in the area to run point?
Curtis just left division.
He's heading over here right now.
Divert him to western gas station.
Have field ops meet him there.
All right.
This is audrey.
Hey, it's me.
Hey.
Are you on your way back here?
Yeah.
How much of the weaponry has
been accounted for so far?
72 percent.
We're having problems getting
confirmations from the midwest.
Why?
There are several convoys
shipping weapons to be
dismantled in accordance with
the arms reduction treaty.
A lot of them were re-routed after
the train bombing this morning.
Just use local channels.
All weapon transports have to
check in with regional substations.
Just call them directly.
All right, I'll do that.
How you holding up?
I'm okay.
What have the doctors told you about paul?
They're having a hard
time keeping him stable.
You just hang in there.
He'll fight through it.
Yeah.
Tell Michelle I'll be there in 20 minutes.
All right, will do.
Bye.
yes.
Marwan, it's me.
Is everything all right?
No.
No, it's not.
I made a stupid mistake.
They're going to find me.
What happened?
I stopped to get gas.
While I was driving away,
I realized I used the
wrong credit card, the one
with the name Eric Murphy,
the one you gave me.
I told you to get rid of that one.
I was in a hurry, Habib.
I had to make the arrangements
for the delivery of the warhead.
When that transaction gets flagged,
they'll be searching the highways.
I know, that's why I'm
not on the highway anymore.
Where are you?
Inglewood.
I'm on my way to Prado's now.
You're closer to the marina.
Go straight there.
I'll have him meet you.
Prado can make arrangements
to get you out of the country.
Thank you, Habib.
Thank you.
Mr. President, it may be
precipitous moving to the bunker now.
Working from the oval office
might exhibit a greater
sense of confidence in our
abilities to handle this crisis.
The purpose of the bunker is to protect
the president in times of crises, is it not?
Yes, sir.
now
I feel it's always wiser
to take the prudent course.
Will I be able to function at
100 percent down here, mike?
Absolutely, mr. President.
What kind of protection
does this bunker afford?
Total.
You're 200 feet below the surface.
If the white house suffers a direct hit,
everyone in the bunker would be safe,
as would the communication
infrastructure to the rest of the country.
Let's hope that's not needed.
Mr. President...
Bill Buchanan from CTU is on the line.
Hello, Bill.
What do you have for me?
Mr. President, I'm here with
Michelle dessler, director
of CTU Los Angeles and Tony
Almeida, heading up tactical.
Good.
Let's get started.
Have all of our armaments referenced
in the red chapter been secured?
Not completely, mr. President,
but we're working with DOD on that.
What else do we know?
The man who has choreographed today's
events, Habib Marwan, is still at large.
Most likely he is in
possession of the red chapter.
What are we doing to find him?
We just picked up a thread, sir.
We have a location where one of Marwan's
associates was detected 20 minutes ago.
That sounds promising.
What else?
We're sifting through all of our intel now.
We're hoping to put together
a pursuit scenario soon.
So you're pretty confident you'll be able
to catch this terrorist, this Habib Marwan,
before he strikes again?
It's not an exact science, sir.
All we can do is maximize
the probability for success.
There are no guarantees.
Of course.
I understand that.
We need to get control of the situation.
I can't run the government
from down here indefinitely,
but I'm not going upstairs until it's safe.
Sir...
I think their time is better
spent working up what they have.
I recommend we let them get back to it.
Okay, bill...
call us when you have
something more concrete.
Yes, sir, I will.
All right, let's get back to it.
Wait a second.
Does anybody else feel uneasy
about what we just heard here?
In what way?
Logan's supposed to the
man who speaks to the
people of this country
and exudes confidence.
Not fear.
Air force one was just attacked, president
Keeler is in critical conditional.
Logan was just sworn in, give him time.
We don't have time.
We've got Yosik Khatami.
A traffic cam picked him up,
heading towards the coast.
We have him on satellite.
Link this up to Curtis, I want
him running point on this takedown.
Tell Curtis to remain discreet.
I want to know what Khatami's doing, who
he's meeting, before we take him down.
Michelle...
I was out of line before,
about you and Bill.
It's your life, and I've
got no right to judge you.
I appreciate that.
And whatever tension there is between
us, I want to apologize for my part in it.
I'd like it if we could just let
it go, so we could do our jobs.
Leave the past in the past and move on.
Sounds good.
all right
Curtis just called in.
He's about to arrive at
the marina and set up.
Good, set up a satellite,
also patch in an audio link.
I'll take care of it now.
Thanks, Edgar.
You want me to run point on that?
No, bill and I will do that,
but I want you in on this.
To do what?
I'd like your tactical input.
Fine, uh, I'll have Edgar transfer
everything over to the situation room.
I get the feeling Tony's not entirely
comfortable with the
configuration here today.
We haven't seen each
other for a very long time.
It's uncomfortable for both of us.
The difference is, you seem
to be able to stay on point.
I'm not so sure about him.
I am
He'll be fine.
He's alone.
What's he doing?
It looks like a meet.
He's waiting for someone.
Is the marine unit in place?
Yeah, behind the jetty.
Looks like the man Yosik's meeting
just arrived, he's walking towards him.
Is it Marwan?
I can't tell.
Remember, Curtis, we need them both alive.
All right, copy.
All right, all teams, I'll
close off the foot of the pier.
Keep them contained,
but do not shoot to kill.
Repeat, do not shoot to kill.
Damn it.
Teams respond.
Who is that?
This is macallan at point three.
It looks like a private patrol.
All right, hold your positions.
Yosik..
Brother.
You're late.
I've been standing here waiting for you.
Well, I'm here now.
Let's go.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Wait.
What's the matter?
Someone's here.
This is Miller. Blue base is clear.
It's okay.
It's just marina security.
No, something's wrong.
They're onto us.
Yosik, now.
The man he's meeting is not Marwan.
Is there anybody else there
besides the two of them?
Not unless there's someone else on the boat.
All right, marine units, move into position.
All teams, move in.
We're okay.
I think we should just get out of here.
There was a police officer out there.
I told you, that's harbor security.
They stop by all the time.
Damn it.
Who the hell's that?
This is CTU.
We have you completely surrounded.
Yes?
They found us!
Where are you?
It doesn't matter.
It's over- they're
going to get us.
Yosik, you can't let that happen.
You cannot allow yourself to be captured.
I understand.
Also, you have to kill Prado.
He knows too much.
I'll do what's necessary.
Yosik?
Come out with your hands up!
You're completely surrounded.
There's no escape.
Drop the gun!
Put the gun down!
Step off the boat.
Get off the boat.
There's a man inside.
I shot him- he
was gonna kill me.
He was trying to steal my boat.
It was self-defense.
Put your hands on your head.
Who are you?
My name's Joe prado
I'm innocent.
I have nothing to hide.
Where's Yosik?
He's dead.
This phone was lying next to him.
Get him out of here.
let's go
Secure the boat.
Yosik's dead.
We have the man he was meeting.
He says his name is Joe Prado.
Bring him in.
We also recovered Yosik's cell phone.
We'll try and pull something off it.
I'll report to you en route.
Good work, Curtis.
We're standing by.
What do you want to do?
Control the situation.
Make sure Prado doesn't
talk to the authorities.
He can hurt us.
How do we get to him?
We can'T.
Not directly.
Hello?
This is Marwan.
Yes, Marwan?
Can you reach amnesty global at this hour?
For what?
An attorney.
I'm sure I can.
Tell them that an innocent
man is being held without
charges and is about to be
tortured at CTU Los Angeles.
By god's grace, President Keeler
survived, but more than 75 others did not.
I share in your grief and
anger from this tragedy.
My family and I feel no differently
than each and every one of you.
We are shocked, saddened
and maybe a little afraid.
These terrorists have displayed, once
again, their indifference toward human life.
They will pay for what they
have done, I assure you.
Bill, excuse me.
There's a convoy missing.
What?
It was headed from
Illinois to Jefferson city,
Iowa- it disappeared
just inside the border.
Disappeared?
They were due to call in at their
checkpoint every 20 minutes, they didn'T.
I tried to reach them on comsat.
There was no reply.
What about satellite?
Nothing showing up.
What was on the trucks?
A nuclear warhead.
Our faith and our resolve will prevail.
Okay, we've got the fingerprints.
I'll run them through our databases.
thanks
What do we know about the
prisoner Curtis is bringing in?
Just the name he gave: Joe prado.
Curtis just uploaded his picture and prints.
I'm running them through now.
Prep holding so curtis can begin
interrogation as soon as they arrive.
I want this man broken
in minutes, not hours.
Clear all directories,
put all resources into finding this warhead.
Believe me, Mike, I wish I had
known about this sooner, too.
Look, I'm not pointing fingers here.
I'm on your side,
but the president is not going to be happy
that the statement he
made could be invalidated.
I don't know what to tell you.
We're putting everything we've got
into finding this missing warhead.
All right, we'll get back to you.
Move!
Inside!
Let's go!
Move, move, move!
We've got it and we're heading out now.
General Thomas just told me
we're missing a nuclear warhead.
Yes, I just heard some of the
details from Bill Buchanan.
When did this happen?
It disappeared somewhere between 1:45 A.M.
And 2:15 central time.
None of our satellites
was able to pick this up?
It was in mountain terrain at night.
Our people are analyzing the imagery
now, but it's going to be hard to find.
What are we going to do if
we don't find this man Marwan?
Our people are doing everything they can
to contain him to the Los Angeles area.
It's going to be difficult for him to leave.
Yeah, well, it's difficult
to shoot down air force one
with our own stealth fighters,
but he managed to do that.
Who knows what else they're planning?
I'm sure he's going to come after me next.
Mr. President, there's no
indication that that's his plan.
You don't know that!
I don't know that!
We don't have enough information
to know what his plan is!
The head of Secret service
is on his way over now.
He has a revised plan that I'm certain
will ease your mind about your safety.
That's the bastard curtis
found at the marina.
The one that's helping the terrorists.
I guess.
I'd like to get him in
a room for a few minutes.
What?
He'd talk to me in about ten seconds.
Oh, you want to hurt him to get
revenge for your mother dying.
I can understand that.
Take him to holding.
Did Edgar run the prints I sent?
Yeah. The name checks out.
Joseph prado, ex-marine.
No criminal record, but over the last five
years, he's got no record
of employment, either.
Which means he's a criminal or a mercenary.
That's right.
I'll find out if he knows
anything about the missing warhead.
All right.
Tony
What do you got?
I found the convoy
I've just got off the Iowa highway patrol
Millitary transfer was ambushed
Everyone's dead
what about the warhead?
Gone
Alright,find out what kind of
vechile being used to transport
also tell the local
law-enforcement to put up premiters
I want you to check for
any airstrip server remotely
clearence they might be
able to put down a chopper
Yeah
Remember he's ex-marine
He won't cave easily
I just need to establish that even
we're in the government building
I'm gonna go as far as it takes
How are you gonna start?
i will use Richard
OK
I've told you i'm not talking to you,pal
I haven't been doing anything wrong
I killed that man,it was a self-defence,he
was trying to steal my boat.
We both know it's a lie
So let's not wasting our
time,what do you say,John?
I'm not saying anyting to you.
Now,you're lying to me
What the hell is this?
Yes
Michelle,where's curtis?
He's just about start with pardo
Tell him to stop.
What?
That's an order, both of
you, come to the floor, now.
- It was a
self-defence - Curtis
- You can't do this to me
- Curtis
What?
Bill wants to see us before we start
Wait till I get back
What's this about?
I don't know
We have a problem with that
This is david winston from amnesty globe
And I have a signed court
order here protecting the
rights of joesff Prado who
knew have been in custody
You see US maschalls are here to assure
that i'm taking to the prisoner immediately
That's ridiculous
That's your opinion
But Mr. Prado's rights will not be violated
Take me to him now
We are not assured Curtis
Do as he says
There is a nuclear warhead missing
This is our only lead Bill
I'll get into this with the Justice Department.
In the meantime do what he says
When can i expect his call?
It's extremely important
Yes,i understand that
but i need to talk to the
judge immediately please
have him called me back
Mr. Buchanan
Do you have those hourlies for me?
No, i don't
but i'm here on another matter
you what?
I heard the interrogation on
prado have been put on hold
that's right
why
you have a job to do,please get back to work
I know i'm not supposed to be
interfering in the matters of policy
but considering what i
have been through today
my mother dying because of these terrorists
i want to know why you let some slamy
lawyer protect the dirty-bag like prado
we don't happy that
either,but we're gonna fix it
but it's gonna take some time
that's time we don't have
Edgar stop
i'm trying to cut you some slack here
but you need to get back to your job
you need to put all that
stuff aside and hold for awhile
yes,sir
yeah, Cannon
yes
i'll hold for the judge
what was that all about?you're
supposed to be doing the hourlies.
I know
i don't want anybody keeps telling
me what i'm supposed to be doing
i have a photographic
memory in case you forgot
How can i forgot,you tell me
like every other of the day
i don't know why what's happened here
we have some pc lawyer holding
us up from doing our job
your job is do the hourlies
you're holding yourself up
chole
Have you heard of the mising warhead.
yeah, FBI link up with our department yet?
yes.i'm sharing both of databases
OK. Good. who's questioning the prisoner
You mean Joseph Prado that Curtis broght in
yeah
no one
what are you talking about? the
attorney came in from antis globe
with a court order saying he won't
allow to being-alone with Prado
The attorney came in from
amnesty globe with a court
order saying we won't be
allowed to being-alone with Prado
Buchanan is on the phone with
judge sending the order now
I'll be right back.
I don't believe this
I disagree with you,you honor, this does
not fall outside the boundary of patriot
yeah,alright thanks
what the hell is going on here you got
the key witness on the missing warhead
We should be pressing this
guy with everything we've got
Judge's known more
If you want to appeal we should wait
until 7 A.M. take him to the pillar judge
does he know what the stakes are?
he does,but he's feeling Prado got no record
he shouldn't be treated like a terrorist
What about the fact that
he was caught meeting with
known terrorist in the
middle of the night on appear?
Circumstantial
we need to interrgoate this prisioner, I
don't care what kind of
court order we even get
I agree but the attorney is with him
U.S. Marshal's protecing his right.
Where's attorney?
In holding with Prado
Jack, don't make it worse.
I just want to talk to him.
How much longer do I have to stay here?
I'm trying to get you out as soon as I can.
My office is in the process
of filing a complaint.
They have nothing on me.
I was standing alone on my boat.
I don't even know the man'd going after.
Come in with me, Al.
Who are you?
My name is Jack Bauer, Department
of Defense, and you are?
David Weiss, amnesty global.
Curtis, why is the suspect
not in his restraints?
Amnesty global's order
supersedes our authority.
Mr. Bauer, my client is cooperating.
He's not trying to go anywhere.
All he wants is to be treated
like any other U.S. Citizen.
Your client aided and abetted people who
attacked the president of
the united states today.
You don't know that.
As a matter of fact, we do.
Then charge him.
May I speak with you privately?
Get the door.
You and I both know that
your client isn't clean and
that he conspired to steal
a U.S. Nuclear warhead.
All my client wants is due process.
Mr. Weiss
these people are not gonna
stop attacking us today
until millions and millions
of americans are dead.
Now, I don't want to
bypass the constitution,
but these are extraordinary circumstances.
The constitution was born out of
extraordinary circumstances, Mr. Bauer.
This plays out by the book, not
in a backroom with a rubber hose.
I hope you can live with that.
Sir, can I help you?
No, it's all right.
How did you get here so fast?
What?!
Who asked you to represent Mr. Prado?
I don't have to give you that information.
Curtis, from the time of his arrest, did
the suspect have time to call a lawyer?
No.
Marwan called amnesty global.
This is his play.
That means prado definitely knows
something Marwan doesn't want us to hear.
We still can't get around that court order.
We need to call the president now.
We cannot have any leaks
regarding this missing warhead.
I've contacted General Wilson in Iowa.
He's sealing off the roads while
we clean up the ambushed convoy.
What about those highway patrol
officers who discovered it?
Wilson's already brought them in
and is explaining the situation.
The good news is, this is happening
in the middle of the night.
Most of the country's still asleep.
yes.
CTU Los Angeles is on the
line for president Logan.
They say it's urgent.
Thank you, gentlemen.
That'll be all.
Walt.
Stay.
Put 'em through.
Go ahead, please.
Mr. President, this is Bill Buchanan.
I'm here with Jack Bauer.
Yes, bill.
What do you have for me?
Sir, in the process of trying
to track down this missing
warhead, we brought a prime
suspect in for questioning.
What have you learned?
Well, that's the problem, sir.
Right now, our hands are tied.
Amnesty global has interceded on his behalf.
Interceded on what grounds?
He's a U.S. Citizen with no previous record.
Why is he a suspect?
We found him with Yosik Khatami, the man
who's linked to today's terrorist events.
I don't understand.
It doesn't violate any
law to question a suspect.
Mr. President, if I may...?
Go ahead, Mike.
Jack, it's Mike Novick.
Hi, Mike.
Am I correct in assuming
that this suspect is unlikely
to respond to the kind of
q&a his lawyer would permit?
That's correct, mike.
If we want to procure
any information from this
suspect, we're gonna have
to do it behind closed doors.
You're talking about torturing this man?
I'm talking about doing what is necessary to
stop this warhead from
being used against us.
Give us a moment, Bill.
Mike, what do you think?
I think we need to do whatever
it takes to find Marwan.
Walt?
Weigh in.
Well, this makes me nervous.
Why?
Should this man be
innocent, as he claims he is,
your first act as president
is to sanction his torture.
Well, that'll...
that'll forever haunt your presidency.
All right, gentlemen.
Here's what I'll agree to.
I'll call a special session with members of
the justice department
and we'll discuss this.
I'll have an answer for you in 20 minutes.
Mr. President, this thing
could be over in 20 minutes.
That's as far as I'm
willing to go right now.
With all due respect, sir,
please let us do our jobs.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
I'll have curtis start
the interrogation of prado.
You and I both know we can't
afford to be wasting time like this.
You heard the president.
He's not going to let us touch this guy.
The president's
not here- you are.
If I authorize this,
they'll know in ten minutes.
We'll all be out the door.
What if I can find
another way to handle this
that wouldn't implicate anyone else but me?
I'm not going to authorize that, Jack.
You don't have to.
What do you mean?
Accept my resignation.
And if I do that, what then?
Release the suspect.
Release him?
We don't question him, don't
charge him, we just let him go.
He won't need a lawyer, or a marshal.
You're going to take him
on as a private citizen.
yes?
how far away are you?
92 miles.
When you get there, you'll meet with Morris.
Is he the one who's going
to configure the detonation?
Yes.
I've given him the codes.
Okay.
You have to follow the plan exactly, Sabir.
We cannot give the americans
time to start an evacuation.
Yes, Marwan. I understand.
No delays.
It'd be done.
Hey, when did you get back?
A few minutes ago.
Thanks.
Good.
I could use your help on the DOD interface.
I can't help you right now, Audrey. Sorry.
What are you doing?
I'll tell you when I get back.
Jack...
Jack!
Audrey, please.
What the hell are you trying to pull here?
First you want to torture me,
and now you're throwing me out?
That's right.
It's okay, Joe.
I'm sure they tried to fight the restraining
order, then realized they couldn'T.
No, that's not what this is.
They're doing something.
Don't be so paranoid.
We're just not interested in you anymore.
I want protection when I get out of here.
The marshal can escort back
wherever you want to go.
No, no, no!
You know what?
Change of plan!
I don't want to leave here until I
know I'm safe for the next few days.
If you don't leave,
I'm going to have to arrest you for
trespassing in a secured
government building.
Once that happens, not even
your attorney can protect you.
Correct me if I'm wrong, David.
He's right.
What's going on?
Where are they taking Prado?
He's been released.
Why?
I don't know.
It came from Buchanan.
Mr. Buchanan, why are you letting him go?
Edgar, not now, please.
But he's working with the
people that killed my mother.
Not now.
Cheer up, Joe, you're a free man.
Yeah, free.
The marshal's going to take you home.
No.
You kidding me? I can't go home.
I've got to go somewhere
public, like a hotel.
Fine.
Tell him where you want to go.
Don't let anyone know you're there.
Here's my card.
You call me if anyone from
CTU tries to bother you.
Yeah, okay.
You're going to be fine.
make a sound, and I will blow your
brains out, all over the windshield.
Handcuff your left arm
to the dashboard, now.
now we're going to talk.
now...
you and I both know
your heart isn't in this.
You just wanted the money.
I don't want you.
All I want is Marwan.
I don't know any Marwan.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, well, I'm running out of time here,
so why don't we just cut to the chase.
where's Marwan?
I don't know!
Where is Marwan?!
I swear I don't!
Okay, okay, okay, Marwan'S...
Marwan's going to be at a place
called the hub club tonight.
Where is it?
It's just...
it's just east...
where is it?!
It's just east of downtown!
Just east of downtown.
this'll help you with the pain
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
www.tvsubtitles.net