Put down the gun!
Put the gun down now!
Drop it, now! Step back!
I'll kill her!
I will kill her!
( yells )
Jack, when I was inside,
I recognized
one of the men.
Who?
I can't place him,
but I know that I saw him
before today.
Why did they think
you were
holding something back
from them?
I will not tell these people
things about my private life
that they don't need to know.
That you don't think
they need to know.
What are you doing here?
Your mother told Madwan
you took care
of the American girl?
Yeah?
Then you'll need help
getting rid of the body.
He's going to kill our son.
Yes.
You brought me here
to kill me!
I took care of the girl!
Madwan knows!
It's not Madwan
that wants you dead!
Who wants me dead?
Your father.
Thank you so much
for helping me out.
They said Maya's arrived?
She's in the exam area.
I'm about to do
her work-up.
ERIN:
She suffers from schizophrenia.
I want us to be together again.
I'm sorry, Paul.
I'm seeing someone.
Paul, this
is Jack Bauer.
Nice to meet you.
What was your courier
transporting?
MAN: A Dobson-type override.
What exactly does
this override do?
It's a combination
of hardware and software
that can remotely take control
of a nuclear power facility.
And the person in possession
of this program,
could they do the opposite
with it?
Create a disaster at a plant,
a meltdown?
Theoretically, yes.
ERIN: How many nuclear
power plants in this country
would be vulnerable?
All of them.
( phone rings )
Yes?
It's me.
They found out
about the override.
Jack, did you get
the surveillance footage from
Hyatt Security? No, they
heard each dinner that
you attended was monitored
by a private company-
Felsted Security- I just
got off the phone with them.
They've got the videotapes
on file, but unfortunately,
they're working
off a closed system.
I've got to go there,
pick up the tapes,
bring them back here
for you to I.D.
Where are you on
the guest list?
I'm having it sent here.
You know,
we're running out of time.
What do you mean?
Is it that urgent?
Yes. As it turns out, your
kidnapping was just a cover
for a much larger attack.
The terrorists used
the broadcast of the trial
to overload the Internet,
and diverted all of
our attention away from
what they were
really trying to do.
I need a full tactical
for my vehicle.
Which is what?
They're in possession of a
stolen device called an override.
With that,
they've gained control
of the 104 nuclear power
plants across this country.
The override device maintains
heat levels within the reactors.
Effectively,
they can meltdown
every one
of those plants.
Oh, God... my God.
Thank you.
The man you saw when you
were being held captive,
right now,
he's our only lead.
Then let me come
to Felsted Security with you
and make the I.D. there. It'll
be quicker. Audrey, I can't.
After what you've
been through today,
I'm not going
to put you at risk.
You just said our nation's
nuclear power plants
will melt down if we don't
find that override, Jack.
We can't afford to
waste any more time.
Come over here.
There are 104 nuclear power
stations in the United States.
We just learned
that terrorists
are trying to convert all 104
nuclear cores into weapons.
Give us the worst-case casualty
scenarios, Curtis.
This graphic represents
a single meltdown scenario.
Edgar, break it
down for us.
If we can't wrest control
of the override,
it will shut down
the entire cooling system
and the core will melt through
the containment building.
In the first
three hours,
the population within
a ten-mile radius
will receive the highest
doses of radiation.
Most people will die
within two days.
Now, the smallest
of these 104 cities
represents
75,000 people.
Multiply that by 104,
we're looking
at three million casualties,
and that's conservative.
The environmental impact
would also be
catastrophic.
30 miles in all directions
of each plant
will be uninhabitable
for at least five years.
Don't these plants
have multiple security systems
to prevent
this kind of breech?
They do, but the override
has already deactivated them.
ERIN:
And if we don't succeed,
how long before these cores
start to melt down?
I'm projecting the first
radiation shock waves
in approximately three hours.
All right, I want everyone here
from Com and Logistics
to work on getting a handle
on the software.
The rest of you will handle
support in conjunction
with NRC personnel.
Let's get to work.
JACK:
Erin, we're leaving now.
Where you going, Jack?
Audrey's given us a significant
lead. We need to follow it up.
What kind of lead?
When we were being held,
I recognized someone
- he was an American. I saw him at
a function here in L.A.
a couple months ago.
We're going to view the
surveillance tapes of the function
at a private security
company not far from here.
I don't want her
going out now.
Why can't you access
the tapes here?
JACK: Sir, I wish we
could, but they're off line.
They would have to record
over four and a half hours
of material for us to view.
We don't have that time.
Jack told me that these
people are trying to use
our nuclear power plants as
weapons. We have to follow
this lead, and we have
to follow it now.
JACK: Sir, Audrey's the only person
who can make this I.D.
If anything happens, Jack,
I will hold you personally
responsible.
I understand.
How far away
is this facility?
Not far. Burbank.
Audrey...
Paul.
I'll get the team set up.
We need to talk.
We'll have to do it
when I get back.
Get back from where?
We're following up
on something.
Paul, please- can we
just do this later?
How many on your team?
Four of us.
Set up a weapons package.
I'll meet you in the motor pool. Done.
( quietly ): ... cannot
see each other anymore.
Look, I don't know
about all of this,
but I know about
you and him,
I am not okay
with that.
Look, you and I
aren't together anymore.
I thought we were trying
to work things out.
Yeah, I tried, but you
kept putting it off.
So I gave up.
We haven't been together
for over nine months.
We're not trying to work out
anything anymore.
Mr. Raines,
I'm sorry to interrupt.
She is my wife.
Paul, please.
Excuse me.
She's my wife.
Don't you forget that.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Jack, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Hey, I just received
these files from DOD.
I need to give them
to Jack Bauer.
Oh, you can't.
Jack just left.
Oh, well, um, can I forward them
to him?
No, he went
with Audrey Raines
to Felsted Security
to look at some archive footage.
Okay... well, I guess I can just
hold on to them for him.
Yeah,
that'd be fine.
Paul.
Jim,
we need to talk.
Come in here.
Did you know about
Audrey and Jack Bauer?
Not till an hour ago.
Well, I've got to tell you,
they were carrying on
right under your nose.
It's pretty unprofessional,
wouldn't you say?
Look, I understand your feelings
about this,
but you and Audrey
have been separated
for almost a year.
Paul, I'm sorry,
but she's a big girl.
She can do what she wants.
Well, what she's
doing is she...
she's breaking my heart.
Maryanne...
Sarah.
What do you need back here?
Um... Edgar asked me to do
a manual reboot of Hub Five.
Oh, I can do that
for him.
No, no, it's fine.
Okay.
( phone ringing )
MAN:
Yes?
Bauer and Audrey Raines left
here about five minutes ago.
Where'd they go?
Felsted Security.
357 White Oak Boulevard.
It's in Burbank.
All right, good.
You're going to need to set
things up on your end.
What are you talking about?
I should be done here.
No. When Jack Bauer and
Audrey Raines are killed,
CTU is going to know that someone
inside leaked the location.
( sighs )
All right. What do I do?
Divert suspicion.
Fine.
I'm standing live in an area
just outside of the perimeter.
Unfortunately, the Pentagon
is not commenting at this time.
But what we do know
is that at 12:10 p. m.,
Secretary Heller
and his daughter, Audrey Raines,
were successfully rescued.
The number of fatalities
is unknown,
but sources say
there might have been
as many as 20 terrorists
inside the building at the time,
and it appears there
are no survivors among them.
It is also unclear as to...
Yes?
It looks like all the critical
instructions went with him,
before the assault.
Yes.
The override has taken control
of the nuclear power plants.
What about Behrooz?
What about our son?
We have to be strong now.
We'll mourn him
when this is over.
REPORTER: ... and as you might imagine,
among the most difficult of days
for Secretary Heller
and his daughter.
The Secret Service
was previously
swarming over this area
to secure it,
but have since taken
the Secretary
to an undisclosed location
for his safety.
( phone rings )
We hope to have
more information,
as officials are preparing
to make a public statement.
Hello?
Mom?
Behrooz?
Are you all right?
Tariq tried to kill me.
He was going to shoot me.
I had to defend myself.
What did you do?
I killed him.
You can't let Father know.
Why not?
Because Father is the one
who told Tariq to do it.
He wants me dead because
I messed up with Debbie.
Behrooz, that's not possible.
Your father would never want
to hurt you.
It's true.
Mom, I don't know what to do.
You have to help me.
Where are you now?
I'm near the Metrolink station
on Lassen in Chatsworth.
Are you using Tariq's car?
Yes.
Hide it. I'll pick you up there
in a half hour.
Hurry.
Who was on the phone?
It was nothing important.
Liar.
What did Behrooz do?
No, what did you do?
Did you give the order?
Behrooz was not committed.
It was just
a matter of time
before he turned
against us.
You ordered Tariq to kill him.
To kill our own son.
No, no, no, you...
Where is Tariq?
Behrooz killed him.
That's impossible.
Because you think he's weak?
He's not.
Nothing... nothing
will stand in the way
of what needs to be done.
Not him,
not you.
Where is he now?
Why?
What are you going to do?
You're hurting me.
I will do more than that.
Now you listen to me, woman.
You will do exactly
as you told him.
You will pick him up
in a half an hour.
What did you say to Paul?
That I'm filing for divorce
as soon as I get back to D.C.
Are you sure
that's what you want?
Yes.
Okay.
Yes!
Do you have something?
It looks like the Dobson
override device
hasn't completely taken control
of all the reactors.
I'm starting to get some
response. What could I do?
Nothing. Just stay off Hub Five.
I need it.
I thought Hub Five
was out for a reboot.
No.
Curtis! Come here!
Could I talk to you
for a minute?
Actually, I'm kind of busy.
You lied to me about
doing a reboot for Edgar.
Yes, I did.
Why?
Sarah, I had
a personal call to make,
and I knew it would be
inappropriate
at the time of the crisis.
I didn't want anyone to know.
Then why'd you do it in here?
Why didn't you just go outside?
I was trying to make it look
like I was working, okay?
Look, I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
( cell phone rings )
It's Madwan.
( cell phone ringing )
Yes.
Has Tariq taken care
of your son?
I haven't spoken to Tariq yet,
but I'm sure
if there was a problem,
he would've called me.
The fact that I'm even talking
to you about this is a problem.
The next two hours are crucial.
I can't be distracted by this.
I understand.
I promise,
I will personally
oversee the situation
and make sure
it is resolved.
Fix this, Navi.
Of course.
What is Madwan going to say
if he finds out Behrooz
killed Tariq?
Tariq is expendable,
like we all are.
Madwan understands that.
All he cares about
is that Behrooz is silenced.
I will not be able to look
at you after today
without thinking about
what we did to him.
I think I got it.
What?
The Dobson override.
I think I've got
a piece of the code.
What does that mean?
If this is really it,
I can turn off the override,
and stop the remaining plants
from melting down.
What do you need?
To get into the software kernel,
but the NRC
will never let me.
It's too dangerous. Why?
If I tinker in there
and screw up,
I can start a chain reaction.
All right, Edgar.
I'm going to need you
to present this to Heller.
He can order NRC
to let you in.
Present to Heller?
Yeah, he's in
the situation room.
I shouldn't do this, Curtis.
Why not?
I could faint.
I feel very nauseous.
I have low blood sugar.
It's just Driscoll
and Heller.
Driscoll's in there, too?
Excuse me,
Mr. Secretary.
I'm going to have
to interrupt you.
What is it? This is Edgar
Stiles, our chief analyst.
He's requesting access
to the kernels
of the power plants.
My understanding is that
no one is to manipulate
those kernels
while the plants are on line.
Yes, but there is a way to do it
if you're careful.
I'd have to stay away from
the pre-compiled headers,
while I was putting
the software lock
on the Dobson override code.
But the chances of causing
a load imbalance...
I don't understand one
thing you're talking about.
Just tell me
what the downside is
if the kernels
are disrupted
because of your
manipulation.
( sighs )
If I make a mistake,
I can accelerate
a core meltdown
in some of the reactors.
This is probably a bad idea.
Maybe we shouldn't do it.
But if you're
successful,
you can regain control
of the reactors?
Yes.
Edgar, what we need to know
is can you do this
without making a mistake?
Yeah, I can do it.
You're not filling me
with confidence, Edgar.
Look...
I'm just a little nervous.
But if I say I can do it,
I can do it.
He'll run away
the moment he sees you.
He won't see me.
You'll be the only one
in the car
when you pick him up.
( cell phone rings )
It's Behrooz.
Answer it.
( cell phone ringing )
Hello?
Are you almost here?
Yes.
What did you tell Dad?
I didn't; I just left.
He was busy working.
What are we going to do?
Wherever we go, he'll find us.
No, he won't.
I know a safe place.
I didn't understand, until
today, what it would feel like.
Doing these things-
they're wrong, Mom.
And I see it now.
Don't think about that anymore.
You'll be safe now.
But I am thinking about it.
Maybe I should go to the police
and tell them everything I know.
We'll talk about it
when I get there.
Okay.
You did well.
Who are they?
Don't worry about it.
Just make sure you take the
second exit at Angeles Crest.
He's going to ask me
why I'm stopping.
Let him ask.
What do I tell him?
Don't tell him anything.
We'll meet you there.
Erin? We're making
good progress.
Tell me. We've been able to take
87 power plants off line,
they're safe.
What about the other 17? The
terrorists were able to use the override
to block a shutdown.
Everything we're trying
is being repelled.
What are we doing
to get around it?
Believe me, Erin,
we're trying everything.
If there's a way,
we'll find it.
I'll keep you posted.
( sobbing )
Sweetheart?
Mom.
How are you feeling?
Not good.
I don't like these doctors.
I want Dr. Runwith.
You can't see him today.
Why not?
Because I can't leave here.
And I want you close by.
Then stay here with me.
I'll be back in a few minutes,
I promise.
But you have to do
something for me, okay?
I want you
to do something.
Look at me.
Maya, look at me.
You need to cooperate
with the doctors.
Okay?
Okay.
Come on.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Take these, please.
Your son was in
sensory deprivation
for a total of two
and a half hours.
What did he say when
you took him off it?
Nothing.
You tortured my son
for almost three hours
and ended up yielding nothing?
You gave the order, sir.
Give us a moment, please.
I'm sorry this had
to happen, Richard,
but we had to make sure
that you weren't withholding
anything from us.
I hate you.
I never want to see you again.
Please understand
that I am responsible
for the lives
of millions of people.
You torture me and now
you want me to forgive you?
This just confirms everything
I always knew about you.
Am I free to leave?
Yes.
( phone rings )
Yeah, Paul.
Audrey, do you have a minute?
Sure, what's going on?
I just talked to your dad,
and he said something to me
that I've been
thinking about it a lot.
He said that you're a big girl,
and I think I've been treating
you like a child.
I don't think that, Paul.
Well, whether it comes off
that way or not,
I need to respect your choices,
respect who you are
and... ( sighs )
I've been so stupid
about all of this.
I've lost sight of the
things I love about you.
Look, uh...
I hear what you're
saying, but I don't...
I don't really know
how to respond to that.
Well, you don't have to.
I just want you to know that
I've been wrong about
a lot of things
and before you make
any big decisions,
decisions that you're entitled
to make,
let some time go by.
Is that fair?
Is that fair of me to ask?
Yeah. Yeah,
that's fair.
Okay, well, I'll, uh...
I'll see you later.
Yeah. See you later.
How far out are we?
A few miles
away, sir.
Okay.
Where are we going to go?
Out of the city.
Why did Father
want to kill me?
I'm his son.
Stop, Behrooz, you can't
think about that now.
Get in.
Mom, we killed
two people today.
I can't do this.
I'm freaking out.
Shh.
Get on the train.
What?
Your father's
following us.
What?!
It was the only way
I could save you.
Now, damn it,
Behrooz, get out, go.
Go!
Obey me!
Oh, God!
Mom!
Go!
( screaming )
( groaning )
Watch out!
( tires squealing )
Is it taken care of?
No, there's a problem.
My wife and Behrooz
have betrayed us.
Where are they now?
I don't know.
But Dina's been wounded.
She'll have to get
medical attention.
So you've come to me asking me
for help with this mess?
I can't do it alone, Madwan.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Allow me to make this right.
What would you need?
To monitor
local hospitals.
I'll also need drivers,
as well as access
to police frequencies.
You think she'll go
to the police?
No, no.
But they may pick her up
if they find out
she's been shot.
I told you...
I can't be distracted
by this right now.
Give him what he needs.
Make sure the woman and child
are captured
before they can
do us harm.
Thank you.
Thank you, Madwan.
No matter what happens today,
you will answer for this.
I understand.
No, we just got here.
How long is it going to take you
to create the database?
Okay.
Okay, Marcie, thanks.
Our office just got
a copy of the guest list
from the dinner where
you saw this guy.
Once you make an I.D. on the
surveillance tape, we'll be able
to send it through a database,
and we'll find out who it is.
Okay.
I'm carrying.
( phone ringing )
Yeah.
Jack, this is Maryanne Taylor
at CTU.
What is it, Maryanne?
Curtis wanted me to tell you
that as soon as Audrey
recognizes somebody
from the surveillance video,
he wants it sent directly
to my system.
I'm on 60 Casper.
Why didn't he
tell me himself?
They're still trying
to shut down
all the remaining power plants,
and everybody else is still
working on that.
Are they going to be able
to control them in time?
I don't know.
Okay, keep me informed.
What is it?
We don't have
a lot of time.
She seems to be doing
better now. She's sleeping.
Oh, that's
very good news.
Did you give her Haldol?
Mm-hmm. Why?
She's allergic to it.
It's in her file!
The date on this is gone.
This is the wrong file.
Maya! Maya!
Maya? She's unconscious!
Mary, we have a code!
I need 25 cc's
of norepinephrine.
How could you have
gotten the wrong file?
I need that syringe now.
Ms. Driscoll,
Secretary Hel...
What is it, Sarah?
Sarah!
Secretary Heller needs you.
For what? He's going online
with the President
in a few minutes
and he wants to know
about our progress
on the reactors.
Um, tell him that
they're still trying to get
control of the system kernel
and that we'll know more
in 15 minutes.
If we do stop
the meltdown,
he wants to know
if there's going to be
any system contamination.
Uh, no, there won't
be any contamination.
It'll take 36 hours
to reboot the reactors.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
All right, go.
We had security cameras running
on only two areas of the event.
One was covering
the main ballroom
and one was
at the entrance.
Okay, put them both up.
The ballroom angle is too wide.
Let's just go
with the entrance.
What time is that?
6:39.
No, that's too early.
I met him when
I arrived,
around 9:00, 9:15.
( keys clicking )
Wait, stop.
Can you back this up
a few frames?
Sure.
Wait, wait, wait.
Stop there.
I think that's him.
Can you enhance him right here? Yeah.
That image
won't process.
We need to make it clearer.
Okay, let me see
if I can get that for you.
Who's supposed
to be at that desk?
Oh, that's Mitchell.
Probably went out
for another smoke.
JACK:
The back gate's wide open.
No one's there.
Greg, do you copy?
Greg?
Rick?
How many ways into this
area of the building?
Two.
Put them up. Rick!
Get down. Get down!
( gunshots )
Are you okay?
Yeah!( tech grunts )
Damn it!
I'm going to look for help,
okay? But first I need to know
about the surveillance tape
Where's the source?
The main...
ser... server...
How do I access it?
Put it on the...
the... flash memory.
Okay.
Watch the security monitors.
Do you have sticks?
( gasping )
Gary, do you have sticks?
In my... in my... pocket.
Okay.
Stay with me.
He's gone.
Jack, they're coming.
JACK:
They're trying to seal us off.
Shouldn't we call CTU?
No, CTU's got to be compromised.
That's the only way
they'd know we were here.
We've got to get out of here.
Move. Go, go!
Go.
Go, go.
There's one in the pipe.
The safety's off.
Jack...
You can do this.
We'll cover each other.
I thought you said
CTU's been compromised.
It has been.
Then who are you calling?
The only person I can trust right now.
If there are 17 nuclear power
plants about to melt down,
I need to update
an evacuation strategy.
I agree, sir.
I've already laid
the groundwork
with the National Guard.
They're preparing to go into
individual communities
and effect a civil defense
evacuation upon your command.
You say our worst-case scenario
gives us
approximately three hours.
That's correct, sir.
Erin, what are our chances of
shutting down the remaining 17?
At this time, I would say
it's less than 50%,
but we're trying something now
that might improve
those chances.
When will you know more?
In the next 15 minutes.
Keep me updated.
Yes, Mr. President.
Let's find out
from Jack and Audrey
if they've come up
with anything on their end. Yes, sir.
Mr. Secretary, I can have a room
prepared for you to rest, if you like.
You've been under a great deal
of strain these past few hours.
No, I don't think I can rest,
but thanks, anyway.
Erin?
Yes, sir?
I understand your daughter
is down in the clinic.
Yes, but it won't interfere
with my work.
I'm sure it won't.
I was just wondering
if everything was okay.
It's something we've lived with
since she was six years old.
There are good days
and bad days.
Today's a bad one.
I'm sorry.
( whispering ):
We're heading right.
Come on.
Come here.
Okay, we're going
to get through this.
You've got to listen to me.
I need to get that
guy's weapon. Mm-hmm.
I need you
to provide cover.
Save your ammunition.
Space out your shots.
You ready?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Damn it.
Audrey, get down!
I'm out!
Go!
I'm empty.
What?
I'm empty!
( gunshots )
Jack!
Tony!
You okay?
Yeah! We're all right!
Move! Move!
Edgar's just started
the final sequence.
Is he in the kernel yet?
Yes. This is where he
can't make a mistake.
If he does, he'll
accelerate the meltdowns
instead of
stopping them.
Sarah, look up
the out codes
for Load "A" registered condition.
"FF-09."
No, that's a jump "A",
I need a load "A."
Damn it, move.
That's it, "AB-A1."
I think I got it.
What do you mean, you
think? I'd like to go
through it again
before I send it, please.
How long will that take?
Ten minutes. We don't have
time. You have to do it now.
Let me just check the headers.
Now, Edgar.
( typing )
I did the best I could,
sir. I hope it works.
So do I.
There's no response.
( quietly ):
Come on.
There they go.
Congratulations, Edgar.
Oh, no, don't tell me that.
ERIN:
Edgar, what's going on?
Why are some of the reactors
still not shutting down?
Edgar?
Edgar, talk to me.
Six of the reactors are immune
to the kill sequence.
The Dobson override's already
taken over their system.
Those six are going
to melt down?
The shutdown codes have been
completely corrupted.
Contact Bauer.
Either he finds
the people responsible
for planning
the override,
or we're looking
at a nuclear holocaust.
Subtitles by Jaxdahl
www.tvsubtitles.net