I'm the Secretary of Defense
of the United States of America!
You will listen to me!
Put down your weapon.
If another one of my men dies,
your daughter will be killed.
We need to get out of here.
What?
You're in danger.
From who?
Don't ask questions,
just come with me.
Please, help me!
( choking )
Debbie, what's wrong?
( coughing )
What did you do to her?
( phone rings )
O'Brian.
The satellite up yet?
No, I have to reposition
without Driscoll noticing.
Where are you?
I'm at a Mercury Martin
in Solmas.
I had to stage a robbery
to keep the hostile in place.
Tell those officers to put
their guns down and stand back!
Edgar, I need you to help me.
Help you with what?
I've been in contact
with Jack Bauer.
What?
That's right.
Now you're involved,
so you're either
going to help me,
or you're going
to turn me in.
You're asking me to do something
that can get me fired.
I know you were working
with her
behind Driscoll's back.
What do you want?
I want to make sure
I have your attention
whenever I need it.
Chloe, why are you
logged on
to an active DOD satellite?
All right,
you're done here.
I was going
to quit anyway.
I want you
to call Jack Bauer now.
Driscoll wants
to talk to you.
Stand down, Jack. It's over.
Erin, right now Hasan is free.
He's looking for a car
and a phone.
Once he has those things,
he's going to lead us straight
to Secretary Heller, I promise.
Son of a bitch.
Get out of the car!
Do we still have
a SAT visual on Kalil Hasan?
He's west of the 14 on Route 11.
Average speed,
62 miles per hour.
All right, I want
traffic workups,
roadwork schedules.
We can't let anything
delay or prevent him
from reaching his destination.
We need the tactical teams
to launch now.
Keep them at Jack's location.
I'm coordinating
with Division.
Do you want me
to pre-emp that?
Yes, at one point.
All right.
Curtis, I can pull up
those tactical teams
for you if you want.
No, you can't.
That requires
a level-three channel.
You don't have that
kind of clearance.
Miss Driscoll?
I have a Sergeant Paulson
from the Sheriff's Department
on line one.
He says it's important.
Sergeant Paulson,
this is Erin Driscoll
at CTU.
How can I help you?
Yeah, I have a man named
Jack Bauer in custody,
He claims he works
with you. Is that true?
Yes, it is.
He just robbed a convenience
store near Route 11
and claims it was part
of some undercover
operation to delay a suspect
until satellite coverage
could be established.
That's also true, Sergeant.
Well, it might be nice
if you communicated
with us a little better.
Well, there were some national
security issues involved,
and I'm so sorry
for any inconvenience.
May I please speak to Mr. Bauer?
All right.
Uncuff him.
Thank you.
Tell me that you
didn't arrest Hasan.
No, he's still
in the vehicle
and we're still
tracking him by satellite.
We intercepted
a phone call
that indicated he's headed
for the site
where Secretary Heller's
being held.
You're going
to need someone
coordinating things
on the ground.
That should be me.
Erin, listen to me.
We can get Heller
and Audrey out of there,
but we need
to work together
and we need
to start that now.
We have to find Heller
before this trial starts.
It's the right move, Erin.
He's our only option.
All right, you're in,
but you coordinate
through me.
And, Jack,
make this work.
I will.
Please advise Sergeant Paulson
of the new chain of command.
Yeah?
In my capacity
as Director of CTU,
I'm vesting Jack Bauer
with the authority to command
and control this part
of the ground operation.
Consider him in charge.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Sounds like you're
the new boss.
Tell me what you need.
The vehicle the hostile
was driving was stolen.
I need to make sure
there's no APB on it.
If there is one,
I need you to get CHP
to cancel it.
I also left
my CTU vehicle
over at the convenience mart.
I'll have it brought
right over.
Thank you.
Why don't you go
get that car?
Hasan's making
another phone call.
Bring it up, patch it
through to Jack.
( phone rings )
Bauer.
Jack, it's Edgar Stiles.
Hasan's making
another phone call.
I'm patching it to you.
Okay.
Yes?
It's Kalil. I'm on my way.
How much longer?
About a half an hour.
The broadcast
must begin on time.
Any problems?
Nothing I couldn't handle.
How are you coming
with the servers?
Dumar and Farez
are managing,
but I'm sure
they could use your help.
I'll be there soon.
All right.
Did Heller sign the confession?
Yes.
He didn't want to,
but we used his daughter.
Did you kill her?
Not yet.
Sergeant Paulson?
What's the E.T.A.
on my vehicle?
Any second, Agent Bauer.
I'll see you soon.
I want to hear it again.
Play it back.
Okay, Jack, one second.
Let me play it back.
Tell your men
to stay on channel three.
Got it.
Any problems?
HASAN:
Nothing I couldn't handle.
How are you coming
with the servers?
Dad?
You did what anyone else
would have done
in your position.
I embarrassed my country.
You signed
a piece of paper;
all lies.
Everyone will know that you
signed it under duress.
It's more than a piece of paper.
This trial is going
to be a spectacle,
broadcast all over the world,
designed to humiliate
and degrade this country.
Dad...
there's still time.
There's no sense
in deluding ourselves.
There's less than an hour.
If we're going
to do anything,
we have to do it now.
We've done everything
that we can.
Not quite.
What do you mean?
What if I'm not alive?
They can't put me on trial.
If I'm dead, their goals
go right out the window.
And they'll be viewed as nothing
more than common assassins.
Dad...
Listen to me.
Even if I say
what they want me to say,
they're not going to let me go.
They're going to put me in front
of a camera, humiliate me,
and then they're
going to kill me
with the whole world watching.
There are people
on the outside looking for us.
You cannot give up.
I have to do something
while I still can.
And I need you
to help me.
Help you?
The chain between
your handcuffs,
see if you can get it
up and around my neck.
No, no.
I can't do it myself!
I don't have
any leverage.
No.
But you can pull
from back there!
Dad...
I'm counting on you
to help me!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
At least try it!
( sobbing ):
I won't do it.
I won't do it, Dad.
I'm sorry.
There's a gas pipe.
If we could break it...
No.
Break that, you die, too.
Do you think
that they are going
to let me out
of here alive?
Do you?
They're going
to kill me, too.
Dad...
Together we can do this.
We can do it,
okay?
Please.
Let's try it.
We're almost there.
Okay, that's good.
You ready?
Yeah.
( grunts )
( loud grunt )
( gas hissing )
I love you.
I love you, too, honey.
I want a full analysis
on both these voices.
Okay. I'll have it
done in ten minutes.
Thank you.
Edgar.
What, Maryanne?
What's a level-
three channel?
It's a logon that gets you
into all the systems,
tactical, district and division.
I want it.
What do you mean?
I want clearance
for a level-three channel.
I can't give it to you.
Only Driscoll
can authorize that.
I don't care who authorizes it.
I want it.
Look, just because
you overheard that conversation
between Chloe and me, it
doesn't mean I'm your bitch.
( telephone rings )
I'm done being scared of you.
( phone rings )
Miss Driscoll,
it's Maryanne.
Yes, Maryanne, what is it?
I've some further information
for you
regarding Chloe's
circumventing your authority.
I'm listening.
I don't think
she was acting alone.
Who was she working with?
I'm not sure, but I found an
electronic echo in her call log,
and every time
she spoke to Jack,
there was someone else
on the line, too.
That's an automated
behavior on our system.
Doesn't mean anyone
else was on the line.
Is that the extent
of your suspicion?
Yes, I'm, uh, I'm sorry
to have bothered you.
You're sick.
You're going to go
to Driscoll and you're
going to tell her you're
overloaded and you need help,
and you're going to ask her
to issue me a level-three
channel clearance.
Unit Three,
this is Bauer, do you copy?
Copy.
Back off another 200 yards.
We can't afford
to be spotted here.
Roger that.
( phone ringing )
Yeah?
The marines have assembled
and are leaving base.
Okay, have Chloe
collate the satellite images.
Make sure they stay in sync.
Chloe's in a holding room, Jack.
She's been suspended.
We could use her help here.
Things are
under control.
I'll have Curtis
collate the images.
Erin, Chloe was just
doing what I asked her to.
The point is, she was supposed
to be working for me.
I understand
that, but...
Jack, it's one thing for you
to disobey me in the field,
but for someone who works
for me here at CTU to betray me?
I can't reactivate her.
It's a non-starter.
Anything else?
No, nothing else.
We have a situation here.
I realize that.
I can do the math
as well as anyone.
The math?
Protocols were violated.
Someone has to take the bullet.
Jack's indispensable
right now and I'm not.
It took a lot of guts
for you to do what you did.
I trusted Jack.
A lot of people
around here trust Jack.
Doesn't mean they're going
to risk their careers for him.
I have a suggestion.
I'm going to leave
this room, call Admin.
They'll fax over
some resignation papers,
and you sign them.
And then what?
And then nothing.
I walk out?
You walk out.
No jail, no sanctions?
That's right.
Although, if you need
a letter of recommendation
for your next job,
you probably should
get it from Jack, not me.
Right.
Sound like a plan?
Yes.
For God's sake,
pull yourself together.
She didn't
know anything.
You didn't
have to kill her.
Yes, I did,
because you didn't have the
courage to kill her yourself.
Courage?
To poison a girl
who did no harm to you at all?
( car door slams )
Your father's home.
What are you doing?
She's already dead.
If your father doesn't
see a bullet wound,
he'll ask questions.
Do you want him to
know that you tried
to help your girlfriend escape?
Do you want him to know
that you failed him again?
Move away.
( gunshot )
Take it.
Behrooz,
take it.
Take it.
This has to stop, Behrooz.
You are my son
and I love you,
but I cannot let you
destroy everything,
everything we worked
so hard to achieve.
( doorknob rattling )
I know this was
difficult for you,
but it was necessary.
He'll dispose of the body
tonight after dark.
Meanwhile, move her car.
Park it somewhere
where it won't be seen.
Then come straight back here.
Navi?
( cell phone ringing )
What?
You got your level-three
channel clearance?
Yes, I did.
So we're done, right?
I mean, I don't
think I should have
to keep doing things for you.
What's this about anyway?
Why do you need a
level-three clearance?
Look, you may be happy
tapping away at a keyboard
for the rest
of your life, but I'm not.
I have an opportunity
here to get ahead,
and I intend to use it.
That's mine.
I'll be right back.
I'm more insulted that you
thought I wouldn't notice,
than by the fact
that you were spying on me.
Driscoll ordered me to do it.
Next time, do it right.
Use a Newman filter,
so the subject
doesn't see red lights
flashing everywhere.
Amateur.
Bye, Edgar.
Could you cover for me
for just a second?
Chloe.
Can you guys give
me a moment please?
I'm really
sorry this happened.
Don't worry, Edgar.
I didn't use names.
Driscoll doesn't know
you were helping me.
She doesn't?
I'm the one who
got you into this.
I'm not going to sell you out.
Thank you.
You're a geek, Edgar,
but you're a good guy.
Stay that way.
I don't really have a choice.
I guess not.
Good luck today.
You're gonna need it.
Sarah, assuming
he continues driving west,
what are our potential
target areas?
Well, within the time
frame he mentioned,
Hasan will reach
one of four
residential communities
and two industrial areas.
Data-mine those areas.
See if you can find
any suspicious activity
in the last six months.
Citizen complaints, known
associates, everything.
On it.
Jack, the hostile's stopping
at an intersection.
Okay, I got him.
( tires squeal )
( honks horn )
Yo, Mohammed.
That's your name, right?
Ain't that what they
call all you people?
I'm just trying
to get home.
It'd be nice
if all of ya'll went home.
Erin, three men have approached
Hasan's vehicle.
Edgar, can you enhance this? Hang on.
Look, I don't want
any trouble.
Too late, Mohammed!
( siren wails )
That's him.
Let's go, man.
Let's go.
You three, stay right there.
JACK: Damn it, the police
have got to stay clear of this.
I ordered a cancellation
of the APB on the truck.
Make sure that that happened.
It did.
It may not
have gotten out yet
to all the local
CHP branches.
If they detain Hasan,
this thing is over.
He'll never lead us
back to Heller.
Put me through to CHP.
Sarah.
This is CTU.
I have a priority call
for local dispatch.
You want to move
this vehicle, please?
Step out of the truck,
please, sir?
What's going on here?
Just working
some things out
between him and I,
that's all.
Is that right?
Yes, sir.
You three, stand
by your car and wait.
Come on.
We're going to lose him!
Get me CHP now!
Want to tell me
what's going on?
There's really no problem,
officer.
They're just upset
about what happened
this morning.
I'm sorry about that, sir.
Can I go now?
Just bear with me
one minute.
Why don't you go ahead
and call this in?
Copy that.
Jack, I have
local CHP dispatch.
Patch them through.
CHP. This is Officer Dudley.
Officer, I canceled an APB
on a yellow pickup truck,
license plate number 4-
Los Angeles-Independent-945,
Did you get that?
Yeah, I see it on the system.
I haven't gotten word of the
cancellation here, though.
One of your officers
is questioning the driver
of that vehicle.
It is imperative
that that driver not be detained
any longer.
We'll get you on your
way as soon as possible.
Don't let those guys
get to you.
They're just talks.
I think everybody's
been a bit jumpy today
with everything going on.
I appreciate your patience
and cooperation.
( radio squelches )
6214, copy.
Roger that.
We're all clear.
Have a nice day, sir.
Thank you, sir.
ERIN:
We're in the clear.
He's moving.
He's making another call.
Pipe it through to Jack.
Kalil's making another call,
Jack.
( phone rings )
Finish the setup
and let's do a test.
Yes?
We may have a problem.
I'm listening.
The police just ran the plates
of the vehicle I'm driving.
And?
They let me go.
Jack, are you getting this?
Yeah.
OMAR:
So what is the problem?
This is a stolen car.
Maybe the owner
hasn't reported it yet?
Or maybe
I'm getting help
from people who want
to make sure
I get where I'm going.
Do not jump
to conclusions.
A police officer was approaching
me, his hand on his gun.
Then he got a call,
suddenly there's no problem.
( sighs )
We can't take any chances.
I'm moving in.
He's not going
to lead us to the site.
The best we can do
right now
is try to take him
alive and break him.
All units, move in.
I repeat, move in.
Okay, I've got a visual.
Set up a roadblock
at mile marker 15.
It has been an honor
working with you, Omar.
The honor
has been mine, Kalil.
Come on.
Allah Akbar.
( horn blaring )
No!
Oh, God.
He just drove head-on
into another vehicle.
He was our only lead.
We're going to switch gears
since we've lost our only lead.
Kalil Hasan committed suicide
en route to Heller's location.
Have they recovered
anything on him
that might help identify
where Heller is?
It's too soon to tell.
They're still putting out
the fire from the crash.
How much time
do we have
before this trial begins
to broadcast?
Some time in the next,
ten, 15 minutes.
( phone rings )
Sarah Gavin.
It's Jack.
Put him on speaker.
GAVIN: Go ahead, Jack,
you're on speaker.
I'm sifting
through the wreckage now,
but there's not much intact.
Hasan said he was 30 minutes
from his destination.
It's 20 minutes
before he stopped.
Do we have
a maximum perimeter?
Edgar?
We're looking at a radius of
60 miles centered at Acton.
We're dispatching choppers
and fixed-wing crafts
to survey the area.
No, that's going
to take too long.
Use the satellites.
Conduct a thermal scan.
It won't work.
Why not?
That area has
a high concentration
of electric power transmitters.
The satellite won't
be able to distinguish
between them and the servers.
Those transmitters
have been in place for years.
If we take a scan,
we can lay it against
the previous grid pattern.
That way we can identify
any new thermal activity.
We can start the scan
immediately.
Do it.
Jack?
We're using a satellite
to check the thermals.
Keep the line open.
Hurry.
Miss Driscoll?
The clinic wanted me
to tell you that
your daughter has arrived.
Thank you.
All right, everyone reset
your systems.
Let's get back on track.
I have to take care
of something
for a few minutes.
Would you check in
with Division?
They're expecting
an update.
Everything okay?
Yeah, just a little problem
with my daughter, Maya.
I had to bring her
down to the clinic.
Is she okay?
She's fine.
Call Division.
What are you
working on?
Personnel allocation tables
and tactical generals
for the assault teams.
I notice every time I look over,
you're talking to Edgar.
What's that all about?
I'm just trying
to learn the ropes, Curtis.
Today is not the day
to make career moves
on people, Maryanne.
The only thing you
should be thinking about
is how to help us stop Heller
from being publicly executed.
Come on, Curtis.
Give me some credit.
Save it.
I know how you think.
Just leave everybody alone
and help us get through today.
Mark?
Hmm?
Thank you so much
for helping me out.
They said Maya's arrived?
She's in the exam area.
We're about
to do a workup.
She's been
on Thorazine.
She stopped taking it.
How long ago?
Based on what
happened this morning,
at least a few days.
What happened?
She's fixated on one
of my neighbor's kids.
What does she do?
She walks
into the yard,
gets verbally abusive.
I'll take good care of her.
Thank you.
Sure.
Maya?
Mom, I'm so happy
to see you.
I was going crazy
at home.
What happened
with Evan?
Why did you go
over there?
I know you
said not to,
but he was throwing things
against the fence.
Maya,
he plays with a ball.
He's seven years old,
sweetheart.
I don't care
how old he is.
He should know better.
Are you going to talk
to his dad about this?
Come here.
Look at me.
Mm-hmm.
You're not thinking
clearly, honey.
You've got to put it
out of your mind.
Dr. Calis is going
to help and you're going
to feel better
very soon.
Why don't we go home
right now?
We can't, honey.
Why not?
There's a little trouble
here in L.A.
and I have
to take care of it.
Are you going
to be okay?
Yes, I'm going
to be okay.
And you're going
I love you so much.
I love you,
too, honey.
Shh...
Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Yes?
OMAR:
Kalil is dead.
Dead? How?
He was being followed here.
He martyred himself
without hesitation.
What about the servers?
Have they been
re-conformed
for the broadcast?
Dumar is doing his best.
I think we'll
be all right.
If you need help,
I can come.
No, no, no.
It is too risky.
If the servers don't work
correctly,
we're in trouble.
This trial
is only the beginning.
I know that as well as you,
my friend.
But there's no need
to worry.
Everything will go
as planned.
You checked out
the package?
It's fine.
I was afraid it might
be damaged
in the train crash.
The case is very strong.
There's no problem.
Good.
Then you can
get started.
Gas.
I smell gas.
Heller.
( gas hissing )
Come on!
Get them out!
Come on, get them out! Come on, hurry!
Come on.
Hurry, open the door!
Come on!
Do whatever it
takes to revive him!
( coughing )
I know him.
She recognized me.
She has to be killed.
She will,
in good time.
Go do your job.
Go.
Yeah?
DRISCOLL:
We got the results
from the thermal scan.
One site matches the criteria.
Where?
An old industrial park
around three miles from you.
Give me the exact address.
It's off a service road
south of Brach.
Okay, I'll set up
the staging area.
Where is the marine strike
force? 20 minutes away.
This trial starts
any minute, Jack.
I know. I'll get back to you
soon as I'm on site.
Meanwhile, have someone download
the schematics to the building.
Send them over to my screen.
Edgar's on it.
( knocking )
We'll take the rest
of these up later.
Yes, Mr. President.
What is it, Robert?
CTU thinks it's identified the
location where the terrorists
are holding Secretary Heller
and his daughter.
Where?
A compound
in the Santa Clarita Valley.
But there is a problem.
The team's dispatched
to the site
may not get there in time
to prevent the broadcast,
and even if they do,
there is a good chance the
Secretary will be killed
in any rescue attempt.
Well, we have no choice
but to hope and pray
that you're wrong.
We do have a choice.
The Secretary's death
would be tragic.
But his execution
on American soil,
broadcast to the world,
would be far worse.
It would be a complete and utter
humiliation for the country.
Perhaps the worst
in our history.
I'm well aware
of that, Robert.
But unless you have
some solution,
I'm missing the point
of this conversation.
The solution is,
we make a preemptive strike.
Assuming we locate the site
in time,
we destroy it.
We kill our own
Secretary of Defense?
To prevent our enemies
from making a public spectacle
of his death.
He's going to be killed anyway.
Jim Heller is a good friend.
A loyal public servant.
You expect me
to kill him to save face?
Not yours, sir.
The country's.
If we look impotent
in this situation,
we'll only encourage
more attacks.
And if I may say so, sir,
having known Jim Heller
many years myself,
if he were here, he'd be the
first to endorse this plan.
The public will never accept it.
All the public will know
is the Secretary died
during the course
of a rescue attempt,
which is certainly
more palatable
than letting him be executed
with the whole world watching.
( car door slams )
It's a woman.
I don't know her.
Oh, God.
Who is she?
It's Debbie's mom.
Go back.
Stay there until she leaves.
What are you going to do?
Go.
( knocking )
It's the girl's mother.
What?
( knocking )
Mrs. Araz?
Yes?
I'm Karen Pendleton,
Debbie's mother.
Oh, good to meet you.
Call me Dina.
It's good to meet you.
My husband and I are
very fond of Behrooz.
He's one of the few boys
who seem to know the meaning
of please and thank you.
Oh, I'm looking for Debbie.
This is my husband Navi.
This is Debbie's mother.
Oh, she's
a very lovely girl.
Oh, thank you.
We just got a call from
our dermatologist's office.
She missed her appointment
this morning. Is she here?
We haven't seen her
since yesterday.
Oh, she left a message saying
she was on her way
to see Behrooz. There
must be a misunderstanding.
Perhaps she stopped off...
No, she wouldn't have stopped
off anywhere,
she knew she had
this appointment.
It'll take weeks
to reschedule and...
Is Behrooz here?
He is studying.
Well, maybe he knows
where she is?
I doubt it.
He hasn't left
his room all morning.
School is very
important to him.
( musical cell phone tones )
Oh, that's her phone.
I know the ring.
Many, many phones sound alike,
Mrs. Pendleton.
No, she downloaded
that ring specially.
It's one of her favorite songs.
That's definitely her phone.
BEHROOZ:
Mrs. Pendleton.
It was my phone.
Debbie and I downloaded
the same ring
when we started going out.
Oh.
Do you know where she is?
She said she had
a doctor's appointment
to go to this morning,
and we're going
to the movies later.
I'm sorry about this.
I'm just worried.
Well, if you do see her,
or if she calls,
will you have
her call me?
Oh, yes, of course.
I told you
not to interfere.
It was her phone.
I shut it off.
He took care of it, Navi.
She went away because
she believed him.
Let's hope so.
Get in the car.
Follow her.
Make sure she doesn't
go to the police.
All right.
I'm less than two minutes out.
Have you worked up
the rescue approach?
We're running up scenarios now
based on the schematics.
Okay, what are the probabilities
of finding the Secretary
and his daughter
in the compound?
Our analysts have
looked at everything.
The data is fuzzy,
but our best guess
is that they're on the
west end of the building.
Together or separate?
We don't know that yet.
Okay, we're going to have
to activate a team split,
one for the Secretary,
one for his daughter.
We discussed that, Jack,
but it was rejected.
What are you talking about?
It comes directly
from the President.
Once we go in strong,
there'll be very little time
to secure the hostages.
Our only priority
is to get Heller.
Curtis that doesn't
make sense.
I don't like it any more
than you do, Jack,
but those are the orders.
Jack?
They're about to begin
the broadcast.
I'm almost there.
Damn it.
We are about to embark
on a process of justice,
that will forever
change the world.
Our people will
finally be liberated
from the tangle
of corruption
that has been choking them
for centuries.
No longer will justice be
the propagandist tool
of the power elite.
It will once again become
the instrument
of the people.
Delivered through
true believers,
whose courage to use the
sword has made this day
not only possible,
but inevitable.
Mr. President, I've
taken the liberty
of having a laser-guided missile
programmed and prepped.
All that remains is
for you to give the order.
...with the same conviction
and resolve...
How long between
my order and impact?
The fighter's in the air.
It needs to get in range,
no more than ten minutes.
...required to render judgment
fairly,
without prejudice,
or we will be judged
the same as our enemies.
As our prisoner shall be
judged today...
Do it.
Let Driscoll know.
...this nation will
also be judged.
Today is the day
the United States of America
shall be tested for
the final time
on your own soil,
before the eyes of the world.
Yes, I understand.
Jack, I have
Miss Driscoll for you.
DRISCOLL:
Jack, where are you?
I'm on site.
Jack, stand down.
What are you talking about?
The marines won't get
there on time.
The President wants
to take out the building
with a missile strike.
With the Secretary
and his daughter inside?
Yes.
Let me speak to the President.
Jack, I've been trying
to get through to him myself.
I'm sorry. You're going to have
to clear the area.
Jack, don't go in
there by yourself.
Jack, talk to me.
The air strike's
already been ordered.
Jack, clear the area.
The building is going
to be destroyed.
www.tvsubtitles.net