24 SO4E14
[yyeTs] Presents
All Subtiles Are 4 Evaluation Use Only
CC: Johnsonh
Timeline: niuniu
Translator: sHiN3
Supervisor: sHiN3 rustyapple
Previously On 24
We know you printed a document
before the EMP detonated.
Where is it?
You decide when the pain stops.
Drop the gun or I'll kill him!
Paul, where's the data printout?
I hid it.
Is this it?
Yeah, it's in code.
I couldn't make any sense out of it.
We're gonna get it back to CTU.
Tony, I appreciate you carrying
the ball until Michelle got here.
Why don't bring her and
everyone else up to speed.
The man responsible for
planning today's attacks, Habib
Marwan, has been a long-term
employee of McLennan-forster.
Jack Bauer and Paul Raines went to the
company to inspect his computer files.
As they were doing so, an
electromagnetic pulse bomb
was detonated, wiping out the
company's entire data base.
We have to assume whoever
detonated the EMP thinks
Jack and Paul found something
and wants them eliminated.
Where do we go now?
Weapons and ammunition.
Get out of here or the next one won't miss.
I'm a federal agent.
Look, we need your help!
Who's after you?
It has to do with the terrorist attacks.
I have critical evidence that I
need to get to the authorities.
If you're fighting the people
who caused today's bloodshed,
then we'll help you.
It's time.
Jack!
I'm here!
You and Raines safe?
Yeah.
I need you to get this to CTU.
It needs to get decoded immediately.
Jack, look out!
Paul...
Paul!
Get me a medic!
It is time for you to go.
Are you ready?
Yes, of course.
Proceed as planned.
The president of the united
states is on a tight schedule.
We can't be late.
The following takes place
between 8:00 p. m. and 9:00 p. m.
He's bleeding out!
Tell them on the ground we need
two liters of a-positive hemo.
Come on, Paul, stay with us.
We're almost there.
Hello?
Audrey, it's me.
Oh, Jack, thank god you're all right.
Audrey, I need you to listen to me.
Paul's been shot!
Audrey?
How bad is it?
The medics are working on him.
We'll be there in a few minutes.
Jack, how did this happen?
We were securing the area.
One of the gunmen tried to shoot me.
Paul pushed me out of the way.
He saved my life.
Audrey?
I'm here. I just...
Jack, I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Surgeons have been notified.
They're standing by.
I want you to know we're going
to do everything we have to.
You understand that?
Yeah, I understand.
I'm sorry.
I got...,I got to go.
See you in a minute.
Yeah, okay.
Mr. President, all the evidence
we've gathered confirms that this man,
Habib Marwan is directly responsible
for everything that's happened today.
The train derailment, my abduction, the
sabotage of our nuclear power plants...
does any of your evidence suggest
that he's planning more attacks?
I'm afraid so.
NSA is reporting a spike in chatter.
They're sifting through
the intel now, trying
to determine potential
targets and time frames.
"Trying" is not good enough.
The chopper carrying Paul
is about to land, sir.
We need to preempt any further attacks.
I understand, sir.
Our best chance to do that
is by capturing Marwan.
How close are you?
Jack Bauer recovered a document we believe
contains contact data on Marwan's network.
CTU is using it to track Marwan.
And if that fails?
Mr. President, we just have
to hope that it doesn'T.
Jim, today's events are continuing to
generate an unprecedented level of fear.
I'm not sure the social and civil fabric of
this country can withstand another attack.
We need to make provisions.
Provisions?
The civil unrest that
I believe is inevitable
in the event of another terrorist strike.
Are you saying we should
impose martial law?
I've asked General Wakefield to meet with
you in Los Angeles to discuss our options.
When?
Now.
His plane landed.
He'll be calling you to
confirm a secure location.
And, Jim...
keep this between us.
Of course, Mr. President.
All right, he's losing pressure.
I need ten CC's of
adrenaline, no compression.
Let's go.
Paul?
Paul, can you hear me?
-Got to get him into surgery now go!
-Paul...
I'm sorry...
please, tell me he's not going to die.
Come here.
Jack, tell me.
We don't know.
We just don't know.
Jack, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Listen, we were able to decode and
pull a name of the list you sent us.
Who is it?
Someone on our watch list.
But we had no idea he
was connected to Marwan.
Come on inside. We'll talk you through it.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Raines,
you need to stay out
here while your husband's
prepped for surgery.
Please, can I just talk
to him for a second?
Paul, hey..
hey, it's Audrey.
Listen to me.
I just want you to know
that I'm here, okay?
I'm here.
We need to prep him now.
And I will be here when
you get out of surgery.
Do you understand me?
Paul...
His name's Joseph Fayed, associate
professor at Green University.
Chemical engineering.
He came to the U.S. In 1985
to get his graduate degree.
We're sending in a team to pick him up now.
That's a mistake.
Why?
From everything that we've seen today,
Marwan's vetted his inner
circle very carefully.
That man will die before he says anything.
You're probably right, Jack, but
what can we do besides arrest Fayed?
Send someone in undercover.
Take a chance.
They might lead us to Marwan.
Come on, Jack, you know we don't have the
time to put one of our
own people undercover.
I'm not talking about one of our people.
Dina Araz.
She's already made her deal, Jack.
We granted her son immunity.
We have nothing left to offer her.
Maybe, maybe not.
Let me talk to her while
you mobilize a tactical team.
If I can't get her to cooperate by the
time they're ready, send them in, but it's
simple- we either
find Marwan or we will
not be able to stop what
he's planning next.
Meet them at the hotel on Old River
Road, half a kilometer from the base.
When?
Leave now.
I'll need his entire flight package,
including clearance and
identification codes.
You'll have whatever you need.
Is that all you've got?
Oh, for now it is.
Oh, come on.
I haven't seen you in two weeks.
Yeah, I've got to get to the base.
I'm flying tonight.
Damn, I'm going to be late as it is.
Look at me, I'm all wrinkled.
I wouldn't worry about that.
Hello.
It's for you.
What?
It's your wife.
That's your cell phone.
Laurie.
They've got guns, John.
They say they'll kill the children
unless you do what they want.
What's going on, Laurie? Who's there?
I don't know.
Listen to me,Laurie, whoever's
there, you put them on the phone.
Please, John, don't let
them hurt the children!
Laurie... Laurie.
Put your clothes on, John.
Curtis is prepping the tactical teams.
Which means you have
five minutes to do this.
Do you recognize this man?
No.
He's connected to Marwan.
I don't know him.
I already told the other agent.
Marwan doesn't permit
communication between cells.
His name is Joseph Fayed.
He's a professor at green university.
You know more about him than I do.
He's also our only way to reach Marwan.
We can't do that without your help.
Why should I help you?
I've already gotten all I'm
going to get for cooperating.
That's not necessarily true.
I know you love your son.
You've already shown me that today.
But unless you help us get to Fayed,
that will be the last time you
see him for the rest of your life.
This is Dessler.
All right, have them stand by.
Tactical teams are ready.
They can be at Fayed's
house in ten minutes.
Let's give him another minute.
I'm offering you your freedom, Dina.
You and Behrooz will be put in
a witness protection program.
You'll be given new names,
identities, everything.
This is a better deal
than you made earlier.
I'm offering you a life with your son.
Right now, the only question
is: Which life do you want?
What do you need me to do?
I need you to go to Fayed and tell
him that you need to speak to Marwan.
He won't let me through his front
door, let alone get near Marwan.
He will when you tell him that you've
got a hostage that can help him.
A hostage?
Who?
Me.
So what's this all about?
What are you doing?
I'm delivering you to someone.
Who?
I don't know.
You don't know who you work for?
I work for myself.
Somebody's paying you.
I don't ask them who they
are and they don't tell me.
That's how I stay alive.
All right, it's time.
If you don't cooperate,
your family will die.
Do you understand?
It's all there.
Get out of here.
Get your things.
We got a plane to catch.
Increased chatter indicates that habib
Marwan is planning another strike.
It's imperative that we locate him
before he's able to trigger this.
We are mounting an
undercover operation that
we hope will lead us to
him through this man...
Joseph Fayed.
We've struck a deal with Dina
Araz to work undercover for us,
and approach Fayed.
But Marwan knows we had
Dina Araz in custody.
We're trying to use that to our advantage.
Jack will run us through the
cover story we've fabricated.
The cover story goes as follows:
An hour ago,
I was transporting Dina Araz to the
federal detention center when my vehicle
was attacked by the surviving members
of a terrorist cell run by Navi Araz
at the intersection of
sepulveda and national.
I managed to kill or
wound all of the attackers.
But during the engagement,
Dina Araz secured one of the
weapons and took me hostage.
She'll take me to Fayed.
Hopefully, he'll take me to Marwan.
And if Marwan takes the
bait, we track you to him.
Yeah.
Now we have to assume they're
going to search both Jack and Dina,
which is going to make tracking
and surveillance devices a problem.
We're going to have to
handle this passively.
We're going to use satellite,
parabolics and laser aggregators.
But what about Dina Araz?
Do you think she'll be able
to play this convincingly?
Well, she's managed to live
here in the united states for
the past five years while part
of a terrorist cell undetected.
Yes.
She's an expert at deception.
As long as she doesn't deceive us.
Right now, this is our best and
only chance at finding Marwan.
But no matter how well
we fabricate this story,
Jack will be in extreme
and immediate danger.
We have to be able to move in
at the first sign of trouble.
There is zero tolerance for error.
Thank you.
Good luck, everyone.
Curtis...
the detainees from McLennan-Forster
have been taken over to division.
I want you to run the interrogation.
You got it.
Thank you.
Edgar...
I want you to call LAPD and Caltrans.
We need their logs to reflect
that the ambush on Jack took place.
I need an exact time window.
He just finished telling us.
An hour ago.
I know.
I just didn't know if there
was an updated scenario.
No, Edgar, you weren't paying attention.
Look, we can't afford for you to be losing
focus at a time like this, all right?
I'm sick of people talking to me
like I don't know what I'm doing.
Especially people who
don't really work here.
Is there a problem with Edgar?
Well, his mother was caught in the
contamination zone at
the San Gabriel Reactor.
She took her own life.
Now up till now he's been
handling it pretty
well, but I think it may
be catching up with him.
Do you think he's in good enough shape
to run the comm part of this operation?
Based on what just happened?
No.
Where's Chloe?
I didn't see her on the active roster.
Driscoll forced her to resign.
Why?
Well, apparently, Chloe went
against Driscoll's orders,
sided with Jack.
Turns out, Jack was right.
Thank you.
Hello?
Chloe, it's Michelle Dessler.
You're calling me from division?
Actually, I'm back at CTU.
Secretary Heller asked me to
take Erin Driscoll's place.
She got fired?
That's too bad.
Listen, could you tell Edgar to upgrade
the langley pattern recognition software?
He gets a little overwhelmed sometimes.
Yeah, I'll make sure he takes care of that.
Thanks.
Listen, Chloe,
you're better at what you do
than anyone I've ever worked with.
I need you here.
Thank you for saying that, but I
think I've had enough for today.
Chloe, this would be for Jack.
not just for CTU
What are you talking about?
He's about to go undercover
in a high-risk operation.
We need to mount a massive
surveillance in very little time.
I don't have confidence that
Edgar can do this on his own.
Well, there's nothing I can do about that.
Chloe...
I just need a few hours of your
time, and then you can move on.
I just want to do everything
I can to ensure Jack's safety.
Fine.
But it's just for today.
Thank you, Chloe.
You're welcome.
They're setting cars up at the ambush
site in case Marwan wants to verify.
We're using the dead bodies of
terrorists from Heller's rescue.
All right, the follow team
will stay as close as they can,
but to tell you the truth, Jack,
you're flying without a net on this one.
If a hostile decides to
take you out without warning,
there's nothing we can do.
I know.
Look, Audrey's still at the clinic.
There's time if you want to say good-bye.
She's got a lot on her mind right now.
Jack, she should know
what you're about to do.
She's been through enough today.
Want you to look over the time line,
then we'll talk through the details.
I'm not doing anything until I see my son.
We don't have time for that right now.
Seeing my son is non-negotiable.
Tony.
You need to learn every aspect of the
cover story- your life depends on it.
Don't worry about me.
You can see your son,
but only for a minute.
That's all.
Let's go.
Mom...
they wouldn't tell me where you were,
or even if I was going to see you again.
We're going to be together.
What are you talking about?
They wouldn't let you come with me.
Everything has changed.
I agreed to do something for them,
and they'll let me go with you.
What do they want you to do?
Help them find Marwan.
He's too dangerous.
Oh, I can handle Marwan.
Please, mom...
no.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Please, mom.
Mrs. Araz, it's time.
is field surveillance in place yet?
We have audio.
There might be some dead spots, but we
should be able to hear inside the house.
That's assuming they get that far.
Okay, thank you
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Why aren't you going through?
Damn it!
Use a danziger filter.
You can download it internally
if you know what you're doing.
There, you're in.
Chloe, what are you doing here?
Michelle thought you could use some help.
Offload your task list at station 12.
I'll cover your overflow.
I can handle my assignment.
Well, obviously you can'T.
Otherwise Michelle
wouldn't have called me in.
Edgar, I meant to tell
you before Chloe got here.
Look, ms. Dessler.
I can do my job.
I don't need any help.
I'm not saying you can't, but
I'm not taking any chances either.
Look, I realize we got off
to a rocky start, but...
Edgar, this isn't a debate.
It's an order.
Now, brief Chloe so she can run
satellite with you, and do it fast.
Jack's approaching the staging area.
This is Baron.
This is Dessler, we're set on our end.
Satellite and surveillance
teams are in place.
Go in at your discretion.
Roger that.
We'll leave this line open.
We're going in alone?
Our agents are conducting audio
surveillance with mobile parabolics.
What does that mean?
Acknowledge that you hear me.
Copy that.
What are you doing?
I have to make it look like I
was injured during the attack.
Take my gun.
This has to look as convincing as possible.
You must know that I want to kill you.
Yes.
But I know you won't because of Behrooz.
Let's go.
They're going in.
We're standing by.
What if Fayed doesn't believe us?
Then we're both dead.
Who is it?
Joseph, it's Dina Araz.
Who?
Dina Araz.
I'm a friend.
My husband is Navi.
He's been killed.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Now please go away.
I need to speak to Marwan.
I don't know any Marwan.
Yes, you do.
Go away before I call the police.
You won't call the police,
and we both know why.
What do you want?
I have a hostage.
Someone Marwan will want.
His name is Jack Bauer.
He's a CTU agent.
Now please, let me in
before someone sees me.
Close the door!
Put your gun over there!
Do it!
How did you find me?
My husband told me.
I don't know your husband.
He knew you.
Tell me what happened.
My husband was killed and I was arrested.
They were transporting me to CTU.
I heard an explosion, and the
van we were driving crashed.
It was our people...
they came to rescue me.
Everyone fell except Bauer and me.
He was wounded, and I
managed to get his gun.
Where did this happen?
At the intersection of
sepulveda and national.
Half a mile from here.
Don't move.
What is it?
The is Fayed.
A woman named Dina Araz came to me.
How did she find you?
She claims her husband told her.
What does she want?
She wants to bring you a hostage.
A CTU agent named Jack Bauer.
Jack Bauer?
Can you break into the other
side of the conversation?
No. The call's being piped
through a satellite switcher.
The signal's scrambled.
As she was being transported
our people ambushed the
vehicle at the intersection
of sepulveda and national.
Everyone was killed, but she
managed to escape with Bauer.
What do you want me to do?
Bring them to me.
I will call you back in five
minutes with the details.
Be ready.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I understand.
Marwan wants to see him.
Baron, it's a go.
I heard.
Set a follow grid, and we'll
coordinate from our end.
Evening, sir.
Evening.
Pop the trunk for me, sir.
Since when are you searching
officer's cars at the gate, sergeant?
An elevated threat level.
Okay, you're good to go, sir.
Thank you.
I'm on base.
Continue to the next phase.
Okay, I got you on base.
Let me talk to my family.
- Open the trunk, captain.
- Let me talk to my wife.
I said open the trunk.
Please...
let me talk to my family.
Your family is dead...
And so are you.
Mrs. Raines, your husband sustained
bullet wounds to his chest and abdomen.
Now, we were able to extract
one of the bullets, but I' called
a neurosurgeon in from Cedars to
help extract the second bullet.
Why a neurosurgeon?
Well, the bullet is lodged
against his t-5 vertebrae and
we want to be careful to avoid
any further spinal trauma.
I can't believe this is happening.
I'll let you know as soon as I
get any news on his condition.
Thank you.
Dad...
I don't think I realized how
much I cared for Paul until now.
I know this is terrible timing, but the
president has called and I have to leave.
You'll be able to reach me on my number.
The doctors will keep me up to speed here.
Okay.
I love you, Audrey.
And I'm proud to be your dad.
I love you, too.
Be careful.
Where are you taking me?
Shut up!
How far are we going?
It won't be long.
You look nervous.
What do you expect?
I wouldn't have contacted
you if I felt I had a choice.
And as a result, I have no choice.
We do whatever we have to for the cause.
So what's the problem?
There is no problem.
He's approaching an intersection.
They're turning off olympic.
Moving to next sub-channel.
He's turning onto a side street.
Collier avenue.
Hold that distance.
Understood.
He's heading towards
the broad street tunnel.
He's slowing down.
Baron, drop back.
Can't afford to have them spot the tail.
We're backing off.
He's turning into the tunnel.
Maintain your distance.
He's too far ahead for the parabolic.
I couldn't be able to hear
what's going on in there.
The tunnel's 400 yards long.
They'll be out of satellite view
for approximately 20 seconds.
Pull in front of this truck.
What's going on?
Out of the car!
What are you doing?!
From Marwan.
Yes.
This is taking too long.
We got them. They're out of the tunnel.
Do you have a visual?
That's it.
We've got them up ahead.
Fayed's turning onto Napier.
Napier loops back around to olympic.
That means he just spent the last
five minutes driving in a circle.
Maybe he's trying to detect surveillance.
Chloe, can you switch to infrared?
Hold on.
There's only one person in the car!
They made a switch in the tunnel!
Baron, the covert part
of the operation is over.
All teams move in on the target car.
Alpha team, cut him off at
the bridge. We're right behind.
Establish a perimeter around the area.
Stop and search all vehicles.
Chloe, do you have anything on satellite?
Nothing around the immediate
area of the target's car.
Can you go back into archives
and find out what happened?
Yeah, it's going to take a few minutes.
Do it.
Baron, what's your status?
Closing in now.
We got him surrounded on the bridge.
Passenger side
On your left
Flank him.
Get out of the car and
put your hands up now!
Out of the car!
Bomb!
Oh, my god.
Marwan set us up.
Almeida.
Agent Baron's dead.
So is Fayed.
Is there any sign of Jack?
No, not yet.
Any other hostiles in the area?
The area looks secure.
Okay.
I'll get you another back
up team as soon as I can.
I've the archives satellite footage.
Play it back..
Okay, during the time Fayed's car is
in the tunnel, three vehicles exit.
Check the van.
Can you get me a license number on that?
Not from the satellite. Let
me check the traffic cameras.
Edgar, get me the caltrans interface.
We have a socket open.
Logging in.
Done.
Okay, there's a camera at
the entrance to the tunnel.
Looking for the right frame.
Got it.
Send this out to all the field teams.
I want interagency support
on setting up the grid.
I'm on it.
We have an ID on the
vehicle: White chevy van, late
'90s, license plate charlie
victor alpha, three-two-two.
You've caused me a lot of trouble.
I'm sorry for your loss, Dina.
Navi was a great man.
I hope my men weren't too rough with you.
It was necessary, in case
you were under surveillance.
I understand.
But we weren't followed, I was careful.
You're a good liar, Dina.
What?
Fayed martyred himself.
The men who were following you are dead.
What men?
Enough with the lies!
Marwan, please believe me.
I did not betray you.
Prove it to me.
Kill him.
Just what I thought.
Get him out of here.
www.tvsubtitles.net