Aliens are all around us.
This is the story of a band
of four such explorers.
In order to blend in they
have assumed human form.
This is the high commander.
He has assembled an elite team of experts.
A decorated military officer.
A seasoned intelligent specialist.
And...well, they had an extra seat.
The Earth is covered with
a deep hard crust.
Although it does have
a wonderful chewy center.
Is it cable yet?
hey, hey, is it cable?
You're wired.
Ohhhhh
This is the second
most exciting thing
I've ever held
in my hand.
Harry, you ready to go?
Oh Dick, we've got cable,
72 channels.
And unlike primitive
free television,
this one you get to pay for.
That's nice.
Sally, are you finished in the bathroom yet?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You live in an attic?
You're poor?
It's so cool.
Thanks.
Hi!
Who's that?
This is Cheryl. She's a cheerleader.
A what?
Show them a cheer.
Oh not in front of all these people.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
Ready! Okay!
R a m s
Let's go, rams!
Whoo!
So...
she's proud
of her spelling.
I'll meet you in the
kitchen. We can study in there.
Tommy, what happened
to August?
August?... well, August
is bright and intelligent
and funny, and I love
to be with her, but,
Cheryl's easy.
So you're jeopardizing
a meaningful relationship,
for pure physical pleasure.
Exactly.
Very well. Carry on.
Thank you, sir.
Sally, here's your coat.
And I want you to be
on your best behavior.
This is a party in honour
of Leonard Hanlin.
Why? Nobody
likes him.
They hate him,
but they honour him.
It's a human phenomenon
that I find fascinating.
Behind his back
they deride him,
but to his face
they kiss his ass.
Well, that's just the kind of
stunt you can see only on cable.
Plus we got sports,
music, movies.
Oh, and look.
"El mundo pacífico"
Ah, that's muy bueno.
No.
Oh.
English, Spanish, French...
I know, I know.
Earth.. go figure.
Dr. Hanlin, it is an honour
to have you here.
Well, thank you,
Dean Sumner.
And, you,
be a pleasant toady
and bring me another one
of those, would you?
Dr. Hanlin, we so admire
your accomplishments.
Well, I admire your
courage, Mrs. Sumner.
An Audubon print over
the mantle passing for art..
that takes guts.
Look who I found.
It's Dr. Solomon.
Well, an honest man
in a den of bootlickers,
not that I don't enjoy
having my boots licked.
It's just that I find
you all contemptible.
So tell me, Dick, what
do you think of my work?
Mechanistic
and disturbingly fascist,
but pretentious high schoolers
might find it thought-provoking.
I think it's
groundbreaking.
I don't need the opinion
of a water boy with tenure.
I'm talking
to my friend.
I like you, Solomon.
Well, I don't
like you.
But I don't think anybody
hates me more than your friend,
doctor, um...
- Albright.
Yes. Probably because
I turned her down.
I need something
from the bar.
Yes, that should solve
all your problems.
Well, then let's
get drinking.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Well, somebody
said there was a
giant flaming
jackass over here.
They put it out.
I hate that man.
I wish there was some way he could be..
nicer?
No, dead.
Well, you're published
again. Congratulations.
Nina, what are
you doing here?
You're a secretary.
You're Dr. Solomon's
sister.
You're a lot better-looking
than he is.
Hey, I'm up here.
Yes, all women would
like to think that.
How would you like
to have your eyeballs
in the bottom of a martini
glass? 'Cause I can do it.
Oh, oo-ooh.. The amazon's going
to manhandle me.
You're not worth
a broken nail.
Dr. Hanlin?
Dr. Hanlin!
Somebody call 9-1-1.
I think he's dead.
Dr. Albright,
you got your wish!
Okay, so the kinds
of triangles are
isosceles,
equilateral, scalene.
And what's
the other one?
Why do I have to know this
if I'm going to be a teacher?
You want a soda?
'Kay.
Em, there's juice, too, if you'd
rather have that, or water.
Hi.
August, you're here.
Yeah, we have a science
project, remember?
em, yeah, right.
I think I want a soda.
Oh-hh! Hello,
Auggie.
Cheryl. There's
something different about you.
Is it your hair? No.
Oh, you're
holding a book.
Tommy, could
you hurry up?
I'm really thirsty.
Cheryl's helping me
with my math homework.
She is
You know, if you want to hang
out with Cheryl, that's okay.
We haven't made any serious
declarations of our feelings,
so there isn't
the issue of ownership.
But.. and,
just like Cheryl,
this is a big "but"...
you could at least
be honest with me.
August, I'm sorry.
Hello!
I thought you were
bringing me something to drink.
Oh, right.
Sorry. Sorry.
Diet.
- Sorry.
I can't believe this. I've
never seen anybody die before.
I know,
it's amazing.
One minute, he's active,
and the next, he's inert.
First he's limber,
and then he's stiff.
His eyes are twinkly,
then they're milky.
He's rosy, then sallow.
Oily, then dry.
Gurgly, then silent.
- Will you stop!
Dick? Dick,
we have a problem.
What?
- I killed him.
Oh, that's
just great.
Didn't I say
best behaviour?
I never meant to kill him.
- Why can't you be like Dr. Albright?
She wanted him dead, but
did she act on it? No...
because she's
a lady.
The police are here.
We've gotta get outta here.
We will. Just walk out calmly.
- Okay, here we go.
Look casual.
No. No, no. I think we all know
why Dr. Hanlin died.
He had a bad heart.
He ignored his doctor's
advice. He brought it on himself.
Oh, thank god!
- Yes!
Let's eat!
- All right!
Promise me something.
what?
Promise me that you'll never do
what Dr. Hanlin did at the party.
Feel up the caterer?
I won't.
Promise me you'll
never collapse
and be hauled away
under a sheet.
Because the thought
of you lying there,
purple, rigid
and distended,
just makes me
so sad.
'Kay.
You know what we
should do right now?
Run out of here,
grab a couple of horses,
ride bareback through
the woods all night,
and make love
in a meadow at sunrise.
I have a class
in five minutes,
and that's just the first
of my reservations.
Forget class.
Let's live!
Let's taste danger.
Let's go for the gusto,
consequences be damned.
Let's drive fast
and eat cheese.
Are you insane?
I've simply awakened to
the sensual possibilities
of everything
around me.
You know, I think
she's fully inflated.
What is it, Nina?
This letter just came for
you. It's from Dr. Hanlin.
"Dear Dr. Solomon,
if you are reading this,
it means that I am dead.
As one honest man
to another,
it is my dying wish that
you deliver an honest eulogy
without any embellishment
or flattering crap."
An honest eulogy,
I can do that.
No, you can't.
An honest eulogy for
that man would be insulting.
Well, I'll just have to
find something to say about him
that's both honest
and uplifting.
Oh, how about
"we love him more today
than yesterday"?
S  P... I R... I T
Go, spirit, let's hear it!
S P... I R... I T!
Go, spirit!  Let's hear it! Go, spirit! Let's hear it!
- Oh, gosh!
oh, that is..
she's got the spirit.
Isn't she wonderful?
Yeah, the magic
never ends.
Mrs. Dubcek, did you hear this?
- Yes, I heard it.
I don't know what
is going on up here,
but I have plaster
falling into my jacuzzi.
I've never heard it
called that before.
Take it outside.
- Later, Tommy.
So, Tommy, can't
find fulfillment
in a meaningless
relationship
with a superficial,
simple minded bimbo?
I know. I'm just
as baffled as you are.
Mrs. Dubcek,
have you ever been involved
in funeral arrangements?
Well, not for myself..
for my second husband.
Lovely funeral, very nice.
- Well, I..
I've been working on this
eulogy. What was his like?
Well, it was
an outdoor service.
And then this woman came
along, asking for directions
because she was lost and she
couldn't find her way home.
And we were so touched,
that we just forgot about
Carl's eulogy and just planted him.
So I-- I just
need to find
some babbling eccentric
to create a diversion.
What are you doing
on Saturday?
You're just lucky, you're so
damnedably handsome.
Why does death have
to be so inconvenient?
Mmm, to die,
to sleep.
To sleep,
perchance to dream.
Ohh!
There's the rub,
for in that sleep
of death
what dreams may come...
when we have shuffled off
this mortal coil
must give us pause.
What's that from?
- I don't know, some Mel Gibson movie.
Mel Gibson, he's dreamy.
Mmmmmm.
If we measure
"x" in grams
and "y" in centimeters
per second,
then "z" is measured in a
unit of energy we call ergs.
The complete conversion of
one gram of mass into energy
thus releases one times three
times 10 to the 10th power squared,
which brings me to another
point-- Your lives are fragile,
and you're all
going to die!
Your time is short, and...
I barely know
any of you.
Close your books.
I want to sit
among you.
I want to share your
thoughts, learn your fears,
expose your darkest secrets. Who's first?
Bug, what about you?
- Uh...
why are you called bug?
- I got hit by a Volkswagen.
And, Leon.
- What?
Where are you from?
- Here.
You see?
This is fascinating.
Uh, who's next?
Pitman.
Uh... what about you, Dr.
Solomon? Where are you from?
Okay.
I'm sure that you've all
heard of the radio telescope.
Well... funny story,
true story.
I'm not human.
Well, that's all
the time we have.
Oh, and by the way,
I assume that some of you have
taken a class from Dr. Hanlin.
Does anyone have any
stories about him?
I need something nice.
- oh, sorry.
I know that it was
his final request,
that I be forthright
and honest,
but the problem is, I can't
seem to find anything good
to say about this man,
and I've been looking.
You know, Dick,
everyone has goodness
within them.
If you look beneath
the surface far enough,
I think you're
going to discover
a basic inner core
of goodness
that, well, makes us all
children of god.
Well...
I guess I'll just have to
try to find that in Dr. Hanlin.
Leonard Hanlin?
Oh, well, good luck.
Listen, August, about Cheryl..
- No.
No, look, we used to be
involved. That's over.
I'm okay with that.
Now let's not let it affect
our academic relationship.
No, I made
a mistake with her.
See, I don't want Cheryl. I want you.
Of course
you want me.
What can I do
to fix this?
You could take me
someplace nice.
All right,
um... okay.
There's this thing I got
to go to tomorrow afternoon
'cause my dad
knew this guy.
It's, um...
you have to dress up,
'cause it's really,
really nice.
Sure.
So when they asked me to come
to earth, I thought, "why not?"
I was in a rut, working
for the big giant head.
You know him.
- Harry!
Uh, just a minute.
Who were you talking to?
- Nobody.
Dr. Hanlin.
How did he get here?
- I gave him a ride.
This isn't
Dr. Hanlin anymore.
It's an empty vessel.
See, if he were alive,
could I do this?
Could any man alive
resist a fresh banana?
I rest my case.
But, Dick, when
our mission ends
and we leave this planet,
will our bodies
end up like that?
Of course. It's happened a million times.
We study a planet.
We take on the life-forms.
We finish the job. We
discard the life-forms. The end.
Dick, I feel
different here.
I mean, I like Sally. What
will happen to her when I'm gone?
What happens
to all her stuff?
All her shoes?
You won't care,
because the thing
that's really you
will be
in another galaxy.
And Sally will be...
just like Dr. Hanlin.
Whoa, Dick, he's
going for the banana.
Oh, no!
I need to run
this eulogy by you.
Just say whatever
you're going to say.
No, no, I think I've found
a positive angle.
"Office space is at a premium on this campus,
so you'll be happy to hear--"
- Stop!
The man is dead.
We're ready to start.
See how nice it is?
This...
is the thing for the guy
you invited me to?
Yeah.
What?
How...
can we honour
the memory
of a man like
Leonard Hanlin?
Well...
he was governed
by the laws of physics,
as are all
living things.
It is a scientific fact
that hearts
and clocks slow down
as they approach
the speed of light,
the point
at which matter
is converted
into energy.
Dr. Hanlin's heart
approached that speed
on Friday evening...
at 7:57,
according to
the coroner,
converting his matter
into energy,
into pure white light.
Though he is
no longer with us,
he is all around us.
Thank You.
That was absolutely
beautiful.
Matter to energy?
Could you have
been more trite?
Why didn't you
just phone it in?
The fact that someday
we'll lose these bodies
makes me want more.
I want to share
myself with someone.
And I think
we all know who.
I want to savor
every moment.
I want to see places
outside of Ohio.
Hmm, I want one of
those big cheeseburgers
with three buns.
I want one
of those things,
you see people with them. You
know, they're like this big.
A baby?
- Yeah.
Aren't you kind of stuck
with a baby for your whole life?
No, you only have a baby
for, like, two years.
Men.
Dick, when are we going
to leave these bodies?
When we've learned
everything there is to know
about life.
Whoa. Good thing
we got cable.
www.tvsubtitles.net