Why do we have to come to
school to talk to Tommy's teachers?
I know, it's a waste of time.
Why can't they come to us?
The high school teachers on this
planet are so full of themselves.
It's all those TV
commercials glorifying learning.
You know,
"the more you know".
It makes them
drunk with power.
Yeah, well, that's going
to change right now.
Where's this
Mr. Randell, anyway?
When that mealymouthed
little worm shows up,
I'm going to teach him
the meaning of the word..
hiya.
Dr. And Mrs. Solomon?
- No.
No, no, no.
I'm his sister,
a woman.
Not married.
Just me,
single Sally.
Mr. Randell, I'd like to get out of
here while I'm still clean-shaven.
So you can begin lavishing
Tommy with praises
anytime you're ready.
Well, the truth is
that...
I think Tommy can do
a lot better.
Be careful, sir. You're
talking about the creature
I've come to
think of as my son.
He could do better.
You know...
whatever.
- Excuse us.
What are you doing?
- I don't know.
He's giving off this vibe.
Can't you feel it?
Yes, I think I do.
Does it feel like a
stabbing pain in your left buttock?
No.
- Then I appear to be sitting on a tack.
Dr. Solomon, Tommy's
very bright, no question.
Unfortunately, Tommy's having
a little trouble fitting in.
What do you mean, fitting in?
- Excuse me,
but there's something about
the thickness of your neck
and the broadness
of your shoulders
that makes me think
you'd be an agile hunter
and provide well
for our children.
I chaperone the school
dance every year.
Would you..?
- Yes.
Great.
- Wait a minute. What about Tommy?
He's fine.
Great kid.
Well...
why didn't you say so
in the first place?
Next time, you might try
organizing your thoughts
on a little index
card first.
Come on, Sally.
- Ow!
Wasn't he cute?
- Totally adorable.
A little on the scattered side, though.
- He asked me to a dance.
I get to go dancing!
- Nice.
What's dancing?
Harry, can I ask you
a question?
Uh, sure.
Just give me a second
to finish what
I was doing.
Okay, what is it?
Can you dance?
- Hmm.
I have no idea, but I'll try.
Why, yes, I can.
It appears
I'm quite good.
How are you doing that?
- I have no idea.
I think it's sort of a
built-In function. You try.
Wow! You suck.
You must feel
like crap.
That's it,
spank me.
Tommy, I talked to your
teacher, Mr. Randell.
He said that you're not fitting in.
- Of course I'm not fitting in.
To fit in, you have to be something.
- Well, we're something.
We're human beings. Why,
has anyone said differently?
No, it's just everybody at
school is something extra.
You know, they're African-
American or Italian-American
or Asian-American,
audio-Visual American.
Well, we're human-American.
That should be enough.
Dick, it's part of my
mission as an adolescent
to rebel against
my upbringing.
If you don't tell me what we
are, then I can't do my job.
Frankly, I can't work like this.
All right, if we have to be
part of some group, we will be.
I'll do some research.
I'll ask around.
I'll find out what
the best thing to be is.
By the end of the week, we'll be that.
- What should I be till then?
Well, we're
carbon-Based life-forms.
Just tell everyone
we're carbo-Americans.
Aztec, Toltec,
Toltec, Inca, Inuit,
Bedouin, Indian,
Sikh.
Aztec, Toltec,
Toltec, Inca, Inuit,
Bedouin, Indian, Sikh.
Aztec, Toltec, Toltec,
Inca, Inuit, Bedouin, in..
what are you doing
at my desk?
Anthropology,
it's fascinating.
Such a wealth
of cultures.
Up until now, I always thought
that what you did was pointless
and of no interest
to anyone but yourself.
It's certainly not as fascinating as physics.
I mean, everybody
loves maths.
Get away from my desk.
Nina, what is that thing on your head?
It's called a "daku".
- I think it's beautiful.
Thank you.
It's authentic.
It makes me feel connected to my ancestors.
- Oh.
So that's the traditional
headdress of ancient secretaries?
No, of my African
ancestors.
In case you haven't noticed, I'm black.
Well, of course
I noticed.
And, Dr. Albright,
you are?
Could I be
any whiter?
What?
I'm sorry, all you people look alike to me.
Excuse me?
- What was that?
Nothing, I just don't see why
people have to divide up
into these
arbitrary subsets.
I mean, skin color? Please.
you may see color,
but I see people.
Aren't we fortunate to
have someone so enlightened?
O pious one,
show us the way.
This verges
on sarcasm.
You know, my heritage
happens to be very important to me.
As it should be. I'm Irish,
and I'm very proud of that.
And you're... what?
Me? Uh,
I,I,I'm, uh...
one of those, uh...
you know, one of
the really good ones.
You're this big
anthropologist. You tell me. What am I?
Certifiable.
- Yes, that's what I am....Certifiable.
Certifiable and
damn proud of it,
as my father was before me
and his father before him
and his father
before him.
Certifiable.
Of course,
we no longer practice.
You see, Sally, dancing
is all about attitude.
Watch Harry.
See, I got that "hip-hop,
street, don't care about Nothin'
'cause I'm all of that
and a side of fries"
kind of attitude.
Right, whereas
my attitude is more
got home from teaching physics
and I'm wondering what's for dinner
but I ain't gonna sweat it '
cause I ain't even from here.
hey! Ho, ho!
Hey! Ho, ho!
Although we dis 'em,
we love this solar system
I hate this!
- What?
I can't believe I have to
learn to dance to be with this guy.
Well, you know, if you
really want Mr. Randell,
use the skills you're
comfortable with.
Shoot a tranquilizer dart into his
neck and drag him back to your place.
Harry, that is not the
behavior of a human female.
Exactly. I want to
charm him, beguile him.
I want him to buy me
a pwesent.
Tommy, how was school?
- Awful.
I lost my math book, and I couldn't
convince anybody that I was Samoan.
Well, don't worry.
The answer to all our
problems is right here in this book.
It's loaded with every
possible genre of human.
It's like a catalog.
You can take your pick,
whatever you want to be.
So who do you want to join, hmm?
- They're too scrawny.
Mm-hmm. Them?
- No, ugly flag.
Nah, too many gods.
I'm not putting that
on my head.
Ah-ha! Here we go.
Canadians.
Yeah, right.
Now, let's have a look at
Einstein's boundary conditions
according to the theory
of relativity.
Einstein, a Jew,
never could have made
this breakthrough,
had it not been for the
earlier work of Copernicus, polish,
or tycho Brahe,
the unlucky Dane
from Prague.
Which brings up
another question..
how many Puerto Ricans do we
have in class? Any Puerto Ricans?
Leon, what are you?
- You don't have to answer that.
Dutch.
- I love your tulips and your dikes.
Oh, thank you.
However, I turn your people
down because of the silly shoes.
Okay, no Puerto Ricans?
Any Latinos in general?
Anyone with
Latino information?
Dr. Solomon, with all due
respect, I find this offensive.
Pittman, you won't be left
out. I'll get to the Asians.
Why are you suddenly so
interested in what everybody is?
I have to know. It's important.
- No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
The only thing that
matters about a person
is what they
have inside.
Oh, yeah?
Then how come
you only date
good-looking guys?
That's not true.
- You turned him down.
Shut up!
Here are your books.
I read each one of them,
and I'm just as confused
as I ever was.
You read 15 books
in one night?
I took a couple
of hours out
to watch Japanese
golf on cable.
The problem is, these
books are full of dry facts
but no value judgments.
I mean, this is your field.. you tell me.
Out of all the possible ethnic
groups, which one is the best?
Oh, no, there's no best.
It's all subjective.
Which do you find the most interesting?
- There are so many.
Um... I love the creative
ambition of the Maori people,
uh, the Polynesian
culture
with its joyous
embrace of nature,
uh, the quiet
dignity of..
what's the sexiest?
- Italians.
Italians?
- Smoky, swarthy.
Gotta have 'em.
Gotta go.
Italian?
In napoli
where love is king
where a boy
meets a girl
here's a-what-a
they sing
when-a Da moon
hits your eye
like a big pizza pie
that's Amore
what are you doing?
- Buona sera, Signorina.
When-a Da world
seems to shine
like-a you've had
you too much wine
that's Amore
there's a ring
ting-A-ling-a-ling
ting-a-ling-a-ling
and we sing
vi...
Ta Bella
hearts will play tippy-
tippy-Tay tippy-tippy-Tay
like a gay...
tar... antella
What the hell's going on out there!
Nothing, Mr. Wagner!
Would you please get out of here
before somebody calls the cops?
The cops, they cannot-a thwart my passion!
I will stand
right here
till a pack of wild dogs,
they chase-a me away!
Dogs!  Run!
Usually when a student gets
hurt, we let them go home early.
Someone from your family
could come pick you up.
Someone like...
Sally.
Why did you say
her name like that?
All I said was...
Sally.
No, thank you. I don't
really need to get picked up.
Exactly what happened?
- I don't know what I did wrong,
but I'm kind of new
at being Korean.
Oops. You left this
in my driveway.
What happened to it?
- I backed over it
five or six times.
It was an accident.
Do you have any idea
how badly you embarrassed me last night?
how hard it is
to find a concertina
in Ohio?
What the hell was
going on in your head?
I know what this is. You don't
like Italians as much as you claim.
Wait a minute, since when
don't you like Italians?
Please, we're discussing prejudice
here, something you know nothing about.
I'm black.
- Oh!
Right, right.
Nina is... black.
Sally, come out of there.
- Go away!
Then we're coming in!
What's wrong?
You look beautiful.
Sure, you can put on a tight
little dress and look sexy and gorgeous,
but you know
how men are..
all they care about
is how you dance.
What's the matter with you?
- I'm afraid.
Of what?
- I'm afraid I'm going to do something stupid,
and he won't
like me.
Don't leak. I hate it when you leak.
What's wrong with me?
- I have no idea.
Dick, maybe I'm just
shooting pork in a barrel here,
but isn't that exactly how
you feel about Dr. Albright?
Oh, please.
- That is so wrong.
What I have with Dr. Albright...
- Mr. Randell is young...
Come in!
Ow.
Sorry to interrupt, but,
Sally, your date's here.
What am I going to do?
- I'll tell you what you're going to do.
You're going to be great! You know why?
- Why?
Because you're one of us. And
although I don't know what that is yet,
when I find out, that's what you'll be.
- Thank you.
Everybody ready?
- Ready.
Let's go.
Now go out there
and be a girl!
You look incredible.
Come on!
- Thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
Well...
well... so..
- What?
Would you like to..
- Bear your children?
No. I was going
to say "dance.
Oh.
Uh, that was really
embarrassing, wasn't it?
No.
No, not at all.
So would you like to?
Bear your children?
Dance?
Oh. Um...
well, see, I don't
really think that that would...Okay.
Ahhhh.
Now, this I can do.
I was kind of afraid
to come here tonight.
Why?
- I just wasn't sure I'd have a good time.
Oh. Are you having
a good time?
Oh, yeah.
Can I put my arm
around you?
Yes.
Can I put my head
on your shoulder?
Please.
Can I put my hand
in your pocket?
Do you need change?
Desperately.
You're so
wonderful. My whole front is warm.
You mind if I turn around?
- Well, I..
mmm.
Toasty.
I don't want to put you on the
spot, but if we don't kiss soon,
my head's going
to explode.
You know what's good for that?
What?  Calcium.
Whoa, this
planet sucks
lord, it makes me
wanna cry
yeah, I said
this planet sucks
lord, it makes
a poor boy wanna cry
anybody'd know
we was leavin
lord, I might just lay
my head down and die
Tommy, what are
you doing?
Well, I'm black now.
I'm black,
and I got the blues.
You can't be black.
Nina is black.
I get the impression from her they
have strict rules about these things.
I can't even be black ?
- I command you to put that thing down.
High commander
starts bossin'
best believe
you better jump
ooh!
All right, stop it!
Stop it!
Who died and made you
t-Bone walker?
Mrs. Dubcek, as long
as you're up here,
what ethnic group
do you come from?
Well, I'm a little Czech, a little Romanian.
I'm your basic Slavic mutt,
like my third husband.
Oh. What were
your first two?
Well, the first was Irish, and
the second was one of your people.
Our people?
- Yeah. Well, you know, Jewish.
Jewish! Oooh!
So what tipped
you off?
With your name it's pretty obvious.
- Our name?
Solomon.
Oh, you wonderful,
wonderful woman!
Thank you so much!
I have to go now.
This rules.
I'm still a minority.
You know, chicks
dig minorities.
Oh! Who knew that Solomon
was a Jewish name
when we took it off
the side of that truck?
Go figure. We could have
been the wal-marts.
We're Jewish.
I don't know
what to say.
Mazel tov!
I'm sorry,
it just popped out.
Isn't it great
to know who we are?
I finally feel
like I belong
to big melting pot
they call earth.
What a magical night.
Everything was perfect.
I was great.
He really liked
my kissing,
except the spitting
and biting.
So you really like him, huh?
- What's not to like?
He's intelligent, kind,
sweet, gentle.
So...
is he Jewish?
www.tvsubtitles.net