As many intelligent people know,
aliens are all around us.
This is the story of a band
of four such explorers.
In order to blend in, they
have assumed human form.
This is the high commander.
He has assembled an elite team of experts.
A decorated military officer.
A seasoned intelligent specialist.
and...well, they had an extra seat.
The people of Earth sometimes divide
against each other,
based on national
origin or skin colour.
Of course no-one else in the
Galaxy, can tell them apart.
Oh, I've been there
and there,
and I've been there.
Wow! The long, boring
stories you must have.
Well I have another destination
for you, Tommy.... high school.
Why? I finished
my education,
when you were nothing
but a snot-nosed gas ball.
Hey that sounds like a very
dangerous assignment Dick.
Shouldn't I take that on?
- No. We have to try to assume,
the roles of
a regular human family.
Since Tommy's the adolescent,
he'll have to go to school.
And you will explore the
lifestyle of a young adult woman.
And I, as the benevolent
father figure,
will provide the major
source of income,
and give you
cute nicknames.
Dick?
- What is it, kitten?
What's my role
in the family?
Harry, we have been
through this.
You're the brother
who tries hard,
but still doesn't have the
nerve to move out on his own.
But we love your pluck
and determination.
But I can do more.
You see? That's the pluck that we love.
Now, let's just be the
warm human family that we are.
After you.
- Why are you doing that?
Well, I've seen men
do it all the time.
Apparently, women don't know
how to operate doors.
Well, I do.
Oh, Dick, I've thought
of a job for myself.
I can catalog
the dangers,
that surround us
on this planet.
For example, getting
your fingers crushed
in a car door.
Ow.
Ow. Ow.
Why are you listening
to the serpent?
Don't eat the fruit.
Don't eat the fruit !
Women.
Dean Sumner's office called.
You parked in his space.
I know. It's so much
closer than mine.
Move it, lady!
- And your sister's here.
Sally, I thought I left you at home.
- You forgot your shoes.
Hey, what's with
the guy in 114?
Every time I walk by, he
follows me and talks to me.
I think somebody
has an admirer.
Great. Now can we
talk about me?
Sally, are you
seeing anyone now?
I'm looking at you,
aren't I?
For god's sakes, he's
trying to ask you on a date.
A date.
It's a perfect opportunity.
You'll go.
- No, I won't.
Trust me, I know what's best.
Why are you treating me like this?
Like what? - Like this? This?
There! you just did it.
I don't know what I'm doing.
You're acting as if I can't
make decisions for myself.
I am second in command.
One of us has to experience sex,
and I'm getting
nowhere with her.
Well, why didn't
you say so?
If sex is so important,
you and I could do it
right here on the desk,
get it out of the way.
Okay.
I'll leave you clampetts
alone to your banjo lesson.
When beetles fight these
battles in a bottle with their paddles,
and the bottle's in a poodle
and the poodle's eating noodles,
they call this a muddle
puddle tweetle poodle
beetle noodle
bottle paddle battle."
This man is a genius.
Well, if it isn't
our proud little student.
What did you learn
on your first day?
I'm wearing the wrong
kind of sneakers,
and girls
only like seniors.
And, man, you can't
compliment anybody in the shower.
You see, and you thought
you knew everything.
Sally, you're going to
be late for your date!
I just don't know what to wear!
Is this appropriate?.
Come on, men.
What do I even do on a date?
Oh, I've been reading about it.
I'll walk you through it.
Yeah yeah I'll be your date.
- You're not doing anything,
until you've done
your homework, old man.
Oh, so you guys get
to talk about sex,
while I make an Aztec
village out of macaroni?
This is fair.
Okay, Harry,
you're brad,
and the two of you are
at a romantic restaurant.
Here.
Okay, now go ahead.
I don't know
what to do.
Gaze into his eyes
the way Dr. Albright
gazes into mine.
You know...
That's perfect.
Now, break the ice
by telling him something
personal about yourself.
Well, uh, brad...
once every lunar cycle, my
uterine lining sloughs itself, thereby..
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, oh!
That may be too personal.
It does.
One minute, I'm fine..
..and the next, my uterus starts throbbing..
- Hey!
You know, there is something
to be said for keeping..
some mystery
in a relationship.
When do I get to touch
your breasts?
Right before you die.
Fair enough.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Rainbows, daisies,
snowflakes,
that girl.
My boys.
She's swallowed
a tiny monkey.
So, lieutenant, give us a
full report on your assignment.
He was wonderful.
He thinks I'm wonderful.
He asked me where
I'd been all his life.
You didn't tell him?
- All the coordinates.
Thank goodness he didn't believe
me, so I didn't have to kill him.
What happened after dinner?
- Well, he wanted to sleep with me.
I wanted sex, but since he was tired
I let him go home.- Damn.
But...
the good news is...
he's gonna call me.
I wish I could meet
a guy like that.
Come on, sport,
I'll drive you to school.
Bite me.
- Bite me, what?
Bite me, daddy.
That's better.
See you tonight,
slugger.
No, you won't 'cause
I'll be out with brad,
having fun.
All right,
good job.
Come on. Let's keep it moving, Solomon.
Climb the rope.
- Yeah. What's at the top of the rope?
Your self-respect is
at the top of the rope.
Run this by me again.
I climb up there,
and then I...?
You climb down!
And this gives me
self-Respect because...?
Okay, look, you don't want
to climb the rope,
you can go sit over
there with the girls.
So, if I don't
climb the rope,
then I sit with the girls.
- That's right.
Now help me out here 'cause
I'm not seeing the downside.
Must you make
such a racket?!
Okay,
you've bossed me around
for the last time.
Oh, I'm sorry
I blew up like that.
There he is.
You know, what goes on
outside this office
is really none of my business.
- There he is.
Just because I set
Sally up with brad
doesn't mean you're under any
obligation to tell me how it went.
There he is.
- I'm not even curious.
Mm-hmm, right there.
Sally's date?
Start talking.
Well, what can I say? In her
own words, it was wonderful.
mm-hmm.
- She overate, and he found her charming.
Mm-hmm.
- In fact, he's going to call her.
Hmmm.
What?
Orange juice.
Ahhh! Nontoxic.
Tabasco.
Ahhh! Also nontoxic.
He said he'd call.
- Yes, I know.
He promised.
He said he'd call.
That changes everything.
- I can take more pain
than the rest of you put together
, but right now I just feel so...
icky.
Damn it, Dick, give me
some pain I can define.
I am not going to jam your
hand in the toaster again.
You just can't imagine
what it feels like, Dick.
It's like he reached in,
pulled all the bones
out of my body.
My god!
What are you doing?
Apparently, I'm leaking.
Well, stop it!
All right, commander.
Wine cooler.
Ahhh! I could go
either way.
Lieutenant,
we need to talk.
This is all your fault. I didn't
want to be the woman.
You made me be the woman.
You're a decorated veteran.
I thought you could handle it.
Well, I can't.
This is hard.
Please, don't.
No no, Please don't.
It went so great.
Brad said he liked me.
Why won't he phone?
There, there.
Maybe he can't call.
Maybe his phone is out.
Maybe he injured himself
running with scissors
or used a dry cleaning
bag as a toy.
Dick...
I've lost all feeling in
the left side of my body.
Could somebody
please call 1-1-6?
Do not touch
that phone!
Oh, dad!
- Now what is it?
My teachers want to talk
to you about my attitude,
as if I have
an attitude.
This is just perfect.
I try to mold us into a
family that will blend in,
and what do I get?
A surly teenager,
a sister obsessed with a man,
and a brother who drinks too much.
Is there another family in
the whole world like this?
I don't think so.
Frankly, I can't take it anymore.
Me neither I'm outta here.
I have got to find out
what happened to brad.
"Induce vomiting".
There's an idea.
If anybody needs me,
I'll be in the garage...
putting up peg board.
Hello, brad.
- Sally.
I've come to check
your phone.
Sally, please,
calm down.
No, you may not
maim Harry.
I don't know,
find someone on the street.
Trouble at home?
- No. Why would you say that?
He didn't call, did he?
- Not yet.
hmm.
I just wish Sally had some
woman friends to turn to.
Are you asking for my help?
- Are you offering it?
How can I be offering if I
don't know what you're asking?
Why would I ask? I don't need help.
- Then I'm not offering.
Fine with me.
You can't say it,
can you?
Help me!
I don't know what to do. I
can't stand to see her like this.
There, that
wasn't so hard.
Then you'll help?
- No.
Can't you just take her
out tonight and talk to her?
You don't have to go alone.
Nina would be happy to join you.
Ooh, I'm sorry,
tonight's the night I'm
having my eyes gouged out.
Can't you reschedule it?
Put yourself in her position--
you go out on a date,
you have a wonderful time,
various arousing stimuli
fly back and forth
across the table,
and then he doesn't call.
How would you repair yourself?
I'd get good and toasted
and call him filthy names.
Yes, great. Now go and
do that with Sally.
You're buying.
Oh, of course.
Oh, she's way more
upset than that.
Dr. Solomon,
let me be blunt.
Tommy seems to have
a problem with authority.
Only Tommy refused
to climb the rope.
What was at the top
of the rope?
If he were my boy,
I'd warm up his little bottom.
You're the one who didn't want
him sitting with the girls, right?
I think he's just jealous because
I've done so much better than he has.
Dr. Solomon, nobody ever
said being a father is easy.
You're telling me. Some
of you must have children,
as frightening
as that thought is.
What do you do?
You need to set a good
example for your son to live up to.
Since when did my son
become my responsibility?
You're the ones who are
falling down on the job.
You're supposed to
be educating him.
Knowledge is the only chance
this planet has for survival.
One day you're going to have to find
someone to pull your collective butts,
out of the cosmic pliers, and
all you'll have to pick from,
is a bunch
of rope climbers!
Dr. Solomon,
I think you're avoiding
the real problem..
the home environment.
Well, of course
I'm avoiding it.
It's full
of crazy people.
Oh, come on, Sally. I
know you're in a lot of pain,
but holding it in isn't
going to do you any good.
You've got to let it out.
Come on, open up.
That really helped.
This can't be the first bad date you've ever had.
- Well...
a couple of years ago,
a friend set me up,
and my date turned out to be
this giant, slimy yolk sac.
Yeah, I've been there.
- Who hasn't?
I once dated this chemistry
professor, Dr. Abrams.
Oh, god, she's starting
with the A's.
He invited me to portage
lakes for a romantic weekend,
and then just
never showed up.
Did you kill him?
- No, no.
I don't believe in violence.
Violence doesn't do you any good.
However, a gas tank
full of sugar
and a flaming bag
of dog poop will.
And you take that orally?
Tommy, your teachers
seem to think
I'm not acting enough
like a father to you.
You're not my father.
- Well, that's true,
but I want to try
to act like one.
Fine. What do fathers
and sons do together?
Oh, they do this.
Yes, I've seen that.
Aw.
Excellent.
We're roughhousing.
Son.
This has taken
a wrong turn somewhere.
I've got a better idea.
We can do what the guy
downstairs does with his son.
They watch Tv for
18 hours straight.
Yes, it's the classic
male-Bonding ritual.
Oh, look,
Monday night football.
all right!
What is it?
Isn't there someplace
where people can just have
meaningless sex
with various partners?
Yes, it's called
the '70s.
Well, how late
is it open?
Hey, check out
the bartender.
Ooh, god's gift
to women.
I hope he kept
the receipt.
Oh, get a load of
the guy in the vest.
- I hope he kept the receipt.
See, Sally, you are
not the problem.
Guys are jerks. You're just
never gonna find the perfect man.
Yeah, the perfect man
would have,
Bill Gate's money,
Jimmy Smit's ass.
Liam Neeson's shoulders,
Michael Jordan's thighs,
and we need a brain.
Oh ho, no we don't.
Yeah, you're right,
then he'd think like a man.
See, Sally, there's just no
dealing with the opposite sex.
Yes, yes, the opposite sex.
I didn't do
anything wrong.
It's men.
They're a completely
opposite sex.
They hunt. We gather.
They sweat. We glow.
They shake.
We wipe.
You, your sexual organs
are in total diametric
opposition to mine.
Well, hey, so can I give you
a call sometime or...?
Oh, yeah, I'll be
waiting by the phone.
Have we poisoned her?
- No...
now she's
a buxom, leggy,
pouty-lipped bitch
with attitude.
I think she'll do
just fine.
Hello, brad.
- S-Sally.
I came here to tell you
that I understand
your limitations.
I expected too much.
I'm so sorry.
All the best.
Got your knob.
Hasn't tonight
been great?
Just us boys drinking
beer, yelling like idiots,
emitting various gasses.
Oh! Oh, look.
They're doing
that thing again.
Ohhhhhhh oh yeah !
Sally's back.
- Party's over.
thank god.
- Sally, you're smiling.
You're fixed.
- No, Dick,
I'm not fixed because
I was never broken.
I'm supposed to be this way. I'm a woman.
Yes, and...?
- Tell me, Dick, what kind of shampoo do you use?
I don't know.
Exactly, and do you feel
the urge to have,
an eight-pound
screaming larva,
rip its way out
of your lower abdomen?
No, I think I can
do without that.
You see, here,
you and I,
are completely
different life-forms,
and it's just
some sick cosmic joke
that we have
to share a planet.
You know, I've been thinking
about your assignment,
maybe it wasn't fair of me,
making you the woman.
I'm all right.
I can handle the mood
swings, the emotional issues,
the catcalls,
the punitive underwear,
because, frankly, when I
think of the alternative...
I just have to laugh.
Mother earth.
Father time.
Lady luck.
- Gentleman's quarterly.
Daughters of
the American revolution.
Son of Kong.
Fairy godmother.
- The godfather of soul.
Mississippi.
Mister sippi.
www.tvsubtitles.net