Earl, time to play
"Marry, Sleep with, or Kill:
Diner edition."
Ladies, booth one?
Sleep with, sleep with,
slept with.
Nice.
Okay, Max,
the dude at table ten.
Is there a "Throw food
in the cage and run" category?
Hey, jump in.
We're playing "Marry,
Sleep with, or Kill:"
Diner edition."
No, if I slept with
anyone in this diner,
I'd kill myself.
Even in a fictional scenario,
I cannot permit myself
to go there.
Girl, you'd take the fun
out of the punch bowl
full of cocaine.
Okay, fine.
Sleep with Earl,
marry you.
Not us!
Jeez.
What are you, a freak?
I feel uncomfortable,
Caroline.
Like, I don't know
how to look at you anymore.
Now, I can only see you
in a creepy lady tux.
You said it
was just a game!
I'm not in love with you.
Back off!
It was just a joke, Earl.
The things we say
in jest, darling.
in jest.
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
[cash register bell dings]
ooh ooh ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, my God, look at the RSVP
list for our opening party.
Max's Homemade Cupcakes
is at capacity.
Hey, we might
even be overbooked,
because in my experience,
even when guys
say they're not going
to come, they do.
Caroline, booth two
has been waiting
for service
for ten minutes!
And Han knows
how frustrating that is,
'cause he's been waiting
to be serviced for years.
Not that it's any
of your business, Max,
but I have a very active
sex life.
So then, Han, will you be
bringing a date tomorrow night?
Ah, no.
You do understand that sex
involves two people, right?
And that one of those people
has to be you?
What is all this dirty talk?
This is a diner,
not a dirty talking place.
Sorry, Han, I know
we still work here at night.
I'll go right over
to the booth.
We were just talking
about our big opening party.
All you ever talk
about is your big opening.
Now who has
the potty mouth?
Max, I need
your guest list names.
Oh, okay, I'm still waiting
for them to confirm,
so just put me down
for ten.
Okay, but I need
their names asap.
I'm running
a tight door.
I got a bouncer
from a local club
to donate his time.
I told him it
was a charity event for eczema.
What? We'll make a big donation
when we're successful,
but, for tomorrow,
every now and then,
scratch a little?
Hi, everybody!
I got great news.
What? You finally found
the thing we lost in there?
No. I knew we should've
tied a string on it.
No, look.
I got a fax from Poland.
My dream house is done!
Isn't it amazing?
It is amazing.
I haven't seen a fax
in, like, five years.
Sophie, it's so pretty!
Look at all this sweet
gingerbread woodwork
on the porch.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I'm going to be
on Air Poland flight
right after big party.
You are going to Poland?
That's news.
And when were you
going to tell me?
Um, now, yeah.
Um, I'm going to be gone
for a month.
Oh, okay.
It will be good
to have some time away
from the old ball and chain.
Yeah, he's not talking
about me.
We use a ball and chain
in our lovemaking.
That's the thing
I can't find.
All right.
Okay, yeah.
Well, buh-bye.
I'll see you tomorrow night
at my big going away party!
Sophie, the party's
for our cupcake business.
Oh, see, this is why
I don't like you so much.
Guys, thanks again
for donating your time.
It's fundraisers like this
that will help
put an end
to undescended testicles.
Hi!
I'd like to meet the owner
of this awesome
and totally cool
cupcake shop?
Oh, nevermind!
That's me.
Max, you got a blow-out!
Yeah, I'd figured
I finally see
what all the fuss
about getting blown is.
Oh, hi, we're not
quite ready for guests yet.
Girl,
I'm your doorman, Nevel.
Oh, I'm confused.
I thought my doorman was--
Straight, white, and boring?
He was.
Then, boring came down
with the flu.
Now, you've got gay, black,
and definitely not boring.
So what's
the charity tonight?
- Eczema.
- Undescended testicles.
People with eczema
and undescended testicles.
Lord, child.
That is a cross to bear.
Get me the door list,
and let's make
those poor, itchy boys
some money.
Another fake charity?
You've got some balls,
even if they aren't descended.
Max, we so lucked out.
Nothing says
"successful party"
like a bitchy, gay doorman!
Give me your guest names.
I'll write them down.
Okay, fine.
Put down Tommy, Dylan,
Robbie, Johnny--
Robbie and Johnny?
Wait, Max, are these
all your ex-boyfriends?
Perhaps.
Max, the invited guests
were all supposed
to be business contacts.
See, this is why I didn't
tell you sooner.
You're a control freak.
And for the record,
these guys have all had contact
with my business.
You're using
our launch party
to get back
at ex-boyfriends?
Uh, yeah!
That's what success
is for,
to say "suck it"
to people who dumped you.
"See my blown-out hair?
Suck it!
"See my cool cupcake shop?
See these in this blouse?
You wish you could suck it."
And here, it is not just
boyfriends on my list.
I also invited
the lady from Staples
who gives me attitude.
She can suck it too.
Fine, but how
is inviting Johnny
and his new wife
a victory?
Oh, like this.
"Hi, Mrs. Johnny.
Nice to meet you."
You got him,
but I got these
"And all this,
so suck it."
I'm not so sure
this is healthy.
Are you kidding me?
This is the healthiest thing
I've done in my life.
I even thought
about inviting my mother
to come and suck it,
but then she'd realize
maybe I didn't commit suicide
two years ago
like my note said.
I'm about ready
to open.
Shouldn't we be putting up
some testicle banners,
or scrotum posters,
or something?
Also, there's a cute blonde boy
out here asking for you
that I'm about
to eat alive.
[Groans]
That's Andy
with the free bar stuff.
Go, I'm gonna stay here
and practice my "suck it" face
for a while.
How's this?
That look
is so much more "suck it"
with the straight hair.
[Laughs]
I know, right?
- There's my cute boyfriend.
- Hey.
How did everything go
at Spike's Liquor?
Well, I got
a little bit confused
about what charity
we're pretending to help,
so I told them
my sister's homeless
and my balls
are up inside me.
Now, we just gotta hope
Spike's not the chatty type.
[Laughs]
Oh! They just dropped.
Hey, Andy, question.
What does this face
say to you?
I don't know,
like, "I'm cool."
So close!
Guess again.
Okay, like,
"I'm better than you."
No, like, "I'm it,
and you can suck it."
Yes! Yes!
They can suck it!
Is that
what you're wearing tonight?
Yeah.
No?
A sweater?
I always saw you
in a suit tonight.
Run home real quick
and put on a suit.
Hurry, people
are starting to come.
Uh, Max is still
making the face.
I know.
I can't stop.
I've waited my whole life
to make this face.
[Giggles]
Max, look.
Our business is open.
Wait, wait, wait.
Not quite.
In five, four,
three, two.
Both: Whoo!
- Name, please?
- Sophie Kuchenski.
Guest of honor.
[Cheering]
- How many in your party?
- See, I knew it was my party!
[Cheering and clapping]
[Lounge music]
Max, there's a line
all the way down the hall
and I've given out,
like, a hundred business cards!
You know what that means?
Being poor can suck it!
Girl, the Fire Marshal
just dropped by,
and told me
we can't let anymore people in
till some of these folks
go out.
Nevel, none of my guests
are even here yet.
It is very important
to let in any guy
who looks hot, but you know
would screw you over.
Is there any other type?
I'll go get
some more cupcakes.
Hey!
How's it going so far, babe?
Andy, what are you doing?
I told you to come back
in a suit.
Yeah, I know,
but I like what I'm wearing.
So you're telling me
you'll just go
and do what you want,
no matter how much
I try to control you?
Yeah.
That is so freaking hot.
Caroline!
Caroline, I can't get in!
Caroline! Less kissing,
more noticing me!
See, I know her,
and my name's on the list.
Han Lee.
Honey,
if I was a fat girl,
and your name was Sara Lee,
you still
wouldn't be getting in.
We are at capacity!
Hey, Robbie.
On the list.
Go right on in, child.
Uh, hello?
Do you need a dictionary
to define the word "capacity?"
I have clear orders:
Only very hot men
who look like trouble.
Mm-hmm.
Excuse me, you know
where I can find Max?
- Yes, she's in the back.
- Cool.
Robbie, it's me,
Caroline.
Oh, sorry.
Did we have sex?
What? No!
I'm Max's roommate.
Oh, Max had a roommate?
I was pretty much wasted
the whole time.
I remember,
like, nothing,
but I'm in the program now,
so it's one day at a time.
- Well, Max is through there.
- [Chuckles] Cool.
But we did have sex, right?
No!
We did not have sex.
You offered,
but I wasn't into you.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, right.
- Hey, Max.
- Robbie!
Why are you
making that face?
You have a toothache
or something?
No, it's--
I'm successful now
and this is my shop.
Wow. Cool.
So listen,
I'm an alcoholic now,
and I did a lot of stuff
that wasn't cool,
and I came here
because the program
says that I have
to make almonds.
"Almonds"?
You mean "amends"?
Cool. So, look,
I cheated on you
behind your back,
like, every day.
Well, um, we don't have
to go into all this now.
It's kind of a big night
for me.
And I stole money
from you too,
like, every time
we had sex.
But we had a lot
of sex.
[Chuckles]
I know.
Well, I stole a lot
of money.
Well, this just went
from "suck it" to "it sucks,"
so lift up your shirt.
I gotta get something
out of tonight.
[Inhales sharply]
Money well spent.
Just found out
I paid for more sex
than an Arab businessman.
Maybe this wasn't
the healthiest thing
I could've done tonight.
So what do you
wanna do?
Should I tell Nevel
to keep Johnny out?
Too late.
Way too late.
Max.
[Weakly]
Hi.
You look even better
than I remember.
Well, I should.
I just got blown.
[Chuckles]
Suck it, suck it,
suck it, suck it.
Max, this place
is so awesome.
It's like
you're telling everybody
who ever doubted you
to suck it.
No, we're not petty
like that.
Hey, it's a little loud
in here.
You wanna talk
in the hall?
Uh, wait, let me take a look
around my big, successful shop.
Yeah, I can go.
Keep your eye on Max.
That guy
in the Brad Pitt glasses
broke her heart,
and I don't trust him.
Max, you look insanely good.
Thanks.
Now, maybe you could repeat that
to your wife,
and where is she?
We never got married.
Max! Max!
I can't get in!
Wait, what do you mean
you didn't get married?
Johnny!
Hey, Johnny, I'm back here!
I didn't know
if I was gonna tell you,
but then I got your invite--
Max! Johnny!
I'm back here!
Should we just
go say "hi"?
Uh, no,
not right now.
Max! Max!
I can't get in!
Max! Johnny!
Max, I've been thinking
about you a lot.
Stop. Before you
say anything else,
I just have to say
I need candy.
[Mumbling] All right,
what were you saying?
I called off the wedding
because she wasn't the one,
and you wanna know
how I know that?
[Banging on glass]
Max! Johnny!
I can't get
into the party!
Come here.
Help me out!
Seriously!
That doorman
is a biatch!
Okay, so, uh--
[gasps]
Wait, what are we doing?
Making out
in a room full of candy.
Right.
No, no, this can't happen.
I was gonna give you
my "suck it" face.
Okay, give it to me.
I deserve it.
Your "suck it" face
is hot.
It's the hair.
[Moaning]
Ow!
- [Sighs]
- [Giggles]
Greatest night
of my life!
[clears throat]
Disclaimer:
This is not my T-shirt,
though I am
all about the Girl Power.
Disclaimer:
It's not my T-shirt either.
Some nerd left it in the dryer
at the laundromat.
It's mine.
Girl Power!
No way.
No way!
Do I smell
chocolate chips?
And is Uncle Andy
making pancakes?
You do,
and I am.
Dude, I don't know you,
but chocolate chip pancakes
are the balls.
How did you two sleep?
Did we sleep?
Great! So what's
gonna happen now?
I meant today,
at the shop,
our big first day
in business!
You thought I was talking
about you two?
Plbbt! I don't care
about you two.
Plbbt! Nobody cares
Well, first, we have
to clean the party mess up.
Andy and I
did it last night
when you didn't come back.
Um, can someone here
mellow out
and put some pancakes
in her pancake hole?
No, Caroline,
I get it.
It's been a rocky ride
for Max and me.
See, when we met,
I had a girlfriend.
Which he never told her
about, and--
And keep eating.
And because of that,
Max and I
never really
got together,
and then that girl and I
broke up,
and by the time
I saw Max again, I was--
Engaged to be married?
Yeah, yeah,
I was gonna get married.
Wait, to that
same girlfriend?
Different one.
Yeah, but that
didn't work out either,
and I've had a couple
girlfriends since--
[mumbling]
Oh! Only a couple!
Yeah, none of them
seemed to work out.
None of them are Max.
Hey, save me a pancake.
It looks like Caroline
has plans to eat them all.
Well, Max, as far
as the "suck it" plan goes,
it looks like somebody
sucked something.
Pancakes, pancake hole.
He's a good guy.
Yeah, he seems cool.
Kinda falls in love a lot,
but hey...
And I did not tell him
to say that.
He never does what I say.
It's hot.
"But hey" what?
Oh, we're continuing?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe I'm partial,
but Max,
you're an "A."
He kind of seems
like a "B."
Minus.
First of all,
look at me.
I am clearly a "D,"
and I don't think
he falls in love a lot.
Man, I love, love,
love pancakes.
If I could,
I would marry a pancake.
What time is it?
10:20.
Well, it's the first day open.
All those people are probably
tired from the party.
Yeah.
Oh, and look!
We forgot to light it up.
People don't know
we're open.
[Laughs]
In five, four,
three, two.
Both: Whoo!
- Go to work.
- [Sighs]
- First day!
- Yep.
No one's here.
Remember: All we have to sell
is 70 cupcakes a day
to keep on track.
70 cupcakes?
That's not so hard.
Maybe we should
do the light again.
In five, four,
three, two.
Both: Whoo!
What time is it now?
Tomorrow, we only need
to sell 140 cupcakes.
140 cupcakes!
That's not so hard.
How many
did we sell today?
Four.
And all were
to Johnny.
I think I've made
a terrible mistake.
It's only
been three days.
Business will pick up.
No, with Johnny.
It's different now
that he's available.
Maybe I'm the kind of person
who only wants something
they can't have,
and then when they get it,
they don't want it anymore.
Okay, but do you feel that way
about the cupcake shop too?
No, I love
our cupcake shop.
Wow, that's the first time
I've ever said
I loved anything
out loud,
except for Robitussin.
It's Johnny.
Well, I know
what I have to do.
Max, you can't change
your mind about him now.
He's our only customer!
By the way,
I've always loved him.
Hey, guys.
Um, could we talk
in the kitchen?
Yeah.
Wait, before you go,
I just wanna say
that no matter
what goes down in life,
we are always open
to your business.
We're either
gonna have crazy kitchen sex
or I'm getting expelled.
We're not having
kitchen sex.
It's way too dirty
in here
from other people
having kitchen sex.
So I'm getting expelled?
It's weird, right?
Between us?
Yeah, I don't know
what it is.
Maybe it's an absence
of a lot of candy...
[Chuckles]
But it's not the same.
Max! Johnny!
I thought I heard you.
Max!
[Banging on door]
I can't get out!
Maybe we're only
at our best
when you have
another girlfriend.
Maybe give me a call
when you get that going
in, like, ten minutes.
[Laughs]
Or I could just call you
on my actual wedding day.
Oh, cool!
Yeah, just call me 30 minutes
before the service,
and I'll be there.
Or better yet, call me at, like,
your 50th wedding anniversary.
Yeah,
now that's hot.
Max!
[Banging on door]
Johnny!
I'm cold!
Kiss good-bye?
Seriously, guys,
I can't feel my toes!
See, it's hot again
'cause we broke up!
I'll see you at my 50th,
if not before.
[Banging on door]
First the party,
now this.
When I have a party,
you won't be on the list.
You're right.
I deserve that.
No, I was doing
a power move.
Please, I'm begging you
to come.
We'll see.
I might be a little too busy
with my big, successful
cupcake shop,
so suck it.
[Cash register bell dings]
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net