Well, here it is.
My last tip.
Only $2.
And to think,
I held in a fart
for those cheap bastards.
This night sucks.
We don't even have enough
to buy supplies
for tomorrow.
We'll just have to go
to that store
where everything's free.
Oh, good.
They're open.
And we have to sneak
all this stuff out.
Han's staying late
to do inventory.
Damn it, why does he always
have to be so Asian?
Let's see, what do we need
for our cupcake shop?
Eggs, sugar--
A stripper pole?
Do you want to make money
or not?
How are we gonna hide
these eggs?
You could put some of those
"Grade A large"
where there's
"Grade A itty-bitties."
Rude,
but I don't hate it.
I can probably fit
four to six in each.
So positive!
I love that you're a "cup's
half full" kind of person.
So come here often?
This is my first time.
- Well, you're very pretty.
- Oh, thank you.
Heads up.
Han's coming your way.
Should I fake a stroke?
And P.S., if I don't get up
in three minutes,
it's a real one.
No,
I'll deal with him.
You keep going.
Keep it up,
and we'll finally have
an answer to the question
"What comes first?
The chicken or the Oleg?"
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Here you go.
I just found
the greatest thing online.
The ultrasound
of the Kim and Kanye baby
where someone photoshopped
a "666"
on its little baby butt?
Wait, this kid's
half Kardashian.
Its big baby butt.
Wow, that baby's already
famous for doing nothing...
Just like its mom.
No, what I found is a site
where we can apply
for a small business grant.
There's a couple of categories:
Women-owned business--
No thanks.
I've been to jail.
I was already owned
by a woman.
There's also
a minority-owned category.
You don't know
who your father is,
and you do have
an exotic look.
Any chance he could be
Native American?
Yes, in fact,
I think his name
was Chief Running Away.
Wait.
Maybe we don't even
need your father.
We are white,
which according to
the last presidential election,
is the new minority.
So now all we need is
a letter of recommendation
from someone who owns
another start-up business.
I was thinking
of a recommendation
from Candy Andy's
Sweets and Treats.
I've already written it,
so he just has to sign it.
Will you ask Andy?
I can't, he's my ex.
And I'm saving up my favor
for a booty call
on a cold night.
I hate asking men
for things.
Favors, last names, to stop.
Excuse me, could I get
some more Sweet'n Low?
Why don't you look
in your purse?
It's where I saw you
put them.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be.
I wasn't when I stole them
last night.
What did Andy say?
He's gone.
- For lunch?
- Forever.
The man is gone.
His store is empty.
Oh, my God,
this is so sad.
I know.
There goes the candy.
And my booty call.
- He didn't even leave a note?
- Or a razzle?
Forget the candy.
Are we not gonna talk about
the fact
that my ex-boyfriend left
without so much as a peep?
Great.
Now I want peeps.
Hey, Max.
Is today the day
we're gonna get married?
Sure, Amir.
'Cause my dream in life
is to be detained
for four hours
on our honeymoon flight.
Max, you do know I was born
in this country, right?
You were born here?
How old are you?
About Zero Dark Thirty?
Yeah, you were born
in a Walmart, right?
Where do you think
the expression
"Clean up on aisle 12"
comes from?
Hey, Caroline,
you bummed you drove
your boyfriend out of town?
For the record,
I did not chase Andy away.
We ended
our relationship well.
Right, that's why
I helped him move out
in the middle
of the night.
Man, you messed that up.
So self-involved.
Wow.
Coming in a little hot, Amir.
Yeah, guns ablazin'.
If I was allowed
to carry them.
Oh, Amir.
You're the bomb.
Look at us.
We're like Homeland,
if it was a rom-com.
You don't have to read it, Han.
It's just a standard letter
of recommendation.
Don't be a bitch.
Just sign it.
I'm not comfortable
putting my name
on a document
I haven't read.
I understand,
but don't be a bitch.
Just sign it.
"Max's Homemade Cupcakes is
an up-and-coming
powerhouse business."
I can't sign this.
This has more lies
than my OKCupid profile.
Don't be a bitch.
Just sign it.
That one's on me, girls.
If I sign this, it's lying.
I could get deported.
And I'm one home inspection away
from a poodle adoption.
A poodle? That's cool.
You can share sweaters.
Hurry up, bitch.
The deadline
to mail that is tonight.
Well, if you just wanted
to steamroll someone,
why didn't you get your
boyfriend, Andy, to sign it?
They split.
He left last night
without a peep.
Damn it, now I'm thinking
about those peeps again.
Oh, I was worried
you two wouldn't make it.
You always have your mind
on business,
and Andy was such
an easy spirit.
I think you mean
"free spirit."
Easy spirit is a shoe
worn by people
whose spirits have died.
I have two pairs.
Okay, fine.
Give it back.
I'll find someone else
with a business.
What about Sophie?
She owns a small business,
and she loves to give,
not as much as she
loves to receive.
I'm not so sure
Sophie's cleaning business
is totally, well, legal.
I mean,
when we worked for her,
on the memo line
of our paycheck,
she wrote "colonoscopy."
And for the record,
Sophie's cleaning business
is totally legit.
Her organ-trading
might not be.
Forget it, Caroline.
We might deport you
ourselves.
All we need is a FedEx box.
Um, Caroline.
Come over here.
I think I can help you
with that.
Thanks, Earl, but you
don't have a small business.
The size of my business
has never been in question.
And I may not
have a business,
but...
Han Lee does.
Max, look.
Earl forged Han's signature.
That's what his signature
looks like.
When I forge it,
I just draw a picture
of Hello Kitty.
You want to know
your future?
Oh.
No, no thanks.
You sure?
I have a message
about your love life.
$10.
Are you asleep?
Max?
Max, I really need to talk.
Oh, just come in
and get it over with.
Everybody else does.
Max, I'm sorry,
but I really need to talk.
I went to the fortune teller
near the diner,
and she told me that
I'd never find love in my life.
Fortune-telling's a scam.
"You'll never find a man,
your moon's in Uranus,
no man will ever be
in Uranus."
I could've told you that
the second day I met you.
Please, Max,
just listen for five minutes.
Come over here.
I'll make you some tea.
Tea?
Who am I, Pippa Middleton?
Toast me an eggo waffle
and maybe I'm listening.
Well, we were
saving that waffle
for a special occasion,
but okay.
Chestnut, we're eating
your birthday waffle now.
I don't know
why I'm pissing him off.
He's gonna be the only man
in my life.
I can't believe you blew $10
on a psychic.
Why didn't you just buy
a Skinnygirl Margarita
like all
the other lonely white chicks?
I spent $50.
I bought a crystal
that protects me from bad juju.
Hey! There's no reason
to get anti-semitic.
You spent money on crystal
you can't snort?
What is wrong with you?
I freaked out.
I didn't want it to be true.
Is it true, Max?
Am I never gonna find love?
Was Andy my one chance?
Did I screw it up
because I wanted success?
Was everyone right?
That is a lot of questions
for one waffle.
And where is that waffle?
You're a bad waitress
at home too.
Who could that be?
I don't know.
Let me consult the spirits.
Who is it?
It's Sophie.
Yeah, it's me,
the shady lady
with the illegal business.
Yeah, and Caroline,
you owe me an apology
or I will take out
these hoops,
and we will get into it,
girl.
Yeah, and I warn you,
I did some extreme fighting
in Warsaw.
Extreme fighting?
That's awesome.
Yeah, they would throw
a big hunk of cheese
in a trough
and let all the village girls
just go at it.
Sorry, Sophie.
It just seemed like
a better business decision
to go with the forgery.
What is that?
Is that a waffle?
Okay!
You are forgiven.
Damn it.
I didn't even get a bite.
I'm awake and sober
for nothing.
Sophie, do you believe
in psychics?
Oh, no.
That's all fake.
You know, I knew a family
of gypsy psychics
who couldn't even predict
that they would all die
in a barn fire.
Hey, girls.
Sorry to interrupt,
but Sophie promised
to rub antifungal cream
on my thick,
yellow toenails.
Oleg, come over here.
I'll do it in between bites.
This is what you're afraid
you're missing?
Because
this is a relationship.
Seriously, Max.
That's something I really want.
And now
I'm never gonna have it.
Get in there, baby.
I have two feet.
Interesting.
She's a psychic,
but she needs a bell
to tell her someone's here.
Max, please
don't make me do this.
I don't want to hear
any more bad things.
Nothing bad's gonna happen.
She's gonna tell you
you have
a bright, love-filled future
or I'm gonna kick her
in the crystal balls.
Hello, girls.
I'll tell you your future
as soon as I finish eating.
It'll only take a minute.
Since I quit smoking,
I eat like a prisoner.
Come, sit, ruminate
on your wishes and dreams.
Well, my wish is that you give
my friend her money back,
and my dream is
that I'm a backup dancer
for Missy Elliott.
Great. A wise-ass.
Do you want to know
your future or not?
Um, you already told me
my future.
That's why we're here.
You said
I'd never find love.
When did I say that?
And you, tough guy, don't say,
"Well, you're the psychic."
Maybe she is a psychic,
because I am a tough guy
and I was gonna say that.
You know,
it's hard to remember.
I see a lot
of sad, single girls.
But looking at you
right now,
it makes sense.
And here.
Take your phony crystal back.
And I'm not so sure
this is a real crystal.
It looks like one of
those vegan deodorant things.
And we want our money.
Oh, okay.
What just happened?
I put a curse on you.
Max, you said nothing bad
was gonna happen!
Well, I'm not a psychic,
and neither is she.
Laugh, Buster.
Nothing in life
will go your way,
and you will live
under a dark cloud.
Will this dark cloud merge
with the current dark cloud
above me
or fly alongside of it?
Look, we don't want
to trouble you,
but if you could
remove the curse
and possibly that noodle
on your blouse...
Oh, no.
Did you just--
Cursed you too.
Tell you what.
I'll lift both curses for 50,
or else your whole life
will come crashing down
all around you.
The only way I'm giving
a strange woman 50 bucks
is if I'm walking out of here
with a genital piercing.
I do that as well.
Don't believe in curses,
never have.
Not since Jennifer Martin
told me I was going to hell
for sleeping
with her boyfriend.
But I didn't.
I just ended up going
to homecoming with him.
Max, we have to go back
and pay her.
Our lives are hard enough.
We don't need things to come
crashing down around us.
Relax. Nothing's coming
Don't jump, Paul!
Paul, don't jump!
Paul? Who's Paul?
Oh.
And what is he doing
on the roof?
Okay.
That was Paul's life
that came crashing down,
not ours.
Max, I think
we all know that
I'm a highly educated woman
who doesn't really believe
in curses,
but I am putting every penny
we make tonight
in the "lift the curse"
fund.
And I'm gonna tell you
one more time,
we're not spending
another 50 bucks
on some stupid curse.
A body fell from the sky!
Paul got a bad batch
of shrooms.
It had nothing to do
with the curse.
Everyone knows
you don't take psychedelics
above the second floor.
Poor amateur bastard.
And we need our money
for essentials, like food
and the penguin statue
I saw at the Dollar Store.
The one that says
"Chill out."
So chill out.
Caroline,
I feel bad
about not signing your letter
of recommendation.
So I wrote one myself
and signed it.
Here.
That's so nice of you.
"The extremely hardworking
Caroline Channing,
"who has devoted her life
to business
and nothing
and no one else."
Han, this is supposed
to be about getting a loan,
not being alone.
I totally get it, girl.
I'm alone as well.
We have our eyes on the prize,
so our beds are empty.
But occasionally,
I pay for it.
Did Han just intimate
that he occasionally
gets a hooker?
Lucky bastard.
He probably gets
a child's discount.
Max, look.
The future's already happening.
Even in Han's letter,
I'm alone.
The only chance for
a love life I have now
is going halfsies on a hooker
with Han.
We have to reverse
the curse now.
News flash:
Everybody is cursed.
You lost your money
last year.
Literally nothing good
has ever happened to me.
Han hasn't grown
since the fourth grade.
Oleg's toenails
look like Fritos.
And Earl was born black at
the eighth-or ninth-worst time
to be a black man
in America.
Look around,
it's the valley of the damned.
Name one person
who isn't cursed.
Hey, guys!
I just found a $100 bill
on the sidewalk!
Drinks for everyone!
Max,
pop open the fancy brandy.
"Fancy Brandy"
is gonna be my stripper name
if you ever let me
put in that pole.
Sophie, guess what?
We went back to that psychic
to complain,
and she put a curse on us.
Oh.
You're cursed?
Uh...
But it's stupid,
like you said, right?
Yeah, yeah.
That's stupid.
Yeah.
Did she mention me?
No.
She just cursed us
and said
our whole lives would
come crashing down around us.
And 30, 40, 50.
The curse is lifted.
Oh, I don't think you got me.
What about my curse?
Talk about phoning it in.
Couldn't you wave a feather
or spin your head
or throw up
or something?
That's extra.
You know what?
I'm in a good mood tonight.
I got through the whole day
on 15 cigarettes
and one sheet cake.
I'm gonna give tough guy
a free reading here.
Oh, free, as in the $50
you just shook us down for?
Should never have quit.
Okay.
Future coming right at you.
I see that you will
have a happy life.
Me, happy?
All right, get your hat,
mother. We're leaving.
And I see a large sum of money
coming your way.
Over $10,000.
Max, it's the grant.
We applied for $12,000.
Is that it?
Sure.
And in spite
of your bad childhood...
She knew
you had a bad childhood.
Come on,
every childhood is bad.
You're stupid.
You can't reach stuff.
It's rough.
In spite of it,
I see great love and children
in your future.
Max.
Me?
No, wait.
You must be picking up
on her vibes.
Check again.
No, great love
and children
will be part of your future.
She will die alone.
Okay, well,
that's all I can take.
I'm not gonna sit here and wait
for the other Paul to fall.
- Let's go, Max.
- No, no, no, no.
No, no. Wait.
She obviously got it wrong.
Didn't you?
Nope.
Still dying alone...
With nothing
but her great success.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What?
I see great success
in your future.
You do?
Oh, thank God.
I'm gonna have success?
How big a success?
Oh, honey, it's so big,
you won't even know
you're alone.
All right, go.
May you live
a long and healthy life.
And put on your hat
and gloves.
I'm predicting snow.
It's not going to snow.
At most, it's gonna rain
30-year-old dudes.
Maybe she isn't so psychic.
Stop fighting it, Max.
You're gonna find love
and be happy,
and I'm gonna be successful.
You hear that, New York?
I'm gonna be
successful and alone!
And robbed and raped
if you keep calling that out.
And it all started
when I dropped
that grant application
into that mailbox
that those guys are unbolting
and taking away.
What's going on?
It's called emails.
We're getting rid of this.
No one mails anything anymore.
Yes, they do.
I did yesterday.
And our $12,000 depends on it.
Sorry, doll.
This box has been
out of commission for a week.
According to a psychic,
her box is gonna be
out of commission forever.
We had to tell him.
You expect me to lie
to a city employee?
So I guess
we're not getting that grant.
The psychic was wrong.
Maybe nothing she said
is gonna come true.
I told you,
it's a scam.
Max, look.
It's snowing.
And she predicted snow.
Oh, crap!
Am I gonna have kids?
So she was right on snow,
but not on the money.
So what is it?
Am I or am I not gonna die
old and alone?
Why are we even
talking about this?
We're probably not gonna
make it through the winter.
And by the way,
if you die first,
I am totally eating you.
Oh. I know.
And besides,
no one person
can get it all.
You're right.
No one person can,
but what about two?
You'll have
the love and the kids
and I'll have success.
Maybe we can share,
like we share our tips
or that wheat thin we found
in your pillowcase.
Are you asking to bang
my great love?
Which is fine with me,
because I'm already bored
and sleeping with
his poker buddy.
In fact, let's switch.
You can have my great love,
and I'll die alone.
Max, you don't want
to die alone.
I am dying to die alone.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net