It is with great pleasure I
would like to announce that
the recipient of this year's prestigious
ge follohip award is none
other than our very own.
liz lemon.
Wait,how could liz
win a fellowship award?
She doesn't like people.
No,followship.
Presented annually to the woman.
sorry,person,who best
exemplifies a foller.
I'm not a follower.
It also comes with ten grand.
I accept this proudly on
behalf of followers everywhere.
When I think of the free.
spirited liz lemon I
met just one year ago.
So resistant to product
integration,cross.
It pleases me to see how
well she's learned to follow.
Uh,is this because of that ge sketch?
He has a microwave for a head!
But it's such an excellent ge microwave.
You said i didn't have a choice.
So what are you gonna do with
your money,put it into a 401k?
Yeah,I gotta get one of those.
What?
Where do you invest your mo ms.
-***
***I can't believe how
fast you lost the weight.
If I can't be monique fat,I
have to be teri hatcher thin.
Either way,you're laughin'.
My uniform!
Let me get that off.
Turn around.
It just needs a little bit of water.
Oh,god,it hurts!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-马克斯 大花
30 Rock
Season 2 Episode 4
You're honestly telling me you
don't know who rosemary howard is.
Is she one of the ladies who
tried to shoot gerald ford?
No!She's the first female
writer for laugh.in.
She wrote all the political
stuff for donnie and marie.
I grew up idolizing her comedy.
Pardon me.
Pardon me.Pardon me!
Pardon you?
You were already pardoned!
It's funny 'cause it's true.
Hi,I don't wanna sound
like a weirdo fan，
but Iam obsessed with
everything you have ever done.
And I used to make my friends
act out your skits the next day.
When I say my friends,I
mean my fisher price.
my friend dolls.
Because I didn't have a lot of friends.
Oh,boy.***
You're gonna kill me,aren't you?
No,that's.
Oh,you are great!
I grew up wanting to be you.
I grew up wanting to be
samantha stevens on bewitched.
Closest I got was being married
to a gay guy for two years.
Oh,thank you.
Um,you are my heroine.
And by heroine,I mean lady hero.
I don't wanna inject
you and listen to jazz.
Good lord.
- Are you hungry?
- Always.
Well,I'm gonna let you take me to lunch
later and get all this out of your system.
That would be great.
I would love that.
But you're supposed to
take me hat shopping.
Hey jack!
Could you hold on a second?
If you desecrate something,is that bad?
Tracy,what happened now?
I doubt if anybody noticed.
Who brought stars and bright stars
to the party last night
for the rascals we fought
who wouldhave ever known
there was so many words?
It was like a mos def cd.
Tracy,it's all right.
You're a star,you can
do whatever you want to.
That's your job.
It's our job to make it go away.
I love this country.
You go forth and be crazy.
I think I can manage that.
You do anything you wanna do.
Except no dog fighting,okay?
That seems to be the one thing
that's off limits these days.
What's on your mind,tray?
You've been curiously
quiet for 20 minutes.
We gotta start doing dog fights.
Dog fighting?
I know it's repulsive and hideous.
But it's the only thing jack
donaghy told me I cannot do.
So I gotta do it!Understand?
No no no no no no no!
Dog fighting is the most disgusting,vile
thing a human being can do.
You cannot do it!
Dog fighting it is.
Make it happen.
Man,this is phil spector's
entourage all over again.
And his foot lingered.
Ah,that is such an upsetting story.
I'll never watch happy
days the same way again.
But you know,I miss live tv.
It's like sex,you know?
It's almost better when
everything goes horribly wrong.
Well,you know,we do hire guest
writers every now and then.
I mean,I don't know if that'S.
something you would
ever be interested in.
That'd be great.
God,I haven't been in
that building in so long.
Does everyone still do blow
in joe garagiola's office?
Which one is blow again?Is that cocaine?
Hello?Where's the head page?
You may enter.
You're a machine.
No,I wish.
This is a prop from the classic
nbc series supercomputer.
1975 to 1975.
Look,you obviously know who I am.
But what you don't know is that I accidentally
damaged kenneth parcell's page jacket and.
Really?
Mr. Perfect,Mr. Jesus loves
me parcell finally messed up?
Do you know how long i've been waiting to transfer
that thumbhead to cnbc in paramus,new jersey?
But you can't transfer
someone without a demerit.
- But now.
- oh,boy.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You've probably never
seen breasts before.
So I'm gonna lean over this desk,and
you're gonna give me a new page jacket.
Please,I breast fed 'til I was 11.
So I've forgotten more about a
woman's chest than you'll ever know.
But.I'm on tv.
I said,"good day.
" No,you didn'T.
Well,I meant to.
Kenneth parcell is finished.
Finished!
All right,what's in the
news this week,everybody?
Any ideas?
I have an idea.
We open on a new
orleans abortion clinic.
A beautiful mulatto.
uh,I don't think we're allowed
to use any of those words.
Why not?
It's live television.
I mean,we used to say And .
no,you didn'T.
-Did you?
-We did.We pushed the envelope.
Remember.
the mailbox sketch that shocked america?
There's nothing wrong here.
Don't you get it?
The mailbox was haldeman.
Is that a person who lived?
What about race?
I mean,I say that is the last taboo.
We get josh in blackface,right?
And then we get tracy to call him a !
I'd watch that.
No no,you can't do race stuff
on tv.It's too sensitive.
We would have done that
on the mandrell sisters!
Look,I want the show to be edgy too.
I mean,but my boss,jack donaghy.
let me talk to him.
- I am great with suits.
- No,we don't talk to him.
Liz,you're not a cog in their machine.
I know.
I'm not some.
follower.
I just.
we are very subversive on this show.
Frank,what do you have this week?
Uh,barry the humping dog is
shopping for a ge washer and dryer.
Have not seen that before.
Sharp idea.
Yo,I got the dogs outside.
Well,bring them in!
I feel sick to my stomach
about dog fighting.
But what can you do when
they tell you not to?
This could get ugly.
What?
No!
You idiots!
I built a dog fighting pit
in my basement for this?
Tracy.
Can I speak with you privately?
Tray,what's the one thing
i asked you not to do?
That 227 movie new jackee city?
Dog fighting!
What is it about your wiring that compels
you to do exactly what you're asked not to?
I don't know.
Always been this way.
Tracy,don't play with matches!
You're not my dad!
Tracy,don't stare directly at
the sun.It'll make you crazy.
You're not my dad.
Tracy,you're not going out
the house dressed like that.
You're not my dad.
I'm beginning to think this has
something to do with your dad.
You're not my dad!
You can't tell me what it's about.
Hey,props gave me a bunch of
dog penises for you to look at.
Oh,great,thanks.
Liz!
Your grandmother is in jack's office.
You better do something.
Nana lemon?That's weird.
Oh,no.
Rosemary.
Lemon,rosemary here was just telling
me some of her fantastic sketch ideas.
Liz,he totally gets it.
He understands that what we do is
far more important than what they do.
I do.I really do get it.
Rosemary,thank you so very much.
Oh,no,my pleasure.
What a pleasure.What
fun catching up with you.
You too.
- You take care now.
- You too.
Fire her.
And don't ever make me talk
to a woman that old again.
I can't fire rosemary.
Yes,you can.It's easy.
Observe.
Jonathan,you're fired!
What? No! God,no!
No,I won't fire her. It's mean.
And I like her. And she's right,we
should be pushing the envelope.
Oh,god. Push the envelope.
People who don't have the guts or
the brains to work inside the system.
Letter writers,radicals,howard dean.
You just don't get her. You're
like the talking mailbox.
I'm going to assume that's a haldeman
reference. In which case,I thank you.
I got into this business to be
like rosemary. To make people think.
No. No no no,lemon.
You got into this business because you're funny
and you're weird and you're socially retarded.
And you also got into it because it pays well,which
means you are not like rosemary; you are like me.
No,I'm not. You are a suit.
You feed off the creativity and hard work of other people and
turn it into commercials and pie charts and triangle graphs.
What's a triangle graph?
I don't know! It sounded real.
-This is my show.
-No,this is my show.
And once a week I rent it out to the good
people at the erectile dysfunction companies.
Be that as it may,rosemary is my idol.
And if you wanna get rid of
her,then you will fire me also.
suck it up,nerd.
Oh,my god!
Rosemary,that was such a rush
standing up to jack like that.
And I never would have done
it if it weren't for you.
I am so proud of you!
He heard you roar and now things
are gonna change around here.
Jack says you're both fired.
Yes!
Hey tray,whatcha doing?
Just some heavy thinking.
This spotlight is the only place that
I could go to get away from it all.
You know,tray,I get this dad thing.
I mean my father belongs in the
smiling irish bastard hall of fame.
And the pent. up,unresolved anger i
have toward him,it still overwhelms me.
You've got to learn to forgive.
But how do I forgive
someone that I don't know?
Boy,if I could just talk
to him once. Just once.
Tracy,we're gonna do this together.
You've got to get into therapy.
I don't need therapy.
I'm just mentally ill.
Tracy,what if I told you that the
one thing you cannot do is therapy?
You're not my dad! We're doing therapy!
All right,thank you. Good. bye.
Kenneth,I may have made a mistake.
-I was talking to donnie.
-donnie?
Head page donnie
lawson,the king of sting?
What did you do?
I was just trying to make things right.
Nice jacket,parcell. I hope that it and you
will be very unhappy at cnbc for the next year.
Of course,there is one other choice.
A page. off.
A page. off?
It's a savage contest. Mixing
physical stamina with nbc trivia.
What's a page. off?
You wanna page. off?
I don't know what kind of
corporate mind games he's playing.
But if jack thinks i'm
crawling back there.
oh,screw him. But now that you're
free,we can work on something together!
Yeah,we can start our own
network called bitch tv!
Or the second idea that we think of.
Look,when we get back to my place,we
start banging out some ideas.
Welcome to the first day
of the rest of your life.
What neighborhood is this?
Oh,they call it little
chechnya. So gritty and real.
More murders per capita than detroit.
Try not to write when
you're living here.
Is that guy carrying a gun?
Yeah,but don't worry. He's not a cop.
Hey,tracy,this is susanne
hawker,the nbc therapist.
Who's crazier,me or anne curry?
Hello,tracy. Jack informed me
of the talk you had earlier.
And if you don't mind,I'd like to hop
right in and start with some role play.
Like my wife and I do? Cool.
Donaghy,you play the matador.
Uh,no,tracy. What I want you to do is talk to that
empty chair as if your father were sitting there,okay?
Man,this is stupid!
Come on,tracy. We're here to help you.
Uh,tracy,maybe it will help if jack sits
in the chair and pretends to be your father.
I wanna talk to you,son.
You sound nothing like my dad.
Well,where is he from?
All I know is he's
from funky north philly.
He worked in a campbell's soup factory. And he
had a droopy lip due to an unattended root canal.
I think I can do this. Okay,go.
I'm mad at you,dad.
Hey,dummy! I'm mad at you too.
-Uh,that's not exactly what I had in.
-'cause you left me,dad!
I was young and confused and your
moms didn't want me around no more.
Now,pass me them damn collard greens!
Is this true,mom?
He gambled away my welfare check.
Woman,I got a mind to
smack you upside the head.
-Uh,this is not helpful.
-Be me now.
I only act out because I
want your love! Dyn.o.mite!
I think we're just doing good times now.
Now do the white dude that
my moms left my dad for.
Uh,now,see here,tracy. It's
impolite to slurp one's soup.
Whoa,no need to resort
to ugly stereotypes.
You always gonna be my son.
Tracy,just because i stopped loving your
dad,doesn't mean we stopped loving you.
Stop puttin' words in my mouth,woman!
Oye,papi,kayate! People are sleeping!
Mind your own damn
business,mrs.Rodriguez!
All right,this is ridiculous.
Lady,just because i'm
an ignorant black man.
And you paid me a nickel to bust up your chifforobe,doesn't give
you the right to call me ridiculous just 'cause I'm proud of my son.
They got me.
The honkeys shot me.
No,dad!
Don't die! I love you,dad!
I don't wanna dog fight no more!
Tracy,that's it! That's it!
Thank you for showing me there
really is love in my family after all.
And I need to stay the
hell away from them.
Donaghy,you're the only
family I need,jackie D.
You got that right,tray.
You know,it's too bad you didn't know howard cosell when you were
growing up. 'Cause I had that one in my pocket the whole time.
There we are.
Oh,crapballs! What was that?
Okay,let's find a pen
and start that screenplay.
This movie is gonna
knock them on their asses.
Right. What's it about?
Women in their 50s go on spring break and
get laid by a bunch of grateful 18.year.olds.
Oh,god.
Yeah,exactly.
I predict opening
weekend,a million dollars.
Have you been drinking wine all day?
Oh,it's heart healthy.
-All day?
-Oh,come on,liz. It's the '90s!
Did an f train just go by your window?
I know that look. Don't even
think about jumping for that train.
You know,I think i should
go home before it gets dark.
You can't abandon me,liz. You are me.
No,I'm not you.
Really? You pick up guys
that are smart and funny.
You're never gonna get married,liz.
You're married to your job.
Oh,my god. I lost my job.
You're just like me.
You get up in the
morning and smoke weed.
-no,I don'T.
-You obsess about the jamaican man across the hall.
Oh,my god. I lost my job.
You wouldn't have a job if it wasn't
for me. I broke barriers for you.
I really have to go.
I sat around while my
junk went bad. All for you.
I didn't have any kids. You're my kid!
-You're my kid that never calls!
-yikes.
Help me,liz lemon! You're my only hope!
Okay,which nbc series spun off,among
others,cosby,miami vice,cheers,and highway to heaven?
-Supercomputer!
-Oh,you're gonna do great!
Ready!
Page.off,page.off
Come on,kenneth! You can do it!
Hey! What the hell
is going on down here?
The phones are ringing off the hook,there's
no one seating the conan audience!
Get to back to work,you morons!
Pete,wait. You don't understand.
I ruined kenneth's jacket and he needs to get a new one,but
can't have any demerits,so we have to have a page.off.
what,are you kidding me? This
is a billion dollar company!
Demerits?
Donnie,give kenneth a damn jacket!
This isn't over between
us,moroney. You're in it now.
It's finally over,ms.Moroney.
Yes. And it's hard to even
remember how it all began.
You burnt my jacket.
All right,I need my job back.
But this is not crawling,this is proud
begging,like those kids that dance on the subway.
Of course you can have
your job back,lemon.
Oh,thank god. It was terrible.
I went to her apartment. I
don't think she has a toilet.
I saw my future,jack.
Never go with a hippie
to a second location.
I can't end up like that. I have
got to make money and save it.
And I have to do that thing that rich people
do where they turn money into more money.
Can you teach me how to do that?
With my eyes closed.
Oh,good,because I want to send
rosemary $400 a month for. forever.
You should,that woman is unemployable.
Rosemary says that women become obsolete in this business
when there's no one left that wants to see them naked.
You make enough money,you can
pay people to look at you naked.
To the future,lemon.
Oh,and by the way,ge has a
problem with the dog penis sketch.
I'll change it.
Hey,what about cat penises?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-马克斯 大花
www.tvsubtitles.net