Hey,I wanted to come say merry christmas
before we all leave for the break.
Oh,thank you,lemon.
That's very thoughtful.
Help yourself to a gift.
It's our new handheld photo
scanner/paper shredder.
Oh,well,won't people just
end up shredding their photos?
No,no,it's very to use.
If you want to
pto-scan,you flip the stc.S.
And if you want to paper
shred,you flip the switch to--
I'd like to make
an announcement!
I just want to say that I'm really sorry for
whatever I'm going to do at the party tonight.
And I forgive all of you in advance for leaving
me passed out by the elevator in my own gravy.
Merry ludachristmas,everyone!
Are you gonna do horny
santa again,frank?
That was so funny last
year when I sat on your lap.
Yes,funny.
So big plans for the holidays?
Yeah,my parents are
coming with my brother,
and we're gonna go see
jersey boys on broadway.
And we're gonna go to that restaurant
where they pretend it's mars.
God,you must be a ball
of anxiety right now.
No,I'm really excited.
What are you trying to say,lemon?
That your family's perfect
and you never fight?
No,I remember them arguing a
lot during the gas crisis of '79.
But since carter left office,it's
been pretty smooth sailing.
You got that right.
So is your mom
coming up from florida?
No,I invited her out of
my paralyzing irish guilt,
but her plane was grounded
because of hurricane zapato.
Look at that!
That's where she lives.
Jupiter,the eye of the storm-
So are you alone for christmas?
No,I was gonna drive up to
vermont and surprise C.C.
Sir!
Your mother is here.
She took a bus to atlanta.
She got jet blue to accept an
amtrak ticket. - Tell her I'm--
jingle bells,jingle
bells,jingle bells surprise!
It's your mother. Merry christmas.
Jack...
isn't this the
office you had before?
I thought you were up
for a big promotion.
I am,mother,and there are only two
nicer offices in the whole building.
Only two? I don't like the odds.
I think you better
let that dream go.
Hello,liz!
What the hell was th?
It's a message on my
phone from a friend.
Oh,jackie,please. Who is she?
Her name is C.C.
Is she spanish?
What if she was,?
She's very smart,colleen.
You'd like her.
My thanks to the peanut gallery.
Jack,this coat isn't
going to take itself off.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
30 Rock
Season02 Episode09
Ludachristmas is tonight?
Well,I guess I can make it.
I just hope i don't get drunk and sing
christmas carols like I did last year.
Well,I'm not going,because my parents
and my brother mitch are in town.
Mitch is here?
- Yes.
For those of you who
don't know my brother,
mitch was in a skiing accident
his senior year of high school,
and he has what's called
trauma-induced niveaphasia.
Basically he's just stuck in
the day before his accident.
Oh,tomorrow's the big day!
It's gonna be totally rad!
Yeah,mitch,rad!
He thinks it's 1985. So if
you meet him,just be cool.
It should be mentioned that
sexually mitch is very much an adult.
No,it should not be mentioned.
Merry christmas from
sheinhart-universal,everyone.
Merry christmas.
- Thank you!
Merry jewish.
Merry christmas.
What is this?
It's a ps-575
photo shredder.
Well,that's not
the christmas spirit.
Christmas is about
gratitude and togetherness.
Sitting with friends and family around a
crackling fire waiting for the owl meat to cook.
Sometimes I don't think you
people understand christmas at all.
Hi,I think I'm early.
I'm here to have christmas meats
eaten off my chest at some party.
Merry christmas,ms. Lemon.
Oh,thank you,kenneth.
Well,fancy suits. How was court?
Not great,beth.
Oh,you really
were in court?
all tray had to do was sign
his community service papers.
But he makes a stop
for breakfast first.
So it's my fault diners can
serve alcohol in new york state?
That's on me now?
Now I have to
wear this for 30 days.
Oh,my goodness.
If I even had a drop
of alcohol in my sweat,
a signal goes to ankle bracelet
headquarters in denver,and I go to jail.
And now? This
time of the year?
Ludachristmas?
Nude year's eve?
Martin luther king day?
All you do is drink.
No,tracy,you are not going
to ludachristmas. - But--
the three of you are in charge
of keeping him from drinking.
Okay. But who's
project manager?
Hmm,that bad,huh?
Oh,these aren't for me.
I'm sending them to my mother's hotel room
because the room service there is too salty.
Family stuff can be tough.
Lemon party!
Permission to land!
Permission granted!
There's my baby!
Hey,liz,you want to go skiing
up at piper's peak tomorrow?
It's gonna be rad.
Psych! You can't go!
It's the senior class trip!
Oh,psych! You
got me,mitch!
Jack,these are my parents.
Dick lemon. This
is my boy mitch.
And my first wife margaret.
First and last,hi!
- Jack donaghy.
You are a very,very handsome man.
He looks like an
arrow shirt model.
So,jack,is this beautiful
genius the best employee
you've ever had or what?
No.
I like this guy's honesty.
Yeah,me too.
Show us what you've been working on...
wilma shakespeare.
Oh,I'm just so proud of you.
Oh,you boota boota boota!
Nice to meet you,sir.
- Yeah.
Would you wrap these up and send
them to the ritz-carlton,please?
Oh,my goodness!
Look at this!
They built all of this because
of your words you wrote.
Thank you,thank you.
Hey,liz,guess who's
going skiing with me?
Chris stanek,your boyfriend!
Aw,what? Shut up!
I don't like him! Boys are gross!
Did you hear that chris
stanek got divorced?
When? Is he dating again?
lemon,could I have a word
with you for a moment?
Oh,excuse me.
Is,uh,everything okay?
- Yeah,why?
Your family is strange.
Oh,mitch? No,he was in a skiing
accident,and he thinks it's 1985.
No,I get it. I'm talking
about your parents.
What did your mother mean when she
said that you were a beautiful genius?
Was she taunting you?
No,they're just super supportive.
They've always been like that.
Even I when I sued the lower white haven
school district to let girls play football.
Hut!
Feminism!
What?
We didn't make the playoffs that year,but
I think we led the league in bravery.
My god,I've never seen such
relentless blind encouragement.
No wonder you're a sexually
frightened know-it-all.
hey,dad,take my picture,look.
I'm the lady from flashdance.
that's a good
flashdance,honey.
Good flashdance.
The holidays without drinking is rough.
Turns out football is boring.
My wife's sister ain't as
cute as I thought she was.
And I cannot play the guitar.
Mr. Jordan,I know
how difficult this is.
I was pretty addicted to coke
back in my wall street days.
But you can get through this.
The first night
is the hardest.
But tonight is
ludachristmas.
No,tonight you and i are gonna
have some real christmas fun.
We can play party games.
Like murder!
First,everybody takes a
slip of paper out of a hat.
And one person's
slip says "murderer."
And another person's
slip says "inspector."
Then everyone
puts their head down.
Except the murderer.
He's the inspector.
No,that's not right.
K,thanks for trying to help.
But I'm gonna go
home,do some thinking,
and tell my wife's sister
to disregard all my emails.
That hotel was
a disaster,jack.
The tv had over 100
channels,for god sakes.
I'm only gonna be
here for three days.
Fine,mother. You
can stay with me.
No,I will not let you
do that. Are you sure?
Yes,mother,I'm quite sure.
All right,then,that's settled.
Jack,do you have a bathroom
that I can get to in a hurry?
Yes,right in here,mother.
Well,that is close,isn't it?
I'll be right out.
She should've been there.
Knock knock!
It's just the lemons.
We've come to drop off a
little good-bye present.
Oh,thank you!
Oh,my goodness!
What a beautiful office.
Oh,your mother must
be so proud of you.
wow,look at this carpet.
I feel like we should
take off our shoes.
Should we take
off our shoes?
No,please sit down and
make yourselves comfortable.
Well,we don't
want to bother you.
We know you must have big plans.
Well,I was going to drive up to
vermont and visit my girlfriend C.C.
Oh,I love that name.
- C.C.
Ooh,I'll bet any girlfriend
of yours is a real winner.
Well,she is a
congresswoman.
Oh,my goodness!
And she does have her
own lifetime movie.
Lifetime!
- Wowsers!
Why don't we cut the charade and you two
tell me what exactly it is you want from me.
now,alfonso,let's find where
you should put the keyboard.
Open,open hommina,hommina,hommina
open pit barbecue sauce
yes,this is the sweet spot.
Oh,and no chitchat
between songs this year.
People don't watch
letterman for paul shaffer.
Excuse me,ma'am,do you
know where the bathroom is?
Hi there,mitch.
It's jenna. Maroney.
We know each other.
Are you,like,a friend
of my mom's or something?
I mean,I'll tell
her you said hi.
What's up? Do
you like wham?
'Cause I'm kind of like the
george michael of my school.
Oh,you're mitch.
- Yeah.
Coming to the
party tonight?
Oh,I wish.
I gotta rest up for my
big ski trip tomorrow.
You know,maybe you and i could
do something together next week.
Definitely.
My parents are
away next ********
******
that's a filthy
christmas miracle.
There you guys are. I'm sorry
they just barged in like that.
On,not at all.
They were just dropping
off this christmas present.
Oh,and look at this.
It got cheese and butter and
caramel. All my favorites.
How did you know?
Well,we will let you go.
We've got a lot of
window shopping to do.
Jack,why don't
you come with us?
Come on,you can talk to
mitch about president reagan.
Oh,in his mind reagan
is still president.
You lucky bastard.
What?
I would love to go with you.
Good,good,good!
jack?
Hey,dude,I thought you left.
Yeah,I mean,what are you guys
doing? Going to ludachristmas?
Yep,we heard you can't drink.
You still coming?
No,no,I can't go because
of the ankle bracelet.
But maybe I could
go and just not drink.
Hey,maybe I'll compromise.
I'll go to the party,cut off
my foot,and drink all I want.
Luda-christmas!
Luda-christmas--
grizz,dotcom,shut the doors.
Some people need to
learn about christmas.
Hey,watch out
for her,jack.
She's a natural athlete.
Played high school football.
It was just one game,dad.
Although I did kind of
change everything forever.
I'll never forget that day.
Jack,you laced those
up like a professional.
Good for you!
It's nice to have some
positive reinforcement,isn't it?
Well,it's only positive
reinforcement when they say it to you.
In my case,they're
just stating the facts.
I do look like the arrow shirt man,I
did lace up my skates professionally,
and I did do a fabulous
job finishing my muffin.
You wish you were in my family.
Don't be ridiculous.
So this disney cruise in
march,are you in or out?
hey,huddle up.
We're gonna take a picture.
- Yeah.
Oh,thank you.
Say "lemon!"
lemon!
jack!
Having fun?
Under the bridge,under the bridge,woo!
Jack,what the
hell are you up to?
Mother,I'm sorry,but the lemons
invited me out,and I couldn't say no.
They're very nice people.
oh,nice. I'll
show you nice.
Let's all meet down at the soda shop
while this country turns into mexico.
Now,you see,they don't
say things like that.
They're very polite to each other.
I suppose you think that
they're more nurturing than I am.
Mother,there are terrorist cells
that are more nurturing than you are.
Be careful. I'll cry.
You give me ten minutes
with the lemon family
and I'll have them tearing at each
other like drag queens at a wig sale.
Mom,dad,this is jack's mom.
We have heard such
great things about you.
Have you?
You must join
us for dinner.
no,no,no! No,we can'T.
We have plans.
Uh,had plans.
An evening out
with the lemons.
Who could ask
for anything more?
great!
Thank you,reverend gary.
That was both entertaining
and educational.
Christmas has gone off
the rails around here.
Look out there.
That is not a
christmas tree.
It's a way to lure tourists into
the basement to buy $20 salads.
We've lost track
of what's important.
So now we're gonna
go around the circle,
and every one of us is gonna
say what christmas means to them.
Let's start here.
It's so hard to choose.
The photos of the
food look so good.
I am gonna have the fried
onion tower for two for one.
Good for you!
You must be so proud of liz.
Making it on her own
so far away from home.
That gives us an excuse
to visit new york.
I see.
Any grandchildren?
Oh,what a shame.
Must eat you up inside.
Oh,well,champy,our
spaniel,keeps us pretty busy.
See,mother,not all
species eat their young.
Let's change the subject.
Politics.
We don't discuss that stuff.
Life is too short.
- really?
Life is too short?
Because your life seems endless.
thank you,reverend gary.
It was to the tune of american
pie,but so much longer.
Listen,we done learned our lesson
about the big tree or whatever.
This has got to stop now!
Yeah,who care abobout the
true meaning of christmas?
It's about getting crap
and eating too much!
Yeah!
It's about getting drunk and hugging your
cousin until your mom says,"frank,enough."
That's right.
Well,now seems like a good time for reverend gary to
show the video of his mission to guatemala last year.
What?
Is this a culture where
toplessness is common?
Pieces of wood!
Just like I prayed for!
And here is what you did
with your christmas presents.
We take so much for granted.
Instead of having a party,we should
donate the money to those kids.
We should tell all our family and friends
we don't want any presents this year.
yeah!
We should volunteer at a soup kitchen
instead of shopping for stuff no one needs!
Yeah!
We should go downstairs
and chop down the big tree!
yeah!
No! No,wait!
No,no,no,no,no,no,no!
your mother is killing me.
Have I ever kissed a
woman? What is that about?
Welcome to my world,lemon.
She's trying to break your spirit.
- Why?
Because she's trying to prove that
your family is as screwed up as mine is.
Well,that's ridiculous.
Oh,mitch found a newspaper.
Mitch,that's a
joke newspaper!
What?
Why can't you just
leave well enough alone?
Because the lemons are
not what they appear to be.
I mean,I may be heavy furniture,but
I did a pretty good job raising you.
I mean,look at you
today and look at them.
They look happy.
They're in denial.
I mean,come on!
Now,dick,let me
get-- - ah-ah,jack!
It's on me. Wouldn't be a
lemon party without old dick.
Easy on the fried food,honey.
Oh,come on,I can eat whatever
I want. I'm a teenager.
Mitch,don't you ever get tired of liz getting
all the attention her being the baby and all?
Oh,no,my folks make
a lot of time for me.
I mean,just yesterday we
went to see goonies together--
You weren't supposed
to know that,liz,sorry.
Wait,you saw goonies yesterday?
Does he mean 1985 yesterday?
Yeah,december 6,1985. I mean,what
else would I mean by yesterday?
Well,that was the day
of my football game.
Did you not go to
my football game?
We were a little
embarrassed,liz.
Dad,did
you--
it's white haven football,for
god's sake,elizabeth.
It means something.
I wore that uniform.
I was taking a
stand for women.
Are you taking a stand now
by not giving us grandkids?
Oh,you want grandchildren,margaret? Why
don't you ever bother mitch about that?
Because he's 17!
He's 40!
What?
Oh,my god,the
accident. I hit the tree.
no,don't remember.
Oh,I'm so old!
Thank you,elizabeth lemon.
You are so self-centered,young lady.
You didn't even offer
to pay for this dinner.
I'm on a fixed income.
Could I have another drink?
Bingo.
This is not what I meant!
Yes,it is.
We're sending a message to all of those who
have forgotten the scruples of christmas.
'Cause in order to stay
sane,you have to go crazy!
I had a couple of drinks
before the meeting.
Hold that,kenneth. This is a flask.
So y'all probably shouldn't
be listening to me.
* have yourself a
merry little christmas *
* Make the yuletide gay *
* from now on our troubles
will be miles away *
* here we are as
in olden days...*
do you know why i
stay with you,dick?
Yes,I do know.
Because you have no income
of your own,that's why.
I could've been
drinking these for years!
Explain to me again how gay marriage
is gonna tear this country apart!
Merry christmas,mother.
Merry christmas,jackie.
tomorrow night I'm gonna
take you to a cathouse.
I hate cats.
you'll learn to love them.
it was ridiculous to lie
to him that long anyway!
my life is ruined!
www.tvsubtitles.net