There's a situation, Mr President.
There's a nuclear device,
under terrorist control, that's on US soil.
- Where?
- Los Angeles.
This bomb is going to go off today.
Today's gonna be a very long day, and I don't
want my own people working against me.
Hey, you two! Cut it out.
What? I can't kiss my own wife?
She's not your wife
for at least another 10 hours.
When you asked for
a background on Reza Naiyeer,
I was proofing a file on another individual.
Reza's name came up.
There's a man named Syed Ali
with ties to terrorist organisations.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- What are you doing here?
- I just wanted to see you. I miss you.
- Dad, it's too hard for me right now.
- Then why won’t you...
- Every time I see you, I think of Mom.
Are you a complete idiot?
I don't like when he gets like this.
I need a few minutes
with my daughter before I leave, OK?
Did I not tell you to get outta here?
Shut up! Shut up, Megan!
What am I doing here, George?
There's a rogue nuclear weapon
here in Los Angeles.
- How close are you to IDing a prime suspect?
- The most promising one's Joseph Wald.
Are there any witnesses
against Wald in his trial?
Marshall Goren. Apparently
without him there's no case.
You are Marshall Goren?
No, Jack!
- Are you out of your mind?
- You wanna find this bomb?
This is what it's gonna take.
I'm gonna need a hacksaw.
Quantico wants permission to relay the
nuclear threat to their mid-level tacticians.
- How many people are we talking about?
- Between 600 and 700.
Only if they assure
they can contain the information.
I will confirm that
before I give them approval, sir.
I want everyone to know that, besides
the threat of a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles,
I'm just as concerned with the dangers
of panic and mass hysteria.
Absolutely.
So where are we on everything else?
Well, NSA is taking a two-pronged approach.
They're trying to pick up a trail
on any known Second Wave terrorists,
and they're also trying to source
stolen weapons-grade nuclear materials.
Yes, call the rep,
tell them what the matter is, OK?
Why can't she hang around?
I said I'd be back in a couple of minutes.
Thank you. Yes...
Hey, Kim. Stay there.
She's gonna be fine, OK?
We'll work this out
in a couple of minutes. All right?
Hey, Donny?
Yeah.
Yes, no... Uh... It's... it's...
I know it's late.
Why can't she...
OK.
Right, right. Yeah, do that.
Yes, I know. She's being a...
No, no, no.
No, everything's fine. It's fine.
Yes, I know...
Kim, take my keys. Get her away from here.
Right.
Tell them to wait until I get back, OK?
I'll call you back.
Come on!
Kim! Stop the car. I will kill you.
Stop the car! Do not do this, Kim.
Do not do this.
Star-Sat. Password, please.
7073. I need to track
the location of my car, please.
We'll drop you three blocks
from the salvage yard.
- What about the car?
- Ready, with a tracker in the trunk.
Good.
We haven't seen Wald come in the yard yet.
- What about his people?
- We're not sure.
Any of these men look familiar?
No.
Yes, that's Eddie Grant.
He's one of Joe's main go-to guys.
When I was undercover, we were friends.
As soon as I'm in, I don't wanna see any of
our people. You keep everybody at a distance.
You know any more about
the size of the bomb?
Not yet.
Sir, the press is asking questions.
They know you cut your fishing trip short
and they'd like to know why.
If you'd like, I can get Jenny to take care of it.
- No, I'd better take care of it myself.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir, we've got a lot to cover.
- I have to deal with the press.
Sir, we have a serious situation
and taking time out to coddle the media...
What you don't get, Eric, is that once the
rumour mill starts, we've got two problems.
The last thing we need is mass hysteria.
- Mason.
- George, it's Jack. Let me speak to Tony.
- What do you need?
- Have you picked up Kim yet?
Grothy just got to the house
a few minutes ago. Kim wasn't there.
- What do you mean? Where is she?
- We don't know. She wasn't at the house.
I told you to tell me when you knew anything.
I was just picking up the phone. Relax, Jack.
Don't tell me to relax, George.
Grothy's gonna wait until Kim gets back.
Meantime, you hang in there.
George, just find Kim, OK?
That's what we're doin', Jack.
We're gonna find her and get her out of LA.
- Trust me.
- OK. Thank you.
- Hi, this is Kim. Leave a message.
- Hey, sweetheart. It's your dad again.
I can't tell you how important it is
that you leave Los Angeles.
I'm sending a man over from my office.
His name is Roy Grothy.
He's gonna pick you up
and take you over to Aunt Carol's.
Honey, please, do this for me, OK?
Call me back as soon as
you get these messages.
I love you. Bye.
Paula, have we gotten a Division update yet?
Uh, yeah. Tony, shouldn't we
be working from outside LA?
Why?
If there's a nuclear bomb
somewhere in the city...
Try to tune it out, Paula.
You never know how good the intel is.
Almeida, we have a lead. Just caught
a couple of coyotes at the border.
- Who were they bringing in?
- Not who, what.
Michelle, you want to pull it up?
Two forged Middle Eastern passports.
The markings on the paper conform to
a process used by some of our suspects.
They were headed for Culver City.
Let's get somebody over there.
- Who?
- Who's in the area?
- The only one in that section is Roy Grothy.
- Good. Send him.
- George...
- What?
- That's who we sent to pick up Kim Bauer.
- He's idling over there. Kim's not around.
We promised Jack we'd take care of her.
Fine. We'll send a gofer until he gets back.
In the meantime, don't lose this window.
- Hey, cowboy.
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Joe.
- Joe?
Joseph Wald.
Sorry, man. I think you got the wrong place.
Hey, cowboy. I ain't got a whole lot of time.
Why don’t you tell Joe Jack's back in town,
see what he says?
Why don't I tell him, Jack?
Why don't I tell Joe Jack Roush is here?
He'd love to see the guy that put him in jail.
Hey, Eddie. I just came to square things up
with Joe. You know I didn't put him in jail.
Sure you didn't.
Get the back room ready.
Damm it, Eddie.
I got something I need to show Joe.
The only thing he's gonna
wanna see is you... dead.
What about Marshall Goren?
What about him?
Word on the street is that he turned
state's evidence, gonna put Joe away for life.
Go on, Eddie. Look in my bag.
- What for, Jack?
- Think of it as a present for Joe.
I told you, I wanted to
square things up with him.
Frank, give me that bag.
Just open it.
What the hell, Jack.
I don't think you gotta worry
about Goren testifying any more.
Jack's back.
Fortunately for me
the vice president arrived when he did.
We were both running out of small talk.
Mr President?
- Mr President?
- Jane.
We were told you were going fishing this
morning. What brought you back so early?
I already caught my quota. My conservation
policy is coming back to haunt me.
- Mr President...
- Look, let's not have so much fun all at once.
We're here for a couple of days.
I'll talk to you guys later.
- OK, what did Wieland want?
- I think he's putting it together, sir.
How can he? I just found out myself
less than an hour ago.
I'm sure he doesn't know the details,
but Wieland knows everyone
and they all owe him.
OK... Keep your eye on him for now.
If we go out of our way to put off the press,
they'll know something's up.
I agree.
- I have to get back to the OC.
- OK.
What's this?
- My head hurts.
- I know, Megan. We'll be there real soon.
- Where are we going?
- The police station.
You know what?
We're gonna go down this alley.
Do something, Kim.
Make him go away, please.
Where are you going with my daughter, Kim?
Huh? Where you gonna go?
Megan, honey, get out of the car.
Come to Daddy.
Do something.
Get out of the car.
Hurry!
Move! Move, move, move, move.
Kim!
Megan!
Megan, it's Daddy.
Listen to me, pal. Kim is gonna hurt you.
Megan, just call out to Daddy, OK?
I'll come get you.
Megan!
Don't get that stuff tangled. We won't have
time to separate them once we get there.
- Who's that?
- That's Jack.
Are you outta your mind
bringing him here today?
He used to work with us, Dave.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean, Eddie?
I used to work for Joe. I just did a nickel for
him up in Gainesville. That's what it means.
Oh-oh. Is that a fact?
And he happens to show up today
of all days? I'm not buying this, Eddie.
He did a solid for Joe.
He took care of Goren, Dave.
- Well, if he can get to Goren, he must be...
- Hey, Eddie.
Look, man, I just need to speak to Joe, OK?
Then I'm outta here.
- I hear you, Jack.
- If he's stayin', I'm checkin' him out.
- Don’t you have something to do, Dave?
- I'll bird-dog his records in two minutes.
Don’t you think it's worth two minutes
considering what's about to happen?
Check it out.
- Have a seat, Jack.
- OK.
- Jack what?
- Roush. R-o-u-s-h.
He's in. They just went online.
They're checking Jack's background.
Already?
The network addresses aren't ready.
Better send it to me now. Tony, did you
backfill those Gainesville end dates?
- Not yet.
- I need them now. They're looking for it.
- These guys don't waste time.
- I can't believe they got in so quickly.
- You want me to stuff some data in?
- They want this now.
I'm gonna forge their server portal
and hope they don't look too closely.
I'm not finding any
release documents on this guy.
What does that mean, Dave?
That means he's lying. That's what it means.
Keep lookin'.
Listen, Jack, if this time you did
in Gainesville doesn't check out,
I won't let you walk outta here.
It's gonna check out, Eddie.
Anything?
No.
Come on.
- Tony, I need it.
- OK, I got it. Hold on, hold on.
It's still looking.
Wait a second. I think I found it.
Yeah, here it is. It just took a little longer
to come up than I thought it would.
Told you it would check out.
You almost made me shoot a friend, Dave.
I'm sorry about that, Jack.
You still got that '64 Mustang?
No, the lawyers got that.
Eric.
Are we narrowing things down at all?
I mean, are we making any headway?
- It's too soon to tell.
- Too soon?
Aren't we assuming that this bomb
could go off at any moment?
What can I say? I've never been sanguine
about our chances of stopping it.
Not with just a few hours' warning.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- I'm not giving up, sir.
Every protocol is being followed,
every resource tapped.
But I would give serious thought to your plan
of action if in fact we have a detonation.
I still feel a discussion with the Pentagon
this morning is in order.
Fine. Thanks, Eric.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
I just spoke with Jenny.
I'm afraid we have a problem.
- What now?
- Ron Wieland.
He's convinced the network to give him
a 10-minute live report today at noon.
For what?
He's heard the alert condition has changed
and that you are managing a situation.
Damm it.
- He's going live based on what?
- Jenny doesn't know, sir.
But I'm assuming that he will avoid the facts
and present the rumour.
- I'm sorry, Lynne. I'm not mad at you.
- There's no need to apologise, sir.
How would you like to proceed?
Set up a private interview
in 10 minutes with Mr Wieland.
- The condition is no one's to know.
- Yes, sir.
And, Lynne...
Get Armus over here.
Yes, sir.
Hey, man. How you doing?
- Get the hell outta here.
- I just wanted to bum a smoke.
I don't smoke, so get out.
You're packing the fuses a little tight, sport.
What did you say?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
- Makin' friends, Jack?
- The guy's a moron.
- What did Joe say?
- Joe's busy. Maybe tomorrow, bro.
I just need to see him for five minutes.
We got this thing going down today, Jack,
so swing by tomorrow around four.
Yeah, OK. That's cool.
It's good to see you, man.
Good luck.
It's time, Dave.
- Mason.
- George, it's me.
- Did you get to Wald yet?
- Not yet. His crew are shutting me out.
- George, you gotta pick these guys up.
- Why?
They're packing charges. They're involved.
If we pick 'em up, are they
gonna lead us to Wald in time?
I don't know.
Well, stick with them until they do. NSA just
upgraded his probable role in today's threat.
Put him just a click away
from the Second Wave terrorists.
OK, I'll try and figure something out.
Damm it.
- Mr Mason?
- Yeah.
I've opened up that socket
to Division you asked for.
Thank you.
George, where are you going?
- Bakersfield.
- What for?
Following up on a lead. We're short-handed
today so I gotta cover it myself.
- Peter's assigned to Bakersfield.
- I put him on something else.
- What?
- I don't have to tell you that.
Well, I guess I disagree.
I mean, if you're just trying
to get outside the blast radius...
Who the hell do you think you are?
- Do you have access to my information?
- No, George, I don't.
Then keep your mouth shut and do your job.
Get down!
- I feel funny.
- What's wrong?
- My head hurts.
- Where?
Right there.
- Is that where you hit your head?
- I think so.
Honey, we can't stay here. I need to
make a phone call. You can rest then.
- No!
- Why not?
- I can't. My head really hurts...
- It's just over there. It'll be really quick.
Please, for me. You can do it.
- No, I can't. I don't feel good.
- OK, listen, listen. Shh...
We have to stay quiet, Megan.
What do you wanna do? Stay here? Yeah?
OK. But you have to wait.
You promise you'll stay here?
You promise?
We're gonna put you in these boxes.
I'll be right back.
- I don't want you moving.
- I won't.
I'm gonna be really quick.
Please, just don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
- This is Burton.
- Hi, it's Kate Warner.
- Did you get something for me?
- No, I couldn't get his wallet.
There are only a few things we can use
to check out his connection to this guy Ali.
- Actually, a passport would be ideal.
- I don't think he carries that around.
It's gotta be around somewhere.
Check his briefcase. Look in his car.
- Ralph, I can't just steal his passport.
- You won't have to.
Just write down the countries that have been
stamped for entry over the last six months.
Let me know, OK?
Kate!
- What are you doing?
- l, uh...
Craig said more vans were coming
and they needed the space.
- How you gonna drive it without the key?
- I was looking for it.
- Well, why didn’t you call me?
- You were busy.
I'm running for strawberries.
When I come back, I'll park on the other side.
Great.
What are you still doing here?
- My car won't start.
- Well, take a cab. Beat it.
You need to learn to mind your own business.
- Hey, Eddie.
- What?
I hope this job isn't too important.
Junior here packed your fuses too tight.
There's no way it'll blow. He's a joke.
See what I'm telling ya?
Agh!
Jack!
It's broken. He just broke my ankle.
- You broke his damn ankle, Jack.
- He shouldn't have been playing with adults.
This is the 911 emergency operator.
Please stay on the line.
Who are you calling, Kim? The police are
looking for you for kidnapping my daughter.
- Let go of me.
- All right. OK.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna hurt Megan. I promise.
I know it was wrong of me to push Carla,
but I have been under a lot of pressure lately.
You don't understand.
I'm not a bad person. OK?
You were right to take Megan away from that
situation. I would have done the same thing.
But, listen... I'm her father, OK?
I need to apologise to her and tell her
that she doesn't have to be afraid of me.
You understand that, right?
Yeah.
Where is she?
Why don’t you go home and talk to Carla?
If it's OK with her, I'll bring back Megan.
- You don't tell me what to do, OK?
- I'm not...
You don't tell me what to do.
Tell me where my daughter is!
Tell me where my daughter is, Kim!
Tell me!
And the last entry is Frankfurt, May 19th.
- Great. That's a big help.
- So what does that tell us?
We'll compare Reza's travel dates with Syed
Ali's. See if we can find a terrorist connection.
Um... OK. Yes, that would be great.
Thank you.
There's the bride.
Reza's parents are coming in early,
so I called Brent's and I ordered lunch.
- Good. I'll pick it up.
- OK. Thank you.
I finally feel like everything is under control.
- Kate...
- What?
- I never thanked you.
- For what?
For everything.
For being the maid of honour,
for helping me with the wedding,
for... being my big sister.
- Marie...
- I love you.
Oh, honey.
Oh, I love you too.
Now, get to work.
- Ron.
- Mr President.
Good to see you. Come in.
Please, sit down. Can I offer you anything?
Oh, no, thank you, sir.
I understand you're about
to go live with a story today.
Just what is it you think is going on?
I think the alert condition has been elevated
and you don't want us to know that, sir.
You think?
Do you want me to tell you my sources?
You know I can't do that.
You're barking up the wrong tree, Ron.
I don't recall the last time a journalist
got a private interview with the president
on a few minutes' notice.
So... my 22 years in the business
tells me I'm barking up the right tree.
I tell you what, Ron.
There's gonna be a briefing tomorrow.
If you want a 30-minute jump, I can arrange it.
Why are you horse-trading with me?
Because if you go live with a story
about unsubstantiated threats,
you will cause mass hysteria.
- That could be worse than the threat itself.
- So there is a threat.
Ron... we get them every day.
So you want me to sit on this,
even though it's my professional right
to take what I've got on the air?
Ron, you know me.
I've been more forthcoming with the press
and public than any politician you know.
So when I ask you for a favour, I do it in the
spirit of what's best for the American people.
- Let me think about it.
- Fair enough.
- Thank you, Mr President.
- Thank you, Ron.
- Armus.
- Yes, sir.
- I think we're gonna have to deal with this.
Mr Wieland, I'm Richard Armus. I'm with
the president's Secret Service Blue Unit.
There's something the president
wants you to see before you go.
- It won't take more than a few minutes.
- Let go of my arm.
You haven't changed much, have you, Jack?
- What's your point?
- I'm short a man and I'm on a schedule.
I'm looking for work.
This isn't a job. You're gonna
do this for nothing, Jack.
My price is a thousand a day.
Well, Jack, I'd say you owe me a bit more
than that for what you did to Dave.
You do this, I don't tell Joe.
You don't do it, you'll be too busy
lookin' over your shoulder to find work.
- What's the job?
- You're gonna like it.
Megan...
Megan. Megan!
Megan! Megan!
Megan!
No! Megan! No!
Megan! Megan!
Yeah, we're right on schedule.
We'll talk to you in about an hour.
All right, that's great. Rock out.
- Where are we goin'?
- West LA.
- What are we doin'?
- A conversion.
What do you mean?
Well, today we're turning
a government building into a cemetery.
- Which building?
- A branch that's been dogging us for years.
They call it the LA Counter Terrorist Unit -
the CTU.
Good.
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Emery
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net