There's no chance that this bomb
is ever gonna go off
with a Special Ops team
following it every step of the way.
Jack Bauer found
the Coral Snake commandos.
All six members of the team had been killed.
If there's something
that you haven't told me...
Ask Sherry.
She's the one you wanna talk to.
My father works for the government.
He said someone's gonna detonate
a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles today.
- I'm gonna show you something.
- What is it?
It's a bomb shelter.
- It happened.
- The bomb went off?
The radiation. We gotta get
down below, before it's too late.
- Hello?
- There has been a change of plans.
Why? What's going on?
Marie, our mission depends on you now.
I'm counting on you.
They're a rogue unit,
acting on their own authority.
- How do I find them?
- Somewhere at the airport.
Our best bet is still you
getting past them to the bomb.
There is a nuclear warhead
somewhere on-site.
There it is! Go, go!
Put your hands above your head!
Keep 'em there!
This isn't a bomb.
It's been rigged to look like one.
This is not the bomb. This is a decoy.
I repeat: we are still looking
for the nuclear device.
OK, let's go easy with this.
Go.
You have to process the prints here.
Bring in your mobile equipment.
You! Where's the real bomb?
Where's the real bomb?
Do you understand me?
Do you speak any English?
- Search him. I'll get us a translator.
- Yes, sir.
This is Jack Bauer requesting
a translator in hangar 21.
I repeat: I am requesting
Mr Mason, Jack Bauer is on line two.
Good.
- George.
- How's the search going over there, Jack?
Still no new leads on where the bomb is.
What about that plane
you found the decoy in?
It's clean. Use reverse-time satellite to
trace the plane to its original location.
That's where they would've loaded
the decoy. Find out who the players are.
Here and here.
George? You with me?
George, can you hear me?
Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- George!
Yeah, I'm on it! Reverse-time satellite. Yeah.
I'm really sorry about everything
that's happened to you today.
But if you can't think clearly, you need
to let someone else take over command.
- There isn't anybody else, Jack.
- What about Tony?
I got it together. I can handle it. All right?
Yeah, OK.
- We do have another problem.
- What?
The six dead commandos you found,
turns out a seventh may have escaped.
I examined all the gunshot wounds.
Three of the commandos knew the shooter -
their wounds were at close range.
The others showed signs of a struggle,
which indicates they had time to react.
- So the seventh didn't escape.
- Right. He was a shooter.
I gotta go. Get me an ID on the seventh
commando as soon as you can.
- I'm working on it.
- Good.
- What do you got?
- A wallet, no ID, no credit cards.
He wants to talk.
Where the hell is my translator?
Mr Warner, it's your daughter Kate.
- Kate?
- Dad?
- Kate, where are you?
- I'm fine. I'm at an airport.
The airport? Are you leaving the city?
Not yet. I'm helping one of
the agents on an investigation.
Dad... did they tell you about Reza?
Yeah, I... I can't believe
what they're saying about Marie,
that she's with these terrorists,
that she killed Reza. I...
I know, Dad.
- Kate...
- Dad, hold on a second.
It wasn't the bomb. We arrested the pilot.
I need you as a translator.
Dad, I'm gonna have to call you back.
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine. Dad, I love you.
I love you, too, sweetheart.
- What exactly did Roger Stanton tell you?
- Sherry was somehow involved in this.
- The nuclear threat?
- He didn't elaborate.
That's all he said.
They said it was urgent.
Is it about the bomb? Have they found it?
Not yet. Sit down.
I just spoke with Stanton. He confesses
that he's known about the bomb for weeks.
For weeks? Why would he
withhold that from you?
He wanted to wait until the bomb was
on US soil before he intercepted it.
- So he knows where the bomb is.
- The men he had tracking it did.
But they're all dead. The bomb's still
out there, and we don't know where it is.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Am I telling you something
you already know?
- What?
- Tell me now.
Have you done the unthinkable and put
yourself in league with Roger Stanton?
That's outrageous! Of course not!
What did he say?
Sit down.
- David...
- Sit down!
He said you were involved,
working against me.
He's lying, David! I never even met
Roger Stanton until this afternoon!
- That's not true.
- He's playing you!
Whatever he's doing,
he wants you to believe I...
Just stop it!
Sherry... right now we are
teetering on the brink of a war
that will lead to the deaths
of millions of people.
We have to stop this disaster today,
right now, before it begins.
If there is something you're not telling me,
anything that could help us find this bomb,
as President of the United States,
I order you...
No, as someone that you claim you love...
I'm asking: help me, Sherry.
I got a phone call... a few months ago
in the middle of the night
from a friend of mine who's high up in NSA.
He told me that Roger Stanton wanted
to speak to me first thing in the morning,
and so we met at a park in Virginia.
What did he want?
- He wanted to recruit me.
- To do what?
He wanted to know who was loyal
to you and who could be turned.
He wanted... He wanted to
know where you were weak.
And you told him?
Yes.
But I only did it to gain his confidence.
I was not aligning myself with him.
I was doing it for you.
David, I know you don't believe me,
but just give me 30 minutes
to prove to you that I'm telling the truth,
that I did all of this to protect you,
not to hurt you.
I think he's saying he did it for his family.
They promised him money.
Ask him who "they" is.
Syed Ali.
Ask him if he knows about a second bomb.
Eh?
I don't think that was right.
I think we have different dialects.
It doesn't matter. Just keep trying.
Jack, the translator's here.
Jack Bauer.
The subject's there. Kate?
- I'm really sorry, Jack.
- You did great. You did great.
Agent Baker will take you back to
the controlled area. I'll be there soon.
Ask him if he knows about a second bomb.
He said he doesn't know anything.
ID, please. Can I see your ID?
Who are those people over there?
They're locking down the airport, checking
everyone. Excuse me for one second.
Ask him where he went to school
and the name of his sponsor.
I can't believe the bomb went off.
What did you hear? How many people?
I don't know.
The transmission just went dead.
Are you gonna be OK?
My dad, I need to get in touch with my dad.
We will. But for right now, we have
to stay down here, where it's safe.
We have no idea which way
that radiation cloud is gonna travel.
I'll see if I can pick something up
on the short-wave radio, OK?
...LA's favourite all-talk radio
all the time, 24-7.
The school voucher debate is really
beginning to heat up again here...
What did they say?
The radiation is interfering with the antenna.
It could be hours before
we're able to pick up anything.
What's gonna happen to us?
- Shh, it's OK.
- I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
You got nothing to be scared of.
We're safe down here. I promise.
You must be the new assistant Division sent.
Carrie Turner. You must be George Mason.
Excuse me...
You look worse than I expected.
- Is there something I can help you with?
- No, I'm set.
I've been following everything from Division.
I'll be taking over from Paula,
so if there's anything you need
the server to do, I'll make it happen.
Good. The situation reports
have changed in the past hour,
so you have to refresh
all the computer monitors.
No problem. Just make sure everyone
keeps their hands off my system.
OK.
Mr Mason... who do I report to... directly?
You report to me.
No offence, Mr Mason, but rumour has it
you're not gonna be around much longer.
So... who do I report to?
I finally get someone around here who I like,
and I'm not gonna be around to enjoy it.
Tony Almeida.
And Michelle D-Dessler.
- Did you say Michelle Dessler?
- Yes, I did. Why?
We worked together at District.
I was her boss then.
And you're telling me this why?
It'll be fine. It's not important.
Mr Mason?
My God. Mr Mason? Mr Mason!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Picture ID?
- Thank you for your cooperation.
We will try to get you out of here
as quickly as we can.
Arms straight out.
Just stand perfectly still.
Prepare to give the scanners any
metal objects in your pockets beforehand.
It will speed the process through the line.
- Marie!
- No need to be concerned.
Please just cooperate. We appreciate it.
- Whoa, excuse me. You can't go there.
- What?
Everyone is searched before they're let go.
- It's my sister. It's important.
- Sorry.
Wait, here. I'm with Jack Bauer, CTU.
- OK. Go on.
- Thanks.
Could you get in touch with Jack Bauer?
Tell him Marie Warner is here.
He'll understand.
Dispatch, we need to locate
a Jack Bauer with CTU.
Copy that.
- Marie.
- I need your badge, Kate.
Where've you been?
- Give me your badge.
- Marie...
Shut up. You stupid idiot.
Why did you have to start snooping around?
What's going on?
You have always treated me like
I was some helpless injured animal.
Like I couldn't get by
without you looking over me.
What happened to you?
I opened my eyes.
That's what happened to me.
I was pathetic, just like you.
Until I met Syed.
Until I saw the lies and hypocrisy
of my life, of this country,
of people like Dad, who help the
government. He works for the CIA.
I know. So what?
So what? Do you have any idea the
suffering they cause around the world?
Oh, please. What are you, six years old?
You think Dad is the enemy now?
I can't believe how ungrateful you are.
I should be grateful?
Yeah, absolutely. Dad and I turned our lives
upside down for you after Mom died.
This is what we did it for? So you could
be brainwashed by some lunatic?
Wake up! You're about to become
the biggest murderer in American history!
- What are you gonna do?
- Give me your badge.
No.
Fine.
Marie, listen to me.
There's a nuclear bomb in the city.
No matter what you believe, you don't
want all those innocent people to die.
Give me the badge.
No. I don't believe you'd shoot me.
I will... because this is
more important than your life.
Or my life.
Kate, stay down!
- Stay down!
- My arm!
Secure the weapon!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I take it that's your sister.
At least give her something for the pain.
- I will when she tells us what she knows.
- You can't let her suffer.
You're gonna have to let me do this
my way. You have to trust me.
I know you love her.
But I have to worry about
the millions of lives at stake.
She is the only person
who knows where this bomb is.
I need to use every advantage I've got
to find it and stop it.
Surely you understand that.
Just let me do this.
Give me your arm.
Where's the bomb, Marie? The real bomb.
You can go to hell, you bastard.
I'm not telling you anything.
You wanna know why the pain's so severe?
The bullet's still in your arm,
lodged against the bone.
Tell me where the bomb is, and I'll get you
something for the pain and treat your arm.
Please, Marie, just talk to me.
Just talk to me. Tell me where the bomb is.
No!
I know you think what you’re doing now
will further your cause.
Deep down, I don't think
you wanna go through with it.
I don't think you can justify killing
millions of innocent civilians.
Nobody's innocent in this country.
I'm not afraid to die.
I don't believe you. I've seen
people who are willing to die.
I've looked them straight in the eye,
just like right now.
You're not one of them.
I wanna give you a painkiller,
but you must help me first.
Please tell me where the bomb is.
Where's the bomb?
I'm gonna check the radio.
Do you have any sugar?
Yeah, yeah, it's in the back corner,
on the shelf there.
Is the TV hooked up to the same antenna?
Everyone can take out their golf clubs...
...delivery is... Swung on.
...prominent civic leaders
and Hollywood stars...
...record numbers today gathered at beaches
to celebrate the beautiful
weather of California,
which will continue throughout the weekend.
Still nothing.
- This is our man?
- Yeah.
Seventh commando.
Captain Jonathan Wallace.
Led a sniper unit in the Gulf War,
led an assassination detail in Malaysia.
- Have you got this to Jack?
- I'm on it.
Start up a shared volume with OC on this guy.
Hello, Michelle.
- Carrie, what are you doing here?
- Division sent me over to replace Paula.
Right. Do you need help getting into any
of the locked volumes on the network?
No, actually. I'm all up and running.
You look great, by the way.
- Stop it, Carrie.
- Stop what?
You're not my boss today, all right?
If you're here to replace Paula,
then technically you work for me.
Fine. Give me an order.
There's a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles.
We've been charged with finding it.
So why don’t you start by analysing these?
Fine.
- Tony, do you have a second?
- Sure.
What is it?
I think it's time I step down.
I'm not feeling so hot here.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Actually, yeah.
Tomorrow, when this is all over,
say goodbye to everybody for me
and let them know what an honour
it was working with them
and what a great job I think
they all did, everybody.
Sure.
This morning when I told you
I couldn't wait to get out of here...
I don't feel that way any more.
- Here you go.
- What's this?
Access codes for the CTU and Division.
I can't take this, George. Only the CTU
director is allowed that kind of access.
You're the new CTU director, Tony.
You can't promote me, George.
Only Chappelle can do that.
I just talked to Chappelle.
You're the new guy.
Listen, George... I'm sorry, I...
Hey, don't.
Good luck.
I'll be operating from up here,
so I'll need my access codes
piped into the system.
Got it. Everyone's ready.
Good. Thanks.
In case you haven't heard,
George Mason was exposed to a lethal
dose of plutonium this morning.
I'm afraid he hasn't got much time.
He just left the office and won't come back,
which means that I'll be in charge
until further notice.
Now, on a normal day,
we'd be mourning George,
just like we would've
mourned Ivers and Clark
and Paula and the rest of our co-workers
who were killed here today.
Unfortunately, we have to
hold our thoughts of them
until we can get through this present crisis.
So... let's get back to work.
Tony.
- It was a nice thing you just did.
- What's going on at the airfield?
Jack's still interrogating Marie Warner.
We don't have anything new.
- All right. Keep me posted.
- Sure.
Stay with me, Marie. Stay with me.
Steve, walk with me.
Get her Demerol for the pain.
She's going into shock. I need her lucid.
- For how long?
- Five minutes should do it.
- Kate.
- Yeah.
- What did she say?
- She hasn't said anything yet.
- I'm gonna need your help.
- Help? How?
You're her sister.
I need you to bring her back to reality.
You know her like that. I don't.
I thought I did. She's a different person
from the Marie I knew this morning.
No, Kate. She's the same girl
you grew up with.
She's just regurgitating everything
Syed Ali taught her.
I need you to remind her of
the things she used to love.
You can do this, Kate. You can get to her.
All right.
She's going to be a little groggy
because of the painkiller, OK?
You all right?
Yeah.
Hey, Marie.
Hi, Kate.
Get away. I don't need you.
- Why won’t you help us?
- I am gonna help you.
I'm gonna help you stop
being a part of the problem.
So it's OK with you if Dad and I died today?
I killed Reza. And I loved him.
Why would I care about you and Dad?
Because we care for you.
Because we love you.
Why are you doing this?
Marie, you could save everyone.
You could stop this terrible thing
from happening.
I don't want to. I can't.
Marie, I'm begging you. Please.
No.
My arm... God!
Kate, I need you to step back.
That's the Demerol wearing off. Tell me
where the bomb is, and I'll get you more.
Please tell me where the bomb is.
Marie, just tell him, please.
- Where is the bomb?
- Give her something for the pain.
No, no.
Marie, please. Tell me where the bomb is.
Where is the bomb?
- Katie, make him stop!
- No, Marie.
You make him stop.
The pain will get worse.
Just tell me where the bomb is.
It's all right. Just tell me where the bomb is.
In the suitcase.
Where's the suitcase?
- In the van.
- What van?
Where was the van headed?
- Downtown.
- Where downtown?
At the Arco Towers.
What kind of van was it?
What colour? What make?
Uh... green. I don't know what make.
We're looking for a green van.
The nuke may be inside.
- Send a team down to the Arco.
- When is the bomb set to go off?
- Three hours.
- How do you know that?
- I saw the timer.
- Describe it.
- What?
- The timer. Describe it.
I don't...
You're lying to me. A bomb that size
wouldn't have a visual timer.
I'm not lying. It's at the Arco Towers.
Send them all downtown now.
Why now? What's the hurry? I thought I had
three hours. You told me I had three hours.
No, I'm not lying!
Why do you want me and my team
to leave here so fast?
The bomb's still here, isn't it, Marie?
No.
Yes, it is.
Teams A and B, do a grid search
on every outbuilding at the airport,
starting north, heading south.
The bomb is on-site.
I repeat: the bomb is on-site.
Oh, Marie.
They're not gonna find it in time.
We're all gonna die.
I'll sleep on the floor. You can have my bed.
Mr President, your call's ready.
Steve Hillenburg at Langley.
Yes, a CIA operative.
He's on an isolated feed.
Nobody else knows about this
but the three of you.
- Sherry's waiting.
- Good. Thanks.
- Hello, Steve.
- Mr President.
What's your involvement in this?
I got a call from Sherry
about four months ago.
She told me Roger Stanton was trying
to recruit her in an effort to
undermine your presidency.
She wanted an independent source
to confirm that she was doing it to help you.
So you've been building
a case against Stanton
for the last four months
without my knowledge.
Plausible deniability, sir.
What we were doing was illegal,
but... we felt it was necessary.
It could've backfired and landed
Sherry and me in prison.
We didn't want this to touch you
if that happened.
OK, let's say I accept that.
What proof do you have
that exonerates Sherry?
I have photographs, taped
conversations, debriefs,
files filled with the work Sherry did.
These meetings that Sherry and Roger had,
where'd they take place?
Sherry?
Um...
For the first month, we met
at a hotel in Hilton Head.
- I didn't sleep with him.
- I didn't ask.
Thank you. I'll contact you
if I need anything else.
Thank you, sir.
You know, I don't care what
you think of me right now.
The most important thing is that you
realise that I never, and I mean never,
was a part of Stanton's conspiracy.
You know what, Sherry?
You might be telling me the truth.
Then again, you might not.
Right now, I don't have the time or energy
to figure out whether I can trust you.
You have to trust me, David.
Your presidency is in jeopardy and
so is this country. Let me help you.
No. You'll leave now.
David... you need me.
If you resist in any way, I'll have no choice
but to place you under arrest.
- Yes, sir?
- Please escort Mrs Palmer to her car.
We got a ventilation system in here
and an air supply, but it still stays cold.
But don't worry because
we got tons of blankets.
- You tired?
- I'm OK.
You're still worried about
your family, aren’t you?
Try not to think about them too much.
You're probably right.
- So, did you grow up in LA?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah? Me too. What part?
- We moved around a lot.
My foot is still hurting.
Do you have any aspirin?
Yeah, yeah, sure. I got tons.
You're gonna let me out of here right now.
I know the bomb didn't go off.
- Kim...
- Stay away!
OK, it's OK. Just calm down.
- I wasn't gonna hurt you.
- Then let me go!
- I just wanted some company, that's all.
- Then what are you doing out here?
This is where I belong.
I don't.
- I want you to stay.
- I don't wanna stay.
Why not?
What's wrong with me?
I'm not good enough?
- It has nothing to do with you.
- Then why?
You think I'm psycho?
I don't know if you're psycho.
I don't even know you.
Wouldn’t you rather be with
someone who wants to be here?
You don't even wanna get to know me?
Please let me out of here, Lonnie.
Please.
- Here.
- What?
Take it.
There's cougars out there. If you see one,
fire a shot in the air and they'll take off.
Turn right out the front door.
About 200 yards away, you'll see a deer trail.
That'll lead you to the highway.
Thank you.
Kim?
Maybe you'll come back sometime?
I don't think so.
Goodrich, what's going on?
All agents, one hostile down!
Go, go, go!
Over here!
Let's go! Bring 'em in!
- What do we got?
- It's nuclear.
And there's the trigger. This is it.
This is Jack Bauer. We found the bomb.
Initiate a level-one local evac now.
- It's armed.
- How much time have we got?
I can't tell. Could be any second.
Visiontext Subtitles: Tram Nguyen Zelniker
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net