Jim, we both know that you've been
one of the most outspoken opponents
to my decision to call off this attack.
If you have something to say, I would
expect you to bring it to me first.
Does the president have
any idea what's going on?
- I don't think so.
- Let's keep it that way.
Thank you for assembling
at such short notice.
I'm sure you're all wondering
why I've invited you here.
It is my sincere belief, based on
his response to today's events,
David Palmer is unfit to continue
as President of the United States.
Looks like you've had quite a day.
- I didn't kill anyone.
- I know you didn't.
We know Gary Matheson killed his wife.
We're looking for him now.
So you're off the hook for everything
that happened this morning.
I thought I made myself clear, Tony.
We're past Bauer.
No, sir. You are. I'm not.
Now, if you're not comfortable with
me making my own decisions here,
I suggest you relieve me
of my duties right now.
That won't be necessary.
- Thank you, sir.
- Don't thank me.
I just don't have anyone
to take your place right now.
- No!
- Come on, give me that!
- Kate, are you all right?
- Yeah. They've got the chip!
All I want is the chip!
You come in here, I'm gonna smash
this thing. I'll put it right under my foot!
- Tell me who I'm speaking to.
- It doesn't matter.
We got something your girlfriend
was about to pay us for.
Listen to me.
Five hours ago, a nuclear bomb
went off. I'm sure you know.
The chip will show who's responsible.
It's vital to our investigation.
The man you assaulted was an agent
bringing the chip to my office.
Give me the chip back,
and I'll let you walk, no questions.
- You're setting us up.
- Get back.
What are you doing? They killed Yusuf.
We're about to attack
three innocent countries.
I can only stop it with that chip, so I'm
gonna do everything I can to get it back.
Please, Kate, I need your help.
Get in touch with CTU. Please!
You have 30 seconds to open that door.
- Give it to him.
- Are you crazy?
This is the only thing
keeping him from killing us.
You got 20 seconds!
- We should trust you?
- You don't have a choice.
- Give it to him. He's serious!
- So am I.
He's gonna kill us if we don't open the door.
Against the wall! Now! Where's the chip?
I dropped it.
Don't move.
Kate! Kate!
I need wire to tie them up.
- What about the chip?
- I've got it.
Just got this Pentagon briefing stating that
our bombers aren't going back to their bases.
Do you know about this?
I understand they're holding,
awaiting refuelling.
I ordered them back to their bases.
I know. That's why I'm here.
Could you come with me for a minute?
- Come with you where?
- To the main conference room.
What's going on, Mike?
Please, Mr President, come with me.
You're ordering me
to the conference room?
No, sir, of course not. I'm sorry.
I'm... asking. It's very important, sir.
Mike, I'm the President of the United States.
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me what this is about.
Mr President...
it seems there are a number
of people, cabinet members,
who question whether you're fit to continue
as chief executive of this country.
And these people are
in my conference room?
In a manner of speaking, sir, they are.
Then let's go see them.
Mr President.
So now I see why I had such a hard time
reaching you today, Jim.
You were busy.
I apologise if this comes
as a surprise, Mr President.
This is a unique situation
in the history of our country,
calling for unique measures.
Let's skip the sound bites
and cut to the chase.
What's going on here?
Mr President, we are invoking
the 25th Amendment.
Who's "we"?
There's a general feeling that
the decisions made today...
Hold on a minute, Mr Vice President.
With all due respect, sir,
most of us here are scrambling
just to understand today's events.
I think it's way too early to be referring
to a "general feeling" about anything.
Fair enough. For the record,
let me review the relevant portions
of the 25th Amendment.
If the vice president and the majority of the
cabinet determine that the president is unable
to discharge the powers
and duties of his office,
the vice president shall take office
as acting president. Everyone clear?
The 25th Amendment was
designed for situations
where the president is ill or incapacitated.
"Unable to discharge the powers
and duties of his office."
The reason for the disability
isn't limited to any cause.
The Attorney General agrees
with this interpretation.
And just what exactly is
my supposed disability?
It seems clear to me that the stress of
today's events has overwhelmed you.
An atomic device has been
detonated on American soil today.
We have clear evidence
which countries are responsible,
along with details of
the terrorist group they sponsor.
The evidence implicating these countries
is not clear, Mr Prescott. Far from it.
The Cyprus audio has been independently
verified by every intelligence group we have.
I have reason to believe they are mistaken.
Because of this lone CTU agent, Jack Bauer?
Yes. Mr Bauer believes that
the Cyprus audio is a forgery.
He also believes that he will soon have proof.
He's been telling you that for hours,
Mr President. You still don't have proof.
If military strikes do not go ahead,
casualties to American soldiers would
increase by tens of thousands of lives.
That analysis is undisputed.
The risk of attacking innocent countries
is unacceptable. We have to be sure.
Everybody is sure, Mr President.
Everybody but you.
As it happens, I'm the only who counts.
This meeting is over.
Mr President, one way or another,
there will be a vote.
I think that you should be heard
before that vote is taken.
You don't like one of my policy decisions.
You do not have the right to reverse that
policy under the pretence that I'm disabled.
Mr President, I agree.
I intend to show a pattern of erratic
and irrational behaviour on your part
since the start of this crisis.
In that light, your refusal
to authorise military action
is simply another symptom of disability.
Listen to me. All of you.
I know you're not in the same room with me.
But you can see and hear me plainly enough.
Take a good look.
Do I seem scared?
Am I breaking into a nervous sweat?
Am I babbling? At a loss for words?
Is my voice shaking?
Can any one of you look me in the eye
and tell me I'm disabled?
Mr President, the issue is not your
demeanour over the past few minutes,
but your actions over the past 20 hours.
Mr President, the vice president
has raised serious questions
and, in my opinion, it would
be a mistake to ignore them.
For my part, I'm confident that if you explain
yourself with your usual candour and clarity,
all questions will be resolved
to the satisfaction of everyone here.
Mr Prescott, there seems to be a collective
feeling that a discussion is called for.
In the interest of putting this
behind us, I'll agree.
On one condition:
when it's over, if I'm supported,
you tender your resignation as
the vice president of this country.
Very well, Mr President. I agree.
I suggest we all take a few minutes
to compose ourselves
and get on with the proceeding.
Let's not mince words, Mr Secretary.
You mean the trial of David Palmer.
All right, the problem is that
they don't correspond. I need them to.
Ryan, could I have a word with you, please?
Give me a minute.
I just got a message that the president
called off the military offensive.
- Who told you this?
- Someone at DOJ.
- Someone I trust.
- I wouldn't worry about it.
Is it true?
- Yes.
- And you knew about it.
- I did.
- And you didn't tell me.
Why keep my people processing
intel on a scrapped operation?
Because there's a strong possibility
the White House will reinstate the attack.
It doesn't make sense. Why would
the president reverse his orders twice?
Just keep your people on a war footing.
Tony, phones are up.
I got Jack Bauer on line two.
- Where is he?
- Kate's house.
- Why?
- I don't know, but he has the chip.
Conference-call him to my office.
Why are you at Kate's house?
You were supposed to bring that chip here.
We ran into some interference.
Yusuf Auda is dead.
- What happened?
- No time to explain.
He's the only reason we still got this chip.
I'm trying to read it now.
I tried a flash card adapter,
but it's not working.
You may be able to override the reader
function manually. I'll talk you through it.
Good. Tony, while she's setting up,
run a background check on Peter Kingsley.
It may be an alias. Cross-reference it
with every major player in the oil industry.
- Peter Kingsley. Why?
- I'll explain later.
First tell the president that
we've got the evidence he needs.
I told him. I found out he's
called off the military strikes.
Then we've got time.
Not necessarily.
Chappelle said the order may be reversed.
Why?
He didn't get specific,
but something's going on
in Washington that
we're not supposed to know about.
- Michelle, are you ready for me?
- Yeah.
I've asked someone to join us.
Most of you know Ron Wieland.
Ron is a highly respected
national affairs correspondent.
He had a very interesting
experience earlier today. Ron?
I was covering Mr Palmer's environmental
speech when I began to sense a bigger story.
There were rumours of a terrorist attack on
the West Coast, involving a nuclear device.
I kept asking questions. Next thing I know,
I was called in to talk to the president.
He asked me to keep the story under wraps
until later, then he'd give me an exclusive.
- What did you say?
- That I'd think it over.
As I was leaving, a secret service agent
grabbed me and hustled me into a room.
I was kept there under guard
for several hours.
Did you feel this was a violation of your
rights as a journalist and an American?
Of course.
- Ron, were you harmed or threatened?
- No, sir.
Did you understand the reason
for your being detained?
I assume it was fear that if word got out
of a nuclear threat, panic would strike.
Do you think the lives of thousands
of citizens is less important
than a couple of hours of
your First Amendment rights?
No, I don't. But under the Bill of Rights,
that decision was mine,
not yours, Mr President.
Did you feel that things were out of control
in the Palmer administration?
You're putting words in his mouth.
I did sense the president was not in control.
I was trying to balance the need for public
safety against Ron Wieland's rights.
I offered Ron a deal, and he turned me down.
Nothing was out of control. I might add,
I had legal precedent for my action.
Thank you, Mr Wieland.
I'd like to call someone else to testify.
He should be ready in a few moments.
Control CX-5, then hit "enter".
- Done.
- Anything?
I think it's reading it... No, all I'm
getting are numbers and symbols.
Take out the chip.
Make sure the leads are exposed.
- Damn it!
- What is it?
- The chip is damaged.
- How badly?
Part of the microprocessor is gone
and the leads connected to it.
Send me any data you have
to run through our retrieval program.
Can you access a complete audio file?
If it's on there, I'll find it.
- IT.
- This is Almeida.
- Send two guys up here.
- They're all doing MI for Chappelle.
I don't care. I need two IT people now.
- Chappelle specifically...
- Just do it. I gotta go.
Almeida.
Tony, hi, it's Kim. Look, I haven't been
able to reach my dad. Is he available?
We're in the middle of something important.
Can he call you back?
Tony, please. It'll just take a minute.
OK. OK, just hold on.
Are you getting it?
Yeah, I got it, but you were right -
the data is pretty screwed.
I've assigned two IT people to help Michelle.
We should get through it in 15, 20 minutes.
- OK, good.
- Also, I got Kim on the line for you.
Thank you, Tony.
Kim, I got your dad on the line. Go ahead.
- Dad?
- Sweetheart.
- I've been trying to reach you.
- Are you at the sheriffs station?
They're taking me to the Mathesons' house
to pack up my things.
Glad you're OK.
Me too.
When I thought you were gone, I...
I just miss you, Dad. I miss you so much.
I've missed you too, honey.
I just wanna come home.
You'll be home soon enough, I promise, OK?
OK. Hey, Dad?
- Yeah?
- I love you.
I love you too, baby.
I'll see you soon, OK?
Bye.
You knew about this, didn’t you, Mike?
How long have you known?
- That doesn't matter, Mr Palmer.
- It matters to me.
How long?
A couple of hours.
You were part of it, weren’t you?
When all's said and done...
you were on Prescott's side.
No, sir. I'm on your side and always will be.
This could be a good thing.
A chance to correct a mistake
of historic proportion.
David, I'm begging you,
reconsider your position on this.
I'm the president, Mike.
You don't call me by my first name.
Yes, sir.
It's transmitting.
Gentlemen, I'm sorry for the delay.
The man you're about to see
is not entirely well.
In fact, it's taken a great deal of
courage for him to join us at all.
Roger Stanton, head of
the National Security Agency.
Roger, thank you for speaking with us.
Yes, of course. Sorry if I seem a bit tired.
I was tortured for several hours
at the operations complex,
by order of the President of the United States.
And why were you tortured?
Because you thought I knew more than I
was saying about the location of the bomb.
As if the head of NSA would withhold
information from the president.
You're lying. This may work for a while,
but eventually the truth will come out.
I have nothing to fear
from the truth, Mr President.
As briefly as possible, Mr Stanton,
tell us what happened to you today.
I arrived at the OC around noon to find
that my assistant director, Eric Rayburn,
had been dismissed by the president.
What was the reason given
for Mr Rayburn's firing?
Eric wanted to bring the military into
the equation right away, and the president
was reluctant to even contemplate
the use of military action.
That's not true.
For the next few hours, I worked
for the president as best I could.
He was indecisive, erratic and, as I said,
terrified to even think of military engagement.
A little after six this evening,
I was arrested on the charge of treason.
I was taken to a small windowless room.
The president accused me of knowing
more about the bomb than I was telling him.
- Was that true?
- No, of course not.
In fairness to the president, I think
he genuinely believed it to be true.
Why would he hold such a belief?
David Palmer is a decent man.
Maybe he's too decent for the times we live in.
He wanted to avoid war at any cost.
If he could prove to himself that
Americans were behind the bomb,
then he'd have a good reason not to use
military force against any foreign country.
I just heard you ordered two ITs
onto a retrieval project.
They were working military intel.
Jack Bauer has a chip.
It contains an audio file that we expect
will prove the Cyprus audio was forged.
Where is this chip?
- It's been damaged.
- Damaged?
The data Jack sent us is messed up.
The audio file has to be
reconstituted. That takes time.
- How long?
- However long it takes.
It should take about 15 minutes, sir.
Mr Chappelle's office.
- Get a message to the vice president.
- Right away, sir.
Ready to tell me
everything I need to know?
Continue.
We knew about the bomb weeks ago.
Enough!
This should end this discussion
here and now.
Yes, I had Roger Stanton tortured.
It was a horrible thing to do.
God knows I hated doing it.
But just as I suspected,
he knew about the bomb.
You've just seen that.
When I was strapped to a chair
and thousands of volts of electric current
passed through my body every few seconds,
I'm not proud of it, but I dare say I did what
most of you would've done - I cracked.
Told the president what he wanted
to hear, that I knew about the bomb.
You told me more than that.
You told me about the Coral Snake team.
You told me that the bomb was at Norton
Airfield, information that we corroborated.
I don't know what you’re talking about.
Mr Prescott, play the rest of the tape.
There is no rest of the tape.
- What?
- That's all I have.
That can't be. I was in that room
for another ten minutes.
This is all that was transmitted by the OC.
We did ask for everything.
There must be a mistake,
or deliberate sabotage.
Mr Stanton had a lot more to say
than what you just saw.
Mr President, couldn't Agent Simmons
verify what you’ve been telling us?
No. I sent him out of the room.
But the fact remains that Roger Stanton
told me about the Coral Snake team
and the location of the bomb. Where else
could that information have come from?
We have many intelligence
agencies, Mr President,
thousands of agents combing the planet.
It could've come from anywhere.
I know it didn't come from me.
That's a lie and you know it. Tell them, Mike.
I only know what the president told me.
I wasn't in the room.
Mr Stanton, thank you again.
You will remain in custody as the president
has ordered until this matter is resolved.
I understand.
Mr President, if you have any evidence
you'd like to present, please do so now.
The testimony that's been presented here
so far is inaccurate and incomplete.
Roger Stanton is directly responsible
for placing a nuclear weapon on US soil.
I have evidence that proves it,
but you’ve given me no time.
While my behaviour may have been extreme,
I was just responding to
the extremity of today's events.
Make no mistake. If we unleash our military
power on nations that later prove innocent,
it will rank as one of the most
despicable sneak attacks in history.
Any chance for peace in the Middle East
will vanish forever.
Even if it costs American lives in the future,
we must delay the attack
until we are certain of our ground.
Excuse me.
I just received an urgent message
from CTU division chief Ryan Chappelle.
Jack Bauer has evidence he claims
will prove the Cyprus audio was forged.
Please, everyone... Sh. Please settle down.
The evidence is being reviewed at CTU now.
Mr Chappelle says that the analysis shall
be complete within the next few minutes.
Considering the impact that this evidence
will have on these proceedings,
I think it's incumbent upon us to wait.
- I'm looking at it right now.
- We can't configure it, either.
- Did you run it through default mode?
- The audio files are gone.
They're just some markers that repeat.
- Thanks, Jason.
- All right.
He didn't find anything, either.
Well, what have you got?
The chip was more compromised
than we thought.
- Do you have the audio file?
- Michelle recovered some information.
It may tell us who programmed it.
Did you find the audio file?
That's all I need to know.
No, we didn't.
So... Bauer wasted our time.
Come on.
Kate?
Kate, are you all right?
Everything that's happened today,
everything that's still happening...
I keep thinking it's all my fault.
Come here. We would never have found
the bomb in time if it wasn't for you.
My sister was the one behind the bomb.
She helped those fanatics.
Yes. But you’re not your sister.
I should've seen something
was wrong before it got this bad.
Because of what she did, it could start a war.
I could've stopped it.
No, Kate, you couldn't have.
There are things in this world
that are out of our control.
Sometimes we blame ourselves for them
so that we can try and make sense out of it.
Come here.
There was nothing you could have done.
Sorry. Yeah?
It's Tony and Michelle.
Excuse me.
- You got the audio file?
- No.
What do you mean? Are you saying
there's no audio file on that chip?
If there were, they were destroyed.
Chappelle wants you in
on a call to the president.
Yeah, I bet he does.
Some of the information Michelle
recovered may be worth looking into.
What information?
Identical code fragments
in several data streams.
- What are the fragments for?
- Nothing. That's the point.
It's junk code. Programmers sometimes
embed it into their programs as a signature.
Michelle traced the sequence
to a hacker named Alex Hewitt.
He's got a file with the FBI.
You think this is the technician
that created the Cyprus audio?
Yes.
We can't follow up any more leads,
so you have to talk to this guy.
What's his last known address?
210 Laurel Canyon Boulevard,
North Hollywood.
I got it. I'll get back to you.
All right.
- I'm sorry. I've gotta go.
- Where?
We got something off the chip,
not what we're looking for, but it's a lead.
When you're ready, an officer will take you
back to CTU so you can be with your father.
Thanks.
OK.
- Jack?
- Yeah?
Be careful.
Thanks. I will be.
Squadrons have been in a holding pattern
since the president called off the attack.
They just refuelled.
If we want to resume the operation,
we need to come to a conclusion now.
A few more minutes. This is the difference
between peace and war, Mr Prescott.
It's also a pattern that's been recurring
over the last few hours.
Everything will change once Mr Bauer calls.
It just never quite happens.
- Yes, what?
- CTU.
Jack Bauer and Ryan Chappelle
are on the line.
- This is President Palmer.
- This is Ryan Chappelle.
- Hello.
- Jack Bauer is on the line as well.
He'll give you an update.
Mr President, I found the chip.
Unfortunately, it's been badly damaged.
Can it prove that the Cyprus
recording was forged?
In its present condition, it proves nothing.
- Can it be repaired?
- No, sir. But about an hour ago,
I was tortured by men who wanted the chip.
They worked for Peter Kingsley.
He's part of the group behind the bomb.
They've manipulated
today's events to start this war.
What?
To improve their oil contracts
in the Caspian Sea
and to control the oil
coming out of the Middle East.
I need something concrete, evidence.
I understand. I'm checking up
on an address of a man
who we believe engineered the recording
for Kingsley. It's the best we've got.
Everything you've seen,
are you absolutely convinced
the Cyprus recording was forged?
Yes, sir, absolutely.
All right, Jack. Thank you.
The evidence I was hoping for is not yet
available, but I believe it will be soon.
- When, Mr President?
- I don't know.
Meanwhile, the window for
a surprise attack is rapidly closing.
It's time to vote.
Mr Vice President, if you could
indulge me for one minute.
Mr President.
This Bauer thing is an illusion, a mirage.
Every time you get near it,
it moves further away.
For your sake, for the country's,
authorise the attack.
All this will just go away.
And a lot of people, Americans and
non-Americans, will die for no reason.
We don't know that, Mr President.
Let's get on with the vote.
Members of the cabinet, you've
been presented with the evidence.
You know what's at stake.
Those of you who believe the president
is able to continue in office, vote yes.
Those of you who believe he isn't, vote no.
Mr Novick will conduct a voice poll.
The numbers will be reflected on the screen.
Mr Novick?
Ms Secretary of Transportation,
how do you vote?
Yes.
Mr Secretary of Treasury?
No.
Yes.
- Almeida.
- It's Jack.
I'm half a block from Hewitt's loft.
Has the FBI sent over his file yet?
- Yeah.
- What do I need to know?
The State Department recruited him. He
revamped their entire surveillance program.
He got caught manipulating files
that he didn't have clearance for.
He tried to kill himself,
spent a year in psychiatric prison,
then was released last September.
- No connection to Kingsley?
- No, not that we can find.
As soon as I get Hewitt, I'll get back to you.
Any word on what's happening
with the president?
- No, not yet.
- OK, thanks.
Mr Secretary of Defence, how do you vote?
Yes, I believe the president
should stay in office.
Mr Secretary of Agriculture.
No.
Mr Secretary of the Interior.
Mr Secretary of State, the vote
is seven for and seven against.
- Yours is the deciding vote.
- I'm aware of that.
I've never met a man that I respected
more than you, Mr President. Never.
But we are talking about tens
of thousands of American lives.
I'm compelled to vote no.
Mr President, can you see the results?
You will have an opportunity to appeal this
in four days in front of Congress.
In the meantime, I must ask you to remove
yourself from the decision-making process.
Please take the president to a holding room.
Will you please come with us, Mr President?
Mr President... I'm not a lawyer, sir,
but as far as I can tell,
the Constitution's been followed.
I've got no choice but to
ask you to come with us.
I'm sorry, sir.
I do solemnly swear that
I will faithfully execute
the office of the President of the United
States and will, to the best of my ability,
preserve, protect and defend
the Constitution of the United States,
so help me God.
Come on.
Alex?
Visiontext Subtitles: Tram Nguyen Zelniker
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net