There's a link between Stanton and the
mercenaries that shot down Bauer's plane.
Stanton won't be easy to break. You may
need to expand the limits of how far you'll go.
Mr Stanton, by order of the president,
I'm placing you under arrest.
This falls outside
the parameters of your charge.
What would you like me to do, sir?
I don't know
what you’re talking about.
- Where is she now?
- She ran off after the accident.
Maybe she was trying to avoid the local
police or trying not to get brought back to LA.
Just find her, George.
Ow!
Marie, we have a problem.
Basheer and Marko are dead.
- What do you need me to do?
- They were gonna pick up the trigger.
- Where is it?
- The place Marko worked. In his locker.
You must gain access to this locker
and bring the trigger to Omar.
I'll take care of it.
I've earned the right to know what's going on.
Syed Ali is at the centre of a terrorist attack.
We need you to identify him for us.
He's in there. Syed Ali. He's in there.
Damm it!
He's dead, Jack.
These clothes don't belong to this man.
Maintain secure exits.
Ali is still in the building.
Step outside until
we get the situation resolved.
- Agent Bauer told me to stay. Talk to him.
- As soon as you step outside.
She stays with us. She's gotta make
the final identification on Ali.
This was in the pocket
of the man Ali set on fire.
- It might be a document Ali was carrying.
- Photo it, send it to CTU.
Are you trying to protect this man?
No, I have no misplaced loyalties.
If the man has murdered an innocent, he is as
guilty in the eyes of Islam as he is in yours.
The man that I'm looking for
set in motion a plan today
to detonate a nuclear weapon
in Los Angeles.
- Are you certain?
- Yes, we're certain.
We estimate between one and two million
people will die if this bomb goes off.
That, sir, is why we need to find him now.
Thank you for informing me, but I can be
no more honest with you than I have been.
But if you find this man, perhaps
I can talk to him in a way you cannot.
Persuade him.
Agent Bauer?
Thank you.
We found something I think you should see.
We found this trap door. It's not on
any of the schematics you gave us.
Open it.
- I go down... I'm going down alone.
- I know this is your operation...
Listen to me. We just lost one of Ali's men
to a cyanide capsule hidden in his tooth.
We have to assume Ali's willing to take
his life the same way. He can't see us coming.
Have your men assemble at the base
of the ladder. Await my instructions.
Have you got your baton with you?
Let me have it. OK.
- Hello?
- Marie.
- There has been a change of plans.
- Why? What's going on?
Just go to the rendezvous point.
If I'm not there within one half-hour
of the time we have planned,
then you know what to do.
- You remember what I said, yes?
- I remember.
I've got the suspect!
Engage the room! Engage the room!
Get his legs!
- That's him! That is Syed Ali!
- Get her outta here! Get her outta here!
Get her outta here!
I got the cyanide. Get him ready.
Baker!
Find out who he was talking to.
It's hard not to sit here and think
that there must be some mistake,
even with the evidence you have.
It's black-and-white, Bob. Your daughter
killed Reza and two of our agents.
And I need you to help us understand
what her connection to Syed Ali is.
If I'd known she was involved,
I would have done something.
And now that you do know,
does it help explain any strange behaviour?
Anything you can tell us will help.
Well...
Marie went to college in London
while I was working there.
That's when her mother died,
and it hit her hard, hit us all hard.
And?
She ran away for a while.
How long?
Three, maybe four weeks.
We got the police involved, but...
she sent us a letter saying that she was fine,
that she was travelling
and she just needed some space.
And when she came back...
I was so grateful to see her
that I stopped asking questions.
No sense that anything had changed?
Any fundamental difference?
She had become less politically inclined.
Marie had always flirted with causes,
respectable causes.
Like save the wilderness
or abolish the death penalty.
She stopped talking about all that.
That's precisely what happens
when you're radicalised.
Handlers train you to stop talking
about anything, keep it to yourself,
so you're better able to blend in
with the background.
Marie had handlers?
Hey, can it wait? I'll be right back with this.
This scan came in from the mosque. A burnt
paper fragment found in Ali's clothing.
The only thing visible
is in the lower left quadrant.
It looks like a piece of a number.
A six or an eight.
Are all our forensics people out in the field?
We got Murdoch on loan from San Diego.
He's an expert with computer imaging.
If anyone can see this, he can.
- How are you doing? George Mason.
- Hey, man. Randy Murdoch.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
- Any way to accelerate the process?
- My CPU's faster than anything you got.
Parallel processing could take too long
to set up. If there's anything there, I'll get it.
Great. Where's Tony
and the satellite feed Jack wants?
In progress.
- Thank you. Keep it up.
- All right.
- Who else knew about the bomb?
- I don't know what you’re talking about.
Jack Bauer is interrogating Ali as we speak.
We'll be informed of his progress on
a minute-by-minute basis, but nothing yet.
We're certain he knows
the location of the bomb?
- Jack Bauer is.
- Make sure he has all the resources he needs.
Yes, sir.
The pain's only going to get
much, much worse.
You can stop it.
Agent Simmons tells me that Roger
received the same training
of resisting interrogation he did.
- I'm increasing the voltage.
- But everyone breaks eventually.
You have an entry point?
She entered the forest somewhere
between 8-3 and 8-4 on the topo map.
- And heading?
- No. No idea which way she was headed.
- Keep me posted.
- What are you doing?
- Getting more men looking for Kim.
- I told you to divert resources to the bomb.
The satellite feed is happening.
I was telling the sheriff to look for her.
You're a resource. Don't split your attention.
I promised Jack I'd do everything I could
to look for Kim. Just like you did.
Kim is outside the blast radius.
The rest of Los Angeles isn't.
Stay focused on the bomb, Tony!
That goes for everybody!
- LA County Ranger Station.
- This is Tony Almeida at CTU.
I'm trying to track somebody
who went into the forest.
Hold while I transfer you.
Hey, somebody there?
Hello?
- Who are you? What are you doing here?
- Me? What are you doing here?
I got into a car accident.
I started running, and before I knew it,
I was out here. I had no idea where I was.
I got stuck in this stupid thing.
Look, all I wanna do is get back
to the highway and get outta here.
Why were you running
from the highway in the first place?
I told you, I was scared and panicked.
Damm it.
Oh, God. Thank you.
Coming through here.
We're moving into position now. Baker out.
I know who you are.
I know everything that you’ve done.
Where is the bomb?
Where's the bomb?!
You are wasting my time.
When is the bomb gonna detonate?
You're the one wasting time.
I woke up today knowing I will die.
I can make you die with more pain
than you ever imagined.
Then I will have that much
more pleasure in paradise.
Right.
We gotta figure out how to get you
to the nearest ranger station.
No, that's OK. I don't wanna go back there.
The same reason you ran from the highway?
Here, I got it. Thank you.
The highway is a couple of miles that way.
But the terrain's too rough to follow at night,
and there's cougars up in that area.
My place is a half-mile that way.
I could put a roof
over your head for the night.
I am the imam of this mosque.
Do you deny these men's accusations
that you are planning to explode a bomb
that will kill millions of people?
The Koran clearly forbids the killing
of innocents and non-combatants.
You know this as well as I do.
We have different interpretations
of the Koran.
You are misguided.
Someone has twisted
the words of the prophet.
Allah does not love aggressors.
Listen to me. The murder of one innocent, let
alone millions, will not get you into paradise.
We will continue this debate
when I see you there, Imam Al Fulani.
I want the images from this computer
transferred to these monitors.
I have talked to men who misuse
our religion to channel their hate,
but I have not known anyone
who would act on their impulses.
Can you make an appeal
that'll make any difference?
- I will try again, but I don't think so.
- We don't have that kind of time.
Please, I want to try again.
You can't be involved
with what's gonna happen next.
Please escort the gentleman upstairs.
- Agent Bauer?
- Yeah.
We recovered the last number Ali dialled
on his cell. It's a 310 area code. 555-2130.
- We're doing a work-up on it now.
- OK, good.
Wait. What was that number?
555-2130.
No, that's not possible.
That's my sister's cellphone number.
What's going on?
What are you not telling me?
Why don’t you give us a minute?
Reza and two of our agents
were found shot to death
in your father's building
about an hour and a half ago.
- What?
- Your sister Marie was with them.
- Marie? Is she OK?
- They don't know where she is right now.
When were you going to tell me?
When we had confirmation that
she was the person that pulled the trigger.
What? That is ridiculous.
How could you even think that?
Because we have video tape on her.
She was the only person seen leaving your
father's building in the last hour and a half.
She was probably trying to escape.
She could have been hurt.
You don't know if she picked up.
The phone could have been stolen!
You really believe your sister
has nothing to do with this?
Yes, I really believe it.
There's one way you could prove
that to me. Phone her cellphone.
But if she picks up, you have to keep her
on the phone so we can find her.
That's the deal. Can you do that?
OK.
I'm gonna be right back.
Baker?
We need to trace a cellphone call.
But manipulate the caller ID.
We need to make it look like it's coming
from Kate Warner's phone. Get on it now.
Our equipment will make it look like
you're calling from your cellphone.
Tell her you're worried
cos you haven't heard from her.
We're linked into the cell-provider network.
Once we lock, we can track the phone.
OK, good. Let's make the call.
What if it's not her?
What if it's someone else?
That's what we need to find out.
Finding your sister right now
could save the lives of millions of people.
Please make the call.
Hello?
Hi.
It's me.
I haven't been able to reach Dad.
He's not back yet.
What's going on?
Just taking a drive... to clear my head.
I can understand.
I'm so sorry, Marie, about everything.
Yes.
Do you want to meet
back at the house? Grab a bite?
Can you?
They've found Reza, haven't they?
They know what's happened.
I don't know. I don't know what happened.
Oh, Marie.
Tell me, please, what happened?
You wouldn't understand, Kate.
You killed Reza? And those agents?
People have to die for things to change.
We're locked.
You couldn't have done this. They forced you.
You didn't know what you were doing.
We tracked it to a ten-block section of Sylmar.
Tell CHP to shut down that ten-block radius.
Send vitals on Marie Warner.
- Tell them to find her.
- Got it.
You don't know who she was with!
They could have been forcing her.
You don't know!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Any word back from the ranger station?
- Nothing yet. They mounted a search.
Tony. I just sent this to Jack
over at the mosque. Check it out.
This paper has a very irregular pulp pattern.
The final step in the process
is to take samples from various points,
to create a CGI algorithm
of what the paper looked like
without any of the writings
or other impressions on it.
We then subtract that from what
we've actually got, and what we get...
is a representation of anything
that interrupts that pattern.
There it is. OK. This is only a partial.
There are a few more markings.
Letters or numbers to the right of these.
But I need time. They're more obscure.
Do we have any contacts whatsoever as to
what these numbers and letters refer to?
They photographed the paper on both sides.
That's the only area with any information.
All right. Good job.
Michelle, get anyone we can spare
on that sequence of letters and numbers.
Check VIN numbers, licence plates.
Also get crypto to see if that's a code.
I'm on it.
- Agent Bauer?
- Yeah.
This just came in from CTU.
Open the door. Open the door!
N34, what does that mean?
What does that mean?
You screwed up, Ali.
We're gonna cross-reference
that number in our database.
Marie Warner is being picked up as we speak.
The pieces are starting to come together.
No matter what, we'll find this bomb.
So you can either tell me now
or I can make you suffer.
You wanna suffer?
I already told you. I'm not afraid to die.
The only way you're gonna die today
is if I kill you. Your bomb's not going off.
- We have a live feed.
- Patch it through.
Go.
Those men will kill your family
if you don't tell me where the bomb is now.
I despise you for making me do this.
They're waiting for my order.
This is your last chance. Where's the bomb?
Sir.
Are you aware Jack Bauer's
threatening the lives of Syed Ali's family?
No.
- Where is the family?
- In their own country.
CTU's been in contact with the security forces
there who have Ali's family in custody.
We just got word that Jack has requested
they kill the family one by one
till Ali tells us the location of the bomb.
- Would the security forces do this?
- They do act against civilians.
And their government is afraid of retaliation
if a bomb does go off. Yes, I think they would.
Can we let this happen?
Condone the murder of innocent people?
The bomb is an act of war
and wars result in civilian casualties.
I don't want a rationale here, Mike.
I don't know of a war where
a president targeted children.
Compare this to a weapons factory
near a hospital - a situation we have faced.
A bombing would still be ordered on the logic
that many more people will be saved
by the destruction of the factory.
The numbers are even more compelling here.
A few people may have to die
to save millions.
How could it have come to this?
Your wife's been writing
you letters every day.
She doesn't know where to send them.
Your son Asad wants to grow up
and be just like you.
Turns 12 next week.
I don't think he's gonna make it.
I know what it's like to lose someone,
to watch them get killed right in front of you.
I don't wanna hurt your family.
But I will order those men to pull that trigger
if you don't give me the information I need.
I am...
I am doing Allah's work.
No. You're going to kill millions of people,
that's what you’re doing.
Agent Bauer.
It's important. It's the president.
This is Jack Bauer.
Can't let you do this, Jack.
Sir, Ali was willing to take his own life
to complete his mission.
His only vulnerability is his family.
It is not the policy of this country
to kill innocent children.
The action would take place in his country.
You would not be involved.
This would be a field decision.
My decision is final. I'm sorry, Jack.
Yes, sir.
I understand, Mr President.
No, I do not think that
there is another alternative.
I know it's a difficult decision, sir.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your support, Mr President.
He authorised the action.
- Roger Stanton isn't available.
- When can I talk to him?
That's all I can say, Rich.
If you have a tactical question, talk to
Scott Grant. He's got the NSA playbook.
- I can use your name?
- Sure.
Mike. Can I just have
a quick word with you, please?
Yeah, sure, Lynne.
I don't trust Sherry Palmer.
She shouldn't be here.
I'm up to my eyeballs trying to hide this
interrogation with Stanton from Washington.
If you have a problem, deal with it yourself.
I think you know me well enough
to know this is not some battle over turf.
- This is about Roger Stanton.
- What?
I was waiting for the appropriate time
to tell you. I wanted to be sure.
Someone has approached me
with evidence of communications
between Roger Stanton and Sherry Palmer,
and it has been over the last six months.
Roger said he met her today
for the first time.
Yes. I know.
My God.
You've known Sherry for a very long time.
Is today indicative of how she operates?
Then this shouldn't be
too much of a shock to you.
Sherry Palmer's a lot of things,
but a traitor to this country?
I don't believe that.
What kind of communication? Phone calls?
Yes. Phone calls, emails. Mike.
Face to face.
Who's your source on this?
It's been through an intermediary,
but I actually have a meeting
with the source in about ten minutes.
- Where?
- Off site.
- Are you telling the president?
- No. He's got enough on his plate already.
And he'd want proof, anyway.
You go ahead with your meeting.
Let me know what happens.
- Be careful.
- I will. Thank you.
- Shall we proceed as planned?
- Affirmative. Start with the older son, Asad.
If that's not successful,
move on to his younger son.
- Copy that. Waiting for your orders.
- We are a go.
I can't wait any longer.
Tell me where the bomb is or I will kill Asad.
Ali, I know you think what you’re doing
is right, but it's my job to not let it happen.
Please don't make me do this.
Asad is just a boy. Tell me where the bomb is!
Tell me where the bomb is! Fine.
Kill him!
No! No!
Tell me where the bomb is!
- Tell me, and I'll spare your family!
- I will not tell you!
Your meeting's changed. Now it's with me.
No, don't go anywhere, Lynne.
We need to talk.
- I don't think so.
- Yes, we do.
You think you've connected me to Roger.
That's exactly what they want you to think.
- Who is "they"?
- The people Roger's conspiring with.
So you're confirming that Roger Stanton
is involved? He knew about this bomb?
Roger's more involved
than David could possibly know.
What the hell does that mean?
- This conspiracy, what is its goal, then?
- To take over the presidency.
These people are feeding you
misinformation about me
because they're afraid I'll get in the way.
How did you know about this meeting?
I don't have to be involved
to know the moves.
If you knew what Roger was doing,
why haven’t you said anything?
Probably for the same reasons
you're keeping this line of inquiry to yourself.
I want to have as much
concrete evidence as possible.
Sherry, you could have said any of this to me
back at the retreat. Why come here?
To make a point. That's all.
To make a point?
I think this is a warning.
I think you orchestrated all of this
to show me how powerful you are.
You have your own and not the president's
best interest at heart.
I will do everything to make sure you don't
hurt him or undermine this administration.
Asad is dead. There's nothing
I can do to change that.
You can still save Fareed's life.
I'll give you ten seconds. Where's the bomb?
You're running out of time.
I will tell these men to kill your last son!
Where is the bomb?
That's it. Take him out!
- I will tell you!
- Hold it.
- I will tell you.
- Tell me now!
- It is at Norton Airfield.
- Why? What's the plan?
We were going to fly over downtown
and detonate it.
It is true. It is... it is true.
- Dessler.
- It's Jack. Get me Mason.
It's Jack.
What do you have?
The bomb's at Norton Airfield.
They're planning to fly it over the city.
Norton's a medium-size airfield.
They do cargo, private aviation.
Every plane's tail number begins with the
letter "N". That's probably what this refers to.
OK. We're on our way.
We're moving units Bravo,
Echo and Lima to Norton Airfield,
where we believe that the bomb is located.
Call FAA and have them
ground flights in or out of Norton.
If they do get the plane in the air, we wanna
have two F-16s at the ready to intercept.
We'll get bomb units and SWAT teams
over there as well, so just move.
And, remember, the "no unnecessary contact"
rule remains in place.
Put Miss Warner against the wall.
You killed my boy!
You killed my boy! You killed my boy!
I will get you for this! You will die for this!
How could you? You're worse than they are.
Reroute the satellite back to normal feed.
I want confirmation.
Rerouted satellite.
You should have live picture now.
Thank you.
Hold this for me.
We're gonna come in from the north.
Set up our men coming in from the south
from these two gates.
He's alive.
It was all an act.
Kate, come with me,
help me talk to your sister.
What? Where?
Norton Airfield. It's where the bomb's located.
- Do you really think she's there?
- Yes, I do.
- Please, Kate, we don't have much time.
- OK.
Come on.
Here you go, sir.
Wake up. Stay with me, Mr Stanton. Wake up.
There we go. Who else knew
about the bomb, Mr Stanton?
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net