Six hours ago a cache of weapons-grade
plutonium was found in a warehouse.
We also found this.
What do you make of that, guys?
- This is a bill of lading from our company.
- For a container sent to Syed Ali.
I can track the shipping order.
The database is at the office.
If my father really does
work for the government,
wouldn't he have known
if Reza was doing something illegal?
Who are you?
My name is Syed Ali. You were
looking in places you do not belong.
- I don't know anything!
- Kill her.
No.
We're going down! The pilots don't know
what happened. It felt like an explosion.
- They were shot down?
- By a ground-to-air missile.
That's not Search and Rescue.
- Are they coming here for you?
- I don't know.
Drop it.
I'll tell you where the bomb is in exchange
for immunity, for the murder of Jack Bauer.
Someone from CTU
is supposed to pick us up.
Captain said it's out of their jurisdiction.
- We told you why we can't go back to LA.
- Yeah, I know. The bomb.
Miss Myers, if the information you provide
culminates in the interception
of the nuclear device,
you'll be pardoned in advance
for the murder of Jack Bauer.
Mr President, there was only one
right choice to make and you made it.
You've been told by a well-respected
member of the press, Mr Ron Wieland,
that there is an imminent terrorist threat
levelled against this country.
That is true, so far as it goes.
Please.
The fact is, we get a dozen
such threats every day.
And do I know more about them
than I publicly reveal? Of course.
What is released to the public and when
is a matter of judgement.
You have elected me
to exercise that judgement
in the best interests of this country.
That's what I've done since I took office.
That's what I'm doing today.
And I can assure you that we have
the situation well under control,
and there is no cause for alarm.
Thank you.
Not the Gettysburg Address,
but it should buy us time.
It was fine.
- What's the situation with Jack Bauer?
- Still being held hostage by Nina Myers.
It didn't have to be like this, Jack.
I never meant for it to be personal.
It felt pretty personal
when you killed my wife.
I had to. Teri overheard something
that compromised my escape route.
What about bombing CTU?
All those people you used to work with?
I didn't bomb CTU. I just sold the plans.
You believe what you have to,
but you killed your friends.
Shut up, Jack! Shut up!
Now we are done talking!
We're just gonna wait for Palmer to call
and then this'll all be over. You got it?
You know what, Nina? You're right. I don't
really wanna just sit here and wait to die.
Don't move, Jack!
I mean it!
You kill me before they verify the information,
you'll be in violation of your agreement.
- They'll just slap your ass back in jail.
- And you'll be dead.
I'm already dead.
Last warning, Jack.
That's it. One more step and I'll shoot.
Argh!
- Team one, move in! Go!
- Go, go go!
- Move, move, move!
- Grab her!
Secure the weapon.
Got it.
- Notify the chopper.
- Get her up.
- Let's go.
- We're not going back to LA.
We've been through this.
- I told you before.
- I know, the bomb. Move. Walk.
Forget about us.
You wanna get blown to pieces?
I told you who my dad was.
You think they’d send someone from CTU?
- Get in.
- I'm not going back to LA.
- Miguel!
- Get down! Get down! Don't move.
- I got him.
- Miguel!
- Careful.
- Let's go. Get in.
Yes. Good. Yes, I'll tell him.
It's over.
- Is Jack OK?
- They got to Nina before she shot him.
- What about her?
- As you requested, she wasn't seriously hurt.
They're awaiting orders.
Do you want her taken to prison?
No. We'll honour our original deal.
I'll pardon her as soon
as we confirm her information.
- In the meantime, where do you want her?
- Los Angeles.
Let her share the fate
of everyone she's endangered.
Yes, sir.
That's affirmative. I'll meet the chopper
just south of the gully in the field.
- Roger that.
- Copy.
Now...
We're here to find transactions you claim
Bob Warner had with Syed Ali.
The sooner we do that,
the sooner we're out of here.
Have a seat.
- I can't work like this.
- I'll be keying the computer.
How do I open the invoice files?
- What?
- I need to access the invoice files.
- File, open, warehouse.
- How are they ordered?
- Chronologically, I think.
- You think?
Look, my fiancée just left me on my wedding
day because I'm sending her father to jail.
And since he's my employer, that pretty
much means my whole life's in the toilet.
So why don’t you cut me some slack?
There's a nuke somewhere in this city.
And if you don't give me
something useful in the next hour,
I'll take you back to CTU
and chain you to the roof,
so you'll have a front row seat
when the damn thing goes off.
Do you want to suffer as he did?
No, of course not.
Then tell me what you’ve learned
from your father's computer files,
who you told.
I already told you. I don't know anything.
Jack Bauer.
Jack?
Mr President, the soldiers
that attacked us at the crash site,
they were Americans,
or at least, American trained.
What?
One of the soldiers that was killed
had a tattoo of a coral snake on his arm.
That's a signature of a group
out of Fort Benning.
- What sort of group?
- A deep cover special ops unit.
The only reason I know about the tattoos,
is because early in my career
they tried to recruit me.
Their commander is a Colonel Samuels.
- I've never heard of this unit.
- No, you wouldn't have. That's the point.
They'd be buried pretty heavily
in NSA's budget.
NSA.
OK.
Even if NSA originally trained him, isn't it
possible he's freelancing now? A mercenary?
If it was just the tattoo, I'd agree with you.
But the men that attacked us
had access to our flight plan.
The only way they could have got
that information was from on the inside.
Mr President, I know it sounds very
far-fetched that we got attacked by Americans,
but that tattoo is
very distinctive and very specific.
I appreciate the information.
Where are you now?
We're in a chopper. We're on our way to
the address that Nina Meyers provided for us.
We should be touching down soon, sir.
Our ETA is 15 minutes.
- Keep me posted, Jack.
- Yes, Mr President.
Jack's on his way to the Syed Ali house.
Do you want a feed up here?
No. I assume you have that under control.
Yeah, we do.
Was there something else?
I'm sorry.
So what are you gonna do tomorrow?
- What?
- If the bomb doesn't go off.
Thought about it?
No.
You'll probably come back to work here?
Of course. Why wouldn't I?
I don't know. Are you happy in this job? Hm?
Believe it or not, I used to want
to be a teacher... a long time ago.
You know why I didn't?
Cos DOD offered me more money.
That's how I made my decision.
So I made myself miserable,
and I made everybody else around me
miserable for an extra $5,000 a year.
That was my price.
Sorry.
You know, Michelle,
I'm not a big advice giver,
but under the circumstances...
Don't wait around for your life
to happen to you.
Find something that makes you happy, do it.
Because everything else
is all just background noise.
- Roger.
- Mr President.
Tell me everything you know about
Colonel Ron Samuels from Fort Benning.
I don't know anything about Samuels.
What about a special ops units
from down there called Coral Snake?
No, sir. Nothing.
How could NSA be funding a paramilitary
group and you not know about it?
Without knowing specifics,
I really can't say for sure.
My guess is that the Department of Defense
has used some of their
discretionary resources,
attached our name for budgetary purposes.
It happens all the time.
That's absurd. NSA is information gathering
only. They have no military mandate.
I'd assume that this Coral Snake group,
like many others that we see,
falls under somebody's pet project,
gets funded on the sly.
How would you know that, Roger? A minute
ago you told me you'd never heard of them.
I'm just conjecturing from
past experience, Mr President.
I have no concrete information.
Let me look into it.
You do that.
Jack Bauer's plane was shot down
by an American military unit.
Jack told me himself. I won't go into details,
except to say that I believe him.
American military? Why?
I just spoke to Roger Stanton.
I think he's hiding something from me.
I'm going to arrest him.
Arrest the head of NSA?
Bauer said the unit that attacked his plane
is connected to a Colonel Samuels.
Samuels is funded by NSA.
With all due respect, David, that's pretty thin.
By itself, yes.
But the ambassador's chopper crash,
the evacuation of
military personnel out of LA,
Ron Wieland's escape from custody,
those things happened after Stanton arrived.
Firing Stanton will cause chaos.
All the agencies report through him.
He's running the search for the bomb,
for crying out loud.
If the president's right,
he's not running it, he's impeding it.
- Why would he do such a thing?
- I don't know.
But if he is, we have a better chance
of finding the bomb if we get rid of him.
David...
you can't do this on a hunch.
If Stanton turns out to be innocent
and that bomb goes off,
you'll be blamed for the death of millions.
If you do nothing and he is guilty
of something, you'll be blamed anyway.
No, no, no. At the very least, we need
to get some kind of proof, some evidence.
You cannot just arrest
the head of NSA, David.
Sherry's right, Mike. We need proof.
Find me a connection between Stanton
and this Colonel Samuels. And find it quickly.
LA County 470, go ahead.
This is Officer Brown with Valley.
I'm trying to reach Detective Bill Gucoff.
Brown. You're transporting
two suspects down to Central?
- Mm-hm, that's right.
- Hold on. I'll patch you through.
- Gucoff here.
- Hey, Bill.
- Yeah?
- I'm bringing the prisoners down.
- All right. You got everything under control?
- The guy gave us trouble...
- What?
- Get the bandanna out of my pocket.
- Why?
- To start a fire.
What? You're crazy.
He'll have to pull over and stop the car.
- And then he'll put it out. Then what?
- I don't know.
Maybe it'll do enough damage and we'll have
to go back to the station. It'll buy us time.
That is just crazy.
Crazier than going to Los Angeles where
a nuclear bomb might go off any minute?
Hey, listen, this may sound a little crazy,
but did you happen to hear anything about
some kind of a bomb threat today?
What?
I can't do this. You gotta do it.
- No.
- Kim, you can do it. You're smaller.
No, I haven't heard anything.
- Come on.
- You sure?
Why? Somebody tell you
there was a bomb or something?
What's going on? You know something
that I don't? What's up?
I don't know. It may be nothing,
but one of the kids here,
apparently her father works for CTU.
He gave her some kind
of information about a bomb.
Just check it out for me.
Like I said, it's probably nothing, but...
No problem.
OK, Gucoff. Thanks. I owe you one.
- Kim.
- Hang on, OK?
- Hello. Can anyone hear me?
- This is CHP Station Six.
Kim. Kim. Don't.
We're on San Fernando, the 118. There's
been an accident. We need an ambulance.
- How's the officer?
- Hurt. So is someone else.
- Two injured?
- Yes.
- Stay there. We're sending someone now.
- Hang on.
All units. All units proceed
to San Fernando at the 118.
MVA. Officer down. Officer down.
I'm gonna ask you just once more, huh?
Who did you tell?
No one.
Here's an infrared of the house.
Two people in this room.
We assume one is Ali,
but we'll need to take 'em both alive.
- Your men in position?
- In 90 seconds.
- Good.
- Yeah?
- George, it's me.
- Where are you?
I'm on site. Syed Ali's in the house.
We're gonna move in a minute.
We need auxiliary teams ready to move as
soon as we find out the location of this bomb.
- We're already working on it.
- I'll get back to you as soon as we get him.
Agent Baker?
Let me know when your teams are ready.
This is Bob Warner's access code.
As you can see, he logged on
roughly twice as often as I did.
- This is a restricted area.
- I need to speak with Reza.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
- Just a minute. It's our wedding day.
- I realise that.
- We're in the middle of an investigation.
- Can I talk to him for one minute?
- Can I talk to Reza for a minute?
- I tried to explain.
- Make it fast.
- Thank you.
Marie?
Hey, what I said before, I didn't mean it.
I'm so sorry. This has been such a shock.
No, no, no. It's all right.
You are the man I'm going to marry.
I know, whatever you're doing, you have to
do it. I love you. Whatever happens, happens.
My angel.
We have to get back to work.
You can wait in the next room if you'd like.
Thank you.
It was barely a nick,
not nearly as bad as it feels.
You don't have to kill me.
Just leave me here.
By the time someone finds me,
you'll be 100 miles away.
Something's going to happen, very soon.
Something terrible,
which will cause much suffering.
This will be easier.
Take cover!
Fall back. Fall back.
I have here a woman!
If you come any closer, I'll kill the woman!
- Bring in the shield now.
- We need the body bunker right away.
They don't negotiate. Yet they do shoot.
It's not you they want alive, it's me.
I'll try and take him out with a beanbag hit.
Suspect is secure.
You're all right. You're all right.
It's all right. It's all right.
Just relax. Take a breath.
It's over. It's over. OK?
- Jack, he's going into convulsions.
- What?
- Did you see him take anything?
- I was watching him the whole time.
Cyanide. He must have had it in his mouth.
We need a medic in here now!
We need a medic now!
Copy that.
Damm it!
I want him photographed, fingerprints.
Send it to CTU for analysis.
I want confirmation that that is Syed Ali.
You called them. You should go.
I'll go when they get here.
It'll be too late. They'll see you.
I'll be fine.
Thank you so much... for everything.
As soon as this is all over,
I'm gonna find you. OK? I promise.
Go.
Notify Dispatch. 143.
- Did you get the area locked down?
- Yes, sir.
You should drink some water.
Kate, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm a federal agent.
You've been through an ordeal, but I have
to ask you a few questions. Is that all right?
- How did you get here?
- Um...
I was... trying to help my sister.
So I hired a private investigator.
Those men thought we knew something...
Slow down, slow down. The dead man in
the other room was a private investigator?
Paul Koplin.
What they did to him...
They? There was more than one man here?
How many men were there?
Two. The other one left before you came.
Did you get his name?
- Syed Ali.
- Are you sure?
Can you describe him for me?
Tall. Thin.
Do you remember what he was wearing?
A black shirt.
With... silver buttons down the front.
Black pants.
Do you remember what kind of a car he
got into? Do you know where he was going?
Excuse me for one moment.
Baker, this is Agent Bauer.
Syed Ali is still alive. We are looking for
a Middle Eastern man, wearing all black.
I didn't get a make on the car.
Send out an APB.
- We need to find him now.
- Copy.
Kate, you said you came here
to help your sister. Who is she?
Marie. Marie Warner.
She was supposed to get married today.
Tell Mike what you told me.
There's a back-channel communications
network the CIA used to use, called OPCOM.
It's been shut down for over 20 years.
Last month, NSA was given orders
to resurrect it.
It was an eyes-only order
issued by Roger Stanton.
- I'm not sure that's enough.
- By itself, it's not.
Unless Stanton used OPCOM to contact
Colonel Samuels in the last few hours.
My source is checking on that now.
Mike, call the Attorney General.
Start working on this from the legal side.
If we find this connection,
we'll move on it, have Stanton arrested.
I think we got a positive ID. Cross-reference
his prints with the name Paul Koplin.
- CTU?
- Bauer. Put me through to Tony.
Hold, please.
- It's Tony. What's up?
- I'm still at the house.
I just questioned the woman that
Ali was torturing for information.
Her name is Kate Warner.
Run a background check.
- Did you say Kate Warner?
- Yeah. Why?
I had her family picked up this morning.
I was with her hours ago.
- What's the connection?
- Reza Naiyeer,
her sister's fiancé, had dealings with Syed Ali.
He's denying it.
He says it was the father, Bob Warner.
Richards took Naiyeer to Bob Warner's
office to hack into his computer.
I have Warner here with me right now.
Jack, will Kate talk to you?
Cos her family's not cooperating.
Yeah. But I gotta give her time. She's been
through hell. You should see this place.
Jack, there's one more thing.
What?
The father, Bob Warner,
he freelances for the CIA.
We're gonna have to start from the beginning.
You'll have to run everything again.
Start connecting the dots. These people
are involved. You gotta find out how.
- Get back to me when you've got anything.
- All right, you got it.
Gentlemen, I need you to pack up.
I need the room.
- Agent Baker?
- Baker here.
- How's Miss Warner doing?
- Not so good.
As soon as you think she's ready,
bring her down to the bathroom.
Will do. Baker out.
Those three dates and
anything the following week. Hold on.
OK. Good. Let me know as soon
as you find something out. Thanks.
- Sir?
- What have we got?
- I found a way into the OPCOM channels.
- Good. Tunnel in.
The problem is, the files
are pass code protected.
We'll need someone internal
to open them. It'll take time.
Hold. No, it's not.
I just got the name of a deputy director
who's retired, but his code is still active.
We could use that.
Jean, could you hold on for a sec?
Uh-huh. Let's see.
- Try this. It should work. I'm back.
- I'll head over to the OC and check it out.
- Good.
- Oh, that's terrific.
Jean, I'm gonna cross-reference these,
but I need you to stay in the office.
- No problem.
- Right. OK. Thanks. Bye.
I'm collecting the dates that
Samuels' office logged onto OPCOM.
If Mike can trace Stanton's access,
we can look for a match.
- That's great.
- If we have that, you'll have the proof.
Stanton has a dozen staff who share his code.
How are we gonna pin it on him?
There's a four-digit subcode that only belongs
to him. That's the one that'll nail him.
- Sherry?
- Yes.
You're doing an incredible job here today.
Thank you.
I'd forgotten how talented
you are at all this stuff.
David, I've worked with you
for over 25 years.
It had to rub off on me somehow.
I'm glad you're here.
I have always been here.
You remember that.
Yeah.
All right. Call me if there's anything.
- That was Barbara at the Warner office.
- What'd they find?
Nothing yet. They're still going through
the records. Reza seems to be cooperating.
This is driving me crazy.
It doesn't make sense that Syed Ali has
a connection to this white-bread family.
So you believe Bob Warner?
There's nothing in his profile or behaviour
that suggests he's involved with terrorists.
I agree. But look at the facts.
There is a paper trail between
Warner Investments and Ali.
Kate Warner was abducted for a reason.
I know.
Look, put together a list of all the managers
and directors of Bob Warner's company.
- I want to widen the search a notch.
- Good idea.
Anything else?
Yeah.
I was talking to Mason before, and...
And?
This is hardly the time,
but I don't know how much time we have,
so... I just wanted you to know
that if you wanted to go out sometime...
- Michelle...
- I just wanted you to know how I felt.
No, Michelle...
I feel the same way.
I've just been keeping
my distance because...
Because of what happened
between you and Nina?
Yeah.
So you think I just want you
for your information?
So... what are we saying here, then?
If we save LA from a nuclear bomb,
then you and I can get together
for dinner and a movie? Is that it?
- I'll get that list.
- Yeah, that's...
Syed Ali left... after he killed Mr Koplin.
They talked for a minute or two.
They looked at me a couple of times.
It was like...
like I wasn't important any more.
They embraced, and he left.
Did they say anything to each other
when he was leaving?
Yes, but... they spoke so softly.
And mostly in Arabic.
Arabic? How can you be so sure?
My family lived in Saudi Arabia
when I was younger.
When my sister got engaged to Reza,
I picked it up again.
Can you identify any words that they said?
Anything at all?
Salat. They said "salat" several times.
It means prayer.
But I couldn't really hear anything.
They were so soft.
Baker, this is Jack. Get ahold of CTU.
I want a list of every mosque
in a 15-mile radius.
- Mosques?
- They talked about prayer before Ali left.
- The time fits.
- Roger that.
- Did that help?
- Yes.
Yes, I think it did.
OK.
Kate, the normal protocol would be to transfer
you back to CTU for further debriefing.
But the truth is, I don't know
what Syed Ali looks like.
No one does, except for you.
I need you to identify him for me.
- Stanton.
- It's me.
Excuse me.
- You know better than to call me here.
- They know about OPCOM.
- How?
- I told them.
- What?!
- David had the bit between his teeth.
He was gonna find out one way or another.
This way, I get him trusting
me again, little by little.
- What do we do now?
- They'll connect you to the plane.
David's having an arrest warrant
drawn up as we speak.
Stay the course, Roger. When this is over,
you'll have everything you want.
While, in the meantime,
it's important that you don't talk.
- Don't talk about you.
- That's right.
It's more important than ever
that I stay in place.
- How much time do I have?
- Not much.
Hold on.
Here's the shipping order.
It was entered last January.
- Bob and I were both in Europe then.
- So he logged on from overseas.
That's not possible. It's not international. But
it didn't originate from this terminal either.
Somebody hacked in.
Hold on. This can't be. I set up
this program on my own computer.
- You said you were out of the country.
- I left my laptop here.
Who else had access to it?
Nobody.
Except...
Marie?
I didn't expect you to find anything.
I underestimated you.
Well then, the last two years have just been...
It's just been an act, is that it?
I mean nothing to you?
Huh?
I don't understand. Say something, Marie!
Reza... you really are very sweet.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net