I need to speak with the president.
They can't diffuse it. We'll have to fly it out.
Ground zero has to be a precise location.
A pilot will have to go down with the plane.
It's a suicide mission.
- Who ended up flying the plane?
- Jack Bauer.
- Get Air Force One ready as soon as possible.
- Do you mind if I ask where you're going?
Los Angeles.
- Who's he?
- His name is Yusuf Auda.
His government assigned him as a liaison.
They helped us get the hard drive from Ali.
It's a recording of a conversation
that took place four months ago.
- Conversation between who?
- Ali and high-ranking government officials.
These countries not only
knew about the bomb,
- but they bought it and supplied it to Ali?
- Yeah.
- Kim?
- Daddy. What's that noise? Where are you?
I'm in a plane. We found the bomb.
We needed someone to fly it over the desert,
so when it exploded nobody would get killed.
- That someone turned out to be me.
- No, Daddy.
I love you more than anything
in the world. Goodbye.
- George, what the hell are you doing here?
- Brought something for ya. It's a parachute.
I already told you, I'm taking this plane in.
You still got a life, Jack.
What's left but going straight and level
and taking it into a dive? Am I right?
- You really think you can do this?
- Jack, I'm supposed to do this.
Oh, Dad.
Agent Bauer.
- My orders are to take you back to CTU, sir.
- That's affirmative.
Lieutenant, I need you to get ahold of Tony
Almeida over at CTU. Tell him that I made it.
He needs to get ahold
of my daughter, tell her I'm alive.
Radio transmissions are a no-go,
and cell sites are down for miles.
- You'll have to wait till we get there.
- Copy.
Would everyone gather around, please?
This will just take a minute.
George Mason asked me in advance
to thank you all for your dedication.
Thanks to his sacrifice and your hard work,
millions of lives were saved.
And that's a result that we can be proud of.
To say that this has been a long day
would be an understatement,
and I know you're all tired,
but this isn't over yet.
We still got a lot of work to do.
The Cyprus recording is our primary focus.
And that's critical to any military response
that Washington's considering.
So let's get back at it, huh?
Mr Almeida?
I'm supposed to update my office right now.
But I've got nothing to report except that
I've been excluded from this investigation.
Look, I'll tell you what I can when I can.
My country permitted your operatives
to raid Ali's apartment
on condition that I would be
involved in this investigation.
I understand your frustration, Mr Auda.
You can call your office
and tell them anything you like.
But we've got work to do here.
You're simply not authorised to be part of it.
- He doesn't look too happy.
- Yeah. Are the audio guys ready?
They're waiting for you. Where's Michelle?
- Interrogating Ali.
- Why?
To see if he can shed any light
on the recording. We have a meeting.
The president's waiting for confirmation on
the recording's authenticity. Take care of it?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
This tape was recovered
from the hard drive in your apartment.
It's a record of a meeting you had with
these three men on April 5 in Cyprus.
They're all high-ranking officials from
three Arab countries, one of them your own.
The tape proves you conspired with these
men to detonate a nuclear bomb on US soil.
Were there others present
who didn't speak?
You'll tell the interrogators in Guantanamo,
under much less comfortable
circumstances. I'll ask you one more time.
- Tell me what you want me to say, I'll say it.
- I want the truth.
What does the truth matter
when you have this... recording?
- Explain what that means.
- I never spoke to any of these men.
Are you denying
that the meeting took place?
There was never a meeting.
I was not even in Cyprus in April.
- Where were you?
- Berlin.
They'll find out the truth in Guantanamo.
Why would I lie about this,
when I told you the truth about the bomb?
To protect your country.
The bomb was a Second Wave
operation only.
I have never met those men.
Agent Gibson, your team has finished
the analysis of the Cyprus recording?
- Yes, sir.
- Could you walk us through it, please?
We began by obtaining voice samples
for Ali and the three government officials.
We deconstructed sound waves
and isolated unique qualities.
The voices on the Cyprus audio
are in fact those of Syed Ali and
the three government ministers in question.
The recording could have been created
by putting pieces of conversations together?
Yes, but reconstruction
always leaves artefacts,
mismatched acoustical signatures or altered
cadences. We found no such artefacts.
Is there any chance that it could have been
doctored in a way we couldn't detect?
Anything's theoretically possible.
But I can say with absolute certainty
that the finest experts,
using the best equipment,
cannot find any evidence
that this recording
is anything but a genuine and accurate record
of an actual conversation.
A conversation in which these
four men sat in the same room
and conspired to detonate
a nuclear bomb on US soil?
Yes, sir.
I just finished talking with Ali.
He claims that he's never even spoken
to any of the men in the recording.
He says it's a complete fabrication,
and that he was in Berlin
on April 5, not Cyprus.
- He could be telling the truth.
- He still thinks we killed one of his sons.
He's trying to save his family by denying
that his country's behind the nuke.
I agree he has a motive to lie, but if there's
any possibility he's telling the truth,
- I think we need to investigate.
- But he's not.
- I mean, it's obvious.
- It's not obvious to me.
The evidence versus the word of an attempted
mass murderer? It's clear which wins.
- Carrie.
- And, no offence, Michelle,
but your experience
as an interrogator is limited.
- That's enough.
- I sat three feet away from him,
and I believe he is a broken man
without the strength or resolve to lie.
I'll tell the president what Ali said when I
call him to pass on Agent Gibson's findings.
Now, if we don't have anything else here,
I think we're finished, right? Thank you.
CTU managed to detonate the bomb
within a few metres of the coordinates.
I'm going over the field report now.
I'm not seeing any casualty estimates.
We expect zero direct casualties,
or close to it.
Hmm.
I want to give Bauer's daughter
personal condolences.
You won't have to, sir.
Bauer wasn't on the plane
at the time the bomb was detonated.
- Do we know how this happened?
- Another man ended up piloting the plane.
We're still getting the details.
Sir? We just got word from CTU.
They finished their analysis
of the Cyprus audio.
It's real. And we have proof that Syed Ali,
the man behind the bomb,
was given support
from the three different countries.
Here's the transcript of their analysis...
including margins of error.
Do we have any reason
to doubt the veracity of this?
Ali is denying it,
but I suppose that's to be expected.
- Are the Joint Chiefs ready?
- General Bowden has them on standby.
Given the evidence,
we don't have the option of not responding.
I don't see any way around this. Do you?
I want to issue a statement
that there was a nuclear weapon,
but there were no casualties.
I will alert the networks, sir.
And contact the Hill.
Let them know I'll be calling
for an emergency session of Congress.
During which, I'll be asking them
for a formal declaration of war.
Chappelle wants to see your report.
I'm ordering more data points.
I need another 15 minutes.
Fine.
- You all right?
- Just a little tired, like everyone else.
No, I mean, about before.
- It got tense between you and Carrie.
- I can handle Carrie.
You don't have the training
or the experience to read a guy like Ali.
- I shouldn't have put you in that position.
- We should press him.
- They will in Guantanamo.
- It may be too late.
We're sending him now. I'm heading over
to make sure the hand-off goes as planned.
OK.
General Bowden, my understanding is
it'll take between eight and ten weeks
to call up reserve troops and redeploy
forces for a full-scale ground assault.
We have the resources in place
to initiate a rolling start immediately.
Rolling start?
Surgical strikes against early-warning
radar and anti-aircraft installations,
followed immediately by bombing
of targets that will degrade
their military
and telecommunications capabilities.
Can these first strikes be underway by
the time I address the nation this morning?
- When are you scheduled to go on the air?
- Six hours from now.
We'll be ready, sir.
Mr President.
Gentlemen, ladies, would you hold, please?
Deputy Prime Minister Barghouti is calling.
It's his second call
since the bomb was detonated.
We're well past the point of words.
We're about to invade his country.
But he doesn't know that yet. If you don't
take his call, he may read between the lines.
- Mr Deputy Prime Minister.
- Thank you for taking my call.
The Prime Minister wanted me to express
his outrage for what has occurred.
- Thank you.
- That you found the bomb is truly a miracle.
I'm not sure I believe in miracles, sir.
- My people are good at what they do.
- Indeed they are.
I'm sure you're aware that we've arrested
one of your citizens in connection to it.
- Syed Ali.
- An outlaw. He has eluded us for years.
Expect our full cooperation
with his punishment.
I would expect nothing less.
I realise we've had our differences, and
today has been an especially trying day,
but we are both fighting the same battle.
My government remains dedicated
to the destruction of Second Wave,
as well as any other terrorist organisation
that may have been responsible
for this atrocity.
That's good to know.
I understand you will be under
a great deal of political pressure
to respond to what has happened.
I'm confident that you have
the strength to resist.
Don't be concerned about a rush to judgment.
We're merely gathering evidence.
- I appreciate your candour, Mr President.
- And I appreciate your solidarity.
- Of course.
- You'll hear from me soon.
Come on, let's go.
- Hey, Jack. I'm glad you're OK.
- Thanks.
I'll get out of your way.
How can I get ahold of Kim?
I spoke to a Sergeant Griggs
with the San Jose Sheriffs Department.
He sent a man to your sister-in-law's
to meet Kim. That's his number.
OK, thanks.
- George told me he put you in charge.
- Yeah. How about that, huh?
Trial by fire, right?
- You're gonna do great.
- Look, we'll catch up later, all right?
Yeah.
- Sheriff's Department.
- Is Griggs there?
- I can help.
- I need to speak with him.
- He's not here.
- Is this not his personal line?
- What is this regarding?
- I'm Jack Bauer.
- It's regarding my daughter.
- Sergeant Griggs isn't available.
If your daughter is in any danger,
let me assist you.
No, she's not in any immediate danger.
Listen, ma'am...
Fine, just give me the number.
- Same area code, 555-9464.
- OK.
- I'm glad you're OK, Jack.
- Thanks.
I know Tony's running things,
and I don't want to speak out of turn, but...
- I don't know who to talk to.
- About what?
The president's planning military action
based on a recording from Ali's apartment.
It links officials from three
governments to the nuke.
The problem is... Ali claims it was a fake.
- And you believe him.
- I don't know.
We ought to be sure
before we retaliate against them.
That's Tony's call.
I'm trying to get ahold of my daughter.
I understand,
but you’re the one who broke Ali.
You can read him better than anyone here.
Please, Jack, before Ali is gone.
Only he can prove
whether the recording is real.
Fine, I'll talk to him.
See if you can get ahold of this Sergeant
Griggs. Tell him it's regarding my daughter.
- Sheriff's Department.
- This is Michelle Dessler over at CTU.
- I'm looking for Sergeant Griggs.
- Please hold.
There you go.
Bring him out.
I just wanna talk to him
before they get him to Guantanamo.
Gentlemen... hold up.
Let me have a word with the prisoner.
I want you to know we didn't
kill your son. We staged it.
When you get to Guantanamo,
they'll let you speak with your family.
I need to know something.
The Cyprus recording, is it fake?
What I told the woman was true.
Thank you.
We got shots fired on the north roof!
Get back here. He's dead.
You got a radio on you?
Tell them inside,
Syed Ali has just been shot.
We've got a shooter on one
of the southwest roofs. Tell 'em now!
This is Primary Escort. We have
a prisoner down and a sniper on the roof.
Would you take care of that for me?
- LAPD say the perimeter's set up.
- How'd anybody know we were moving him?
Intelligence knew we had him.
The leak could have come from anywhere.
Shooter's gotta be connected
to a country implicated on the recording.
- Maybe.
- They had the most to lose by Ali talking.
- Who else would it have been?
- Ali might have been telling the truth.
- You talked to Michelle.
- No, I talked to Ali.
- Captain Raskind from LAPD for you.
- One minute, please.
You're taking Syed Ali's word
over every expert we have?
Tony, Ali was killed for a reason.
Find out if it was cos he could prove
the recording was fabricated.
- Our best people have verified it.
- Fine.
- Keep the door open, assign men to it.
- I don't have any men to spare.
We're processing intel from nine countries,
and I think this is a dead end.
- Captain Raskind wants to know...
- Could you give me a minute?
Thank you.
Tony, the president is gonna make
some very, very serious decisions
based on the information
that he got from that recording.
If it's not genuine,
you have a responsibility...
You're gonna lecture me on responsibility?
We both know how you work. You consider
going against the grain some kind of a virtue.
- Why are you talking to me like this?
- I got a job to do, I don't wanna be told how.
I'm just trying to help.
I don't need your help, Jack.
Don't get me wrong, I appreciate
everything you've done for us today.
But I think it's time you go get your daughter,
let us handle the rest of this.
Yeah, fine.
- Thanks. Yeah.
- Mr Almeida...
All circuits are busy.
Please try your call again.
Some kind of problem?
Can I just use the bathroom?
- Please, I'll be quick.
- All right, come on.
In the back, on your left. Watch your step.
Casualty estimates for the initial air campaign
are minimal. A dozen at most.
- And the ground campaign?
- There are numerous scenarios,
depending on how long the campaign lasts,
if chemical or biological weapons
are deployed against our troops.
Which, frankly, I think they will be.
OK, take that all into account,
then give me a number, General.
A simultaneous ground assault against
the three countries, which lasts five weeks,
will result in ten to thirty thousand
American casualties.
And if China and Russia
enter the conflict against us?
There's no upper limit
to that number, Mr President.
But it's unlikely. They'll want to insinuate
themselves into control of the oil fields.
- Yes.
- I have Jack Bauer. It's an emergency.
One moment.
Sir, it's Jack Bauer for you.
Excuse me again.
It's good to hear your voice,
but I'm in a meeting with the Joint Chiefs.
I felt this was important enough
to interrupt you.
Syed Ali has just been assassinated.
CTU was transferring him over
to Guantanamo when it happened.
- What are you talking about? By whom?
- We don't know yet, sir.
I think it has to do with the conversation
recorded in Cyprus.
Mr President, I don't believe it's genuine.
- That recording was authenticated.
- Sir, authentication is never 100 per cent.
Do you have evidence?
Ali said he was in Berlin
when the conversation took place.
- He said the recording was fabricated.
- OK, I'm aware of his denials.
Mr President, I'm worried that
someone is trying to manipulate you
into taking the kind of military action
I assume you're about to take.
Look, the fact that Syed Ali was killed does
not prove that the recording was fabricated.
No, sir. I know that. I know it doesn't.
But I feel a responsibility to tell you
I believe he was assassinated
because he was in fact telling the truth.
Do you have any hard evidence, Jack?
Aside from Ali's denials, no, sir.
Nothing concrete.
Listen to me. I don't wanna initiate a military
action based on erroneous information.
- But I can't stop it based on conjecture.
- I understand, sir, I do.
If I were to get you proof,
how much time would I have?
Our military response
is only hours away, Jack.
- You better do it soon.
- Yes, sir. Thank you, Mr President.
We don't have any updates. As soon
as we do, we'll patch them through to you.
- This is Dessler.
- Michelle, it's Jack.
I want you to keep this
information between us, OK?
I talked to the president. He will not halt
any military action unless we provide proof.
Ali was our only proof.
There's gotta be another way
to establish Ali's presence at that time.
Other foreign agencies
must have been tracking him.
- An official from a target country is here.
- What? Here at CTU? Why?
We struck an agreement earlier today.
He's the one who escorted
evidence from Ali's apartment.
- Think he knows something?
- He might.
Tony doesn't want him talking to anyone.
- OK, fine, what's his name?
- Yusuf Auda. A-U-D-A.
I'll pull up his CV and run a background
check. I'll get back to you.
- Jack?
- Kate.
I didn't think...
I thought you weren't coming back.
I didn't think I was either.
- How?
- It's a long story.
But everything's OK, right?
They said the bomb was detonated safely.
No. Everything's fine. It's gonna be fine.
How are you? Are you OK?
Yeah. My dad's still a little shaken up.
I'm sorry.
- Miss Warner.
- I have to go.
- She needs to be debriefed.
- OK. We'll see you in a little while.
- I'm really glad you're OK.
- Thanks.
The Joint Chiefs are revising down their
material estimate between 10 and 20 per cent.
- That's good news, sir.
- None of this is good news, Mike.
General Bowden is ready to walk you
through the strategy statement.
- I need a few more minutes.
- How long should I tell him?
When I'm ready, Mike.
What is it, Mr President?
The telephone conversation with Jack Bauer
keeps playing in my head.
I'm worried that we may be moving too fast.
Mr President, your ability to analyse
a situation is your strongest asset.
But it's also your greatest liability.
I don't wanna make a mistake that
our children and their children will pay for.
Sir, we have evidence
that's been confirmed
by every military and intelligence expert
on the payroll.
Everyone except Jack Bauer.
It's natural for you to be having doubts.
I'd be worried if you weren't having doubts.
But when the public learns what happened,
they'll want a decisive response.
They'll demand it.
We're not responding to satisfy bloodlust.
No, sir, we're not.
We're responding because three countries
colluded with a terrorist group
to explode a nuclear bomb on our soil.
- And we have proof.
- What if the proof is a lie?
- It isn't.
- Are you sure, Mike?
Are you sure?
I'll tell General Bowden you'll call...
when you're ready.
- Mr Auda, my name is Jack Bauer.
- Don't give me another excuse.
I need to ask you a few questions about
the evidence taken from Syed Ali's apartment.
How would I know what was found?
You people refuse to include me. Ask them.
My colleagues might not be interested
in the same questions that I am.
I'm trying to determine whether or not
the evidence could've been compromised.
Before I tell you anything,
tell me what you know.
Whatever was found, they're keeping it from
me, suggesting it incriminates my country.
I'm sorry. You and I are not even
supposed to be talking.
You're asking me to help,
offering nothing in return.
- I know I'm asking a lot.
- Asking too much.
This is Bauer.
- Hello, Jack.
- Who is this?
The only person who can prove Syed Ali was
not in Cyprus in April, meeting Arab leaders.
The recording they found, in case
you haven't figured it out, is bogus.
- How do you know that?
- Because I'm the one who planted it.
- On April 5, I placed it in Ali's apartment.
- And I'm supposed to believe you?
You don't have a choice. That's why I killed
Ali, so you'd have to deal with me.
- How do I know you killed him?
- I almost had to take you out too.
But you moved. I'm dying to know
what you two were talking about.
- What do you want?
- Kate Warner.
Why? Why do you want her?
Get her out of CTU. Bring her to the
intersection of Meridian and Moorpark.
There's a warehouse.
Look for a door under a neon sign.
- My access at CTU is limited at best.
- You're resourceful. You'll find a way.
- You didn't answer. Why do you want her?
- Don't worry about that now.
She hasn't been released.
She's in debriefing.
You got 30 minutes.
Bring her to the warehouse.
30 minutes is not enough time.
What's the problem?
You'll have a problem
if you don't get out. I'll call the cops.
It's nothing like that!
I just need a few things!
Will you lighten up? My wife's pregnant.
Here's some money.
- I'll be quick.
- Keep moving.
- You have to help me.
- Sorry, I can't do anything.
- I'll pay you, all right? How much?
- I don't...
- Don't walk away!
- Just find another store.
How hard would it be
to open up for one minute?!
There's another store ten miles
down the road, west on Route 14.
- No, we're going to the mountains!
- I'm closed. I'm not gonna tell you again.
- Don’t you know what's going on?!
- I'm calling the cops.
- Look, I have cash. I'll pay you double.
- I already closed out the register.
Please, tell him to let me in.
My wife's pregnant. She can't be here.
- Look, open the damn door!
- That's it. That is it.
- Come on!
- 911?
Some guy's trying to bust into my store.
- Is the store open?
- No, but he's threatening me.
- What's your location?
- It's King's Liquor, Soledad Canyon Road.
Officers are on their way.
They always come out at night.
All kinds of crazy people.
- It's starting.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Don't give me that.
"It's starting." What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
No! Stop it!
Stop!
You should have let me in.
I told you to let me in!
Let go of him and get up!
I said, let go of him!
Now get out of here!
I didn't mean for this to happen.
I'm just trying to get to the mountains.
I said, go!
Give me the gun.
- I'm not gonna hurt anyone, I promise.
- Just go.
Go!
- Michelle Dessler.
- Hey, it's me, Jack.
- Was Yusuf Auda helpful?
- No, not yet. He's got some trust issues.
I'm right behind you.
I think there’s another way to prove
that the Cyprus recording was faked.
But I'm gonna need your help -
you're gonna have to trust me.
- Yeah, whatever you need.
- OK, I'll get back to you in a minute.
You should have let me in when I asked you.
My wife is seven months pregnant.
- I didn't want to hurt anyone.
- Just go.
After I pay. I told you I had money,
I didn't come here to steal.
- I said, I wanna pay!
- All right, all right, all right.
I'm not a criminal.
Turn on the TV.
Speculation has continued
to grow around the explosion
spotted by two commercial aircraft
and a weather satellite.
While a statement from the president
is forthcoming,
one source suggested that the blast could
only have been caused by a nuclear explosion.
It's true. My brother works
at a USGS station in Palmdale.
- He overheard a scientist talking.
- You knew about this, didn’t you?
- Keep your hands where I can see them.
- Hey, leave her alone!
Give me the gun.
No.
Put the gun down
and come out with your hands up.
I said, put the gun down
How long did the two men talk?
Just for a few minutes at a time.
And it was mostly in Arabic,
which I understand a little bit.
They didn't seem...
too much in a hurry about anything.
Do you think that they knew each other well?
- Yeah, like they were partners.
- Baker?
- Yeah.
- You did the Macauley interview last week?
I did.
A page is missing from the transcript.
Have a copy of the original?
- Yeah, but I have another hour here.
- Can't wait. Division wants it right now.
- I'm glad I double-checked before it got sent.
- Sorry, I'll be right back.
OK.
I need you to come with me now.
I'm still with Baker,
then I have to deal with my father.
- This is urgent.
- What's going on?
You said everything was fine.
It's not. I'll explain in the car.
- Almeida.
- Yeah, it's Carrie.
- What's up?
- Unless I'm misreading the situation,
- Jack is trying to remove Kate from CTU.
- I'll be right down.
Oh, God!
- Come on.
- I didn't mean to! He came at me!
Please don't let him die!
Look, I didn't mean for this to happen!
It was a mistake!
I was just trying to protect my wife.
- Lower level, space eleven.
- Thanks, Brian. Come on, Kate.
- Where the hell you going?
- I don't have time to explain.
- Let's find the time.
- What are you doing?
Kate, you stay against the wall.
Tony, put down the gun.
Not till you tell me what you’re doing, Jack.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Who do you think you're kidding? You're
not gonna shoot me. Put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
Kate, come on, we gotta go.
Now. Let's go.
Jack! Jack!
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net