Hey, what are you doing there?
Max!
Joshua!
How'd you get here?
Did anyone see you?
It's OK. He's a friend.
Yeah, sure.
You just threw me back there, that's all.
You're Joshua, right?
Joshua. Right.
Original Cindy. Good to meet you.
I'm makin' breakfast. You hungry?
I was gonna come by
and bring you some stuff.
- Come to find Father.
- Father? Who's Father?
Sandeman. He made us.
He's gonna make Max better.
Your love-bug thing
where you can't touch Logan?
Well, get on it, boo.
I'm tired of seeing you mopin'.
This virus bitch has gotta go down
so that you can get busy with your man.
Max and Logan getting busy. That's the plan.
The plan is we're gonna find Father.
Logan's tracking down some leads.
In the meantime, you gotta lay low.
You can't be walking around out there.
Don't mope. I'm on it.
You want some more? We got more food.
Down.
OK.
Eight dollar.
Chill, Pop. It wasn't me, I swear.
Somebody call an ambulance.
Somebody call an ambulance!
They designed her to be the perfect soldier,
a human weapon.
Then she escaped.
In a future not far from now,
in a broken world,
she is haunted by her past.
She cannot run.
She must fight to discover her destiny.
So then I ran a search
of university records.
Figured if Sandeman
was the genius behind Manticore,
he'd probably have some sort of degree
in genetics or biochemistry or something.
- Anything turn up?
- A couple of PhDs but nothing in sciences.
- And what about the house?
- His name wasn't on it.
Mortgage held by an offshore corporation
and the taxes paid from a numbered account.
If you're splicing genes
for a secret government agency,
gotta make sure you cover your tracks.
In May of '08, the bank repo'ed the property
after six months of non-payment,
and it's sat there empty ever since.
- Looks like Sandeman just disappeared.
- Maybe he retired someplace sunny.
Or he ran for his life.
We're talking about Manticore.
The place wasn't exactly
known for job security.
Yeah, well.
If he had time to pack his bags,
he probably would've taken this.
The Manticore symbol.
We're sure he's one of the good guys?
Joshua's sure. That's enough for me.
Maybe we could check it for prints or DNA.
- I don't know. After ten years?
- Worth a shot.
We got nothing on this guy.
Not even a first name.
I'll call Matt Sung.
See if he can get the police lab to do it.
We're gonna find him, Max.
And we're gonna beat this.
I just want things to be the way they were.
You know, when we could hold hands
without you keeling over on me.
- Asha.
- I just got this close to getting busted.
- Listen...
- They ran my papers on the computer.
I knew they were onto them being forged
because they took forever.
So I just got the hell outta there.
- That's a smart move.
- All I wanna do is go home and take a bath.
- Now I gotta find a new fake ID.
- I can probably help with that.
We gotta talk about Manticore.
I'm glad your friend Max and her furry little
friends got outta there, but it's really...
- Hi.
What I meant was we... My group, that is...
The S1Ws,
the political organisation I was...
Yeah. Government's saying Manticore was
just a VA hospital you guys burned down.
Sorry. From me and all my furry little friends.
I gotta get to work. Have fun.
"All I wanna do is take a bath."
All I wanna do is drown her in one.
Don't get mad. It's not her fault
everything handcuffs you to Manticore.
But what is up?
Is someone trying to tell me something?
- Rafer?
- Lie still.
- I'm OK.
- I don't know. You went down pretty hard.
- That was you?
- Sorry. You came out of nowhere.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Relax. I'm a paramedic.
- You deliver pizzas.
- That was just part time.
We spent a night together
and you think you know me?
Lie still.
I gotta check for broken bones.
Next time you wanna cop a feel,
hit me harder and make sure I'm out cold.
No damage. Just a scratch!
Max.
- Matt, did you get it?
- Yeah, just arrived.
Listen, I appreciate you doing this.
No problem.
I'll send the results as soon as I can.
Great.
Biochemist. I'm a scientist.
I'm sure you got a great team of
scientists working at the precinct.
Hello. The boy that died today
in Chinatown, I was there.
I may have been exposed to something.
The coroner's still investigating.
We'll have her report tomorrow.
- I would like to see a copy of that.
- File a request with the ME's office.
- This is totally unacceptable...
- Just follow him.
- Sung.
- Yeah?
You had a sketch artist
working on something?
Yeah. Rumours flying around Chinatown
about some strange guy in an overcoat.
I'll say.
The eyewitness says his face was bleeding.
Could be the dead kid was exposed
to what he's got.
Could be.
Let's keep this under wraps until the autopsy
comes out. I don't want to start a panic.
You haven't been in Chinatown lately.
There's already a panic.
What happened to you?
Where you been?
Been paging you all morning.
I lost my pager
when I got hit on Charles Street.
- But I'm OK, thanks for asking.
- Here, hot run. Sector Nine.
- Can I borrow...
- No. You're not covered on company bikes.
If you so much as break a fingernail,
we both know you'll sue.
Let's go! Bip-bip-bip!
It's called Jam Pony, not Jam Clydesdale.
Hey.
OK, you are a paramedic. You trying
to make me feel bad for not believing you?
No. I came by to give you this.
And to see if you wanted to have lunch.
My way of making up
for our little run-in.
- Listen, I'm really sorry about...
- Forget about it.
How can I? I put my foot so far down
my mouth, I got teeth marks on my knee.
She must hate me.
Really, forget about it.
Eat something.
I'm not really hungry.
About what happened that night...
- I'd rather just forget about that night.
- Me too.
I was in a really weird head space.
I just broke up with my girlfriend,
like, three weeks before.
Anyway, if I came on too strong
I'm sorry, cos I'm not like that.
It's OK.
I came by a couple of times
and no one knew where you were.
I had to deal with family stuff.
It's complicated.
- Family stuff's always complicated.
- You have no idea.
Thought maybe you had
a boyfriend somewhere.
That's complicated too.
Which has gotta be
the understatement of the century.
Max and I danced around each other
for almost a year.
When we finally figure out what's going on
between us, this virus thing happens.
- We can't be together.
- What do you mean? Why not?
It's hard to explain. It's like...
It's too intense.
Sometimes I think maybe
we're just not meant to be.
I mean, if it's right,
why does it have to be so hard?
I don't know.
Logan's probably just better off without me.
I just want you to be happy.
He'd be lucky to be with you.
Anybody would be.
I should go.
- I'd better get back to work.
- Yeah, me too.
You don't have ID. Asha!
See you around.
This is your bus ticket, sir.
Yeah, that mutant. I saw it here yesterday.
Grabbed a pigeon, bit its head off.
Looked at me like I was next.
- It's worse than I thought.
- What?
Mutant infestation. They're here as well.
Were you born dumb or do you put in work?
Ambulance, we gotta get an ambulance.
22, all Chinese.
- What did the ME say?
- If it's what killed the kid yesterday,
it's some kind of pathogen.
She's never seen anything like it.
- I mean, is it some kind of toxin or what?
- She's running tests, trying to figure it out.
- You see Eyes Only's hack about Manticore?
- Yeah. Why?
The government says it never existed, but the
word on the street is the place burned down
and a bunch of genetically-engineered
whatsits got out.
- Those are just rumours.
- There's a rumour one's hiding in Chinatown.
Supposedly deformed,
bleeds through his skin.
- You think they're connected?
- I don't know. Eyes Only might.
- Can you talk to him for me?
- I'll try and get to him.
- I appreciate it.
- Sure thing.
Listen. I'm sorry, Matt.
- I know this is close to home.
- Yeah.
- It was horrible.
- Those poor people.
The news said anybody there should
get checked for infection. I'm scared.
Can I talk to you?
Five minutes, then I start docking.
Even if there is a screwed-up transgenic, it
doesn't mean he's got what killed the people.
When you were at Manticore,
were you aware of any experiments
that involved exposure
to virulent bacteria or pathogens?
- No. Why are you jumping to conclusions?
- Because the guy's been seen in the area.
If this is linked to me and my furry little
friends, why are all the victims Chinese?
- Manticore's big on equal opportunity.
- Could be that it takes prolonged exposure.
If this guy was downtown,
maybe it'd be rich white people dying.
Ever think it was something they ate?
Or they got bit by the same mosquito?
Or some bug got loose from a lab?
Come on, Max!
This is nothing new to Manticore. Look what
they did to you and me, for God's sake.
Just because I'm poison doesn't mean
we all are. Your five minutes are up.
Hold it right there.
- I love what you've done with the place.
- Laying low.
Good, cos it's dangerous out there,
especially these days.
Like it here. Father's books. Father's house.
Yeah. Listen, about Father.
Logan's come up empty.
He's still working on it.
He'll find Sandeman,
just as soon he's done saving the world...
from us.
Max and Logan. That's the plan.
I don't know.
I'm starting to think there is no plan,
and if there is I'm not clued in at all.
Father ever talk to you about fate?
You know, like whether
some things just weren't meant to be?
Canine with human DNA not meant to be,
then Joshua.
Max and Logan not meant to be,
then getting busy.
- We'll see.
- You'll see.
This virus bitch going down.
It's him.
- Hello.
- If you're calling to apologise...
I'm not but I will if that's what it takes.
Spit it out.
- Asha was heading home and...
- She left already?
Yeah, and she got arrested by sector cops.
I need your help.
- You want me to save her?
- I don't know who else to ask.
- Try Sung.
- I did. He's not answering his page.
- Smart man.
- If they run her prints and see who she is...
- Yeah, yeah. Where is she?
- Sector Four headquarters.
We'll meet you at Crash in an hour.
Look, I told you. I left my ID at work.
I can bring it in tomorrow.
Your prints came through, Ms Barlow.
We know you're with the S1W.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I want the names and addresses
of everyone in your group.
This is crazy.
This department does not take
terrorist activities lightly.
The S1W are not terrorists.
Tell me what I want to know
or this is going to get ugly.
I'm gonna kick your ass!
It's my thing. Come on.
You know a girl named Max?
Hangs out here a lot?
Yeah, hard to miss but hasn't been in tonight.
- I'll have a beer.
- Take that one.
You know Max?
- Yeah. You?
- Yeah.
- Rafer.
- Logan.
Right.
Listen. Thanks.
I know you didn't have to.
It was a favour to Logan.
Besides, it wouldn't be right for you
to take the rap for something you didn't do.
You going in? I'm just gonna get
my ID from Logan and go, so...
- You're waiting here for Max, right?
- Yep.
- That's my cue to go.
- You don't have to.
- Things with Logan are screwed up just now.
- Yeah, but he's crazy about you.
She digs you, man. I'm just gonna back off.
Have a seat.
I don't know how things are gonna
play out between us, so I'm gonna go.
I wouldn't want to mess
anything up for her. Neil!
Yeah?
- You know Asha?
- Yeah, I know Asha.
- I'll give it to her.
- Great. Thanks.
See ya.
Good night.
Help! Help, help!
Help!
Help, help!
What are you doing here?
I told you I'd call you.
- He's clean.
- Clean?
Not a trace of the pathogen.
Let me take a look at that.
What is that?
Looks like a tattoo.
Why do I get the feeling
you guys aren't tellin' me something here?
- What's goin' on?
- You killed an innocent man.
That's what's going on.
- Looked like he was hurting the kid.
- We know, Matt.
- Something killed all those people.
- Lab tests came back today.
It's not an infectious agent.
They were exposed to the pathogen directly.
- Where'd it come from?
- Don't know. I can tell you this.
Mother Nature didn't cook this thing up.
The pathogen's genetically engineered.
If the pathogen's man-made,
then either it escaped from a lab
or somebody's exposing
people to it on purpose.
No, don't worry. I got my hands on
a copy of the ME's report.
They're chasing their tails.
I'm ready when you are.
All I need is a test subject.
I'll be expecting you.
He was downstairs people.
Didn't turn out so good.
Lives in the basement in case Manticore
needs to cut him up for spare parts.
Finally gets out in the world,
and they shoot him dead like he's an animal.
This is why I'm always on you
because it's not safe out there.
People get real scared
when things are different.
Yeah, but what I forgot to tell you is, when
they get scared, they can get really mean.
I'm sorry.
There's a rumour going around the black
market about a new kind of bio-weapon,
capable of distinguishing
between population groups.
A nasty trick no one's been able
to pull off before.
Maybe some kind of anti-Asian hate group.
Maybe. Maybe what's happening
is some kind of field test.
- Why do you say that?
- No one's claimed responsibility.
And look at the way it's playing out -
starting with a single victim,
then a handful in a narrowly targeted area.
I'm not sure what's worse.
Somebody's out to kill me and mine
or that they're using us as guinea pigs.
- Got anything else for me?
- I'm working on some leads but it's slow.
Internet's been crashing all day.
- Do what you can.
- Talk to you later.
Hello.
Hey. I just wanted to call.
- I never got to thank you for springing Asha.
- No big deal.
And because you were right.
I shouldn't have jumped to conclusions.
Whatever it was that killed those people
had nothing to do with transgenics.
Guess our thing has just got me
a little spun, you know?
Yeah, me too.
Is that me or you?
Think it's me. Hold on.
- Logan? I'm at Crash. Come over.
- Max, come over. I'm at Crash.
- I don't think so.
- Not tonight.
I have someone on the other line.
- All right.
- OK. See you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- So.
- Anyway, I just wanted to say...
sorry about everything.
Yeah, me too.
- Good night.
- Hey, Max.
- Hey.
What delays?
I told you three steps
were gonna be involved. Did I not?
Step one, target the pathogen
to a single individual.
Expose him to it via airborne dispersal,
make sure he's the only one it affects.
Went off without a hitch, did it not?
Excuse me.
Could you not put that there, please?
It is a very expensive piece of equipment.
Thank you.
Step two.
Target the pathogen
to a specific race of people.
The Chinese at the bus stop.
I used gene expression on the base pair
for the epicanthic fold. You know, the eyelid?
Worked perfectly. No one died but them, yes?
Your technology is very impressive.
But let's move on to step three.
I'm ready. You see,
it was easy with the Chinese.
I had specific gene sequences
that I could target.
But the kids you're targeting...
Wow, that was tough.
Because they're just
a little bit of everything.
- In the end...
- Cyril.
...I targeted
their immunological surveillance cells.
Cyril! Action is character.
Show me some.
- I showed you, didn't I?
- Yes.
I paid you half upfront.
I gave you everything that you asked for.
Now it's time for you to show me.
This is your test subject.
No problem.
We can do it right now if you'd like.
No, I wanna do it in the field.
I wanna know for sure.
Well, you're the boss.
How does tomorrow sound?
Assuming it all goes according to plan, how
soon can you ramp up pathogen production?
Well, I can manufacture enough to blanket
the entire western seaboard by Friday.
How you disperse it is, of course, up to you.
These are good for small areas, but they're
expensive and very hard to get ahold of.
- We'll use helicopters.
- Well, that sounds like a plan.
By the weekend, there won't be a transgenic
left alive from here to San Diego.
Good. Maybe I'll play
a round of golf on Sunday.
Matt, I think I may have a lead. It said
in the police reports that, both times,
when the boy died and at the bus station,
people thought they heard fireworks.
- Yeah? So it's Chinatown.
- No, listen.
There's a type of bio-agent
dispersion cartridge.
It's fired from a hand-held launcher,
triggered by an altimeter.
According to my source, a buyer just shelled
out for three of them, 20 grand apiece.
Took delivery last week.
- Tell me you got an address.
- Have I ever let you down?
- Three steps are gonna be involved here.
- Why am I not surprised?
Step one. We take the test subject
into the target area. We release him.
Step two.
We use this to disperse the pathogen.
There's enough to kill
any transgenic in a two-mile radius.
That's ample to cover Sector Four.
- What if he escapes the kill zone?
- No, that would be impossible.
It takes a minute for the plume to hit
ground level and four minutes to dissipate.
There's no way on earth
he could make it out alive.
Step three.
We track him and we retrieve the body.
I have a correction to step three.
You track him and retrieve the body.
I'm staying away from here
until this is done.
What if you messed up
and got a couple of base pairs wrong?
We could end up
with a sector full of dead people.
- You don't trust me?
- Make a believer out of me, Cyril.
You'll get the rest of your money.
You have a nice day, now.
Matt.
What is it?
Max, it's me. We got a problem.
You're free to go.
You can run but you can't hide.
What the hell are the cops doin' here?
Son of a bitch.
Drive.
Units three and four, move into position.
They're gonna test the pathogen on an X5.
He busted out of a van on Mercer,
took off down 11.
- I gotta get him out.
- In a minute, it'll hit ground level.
The sector will be toxic
for four minutes after that.
- I'm going in.
- Max!
Jam Pony messenger comin' through.
- Max! Max!
- Hold up. Passes only.
No, wait!
Lady.
I have no idea who you are,
but you just cost me five million dollars.
Thanks for letting him stay the night.
He's had a rough couple of days.
Logan's gonna help me
get him over the border tomorrow.
Killing us all, that was the plan.
It still is. We just got lucky this time.
See you first thing in the morning.
You lay low, little fella.
You too, big fella.
Convinced Sung to let me hang on
to everything we found in the guy's lab.
Didn't want whoever hired him
to get their hands on it again.
- He's a good guy, Sung.
- Yeah, he is.
He's got a lot of questions.
Not sure what I'm gonna tell him.
As little as possible
is usually a good idea.
I'll do my best.
Did I mention I was sorry
for jumping to conclusions?
Yeah.
- Anything turn up on Sandeman's cane?
- Nothing but traces of Rodentia calcium.
The rats tried to eat it.
- Another dead end.
- Yeah.
Listen, about the other night at Crash.
Didn't know you were gonna be there.
Same with me.
I just needed to get out.
I know the feeling.
So.
Anyway.
Rafer.
Asha.
Visiontext Subtitles: Julie Clayton
ENGLISH
www.tvsubtitles.net