- Reza's parents are here.
- Where is Reza?
Men from the government are talking to him.
Who wired that money
into Syed Ali's accounts?
Bob Warner, Marie's father.
Come with me, please.
- What did you tell them?
- The truth.
How did you get in here
without my authorisation?
- I need to talk to you.
- You're not my wife any more.
- It's not about us.
- Then what?
There are members of your own
administration allying against you.
That's why I came here today.
I need to get you out of here
because I want you to be safe.
- OK.
- Come on.
Your daughter's not with
any of the departments.
Then where the hell is she?
Give her to me, Kim.
We need to get out of here.
Get his car keys.
Nina killed your wife.
My goal is the same as yours, to stop
this bomb. Who is the man in Visalia?
The man in Visalia is Mamud Faheen. He's
the only one who knows where the bomb is.
The team's assembled in Visalia.
We'll have tactical and field units. Jack...
It's all right. It's all right. Just take it easy.
Pull up 30 feet from the left wing.
Escort, lay back.
Move.
Jack drugged Miller
to get me alone. Tell Mason.
- Is he in the van?
- Yeah.
He's gonna come to in 20 minutes.
He'll have a headache.
Here's command authority.
- I owe you, Doug. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Get in the plane.
Agent Bauer. Rick Phillips, FBI.
Harris and I will be
your transit team to Visalia.
We'll act as reinforcements
once we're on the ground.
So, we're clear here, Jack?
I know what you did to Ed Miller.
Rick, right? Do yourself a favour.
Stay out of this.
Do your job, get us to Visalia.
My job is to make sure this runs smoothly.
That means keeping her safe.
Consider me your new chaperone.
I need two lines set up through CTU.
One for mobile, one for the translator.
It'll be tricky cos their
phone lines are sketchy.
It's already done.
Good.
Way to go, Kate.
You broke his parents' hearts, too.
I'm so sorry, Marie. But I don't know
what these government people found.
And believe me, I wish they
hadn't have found anything.
But aren’t you curious?
Why are they asking Dad questions now?
You started a witch-hunt in our family.
No, Marie. It's because Reza
is connected to some bad people.
- Maybe even terrorists.
- You're out of your mind.
We're not gonna put our heads in the sand,
Marie. Or this could end up hurting Dad.
We're not gonna let that happen.
Come with me.
What did you tell them?
What did you accuse my father of?
I didn't accuse him of anything.
It's his company.
You're pointing your finger
at him to cover yourself!
- Kate!
- Stay out of this.
You don't talk to her like that.
You listen to me.
I have done more for your father
than you will ever know.
And all I've ever gotten from you
is suspicion and resentment. I'm sick of it.
I didn't connect you to a terrorist.
No? Then who did?
I don't know any terrorists!
All I know is you paid for someone
to dig up dirt on me.
Apparently, he did.
No, he didn't, because all he found
out was stuff about Bob, not me.
So if anybody's guilty, it is your father.
- Don’t you make this about my father.
- Stop it. Stop, Kate! Both of you, stop it!
Nice work, Kate.
Call me when you get that.
- I'll have it today. Four o'clock too late?
- No.
- I'll talk to you then.
- Yeah, good. Alrighty. Bye-bye.
If it isn't the Chief of Staff himself. Mike!
Sherry.
You look beautiful... as always.
What are you doing here?
Did David ask you to come here?
No. I just showed up on my own.
So, how have you been?
- Fine, Mike. Just fine.
- Yeah?
Yeah. You know, it's been a challenging
year. But what is it they say?
We... learn from our mistakes
and grow from our misfortunes.
Have you told that to David?
No.
I don't think he's ready
to hear that yet. Not now.
But he is waiting for you,
so why don’t you just go on in?
I'll see you later... I'm sure.
Here you go, sir.
Don't speculate, don't say anything.
We don't know where he is.
- That is our position.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right, good. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Sir, we have to talk about Ron Wieland.
What about him? Does anybody
know we have him sequestered?
No, but Jenny got a call from his production
crew. They haven't seen him in four hours.
They'll figure out the last person
they saw him with was you.
Then leak a story.
Mike. Good to see you.
I got here as soon as I could. Hi, Lynne.
Mike.
Armus brought me up to speed
on the Wieland situation.
I did some research, found out there
is precedent for the executive branch
taking action against the press
at times of national crisis.
So, when you say leak a story,
what kind of a story?
Make it appear as though Wieland
went to Portland on a personal matter.
Armus can arrange that. It's a band-aid,
but it'll get us through the day.
- Talk to Armus. Put it in motion.
- Yes, sir.
- I saw Sherry on my way in.
- Oh.
- Should I attach any significance to that?
- It was her decision to come here.
That's what she said. But I have to tell you,
I'm surprised you're allowing her to stay.
For the time being, Mike.
Just for the time being.
Let's go to the OC. I'll bring you
up to speed. There's a lot to cover.
- You wanna send that on to Division?
- Yes, sir.
- Mr Mason?
- Yeah?
- I just got off the phone with Ed Miller.
- How's it going between Jack and Nina?
He doesn't know. Jack drugged him
and got on the plane without him.
Please tell me you're kidding.
Sloane's bringing Ed back now.
What should I do?
They're on a plane.
There's nothing anybody can do.
Except hope that his impulse for revenge
doesn't cloud his judgement.
- You mean like drugging one of our agents?
- What can I say? The guy's a little crazy.
That's why I didn't want him here
in the first place, but... he gets results.
And we need some
pretty big results here, so...
Just because Sherry tells you that
there's a conspiracy against you,
that doesn't make it true.
But if it is true, it will affect every
aspect of our response to this bomb.
Sherry was right about
the military evacuation of LA.
That's specific information.
She still has well-routed sources.
But a conspiracy?
Don't forget where she's coming from.
She may have her own agenda.
I'm well aware of that, Mike. She's on
a tight leash. I wanna find her source.
Let me look into this
so-called cabal against you.
If there's any substance to it,
I'll uncover it.
Right now, the country needs
your attention on the situation in LA.
Start with Stanton.
Stanton?
The head of NSA, conspiring against
the president of the United States?
Aside from the implications if that were
true, hasn't he always been an ally to you?
Yes. But he's also Eric Rayburn's boss.
It's not inconceivable Rayburn
could be doing Stanton's bidding.
- They have always been on the same page.
- That's not enough to indict Roger.
I know. That's why I want you to check him
out. I'm hoping you can prove me wrong.
I'll talk to Roger as soon as I settle in,
see if I can get a read on him.
Thanks, Mike.
- How long until we land?
- About ten minutes.
- How far is Faheen from the airport?
- I'll tell you when we land.
We are fighting the clock, so you better start
talking. How far is Faheen from the airport?
We need her to cooperate, Jack.
Threatening her isn't gonna help.
Fine.
Get her changed.
I need her to look like a civilian.
Come on, let's go.
No.
Here. She doesn't leave my sight.
Everything's working out, right?
Why don’t you come by? It's not
the Ritz-Carlton but it works for us.
- OK, I'll come on down.
- I gotta go.
- Yeah?
- Jack's about to land in Visalia.
- Have they got a location for Faheen?
- No. Not until they land.
- Stay on it. I'll be down in a minute.
- Right.
Double espresso au lait, and it's hot.
Out of three. And five cents is your change.
Hello?
John, it's your father.
- Hello? You there?
- Yeah, yeah. I'm here.
Look, I... I know it's been a while.
- Two years.
- That long?
- Yeah.
- That's my fault.
John, I'd really like to see you today.
- I can't.
- It's important.
Dad, listen, you can't just call me
out of the blue and expect me to jump.
I don't really want to see you,
and even if I did, I can't. I'm busy.
I know I screwed up. I understand
if I'm not your favourite person.
But can you do this one thing for me?
Come to CTU. You know where that is, right?
I can't do it today, Dad.
I'm in the middle of something.
- Tell me what's going on.
- I need to see you, that's what's going on.
You're not listening to me, Dad. I'm gonna
have to call you when I have a chance.
Get up.
Let's go.
- I'm Agent Dockerty.
- Jack Bauer. Phillips and Harris.
We're all set up.
All we need now is a location.
Where we going, Nina? What's the location?
- A thrift store on North Collins.
- The name?
- Crescent Collectibles.
- Our transportation?
Three teams, three vehicles.
They're waiting for your orders.
Crescent Collectibles is in
the De Anza district. That's not too far.
- We can set up base camp here.
- Do it. Take her.
- What you wanna do with her?
- She stays with me.
Why? Keep her here
and my guys will watch her.
- I'm gonna use her.
- Use her how?
You'll see.
- All right, everyone. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Roger.
- Mike. I heard you were here.
I understand the president handed
Eric Rayburn his walking papers.
Eric messed up.
The president was right to dismiss him.
Still, he fired someone you appointed.
It takes character to support that.
I got a nasty workload today.
You have to excuse me.
Actually, the president wants me
to insert myself into your day.
That might be difficult.
I'm moving a mile a minute here.
I understand. I'd like to look at any paper
you have on the most active leads.
Let me play catch-up.
All right. We can use a little help
in the civil response area.
Great. I'll be working up here in four.
Get me what you got.
- Update me.
- CTU Los Angeles is yielding good leads.
They raided a warehouse within city limits
and found weapons-grade nuclear material.
Langley is using satellite playback
to determine who was there.
- A suspect was killed?
- There was a shoot-out.
Division's having a hard time ID'ing the body.
What's this?
Jack Bauer is still involved
in the investigation.
I thought he was dismissed
after his assignment.
He's heading the team
that's tracking Mamud Faheen.
And Nina Myers, the woman you granted
immunity to, she's helping them.
Bauer and Nina Myers
are working together?
Yes, sir. I believe he volunteered.
- What's the time divisibility?
- From the time we break in, 30 seconds.
- What about the roof?
- We're looking to see if it's viable.
It's not. He'll have sensors on the wall.
You go through the front door,
Faheen'll commit suicide.
If he's so willing to die, why'd he leave LA?
He doesn't want to be collateral damage,
but he'll die to protect the plan.
We can't take a chance.
We need this guy alive.
- Gas canister?
- He knows our protocols, and he's prepared.
- How does he know your protocols?
- She gave them to him.
It doesn't matter. Nina, you're going in.
- What?
- He knows you.
- He also thinks I'm in prison.
- Make him believe you got out.
The day his bomb's going off?
He'll know I'm lying.
You're a good liar. The only way he's gonna
know is if you let him. We need 30 seconds.
He will put a bullet in my head before I say
hello, and then he'll turn the gun on himself.
We'll make sure he doesn't
turn the gun on himself.
- How's it looking?
- Good. We're just waiting for the feeds.
Do we know what dialect Faheen speaks?
- Yeah. Nina gave us the information.
- Mr Mason? Tony Almeida's on the line.
- Yeah, Tony.
- Naiyeer's starting to talk.
He says Bob Warner is the one
that had dealings with Syed Ali.
Warner claims he doesn't know anything.
Bring them both in.
We'll separate them and turn up the heat.
Are you giving me the OK to arrest them?
- If they don't come willingly, yes.
- On what charge?
I don't care if it's jaywalking,
just bring 'em in.
OK. You got it.
- What's going on with my father?
- Give me a minute, please.
I need you to get Bob Warner.
We're gonna finish this up at CTU.
Got it.
Reza, I'm gonna need you to come with us.
- Come with you where?
- Back to CTU.
- For what?
- Further questioning.
I'm not going with you anywhere.
Look, I'm not arresting anybody... yet.
But I will if you force me to.
Now, you're coming with us either way.
How we do this is entirely up to you.
Do what the man says. Don't argue with him.
- Bob, I haven't done anything wrong.
- Reza.
Reza, please, do this for me.
OK?
- Then I'm coming with you.
- We can't take you with us.
Then I'll follow you.
You've ruined my wedding day.
I'm not gonna let you separate me
from my fiancé.
Right this way.
Dad?
Call everyone, explain
the wedding's been postponed.
I want you to call Larry. Tell him where I am.
- Dad, Larry's a tax attorney.
- It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. He'll know what do.
- OK?
- All right.
Good afternoon.
You two haven't been formally introduced.
Lynne Kresge, Sherry Palmer.
Lynne. It's lovely to meet you.
Mrs Palmer. Mr President, there were
a few guidelines from Director Stanton
that I wanted to go over
with you in this meeting.
OK. Let me just break the ice here.
Lynne, I have invoked executive privilege
and have granted Sherry
a provisional security clearance.
- I see.
- This meeting is about the possibility
of people inside this administration
who may be organising against me.
- Against you?
- David.
Maybe you should bring Lynne up to speed
on where we are with Roger Stanton.
- Mr President?
- Things have been happening too fast today.
Our problems are compounded
by the possibility of a dissenting faction.
- You think Roger might be a part of that?
- It's possible.
If you don't mind my asking, sir,
what led you to this hypothesis?
It troubles me to articulate this, Lynne,
but the ambassador's helicopter accident
solved a lot of Roger Stanton's issues.
- Those issues were shared by many...
- I'm so sorry to interrupt, David.
But there's something else
that you probably don't know, Lynne.
And that is that Roger Stanton
has been having secret meetings
with the minority leader in the Senate,
and Eric Rayburn has been in attendance.
Actually, Sherry,
I am aware of those meetings.
They were trying to forge a bipartisan base
in order to stop questionable allocations
made by the Armed Services Committee.
And, sir, the only reason
I did not brief you on this earlier
is because the vote is not
for another two months.
But I have very detailed records,
if you would like to take a look at them.
This doesn't solve our problems today.
We've got to avert a disaster and we can't do
that if our own people are working against us.
Now, I need to know that Roger Stanton
is supporting this administration.
I'm already working alongside Roger.
Lynne, I'd like you to keep track
of your conversations with him as well.
Now, I've put together a list of people on the
Hill who might be able to help in this matter.
Thank you, Mike.
LA Investigations. Paul Koplin speaking.
Hi. This is Kate Warner.
Is Ralph Burton there?
No. I'm sorry, Kate, Ralph's not here.
Can I help you with something?
- I need to talk to Ralph.
- He left for the day.
He works for me. I'm familiar with the case.
Is there something I can do for you?
I need some help.
I have to get into
my father's private records.
Lynne? Lynne?
- Yes?
- Can I have a sec?
Sure.
I know that you're uncomfortable with me
taking some of these tasks from you.
After all, I'm not officially on David's staff.
Mrs Palmer, my discomfort has nothing
to do with you being on his staff.
My only concern is to serve the president.
I need to know the people around him
are competent. I don't know you.
You seem like a pretty smart woman,
so let me explain something to you clearly.
Mm.
David did not get here by himself.
He's had competent people
around him his entire life.
Obviously, you're one of them.
Not necessarily the best, just the most recent.
So have some respect for those of us
who put him into office.
We just might be able to help you.
Fair enough.
Be careful, Sherry.
I need Lynne.
Don't turn this into a competition.
I understand.
I just... need her to know that I'm not
just around here as window-dressing.
- I'm sure she got the message.
- I'll behave. Promise.
Sherry... you don't have
a lot of friends here today.
In fact, it seems like every time I turn around,
somebody's advising me to send you away.
Then why don’t you?
Because you may be able to get
information that nobody else can.
OK, slow down.
As soon as we get a positive ID,
we'll be in within 30 seconds.
- This is it.
- Get out.
Get out!
All teams on alert.
Nina is in play. Nina is in play.
This is team two. We've got her.
Roger that, team two.
Stay on frequency one.
- Michelle, can you read me?
- Copy.
OK, she's in. We're moving into position now.
Is there something I can help you find?
- I need to see Mamud.
- I'm sorry, I don't know any Mamud.
Tell him Nina is here to see him.
Nina?
Wait here, please.
Go, go, go.
Come with me.
Michelle, I've got static. There's nothing
on my monitor. What's going on?
She's leading her through
a door into a hallway.
Against the wall.
Hands in the air.
They're checking her for weapons.
- What are they saying?
- They thought she was in prison.
Nina said she escaped.
Now they’re taking her into another room.
It looks like the one off the east exit.
- Who is she talking to?
- I can't tell. The target's still in shadow.
What are they saying?
She said... She's explaining who
she had to pay to escape from prison.
- Jack, should we go?
- Not until I have confirmation it's Faheen.
- My audio went dead.
- I lost mine, too.
- OK, that's it. Everybody go!
- OK, OK.
Stand in position!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go!
Phillips! Faheen's unconscious!
She's gone. Nina's gone.
Secure the building.
This is Phillips.
We need medics at the east entrance.
Drop it.
We're leaving LA now, Aunt Carol. We'll
probably be another four or five hours.
OK, we will. Bye.
- Damm it.
- You gotta be kidding.
- Just play it cool.
- Cool? We're in a stolen car.
- Licence and registration?
- Did I do something wrong?
You were speeding.
- Registration, too.
- This is my boss's car.
I'm not sure where he keeps it.
I'm sure it's in here somewhere.
- I think this is it.
- Here you go.
I'll be right back.
- What are you doing?
- Anything else I can do?
- No, Ken. I got it from here.
- Got it.
I'm sorry, John.
Hey, I told you I needed to see you, right?
What happened here?
Never could get you
to watch the news, could I?
If you're looking to bond, having your son
arrested isn't the best way to do that.
I don't have much time, John. Things are
happening here. I can't go into it fully.
- You could never go into anything.
- It's my work.
- Look into it if you start a second family.
- That's not gonna happen.
Look... I understand if you're angry.
I'm not angry, Dad. I don't care.
I really just don't understand.
What are you trying to do here?
I got this bank account.
Nobody knows about it.
It's got a couple hundred thousand
dollars in it. I want you to have it.
The number to my book-keeper, who I've
spoken to. He'll be transferring the money.
You bringing me here to tell me
you're giving me money?
What did you expect me to do? Expect me
to give you a hug? I don't want your money.
Then give it to your mom. I'm sure she does.
- Cos thing is, I'm not going to be needing it.
- Why is that?
Why is that, Dad?
You don't bring me here, offer me a small
fortune, then not tell me what's going on.
I'm dying, John.
You son of a bitch.
Is it cancer or something?
Something like that, yeah.
Look, John... something bad
is gonna happen in Los Angeles today.
- And I need you to leave town.
- You want me to leave now?
Go to Phoenix and stay with
your mom for a little while.
I mean it. It's dangerous to be here.
I can't explain it to you,
but you just have to go, OK? Just go.
Dad, listen. I don't... This doesn't matt...
Damm it!
You're a good kid.
I hope I didn't mess you up too bad.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Get out of here, all right?
Just get out of here, OK?
Oh, God.
The vehicle
is registered to a Gary Matheson.
- We can't let him take us back to LA.
- I know.
Why's he taking so long?
- You say this is your boss's car?
- Yes.
- Who's the little girl?
- I'm her au pair.
- Her what?
- She baby-sits her.
I wasn't talking to you.
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna let you get off with just a warning
this time. But you slow down, all right?
- Yes, Officer. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Hold up!
You want to step out of the car
and open up the trunk?
Step out of the car and open up the trunk.
Put your hands on your head
and lay on your stomach.
Get down. Get down! Get down.
Get out of the car!
Keep your hands on your head.
- What's going on?
- Lay down on the ground.
Carla! Oh, my God! He killed her!
- What's happening, Kim?
- Megan, get back in the car!
Put your hands behind your head.
Stay there. Cross your legs. Stay still.
Officer in need of assistance.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net