You may not be able to contact me.
- Why?
- Chappelle became a problem.
I had to take him out of play
and they're onto me.
- They'll take me out soon.
- Who do I contact if I need help?
Michelle is setting up an off-site station.
- You're under arrest. Where's Dessler?
- I can find her.
Affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
Kim? Hello?
- Who are you?
- I'm Kate Warner.
Your father sent me to come get you.
Why would my dad send someone
he'd just met to come get me?
He trusts me.
The sooner we leave, the sooner
you and your dad can be together.
The Attorney General said
you'd want me for your counsel.
- What have they told you?
- You've been removed from office.
The evidence was manipulated
by a man named Peter Kingsley.
I need you to find out all you can about him.
- What happens now?
- We got one last play. Deliver Kingsley.
He's far too dangerous,
and you'll never get close to him.
You're right. I won't, but you will.
Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's been killed.
If you say you can deliver him,
that should get his attention.
I want the tapes that you made
of our conversation.
I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
All right. LA Coliseum, gate 18, 30 minutes.
- What support will you get from CTU?
- As of now, none. Ow!
Jack? Jack!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Damn it. The car won't start.
We gotta get out of here.
My seat belt's jammed.
Mrs Palmer, I'm gonna need your help.
Mrs Palmer, please don't do this.
I'm sorry, but I have to take care of myself.
When I'm free I'll call an ambulance.
- You can't do this!
- I don't have a choice.
You're a very impressive man,
but you see everything as
either good or bad, just like David.
- The world is so much more complicated.
- No, it's simple.
There's a war about to start and you're
the only person who can help me stop it.
- What about the president?
- He turned away from me.
After 25 years of building a life together,
a family, he turned me away.
Eventually they will connect you
to this conspiracy.
That bomb was never supposed to go off.
None of this was supposed
to happen this way.
I know. I believe you.
You can put an end to it now.
If you help me get Kingsley,
your husband will get his presidency back.
That will be because of you.
Mrs Palmer, please.
God damn it!
What do you want me to do?
There's a knife in the glove box.
Help cut me out.
Come on in.
This is much better. It's simpler.
We gotta be able to explain this thing.
- I need to talk to you, Mike.
- I'll be down in five minutes.
Mike.
It's important.
Excuse me.
What is it?
It's a file on Peter Kingsley.
They pulled it up a few minutes ago.
Peter Kingsley, the man Jack Bauer
thinks is behind the bomb.
There's a record of phone calls he made,
as recently as six hours ago,
to a soldier named Jonathan Wallace.
Wallace was a member
of the Coral Snake brigade.
He apparently killed his own men.
I know who Wallace is.
The planes have passed over
their final checkpoint
and will reach their targets within the hour.
Our primary targets are all military,
but one includes a command-and-control
centre inside a residential area.
As smart as our weapons have become,
there may be some collateral damage.
You mean civilian casualties.
Yes, sir.
- There's no way to avoid these?
- I'm afraid not.
Then it's something
we're just gonna have to live with.
Ryan Chappelle.
- Ryan, this is Mike Novick.
- How can I help you, sir?
I know there’s been some confusion today
about the veracity of the Cyprus audio.
Not really. Our teams came
to the same conclusion as Langley.
Do you know if Bauer's still trying to find
evidence that the recording was fabricated?
Yes, but he's operating outside our authority.
I want you to assist his investigation.
- Sir, I don't even know where he is.
- Then find him.
I'm not sure why you're asking me to do this.
I was told we're at war
and to proceed accordingly.
We're not at war yet.
You have 30 minutes to report back to me
the findings of Bauer and your efforts.
- But sir...
- That's a direct order, Ryan.
You have my channel.
Call me back on this line. That's all.
- I'll be on the plane in an hour.
- Why the delay?
The bomb detonating in the wrong location
created a little extra work.
Nothing to worry about, I hope.
Not at all. I won't bore you with the details.
Bore me.
I still have to take care of Alex Hewitt.
Hewitt is the only one
who can bring this whole thing down.
- You told me you'd have him by now.
- I wasn't able to find him.
But I'm taking care of it. Don't worry.
Sit down, both of you.
You don't need Michelle here.
She was acting under my orders.
- I can defend myself, Tony.
- I said sit down.
I need you to get me in contact
with Jack Bauer.
Oh, I see. Jack got some support above you
and now you're being squeezed, right?
Can you do it or not?
What's goin' on?
Bauer's evidence might
actually have some relevance.
- Which means we were right.
- No. You damn near put me in a coma.
That's assault.
I'll tell you what.
You drop the charges against us...
and we'll help you.
Come on, Ryan. You of all people
know that’s your best move.
- Fine.
- In writing.
All right, in writing.
Just get me in touch with Bauer.
- Shouldn't we call for help?
- I'm not working under CTU's authority.
- To them I don't exist.
- So we're out on our own.
Completely.
- Are you all right? You need some help?
- He got hurt.
- Can you get us to a hospital?
- Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
- Mrs Palmer, you need to drive.
- What do you mean?
- Sorry, but we need your car.
- Hey, easy, all right? Go ahead, take it.
Thank you.
They're ready, sir.
- Miss Warner. Hi. Carrie Turner.
- Hi. Kate.
- You must be Jack's daughter Kim.
- Where's my dad?
He's still in the field. Wait here.
I'll tell Ryan Chappelle you're here.
- I'll handle this.
- I thought you were in custody.
I was released.
Kim, I heard what happened to you.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I guess so. Look, I just wanna see
my dad and make sure he's OK.
No, he's not here right now.
He won't be back for a couple of hours.
- Does he know I'm here?
- No. We'll tell him when he phones in.
- Jack insisted we call as soon as we get here.
- He's just not reachable now.
I'll have Carrie take you back and
get you situated. I'll be there in a minute.
Hey.
It's gonna be OK.
OK.
Miss Warner?
I don't know if you're aware of this but...
your father came back here
after we released him.
Why?
He wanted to talk to your sister
before she was taken away.
- They brought Marie back here?
- Yeah.
You lied to me?
You killed Reza?
You tried to kill your own sister?
You were willing to set off a nuclear bomb
in a city with ten million people?
You tell me why.
Because I need to understand.
Tell me that they forced you to do it, that they
brainwashed you, that they threatened you.
You can tell me that you didn't
know what you were doin'.
There must be a reason.
There is no reason, Dad.
I can't accept that.
I couldn't either.
Until I looked into her eyes and she pointed
a gun at me and started to pull the trigger.
Trust me, Dad.
She's not gonna give you any answers.
She can't. At least, nothing
that we could ever understand.
Dad...
Come on. Let's go.
Kate.
You think you'll be safe out there.
You won't be.
- Jack, it's Tony.
- Tony, you back in play?
Yeah. Jack, Kim's here at CTU.
- She's safe.
- Thank God. Don't tell her what's going on.
- Just say I'll be back as soon as I can.
- I will.
- Jack, this is Ryan. We need to talk.
- You son of a bitch.
You stopped that chopper
picking up me and Hewitt.
- Hewitt's dead. I hold you responsible.
- Listen, things have changed.
You got full support.
Give me your mission profile.
I've set up a meeting with Kingsley.
We're gonna meet him
at the LA Coliseum, gate 18.
Mrs Palmer will wear a wire
and make him confirm
that the three countries had
nothing to do with the nuke.
Stand down until you get some support.
Our people will be there soon.
We don't have time. Kingsley's
expecting the meet to go down now.
You need backup.
If you wanna help me, get me voice prints of
Kingsley and Mrs Palmer for authentication.
Done.
- And a live audio feed to the White House.
- You want an audience with the president.
Yes.
All right. Keep the line clear.
- Copy. We're pulling into the Coliseum now.
- We need to get a SWAT team to his location.
Pull over there.
Wait here for me.
Come on.
Let's get you wired.
Take your jacket off your shoulder.
This is a wireless transmitter.
They won't know to look for it.
They won't be able to trace it.
- This is crazy. We shouldn't do this alone.
- We don't have another choice.
Remember, Kingsley doesn't want
to leave here without Hewitt.
That's gotta be to our advantage.
OK, say something.
I'm scared.
OK, it's working.
- Yes, Mike.
- Mr President,
I am against any delay in our military actions.
I have been from the start.
But there is a good chance we'll receive
evidence soon the Cyprus recording is false.
We know Second Wave brought
the nuke into the country
and we know they're sponsored by
these three countries. What am I missing?
I don't have all the details,
but I just learned about a possible link
between Second Wave
and a man named Peter Kingsley.
Who is he?
He's apparently part of a consortium of oil
interests with contracts in the Caspian Sea.
An oil consortium's behind the nuke?
Bauer believes he can get a confession
from Kingsley. He's set up a live audio feed.
Our bombers are due to drop their payloads
in less than 20 minutes.
Bauer's meeting Kingsley any minute.
This is the live voice print.
And this is the voice file we have on record
which will prove that it is,
in fact, Sherry Palmer.
- It's confirmed.
- The one below is Kingsley?
- Yeah.
- Are you guys getting this?
- We're good here.
- How far out is our backup?
- They're 11 minutes out.
- That's too long. We've gotta go now.
- Just wait.
- We can't.
We're already ten minutes past
the meeting time. Is Prescott ready?
Tony's on with the White House.
They're setting up a live audio feed.
OK, good. We are set to go.
How are you doing, Mrs Palmer?
What's to prevent Kingsley
from shooting me?
He won't do anything until he gets Hewitt.
But the moment he realises
we don't have Hewitt...
I'll be covering your back.
That's not very comforting
considering the condition you're in.
I may not make it out of this.
I'm not gonna lie to you, Mrs Palmer.
That's a possibility.
I'm doing this for David.
You know that, don’t you?
Yes.
Will you tell him that?
In case something happens.
I'll take care of it, Mrs Palmer.
You've gotta go now.
- Mike.
- Yes, sir.
We just finished setting up the feed.
I hope this isn't gonna be a waste of our time.
Believe me, Mr President, so do I.
What's going on, Mike?
The president and I thought
you should be part of this.
Along with Prescott and the Attorney General,
we will be listening to a live feed.
- Of what?
- A sting operation against Peter Kingsley.
It appears he was the architect
of today's bombing
and the delivery of the Cyprus audio.
- Bauer found Kingsley.
- Yes.
But... it won't be Bauer
who'll be talking to Kingsley.
What difference does it make
as long as we get him to incriminate himself?
What is it, Mike?
It's Sherry who'll be talking to Kingsley.
I don't understand.
It seems that Kingsley recruited her
some months ago.
She was part of this.
Sherry was working with this man, Kingsley?
It appears that way, sir.
To detonate a nuclear bomb and start a war?
No.
It's unclear how much she knew,
or how deep she was in it.
We just have to hope she can extract
a confession from Kingsley.
So now Sherry is working with Jack Bauer
to bring down Kingsley?
Yes. And at considerable risk to herself.
Scott, don't do anything until I tell you to.
- We need Hewitt.
- Understood.
- Where's Hewitt?
- He's safe.
Where is he?
You lied to me. You wanted
this bomb to go off all along.
You used Roger Stanton and you used me.
Yes, I did.
Well, now I'm tied to you, and
the nuclear detonation. I want safe haven.
- That's your problem.
- Well, I just made it yours.
Because you won't see Hewitt until I'm safe.
- Don't horse trade with me.
- Don't insult my intelligence.
- We got a match on Kingsley's voice.
- Ryan, you got it.
You're not going anywhere till I have Hewitt.
That doesn't work for me.
I'll call you on this line to give you
Hewitt's location after I'm safely away.
You don't need to know where I'm going.
- We're not getting what we need here.
- She'll get it for you.
- Now there’s the matter of the recordings.
- They're right here.
Every phone conversation
between you and me.
No. I want all of them, including Cyprus.
Why Cyprus?
You had nothing to do with that.
- Insurance.
- Insurance?
Once the country goes to war, the
government will never let that be exposed.
Hewitt is the only one who can hurt us.
- Because he forged the Cyprus recording.
- Right.
- You got your proof. Let me go ahead.
- Get it confirmed from the White House.
- She can't stay much longer.
- Are you satisfied?
CTU wants to know
if that's enough to prove it.
Have you confirmed this is live
and the voices have been authenticated?
Yes, sir.
- So that's it.
- Yes.
When I land... I'll call you.
Hm.
You're bluffin'.
You don't have Hewitt, do you?
- Oh, yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
Scott, take her out.
Kill her.
Run, Sherry!
Come on. Come on.
Mrs Palmer, get out of here. Go!
Jack Bauer.
You've caused me a lot of trouble today, Jack.
You're not gonna give me Hewitt, are you?
Our bombers are three minutes
from the targets.
Initiating sequence
six one tango one.
Target in view. Weapons lock.
Are we go for a strike?
Are we go for a launch?
We are awaiting command.
Abort the attack.
Abort, abort.
What do you mean, Kingsley's dead?
How could that happen?
I warned you not to use him.
So we did use him and he failed.
But it won't matter.
Once the war starts we'll be OK.
- It isn't going to start.
- Why's that?
The president found out about the Cyprus
recording and called off the attack.
There isn't going to be any war, Max.
Well... we're going to have
to do this another way.
- Another way? What are you talking about?
- You'll find out.
It'll start today.
It's me. Go ahead.
The cabinet has annulled its earlier action.
I have instructed the Secret Service
to resume its charge of serving you
as President of the United States.
I see.
I've also tendered my resignation,
effective immediately,
and those members of the cabinet who voted
against you have also agreed to resign.
Jim.
Gentlemen, ladies...
we came dangerously close to war today.
That all of us reacted emotionally
to the nuclear detonation is understandable.
But leaders are required
to have patience beyond human limits.
The kind of action we nearly took
should only be exercised
after all other avenues have been exhausted.
After the strictest standard
of proof has been met.
By casting me aside so quickly,
you effectively lowered those standards.
And that was a profound mistake.
It was not, however,
a mistake you're likely to make again.
Therefore I do not accept your resignations.
We have a nation to heal today.
And all of you play a vital role
in that healing process.
Mr President...
I don't know what to say.
There's nothing to say.
We have work to do.
That'll be all.
- Jenny, set up a press conference.
- When?
As soon as you can. And I want it public.
I want to speak to the people directly.
They deserve my assurance.
Yes, sir.
Mike, I wanna thank you again
for calling CTU in the 11th hour.
Of course, Mr President.
But you should have been with me to the end.
That's what I expected of you.
That's why I appointed you.
I'm relieving you of your post,
effective immediately.
Yes, Mr President.
Thank you, sir.
I can't take all the credit myself.
It's a great team
George Mason put together here.
Yes, I will. Thank you, sir.
Tony. That was District Director Vaughn.
He's so happy with what we did here today
he doesn't know where to start.
That's great.
So... what's up, my friend?
Well, um...
it's like this.
Either fire me...
or get out of my chair.
The chair's all yours.
- Hey.
The new shift is here.
They've been brought up to speed.
I was thinking I'd get
my brother and go home.
Michelle, um...
there's a handful of people
who made a big difference today.
You're one of'em.
You made some tough choices and
went up against me. You were right.
Thanks.
So, um... why don’t you
go home and get some rest?
Michelle.
See you tomorrow.
- I'll need to see the contents of your bag.
- I'm Kate Warner and this is Kim Bauer.
Excuse me.
- Hey, honey.
- Daddy.
It's gonna be all right.
I know.
I love you.
I love you too.
Dad? I'm gonna take care of you.
I urge you in the strongest terms
not to indulge any rumours or theories
that you may have heard, or may soon hear.
Once the facts are known,
I will present them to you myself.
Until then, know that we are all safe
and that we will continue to be safe.
The most patriotic thing that we can all do
today is to keep living our lives.
So I urge you all, go back to work,
go back to school.
Because the freedom we enjoy,
the freedom that we earn every day,
is the very thing that will defeat
our enemies and keep us strong.
God bless America.
God bless us all. Thank you.
Thank you very much. God bless you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Good to see you.
Thank you.
Mr President!
Hi.
Excuse me, Mr President.
Thank you.
Mr President.
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- God bless you.
- Yes.
- It's done.
Thank you.
Mr President?
The president's down!
We need medical assistance. Help!
Mr President?
Mr President? It'll be all right, sir.
We need an ambulance! Help!
Visiontext Subtitles: Abigail Smith
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net