Vice president's on the line.
Jim, I have reason to believe
the Cyprus audio was fabricated.
I thought we proved it was real.
CTU LA is in the process of obtaining
intelligence that may show otherwise.
With all due respect,
it's too late for second thoughts.
- Come out with your hands on your head.
- I killed a man!
If you turn yourself in,
they'll consider that.
If I see you coming in, I will kill her!
Go, go, go!
- He wasn't working alone.
- What?
Baker was keeping an eye on Kate.
Michelle distracted him.
- Did you help Jack take Kate Warner?
- Of course not.
Put a filter on all
of Michelle's communications.
Let me know when Jack tries to contact her.
- What's going on?
- Ten minutes ago a man called me.
Said he had proof the evidence the president
was basing his decisions on was forged.
He'll give me more info
if I bring you to him.
I got what you need. I won't give it to you
until you give me Kate.
How does the evidence prove
the recording was forged?
I have the source recordings.
Why did you follow me from CTU?
When you broke out, you isolated yourself.
You'll need help.
They're coming at us
from both sides of the alley!
The roof!
Fire escape!
Give me the keys!
- Here!
- Yusuf, give me cover!
Kate, get out of the trunk and stay down!
- Left! On the left!
- Go for the door now!
Kate, come with me.
Get down. Stay down!
- Who are these guys?!
- Follow-up team sent by my employers.
- Figured out they didn't get me.
- How'd they know you were here?
Beats the hell out of me.
- Jack, you there?
- Yusuf, are you OK?
- Yeah.
- Where are you?
I've managed to get
to the vehicle and rearm.
- What's out there?
- Three down that I know of.
There's three more. I don't have their
positions. I'll find a better vantage point.
We'll figure out what we're gonna do
in here. I'll get back to you. Stand by.
- Have him cover us. Let's get out of here!
- We don't know how many are out there!
- I'll call my person at CTU. She can help.
- Negative. You're not calling anybody.
The only way you get the proof Palmer needs
is if we do this my way. We go now!
They're trying to kill us.
Doesn't it prove something?
Not to the Joint Chiefs of Staff in DC.
- Call Yusuf, let's shape an exit strategy!
- Jack.
- Yusuf, go ahead.
- Sounds like another Humvee just arrived.
Son of a bitch. Stand by.
We're surrounded.
You've gotta let me make this call.
I've got someone on the inside
that can give us infrared satellite.
I guarantee you,
I will not jeopardise your identity.
- Off line?
- Yes.
Do it.
- Dessler.
- It's Jack. Are we secure?
My cell's scrambled, but don't call
on agency numbers. I'm being monitored.
You were right, Ali's recording was fake.
The president's about to invade the
Middle East based on falsified evidence.
- Do you have proof?
- Not yet, but I can get it. I need your help.
It'll be difficult. Tony's been breathing
down my neck since I helped you.
- Work around it. I need infrared satellite.
- Where are you?
- Get the coordinates off our connection.
- What are you looking for?
We're surrounded.
There's three of us inside.
I need to know how many men are outside.
I got a friendly at the end of the alley,
behind the dumpster.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Thanks.
- Yusuf?
- I'm here.
We're gonna be a few minutes.
We're waiting on satellite.
It's gonna take a while.
We should secure our position.
Come on.
- Is Mr Garcia gonna be all right?
- He'll live.
I'm gonna put down that you claim
the shooting was an accident.
It was.
He'll still have to explain to the DA what he
was doing going into the store with a gun.
- It wasn't his.
- What's that?
The gun, it was mine.
What are you doing with a gun?
Someone gave it to me earlier tonight.
Look, my name's Kim Bauer.
This afternoon,
I escaped from police custody.
And I'm a suspect in a murder.
While most Americans are asleep
and haven't heard the news
about the nuclear detonation in California,
many are up and are starting to react.
That reaction is taking many forms,
and in some cases violence is erupting.
We're still awaiting a statement from
the White House on who is behind the attack.
- That's enough.
- We hope...
- The alert status of the National Guard?
- They're ready in metropolitan areas.
- What about outside the big cities?
- We may have to get help from the military.
Local law enforcement
might not be able to do the job.
Call General Bowden,
tell him to put troops on standby.
The army? We can't do that.
- You're worried about posse comitatus.
- Exactly.
We can't use army or air force
on American soil. Only navy and marines.
No, the navy can't help us. And there are
not enough marines on standby.
- I'll deal with the consequences. Call him.
- Yes, sir.
- The status of our bombers?
- They're proceeding to their targets.
- Where are they now?
- South of Greenland.
They should enter Middle Eastern airspace
in four hours.
Thank you.
What are you doing on the satellite?
Just checking on something.
Prepped the files for the next shift?
Yeah, I'm almost done.
I'm gonna go see if Tony needs some help.
- Hey... what's up?
- You asked me to keep an eye on Michelle?
- Yeah.
- She was accessing a mod-sat screen.
That's not unusual.
We've been on mod-sat all night.
She received a call
that wouldn't lock onto our log.
- It was open?
- Yeah.
- It might have been Division.
- It might have been.
All right... find out what she
was looking at. Let me know.
Yusuf, what's happening out there?
I think they’re repositioning.
We're still waiting on satellite.
I'll get back to you.
With CTU's help, we're gonna
get out of here, I promise.
What does Wallace want with me?
- He needs you to get out of the country.
- Needs me? How?
With your father's CIA connections, his
company has a special travel dispensation.
They wouldn't let him on board
as a passenger unless...
I was on the plane with him.
I know.
Kate.
I will not let you get on that plane.
Is there any way I can find out
how my boyfriend is doing?
I don't know about that.
Wait till we get to the station.
There was also another officer.
His name was Brown.
- He was in the accident as well.
- I don't know him either.
Look, miss, you're under arrest.
So, take my advice, don't say any more.
It doesn't matter anyway.
You can make a phone call at the station.
Who am I gonna call?
My dad was the one who was flying
the plane, the one with the bomb in it.
I don't have anyone any more.
- Almeida.
- She's looking at infrareds.
She's been collecting data.
Pull coordinates off what she's looking at.
If it's for Jack, that's where we'll find him.
- I tried that.
- What's the problem?
She's covered her tracks.
She's pulled 100 quadrants.
I have no idea which one she's interested in.
I'll tell you what, I'll deal with this, Carrie.
All right? Thanks.
- Yeah?
- I don't have a lot of time. Are you ready?
Give me one sec.
- OK, I'm ready.
- I count11, including your friendly.
I'm sending you their positions
on an infrared map.
They're all stationary except for one.
Jack, he's roving.
- OK, send it.
- OK.
- You got it?
- Yeah, I got it.
How much longer do you need
to stay anonymous?
- I don't know, why?
- Tony's watching me. Gotta go.
- How are you holding up?
- All right.
- I've got so much to do.
- I know.
You always take a phone
with you to the bathroom?
- Where's Jack?
- I don't know.
We've been monitoring all communication
coming in and out all day.
- If you're breaking protocol...
- I'm not.
All right, then I'll ask you again.
- Where's Jack?
- I don't know.
But you have to call President Palmer.
Tell him not to act on the recording
until Jack finishes the investigation.
- So you have talked to Jack?
- I didn't say that.
Listen carefully, Michelle.
- You don't work for Jack, you work for me.
- Get past your ego...
Ego? You don't like the way
I'm doing my job, that's your problem.
But if you know anything about Jack Bauer,
you'd better tell me about it right now!
I have no information. I'm not helping Jack.
I hope you're not lying to me.
She counted nine, plus one roving.
If I was a sniper,
I'd cover the building from here.
- Yeah, looks right.
- We'll have to build a corridor.
- Which exit?
- This one right here.
Go between here, let 'em fire at each other.
It'll give us ten seconds to get to the car.
With just us firing?
We don't have another way.
Jack, I know how to shoot a gun.
Take this. You stay right behind me.
- Yusuf, this is Jack, do you copy?
- Yeah.
We're getting ready to make our exit.
- Let me give you positions.
- Go ahead.
We've counted nine, plus one roving.
We got two shooters on the balcony right
above me. Three in the building adjacent.
I just got off with the secretary of defence.
He wants to know how much longer
you'll give Jack Bauer to disprove that tape
before we fail-safe the orders.
Jack Bauer will have up until the time
the planes start releasing bombs.
From the secretary's point of view,
that's tying the DOD's hands.
The longer it takes for your decision,
the less flexibility he has,
and he may want to launch a prestrike...
There will be no prestrikes on this mission.
We're gonna utilise every moment
we have to be thorough.
- He won't like that.
- That's his problem.
I understand.
Sir, there's a situation
that requires your immediate attention.
What, Mike?
Civil unrest is starting
to tip up and down the East Coast.
The area I'm most concerned about
is outside of Atlanta.
What's going on there?
Some ad hoc militias have joined forces
and they're getting very aggressive
in one of the suburbs.
- Is this racially motivated?
- Yes.
The demographics of the area
are predominantly Middle Eastern.
What do you hope to accomplish here?
We want Washington to know
we consider ourselves at war.
We want these people interned.
And if they won't do it, we will.
Who do you want interned? Most people
in this neighbourhood are US citizens.
They weren't born here.
Some of them don't speak English.
They memorise answers to 50 questions,
take the test, then we let them vote.
How do you respond
to claims that these people
have no more to do
with the bomb than you or I?
If we'd locked down our borders 20 years ago,
none of this would have happened.
What's eerie is, even though the crowd
has been here for half an hour,
there are only a few police cars.
Why? I thought we ordered
the National Guard.
Some are on their way,
some are at other flash points.
- Want me to call the FBI and the army?
- And tell them what?
- They've had their orders.
- The problem is resources.
We just don't have enough bodies
to cover everything.
Where's the media heading right now?
It's happening all up and down
the East Coast.
But this city, Marietta in Atlanta, seems
to have the most traction with the press.
All right. This is what we're gonna do.
We may be short on manpower,
but it doesn't have to appear that way.
Send all the Eastern Georgia
National Guard to Marietta.
And tell the media that this is where
something's going to happen.
What's going to happen, sir?
If this is what the people
are going to be watching,
let's show them
how we're going to respond.
I want them to see
how we protect our citizens.
We will not put up with
racism or xenophobia.
If this is where it's gonna start,
this is where it's gonna stop!
All right, I'm all set up here.
Start laying down the smoke.
We're ready to go.
Copy that. Go in on the smoke.
You take the men on the left,
I got the ones right above us. You ready?
Smoke's in place. I'll draw fire
and go pick up the vehicle.
Go!
- Kate!
- Jack!
Kate, get down!
Kate. Come on, we gotta keep going.
Keep moving!
Get in the front seat and stay down!
Get down!
Stay down! Go, go, go!
Let me look at it.
No exit wound.
We gotta get you to a hospital.
- No. LAX, cargo departures.
- You will not make it.
I'll make it. Just stop the bleeding.
Kate, in the glove box, there's a first-aid kit.
Get me all the gauze, pads and wraps.
Hold on, hold on.
Put pressure on it now.
It's a surreal scene in Marietta.
It's 4.30am and normally people
would be at home, asleep.
Yet today a showdown is in the making.
The riots have escalated all over the city.
Fires and looting
are reported to be widespread.
The National Guard continue to roll in,
as do the angry citizens,
who are taking out their frustration on this
peaceful Middle Eastern community.
You got what you asked for.
It's on all the news channels.
Manski of the National Guard wants to know
what tactical rule-set you wanna follow.
- What are they on now?
- Containment only.
Unacceptable. I want the law enforced.
Tell him to start making arrests
and taking people in.
Sir, if you declare a curfew you can start
pulling every one of them in
- before this thing gets out of control.
- That a good idea, do it.
- Tell him we're not afraid to take action.
- Yes, sir.
What will help more
than anything, sir, is your voice.
You need to talk directly to the people.
I know.
Tell Jenny I'll be down in a few minutes.
- Murphy speaking.
- This is Novick. I need Jenny Dodge.
- Carrie.
- Yeah?
LAPD said there was automatic-weapon fire
in Studio City.
Police are finding bodies
and military-spec weapons.
We got the address. Check it against
what Michelle pulled off the satellite.
Right away.
Is that the location, Michelle? Huh, is it?
The police just got there,
they already got four bodies. So let's talk!
- Yeah, that's it.
- We gotta call him. He may need our help.
Jack made it clear that the only way
to get proof is if CTU stays out of it.
We don't even know if he's still alive!
He's on an open channel. You won't be able
to trace it, but you can talk to him.
- Michelle!
- No, Jack, it's Tony.
Tony, trust me, stay out of this!
- What's going on?
- The president asked me for proof
that the Cyprus recording was fake.
I'm trying to do that.
The man who can provide proof will only
deal with me. He won't cooperate with CTU.
- That's why I left in that way.
- How do we know he's not using you?
Cos ten commandos tried to kill him
to stop him from making a deal with me.
- What's he want?
- He wants to disappear.
We'll deal with him here.
He will not cooperate with us
under those circumstances.
I understand, but this country's
about to go to war over this.
This is too big for one person
to handle. Even you.
Keep going straight!
Sorry, I can't do it.
He's still bleeding bad!
Hey, Bobby.
Is this Kim Bauer?
- I'll take her.
- What about processing her?
It's OK. Go fill out the report.
Come with me.
We'll go in here.
Have a seat.
Looks like you've had quite a day.
- Yeah.
- You took Megan Matheson from her home.
- She was being abused.
- Got into a fight with her father.
Then, you took Megan again,
this time from the hospital.
- You stole Gary's car and fled the city.
- I had to. I knew about the bomb.
Understood. But then you were stopped
by CHP Officer Raymond Brown,
who discovered the dead body of Carla.
- I didn't kill anyone.
- I know you didn't.
We know Gary killed his wife.
We're looking for him.
There was a witness, and we found
his prints on the murder weapon.
- You did?
- Yes.
You're off the hook for everything
that happened this morning.
Thank God.
There's still the matter of you and your
boyfriend's attempted escape from custody.
Officer Brown was badly injured
in the accident. But he's gonna make it.
And we now know that you were
telling him the truth about the bomb.
So I'm free?
You should have somebody from CTU
call the DA's office on your behalf.
But yes, you'll be free to go.
I know my father usually does this,
but I have clearance.
An officer of the company
has to be on the flight.
- I'll be on it. Can you hold on?
- Certainly.
- Where are you going?
- Jakarta.
Surprised I'm giving up my destination?
No. You'll just change it
once you're in the air.
Prep a cargo transport
to Jakarta, Indonesia.
Give us clearance so we can leave tonight.
Who else will be flying with you?
What name should I give them?
- Passport, in my pocket.
- I got it.
- William Patterson.
- One moment, please.
Come on, stay with me.
He's losing consciousness!
Wallace, we can't take this chance.
Tell me where the evidence is, and I give
you my word, I'll get you out of the country.
You know what, Jack? You were a real
badass back there at the warehouse.
Son of a bitch.
No.
- I'm losing him! Damn it!
- What are you doing?
I wanna see if there's an urgent
care centre in the neighbourhood.
Come on!
Four blocks. Four blocks, make a right. Go!
I want ID's on the bodies.
See what traces are on the weapons.
- Bauer's actions are CTU's responsibility.
- We won't run from this.
- Let's find out who they are.
- Send in forensic teams?
- Yeah.
- NSA and field units?
Yeah, that's fine.
Mr Almeida,
Kim Bauer on line four.
- Kim, where are you?
- At a sheriffs station in Santa Clarita.
- What happened?
- I won't be charged for murder, but...
- Look, I still might need some help.
- Sure, what do you need?
They were taking us back to LA,
and my boyfriend and I tried to escape.
And we got into a car accident.
A police officer was injured.
- I'll call the DA's office, see what I can do.
- Thank you.
I'm sure you'd rather be talking
to your dad about this,
but I know they probably told you
he's not available right now.
- What are you talking about?
- He's in the field.
In the field? You mean, he's alive?
Oh, my God, Kim.
You still think he died in the plane.
- He didn't?
- No, no. George Mason took over.
He was able to get out in time.
Oh, my God. When can I talk to him?
Not for a while, Kim.
Come on, come on, get him!
- I need to see the doctor!
- You can't do that.
- Open the door!
- I will call the police!
- Lady, I am the police. Now, open the door!
- Let him in. Let him in!
- We need you!
- What happened?
He's been shot. I'm a Federal Agent.
He has information vital to national security.
I need you to stop the bleeding
and keep him alive.
This is a clinic. He needs a hospital.
We don't have time. You've got to do
what you can now. Doctor, please.
All right. Clara, get me suture kits, lidocaine
with epi, and a crash cart. Now, now!
The wound's right here.
He's got a bullet lodged in his back.
- Hello.
- Miguel, it's me.
- Kim. Are you OK?
- I'm fine. How are you?
- I'm OK.
- Yeah?
Look, it's so weird,
but the police know Gary killed Carla.
We're not gonna be charged with anything,
except maybe the escape.
But I think we're OK there, too.
- That's good.
- Good? It's great.
Yeah.
- How about you?
- I'm fine.
Are you sure? I mean, you don't sound...
I don't sound what? Excited?
Gee, Kim, I'm really sorry.
Miguel, what's wrong?
Why are you acting like this?
- I shouldn't have let you talk me into it.
- Yeah, but it worked out.
For you. I'm the one
that's here in the hospital.
- You just said you were fine.
- I am going to be fine.
- I'm just gonna be fine without you.
- What?
- I don't wanna see you any more.
- Why not?
- There's no "why not", it just is.
- No.
Miguel, what is going on? Are you OK?
- I'm coming to see you right now.
- Kim, I said no. It's over.
You mean that?
Yeah... I mean it.
I know the rules.
I know that I work for you.
And if you fire me, I wouldn't blame you.
This isn't about me firing you, Michelle.
This agency is supposed to be supporting
the president and this country.
If I can't account for our actions,
we've got chaos.
Jack is in an impossible situation. I was
helping him get proof the audio was fake.
Yeah? Well, where's the proof?
We don't have any proof.
We don't have Jack,
he doesn't want to be found.
What do you want from me, Michelle?
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, you've said it.
Now, if you don't mind,
I got work to do, all right?
Our planes are over the Atlantic.
They will be reaching
their targets in three hours.
- The pilots' communication posture?
- Comm is open to them.
The planes can be ordered back
at any time.
Good.
I don't know if anyone's told you, but
the sooner we can lock this mission down,
the more comfortable
the Joint Chiefs will be with it.
My job's not to make
the Joint Chiefs comfortable.
Thank you. That'll be all.
Yes, sir.
Mr President. There's been
a development in Marietta.
The National Guard took on a more
aggressive posture at our request.
But the disturbance got to be
more than they could handle.
What happened?
Two people were killed, sir.
The National Guard started shooting
rubber bullets, and there were two fatal hits.
One of the victims
was a leader of the dissent, and...
- And?
- And the other was a young boy, sir.
He was Middle Eastern, and he was from one
of the families that we were trying to protect.
What's going on now?
They've made some arrests,
but the crowd is still unruly.
Now, we might want to think
about taking a step back.
Maybe the presence of the National Guard
is making matters worse.
If we step back now, those families
are left completely unprotected.
Yeah.
A young boy.
What was his name?
The boy?
- I don't know, sir.
- The boy had a name. Find out.
Indeed I will, sir.
It was a tragic accident.
Tell the National Guard to hold their ground.
I want that neighbourhood protected.
I want order restored.
Yes, sir.
There's the bullet. It missed the jugular,
but still caused damage.
- What can you do?
- I might be able to tie off the bleeders.
- You can't get the bullet out without surgery.
- We don't have time for that.
I don't feel comfortable with this.
They can shut me down.
I'm not authorised for this procedure.
I guarantee that won't happen.
I need you to do this now.
- At least tell me what this is all about.
- It has to do with the bomb that went off.
I'm sorry, I can't tell you more than that.
- All right, I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you.
- Give him some Versed.
- No, don't sedate him.
I need him to be able to talk.
Just numb the area around the wound.
Don't worry, beautiful.
I've been worse than this.
- He's gonna die.
- We better hope he doesn't.
OK, so we'll depart at 3.45?
That'd be great. Thank you.
- Is he on?
- They gave us a departure time for 3.45.
Good.
He won't give you information
till we're off the ground.
I told you, I'm not letting you
get on that plane.
All he wants to do is get out of the country.
Soon as we get him to the airport, he'll give
us the information. The rules have changed.
Hold still, almost there.
Stop. It's done.
It's not done. Now, sir, please lie still
or I'll have to sedate you.
- I said, I'm done!
- Push the Versed now.
- Wait!
- Jack.
- What?
- Jack, I'm not gonna make it. I can feel it.
Just tell me where the evidence is now.
It's on a memory chip.
Two AIF files.
The source recordings prove
the Cyprus audio is a fake.
Where is the memory chip?
It's in... inside...
- Inside what?
- Inside...
Inside where? Come on, Wallace.
Inside where? Doctor!
- He's in V-fib!
- Excuse us. We need to get in here.
- No pulse.
- We're at 200 joules.
Here you go, Doctor.
- Charging. 1-2-3, clear.
- Clear.
- Still in V-fib. Charging, 1-2-3, clear.
He's dead.
Jack, what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
We got it.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmin Rammohan
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net