- How long will Prescott detain me?
- Until after the press conference.
In two hours he'll announce our response
to the bomb and his ascension to president.
I've done with Bauer.
He's chasing a trail that leads nowhere.
We're onto other things.
You've been reassigned.
You can't reassign me now.
You have made yourself
a liability I can't afford.
This is Kim Bauer. I need my dad.
- What's wrong?
- I'm at the Mathesons' house.
Gary's here. He has a gun. He killed
the policeman that brought me.
I want you to point the gun at his chest
and pull the trigger now.
- Is he dead?
- Yeah.
I'll send someone to pick you up.
Go downstairs and wait for them.
I am certain the Cyprus audio has
been forged.
I have in custody the man who engineered it.
I'll bring him in soon.
- How will it work?
- I'll make a recording for them, on the spot.
Shift it around, reframe segments,
same specs as Cyprus.
- Where are you going?
- This is taking too long.
We're the only ones who can help you.
Without us, you don't stand a chance.
Alex!
Thank you.
- How's Chappelle?
- Still unconscious, but he's starting to stir.
The drug I gave him is short-acting.
He may need more.
How long can you keep pumping him full?
Long enough for Jack to deliver Hewitt.
How are we coming on the chopper?
It should land at Hewitt's in ten minutes.
We should have him here in half an hour.
- Is Carrie asking about Chappelle?
- Not yet, no.
Image processing should
keep her busy for a while.
Excuse me, Mr Almeida?
Brad Hammond from Division wants
Mr Chappelle. Do you know where he is?
No, I'll take it. This is Tony Almeida.
How can I help you, sir?
- Where's Ryan?
- Uh, I'm not sure.
His office says he arrived
at CTU three hours ago.
- None of your people can find him.
- He must have stepped out.
He didn't log out.
Did he say where he was going?
Not to me, sir, but I'll
let you know as soon as I find him.
No, you'll tell me what's going on over there.
I know Ryan Chappelle was
going to assess the situation.
I cannot think why he would be
out of contact during a national crisis.
Mr Hammond, I'm sorry,
I've told you all that I know, sir.
I'll make sure Ryan calls when he returns.
- You do that.
- Thank you, sir.
- What's goin' on?
- Division knows something's up.
- So what are we gonna do?
- Get Alex Hewitt here as quickly as possible.
Alex!
Alex, if you don't come with me,
Kingsley will kill you. You know that!
I just did what they told me.
I didn't know what was gonna happen.
Your only way outta this
is to let me take you into CTU.
You can cut a deal, testify!
Alex, you're gonna have to trust me!
Alex!
Alex! Stop running!
Alex, listen to me.
A chopper's on its way to take us to CTU,
where no one can hurt you.
Please, Alex. Help me stop this war
and I will help you stay alive, I promise.
Please.
Alex!
Stop, damn it!
I know the oil stocks closed high in
Hong Kong last night, Max, but remember,
once the president announces the war,
the margins will change dramatically.
- Prices will spike immediately.
- It's still worth acquiring shares.
- Do we still have our problem?
- That'll be taken care of.
- This must go smoothly.
- Don't worry about it.
- I have to go.
- OK.
- What'd you get?
- All the recordings and data.
But no Hewitt?
We got there as soon as we could,
but I had no lead time.
Everything, including Hewitt, was
meant to have been vaporised last night.
I won't let some pimply-faced techie
ruin everything that we've planned.
If he gets brought in and testifies, there's
gonna be no place for any of us to hide.
Alex!
Alex! There's nowhere left to run. It's over.
All right. You... you promise I'll be safe?
I give you my word.
Alex, drop the gun! Drop the gun!
If you try to shoot me, I will have
to shoot you back, and I won't miss.
And I don't wanna do that.
I can't stop this war without you, Alex.
Please, drop the gun.
Alex, you're a smart guy. Think this through.
I am the only guy that
can get you through this alive.
Please, drop the gun.
Drop the gun.
- Alex...
- You shot me!
- It's gonna be all right.
No!
Alex, Alex... Can you hear me?
OK, stay calm. Don't move.
You're gonna be all right.
- What happened?
- You fell.
Alex, stay with me.
I want you to keep your eyes open, OK?
Just keep your eyes open. OK...
- Agh!
- You're OK.
The bullet didn't hit an artery.
The chopper should be here soon.
- You're not gonna bleed to death.
- It hurts.
I'm gonna get you something for the pain
as soon as we get on the chopper.
Is there any other part of your body
besides your leg that still hurts?
No, not really.
OK, good. It looks like you got lucky.
You're gonna be fine.
My head... feels wet.
Just relax. Try and relax.
Just put your head down.
OK.
I gotta make a phone call, OK?
I'm not goin' anywhere. Stay with me.
Come on.
- Almeida.
- It's Jack. Hewitt's been hurt.
I need medical assistance on the roof now.
There's no EMT on the chopper,
but there's a med kit. Can you handle it?
I don't know. I hope so.
Look, I gotta get back to this.
- Wait.
- What?
You may not be able to contact me after this.
- Why?
- Chappelle became a problem.
I had to take him out of play,
and they're onto me.
- They'll take me out soon.
- Who do I contact if I need help?
Michelle is setting up an off-site station.
She'll do what she can by remote access.
She'll be on her closed cell,
channel B, node 12-12.
- B, node 12-12. I got it.
- Good luck.
Thanks.
Alex, how you doin'?
This'll get you into the van.
- How will I breakthrough the firewall?
- This has a range of a few blocks.
It's Huffman encoded. It'll get you in.
Give me a call when you're set, all right?
- Michelle.
- Hi.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going out to my car.
- Are you leaving?
- No.
I'm just getting something.
Is there a problem?
- Have you seen Chappelle?
- No.
I've looked everywhere and I can't find him.
If I see him, I'll tell him you're looking for him.
And if you don't see him?
What's that supposed to mean?
My job is to monitor
communications around here.
- You don't think I know what's goin' on?
- Why don’t you tell me, Carrie?
You called Chappelle in to see Rudin.
I just talked to Rudin.
- He doesn't know anything about it.
- Well, of course he told you that.
His system wasn't loaded properly
and it was your fault.
He wanted to see Chappelle
to complain about you.
Stay out of my business, Carrie.
You'll do a better job.
Brian. How did you find out about me?
The Attorney General said
you'd want me for your counsel.
- What have they told you?
- You'd been removed from office
under the 25th Amendment.
- Is what they did legal?
- Technically, yes.
The cabinet can declare
the president incompetent
without further definition or clarification.
- That also gives me the right to appeal.
- Yes, which I will do vigorously.
- Unfortunately, it's a lengthy process.
- We don't have time.
- I don't know how to make it go any faster.
- None of those legalities matter.
We're about to go to war based on
evidence that I am convinced is false.
No one outside this room believes that.
The evidence was manipulated
by a man named Peter Kingsley.
I need you to find out all you can about him.
Mike Novick's tying my hands.
Get him to untie them -
whatever you have to do.
Yes, sir.
- Almeida.
- I'm in place.
- Where are you?
- I'm in the north lot.
Van 15a. Listen, Tony, Carrie's onto us.
- She was asking about Chappelle.
- What did you tell her?
That I didn't know anything,
but we need her out of the way.
- Keep her occupied.
- OK, I'll handle it. Get ahold of Jack.
I gotta go. Hammond's here.
- Mr Hammond.
- Tony.
- What are you doing here?
- I told you on the phone.
I think there’s a problem here.
Where's Ryan Chappelle?
- I haven't seen him yet, sir.
- I see.
Two of you take this side.
I want this section covered.
- What are you doin'?
- I'm locking you down.
We're in the middle of preparing
a domestic response to this war.
That's not what I heard. I heard you were
supporting a rogue agent against orders.
- Where'd you hear that?
- One of your people.
Let's go. Cover every square inch of the place!
- I'm aware of that.
- That flyover space is critical.
- Will David help us?
- I don't know.
Mike.
I don't see us having much success with him.
- We need this, Mike.
- Yes, sir, I'll try. How is he?
David is convinced his decision
to hold off on the bombers was correct.
He'll appeal his removal from office.
- The 25th Amendment gives him that right.
- We'll prove we're being manipulated
and that the Cyprus recording was falsified,
plus we now think we know by whom.
- I'm listening.
- A man named Peter Kingsley.
He's got ties to oil interests
both here and abroad.
Have you found anything to connect him
to the Cyprus recording, or the bomb?
No. We won't be able to without
access to the Intelligence database.
David's locked down until we've
gone public with the military action.
- By then it'll be too late.
- I'm sorry.
Mike, wait. Just hold on a second.
I remember when you signed up for David's
first run at the Senate over 20 years ago.
That's... that's a lot of history
to just throw out the window.
Come on, Mike.
I know you just did what you thought
was right, but let him try to prove his case.
You owe him that.
I'll have Colleen set up
a computer station for you.
You won't be able to transmit
outgoing messages.
That's fair enough.
- What's in here?
- A holding room. No one's in there now.
All right.
- And this?
- The other holding room.
It shouldn't be locked.
- What's wrong?
- Someone must have reconfigured the lock.
Come on, Alex. Keep talking to me.
Everything's... a little blurry.
What's happening to me?
Nothing. You just banged your head.
It's gonna be all right, OK?
You just hang in there.
Alex, I can hear 'em. They're coming, OK?
Help's on the way. Just hang in there, OK?
I've located the CTU chopper
that Tony Almeida sent to Jack Bauer.
They're landing.
Would you like them to detain Bauer?
No, I don't wanna waste
any more resources on him.
Just get the chopper back here.
Mr Chappelle wants you to come back now.
- We're about to land.
- I know.
- I can see him...
- Just do it.
What are you waiting for?
- I'm putting her down.
- No, cancel that.
Land the chopper now!
What are you doing?!
Land the damn chopper!
My witness is gonna die! Land!
Your orders are to pick us up! Pick us up now!
Damn it!
- Dessler.
- The chopper won't pick us up.
- Hammond's locked us down.
- I don't give a damn!
Get me that chopper back! Hewitt is dying!
Alex.
- Want me to deal with Almeida?
- No, Brad, thanks. I'll take care of him myself.
- Michelle, it's me.
- Jack, where are you?
Going back to Hewitt's loft. Set up and
be ready to interface with his computer.
- What about Hewitt?
- He didn't make it. He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Call me when you're ready.
- Yes?
- I need to speak with you.
It concerns national security.
As I am not the commander in chief
any more, that's irrelevant.
We have a problem with
the Turkish government.
Our Stealth bombers are
nearing their airspace,
but one of their fighter patrols
spotted them a few minutes ago.
Ask the prime minister for the flyover.
He should agree.
The secretary of state has spoken to him.
- He'll grant us this under one condition.
- What's the condition?
He wants a personal request
and assurances from the president.
The prime minister doesn't know
I've been removed from office.
He couldn't be told
before the American people.
That wouldn't be right, would it, Mike?
Now that the bombers have been spotted,
it's critical that they get
to their targets quickly.
Any detour will take them
over unfriendly skies.
You want me to speak to the prime minister,
under the pretence that I'm still the president?
Yes.
This mission is going to
continue regardless, sir.
This phone call, no matter how distasteful,
could prevent those planes
from being attacked.
We only have minutes, sir.
Why did you leave me like this?
I've been stabbed!
Let me look at it.
Be careful.
You're lucky. The wound's superficial.
The bleeding's already stopped.
I'll get you a clean bandage for it.
- Where's Alex?
- He fell. He's dead.
Oh, my God. What happens now?
You are going to help me.
Just put this right here.
- Help you do what?
- We got one last play.
- To deliver Kingsley.
- No.
He's far too dangerous,
and you'll never get close to him.
You're right. I won't, but you will.
Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's been killed.
If you say you can deliver him,
that should get his attention.
Kingsley has evidence that will
implicate me. There is no way...
Mrs Palmer, you...
What?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Don't tell me it's nothing. What's going on?
My heart stopped when
Kingsley's men were interrogating me.
Your heart could be damaged.
You need to get to a doctor.
We need to get Kingsley first.
Mrs Palmer, you are going to help me.
I'm not gonna give you another choice.
You wouldn't dare hurt me.
Make no mistake about it.
I will do what I have to do.
What do you want me to do?
Tell Kingsley you'll exchange Hewitt
for any evidence that incriminates you.
He'll want proof that I have Hewitt.
- He'll get it.
- How?
Hewitt's gonna talk to him.
At this point, we can assume the chip
containing the source recordings
has not landed in government hands.
Did you intercept the federal agent
who was in possession of the chip?
No. But since the bombers are still on course,
we can assume that he wasn't
able to deliver it to the president.
Which leaves Hewitt as the last remaining
loose end. Where are we on finding him?
I have several teams out looking for him.
He cannot be allowed to talk.
Not now, nor ever.
Hewitt will be found, and he'll be eliminated.
Clean this up, Peter.
Go over it again, even if you
need to pull a couple of agents in to help you.
I don't need to tell you you're under arrest.
- Where's Michelle Dessler?
- She knew nothing about this.
She called me to the room
where you drugged me.
She didn't know what I was gonna do.
I need to issue a warrant.
Contact local police, issue a memo.
- I can find her.
- How?
This whole thing's been about helping Jack
Bauer. She's doing that somewhere off-site.
- How do we find her?
- Track her access code.
See if she's logged onto
the CTU computer network.
- Then do it.
- Right away.
Put him in Holding 2.
- Yeah?
- I'm connected to his computer.
Press "escape" and I can take control.
- Done.
- What did Hewitt tell you?
He had a program
that could recreate anybody's voice.
With a voice sample,
he could get it to say anything.
He kept all the audio files in a main file.
All right, I think I've found it.
I've never seen this.
Samples connect through an integrator.
- I need anything with Hewitt's voice on it.
- All right, hold on.
I'm gonna need Berkeley
and Wilkerson at that lunch.
- Is that him?
- No, damn it.
There's hundreds of files. Hold on.
Mrs Palmer, when did you call Hewitt?
- Last night, around midnight. Why?
- He might have recorded it.
Michelle, can you filter the audio files
by time and date?
Let me see... Yeah.
Find an audio file that was recorded late last
night or early this morning, around midnight.
This must be it.
- Hello?
- Alex Hewitt?
- Who's this?
- That's him.
- Sherry Palmer.
- We have to let it run.
What are you calling me for?
I know all about
your relationship with Peter Kingsley.
I don't know him.
I also know you had
all his phone conversations recorded.
Let me ask you. Was that to protect
yourself or to blackmail him?
It's OK, Alex.
- I'm here to help you.
- Who says I need help?
Peter thought you’d die in Los Angeles
with everybody else today.
Now that you haven't,
he's gonna come after you.
So listen to me, and I can protect you.
We have enough material
to create a phonetic template.
- Good. What do we do?
- Open up a.gen file
and type in the phrases we want voiced.
What do you mean, open a.gen file?
He created a separate module for playback.
We have to find what menu it's under.
- What am I looking for?
- It's not here.
Try a subroutine called Prologue.
- It's this one.
- They've found me, Jack.
It's loading. What am I looking for now?
A playback graphic interface.
They're almost here.
- Come out of the van!
- Hold on, Michelle. Hold on.
- Ma'am, hands off the keyboard.
- I've got it. Michelle!
- Do we take her in?
- Michelle!
Affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
- Hello, Heather.
- Mr President.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right, Heather.
- Mr President, we're ready.
- David.
I realise how awkward this is.
I hope Mike has told you
how much we appreciate your help.
Make no mistake. I believe
you're making a gross and tragic error.
I'm doing this for the men in those planes.
We're ready here. Patch in the prime minister.
- Mr Prime Minister.
- Hello, Mr President.
I've been trying to reach you for some time.
Kim?
Kim!
Hello?
Kim?
- Who are you?
- I'm Kate Warner.
Your father sent me to come get you.
How do I know that?
OK.
You shot a man who came in here
to attack you. It was self-defence.
Your father, Jack Bauer, called me,
asked me to come get you, take you to CTU.
How else would I know all of that?
How do you know my dad?
Do you work at CTU?
No. My family was involved
with what happened today.
Why would my dad send someone
he'd just met to come get me? Huh?
He trusts me.
Come on, Kim.
It's OK.
The sooner we leave, the sooner
you and your dad can be together, OK?
What do you think they’ll charge us with?
They could push for treason if they wanted to.
Think they will?
Depends on how big of an example
they wanna make of us.
Look, Michelle...
no one can prove that you knew
what I was gonna do to Chappelle.
I'm gonna tell them that you were
helping Jack under my orders, all right?
No.
What do you mean, no?
I did what I thought was right.
I still believe that.
And I won't let you lie for me.
David...
Thank you. I know how difficult
it must have been for you.
How much longer will Prescott keep me here?
Until after the press conference.
I've requested you be released sooner,
but there's only so much I can do.
I spoke to Brian. He requested some
low-security access on your behalf.
I wanted you to know I granted it.
So what's going on with you and my dad?
Excuse me?
Out of everyone he could have called,
he called you.
There's gotta be a reason.
I don't think he trusts very many people.
He trusts you.
- Is it true you guys just met today?
- Yesterday really, but yeah, it is.
I don't resent it or anything.
I just... want him to be happy.
It's been a long time.
Since you lost your mother?
Yeah.
I lost my mother too.
When I was about your age.
I really don't think I can do this.
You'll do fine. Just tell him everything
I told you to say. Make the call.
Understood.
Still no sign of Hewitt.
Yes?
It's Sherry Palmer, Peter.
- Are we on a secure line?
- Of course we are.
I want the tapes that you made of
our conversation, the original DATs.
- Why would I give you those?
- Because I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
- You've found Hewitt?
- That's right.
Where is he?
Don't insult my intelligence.
Agree to the exchange, then you can
do whatever you want with him.
I want to talk to him.
You'll have to hold on. My bodyguard
has him restrained in the next room.
All right, Alex, you can talk.
It's not what you think. They came in here
with guns and threatened to kill me.
I didn't tell them anything
about you, I swear, please.
Who's been there, Alex?
Who have you told about this?
- Do we have a deal or not?
- Not until I know what's going on there.
Give me Alex back.
I'm not gonna keep this call going on
so that you can trace it. Is it yes or no?
Look, this is an ultimatum, Mrs Palmer.
You put Alex back on,
or this conversation is ended.
You force my hand and
I'll make sure Hewitt tells his story
to as many people as possible.
It's your final chance, Mrs Palmer.
Then it's goodbye, Peter.
Fine.
Let's do this.
- Neutral ground.
- All right.
LA Coliseum, gate 18, 30 minutes.
- Just you and Alex.
- All right.
Very good work, Mrs Palmer. Let's go.
Sherry Palmer has Hewitt.
What does she want?
I get this feeling I'm being set up.
Hewitt's just the bait
to draw me out into the open.
So what are you gonna do?
I don't have any choice.
I have to play this out.
Scott'll have shooters in place.
Sherry Palmer and whoever else she's
involved with in this won't leave there alive.
And then... I'm heading outta the country.
Time to roll things up around here.
Now.
Is there anything I can do for you?
You've already done so much.
I'll see you in Lisbon next week.
I am enormously grateful.
- What support will you get from CTU?
- As of now, none.
Wait. You don't expect to take Kingsley down
by yourself? That's insane!
When Kingsley incriminates himself,
CTU will help.
- By then it'll be too late.
- Sorry, that's how it's gonna be.
Kingsley will have people with him who will
kill us when they realise we don't have Hewitt.
- You OK?
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not. Pull over.
- We don't have time.
We've gotta keep moving!
Jack? Jack!
- Agh!
- Jack!
Visiontext Subtitles: David Van-Cauter
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net