- Lemon, it's Jack.
- Who's Jackie?
Oh, Lemon, Avery and I
just got back
from the most amazing vacation
on Paul Allen's yacht.
And for four glorious weeks,
my naturally blonde
lady love and I basked
in the three "s"s...
surf, sun, and...
Sandwiches?
Heh, we didn't need
sandwiches, Lemon.
It was so warm you could pick
fully cooked lobsters
out of the water.
Sheer bliss.
Avery is the most perfect woman
ever created.
Like a young bo Derek
stuffed with a Barry goldwater.
You sound weird.
Do you have a beard?
Not for long.
It's back to reality.
No more making love
on the beach
surrounded by a privacy circle
of English-trained butlers.
But I've got to get out
of island mode
and back into work mode.
How was your summer?
Get this, my gynecologist
committed suicide.
And I'm back!
Carol!
Hey, Lizzie,
I'm about to take off.
I'm in lambert, St. Louis,
and I can see the arch
from here.
No, wait, actually that's
a half-burned-down McDonald's.
Anyway, weather's great,
and I just have to go
St. Louis-Newark,
Newark-Atlantic city,
Atlantic city to Newark,
and then I'll be there.
Who flies Newark
to Atlantic city?
Black bachelorette parties.
Gotta go.
Hello?
Yo, I'm calling to say
that I'm giving you
110% this year.
I'm relaxed, I'm focused,
and I'm gonna be churning out
the good stuff
like you've never seen.
That's great, Tracy.
Oh, I misdialed.
I thought I was calling
my nutritionist.
Good-bye.
Okay, season five.
Here we go.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
What about office supplies?
Can you come down 5% there?
I'll try.
We're already printing
all of our internal memos
on the back of my kids' art.
In order for this merger
to stay attractive
to our friends at Kabletown,
we have to seem like
a sexy, profitable company.
And we're almost
pulling it off.
The Harry Potter theme park
is a huge hit
with both anglophiles
and pedophiles.
The movie division has
a James Cameron movie
the whole world will see,
whether they like it or not.
Only NBC continues to be
the engorged whitehead
on the otherwise flawless face
of universal media.
Lemon, why are you spending
so much money on wigs?
Tracy's head size
keeps changing.
Hang on, what is this
pay increase for Jenna?
Oh, boy.
Look, as we enter
the fifth season of TGS...
and remember, no one ever
thought we'd make it this far...
I believed in us.
That was actually an oversight.
Jenna has some crazy stuff
built into her contract
that kicks in now.
Like what?
Eye contact.
"Everyone must make eye contact
with Miss Maroney
at all times."
She also gets a producer credit.
What?
Oh, it's just
a vanity credit, Lemon.
A low-cost way to make someone
feel more important.
Like executive producer
Ashton Kutcher,
or secretary of state
Hillary Clinton.
Am I late
for the producers meeting?
Eye contact.
Thank you.
- Hey, k-k-k-k.
First day back's
gonna be a busy one.
First, I need you to go
to the dry cleaners for me
and find out
how martinizing works.
I've always been curious.
Then I need you
to be back by noon
to make the bathroom smell
like sandalwood
before I wreck it.
You got that,
k-pax-o-gum?
I'm not Kenneth, sir.
My name's Brian.
Kenneth got fired
at the end of last season.
Of course.
I knew that.
Good meeting.
- So how are things with Carol?
- Good.
Did you know that
if you're a pilot,
that chili's will seat you
right away,
even if the pilot's
dinner companion
has just been yelling
at the hostess?
You are the Jackie o
of our time.
And pilots get
all these travel points
at Starwind hotels.
The one in midtown has
free Internet.
He doesn't stay with you
when he's here?
Why would he?
Those Starwinds are nice!
I mean, the bathtubs are
so much cleaner than at home.
It's almost as bad
as "climax."
You can't just do
the vacation part.
At some point you have to
go home to the same house,
unpack your dirty laundry,
and have a life together.
Then one of you says,
"we should redecorate."
And the other one says,
"please, Avery,
I'm using the commode
right now."
Ooh, she wants to redecorate?
She just moved in.
Avery, uh, has opinions.
I love her for that.
Unfortunately,
she wants to repaint
the upstairs hallway
in a strie faux finish
called "husk."
I prefer the color
that's already there...
a reddish-brown shade
called "elk tongue."
So tell her no.
It's your house.
This is how I know
you've never had
an adult relationship.
If I say no,
then I will be required
to say yes to something else
in the future,
and the stakes in the future
might be higher.
- Then say yes.
- If I give in,
then I'm no longer the Alpha
in my house.
Before you know it,
she'll have me wearing jeans
and reading fiction!
Yeah, well, yes and no
are kind of
your only two choices.
For most men, sure.
But there is a third option.
The Fabian strategy.
I know this.
If an apple and a feather
fall at the same time...
the Fabian strategy
derives its name
from the Roman general
Quintus Fabius Maximus.
He ran away, Lemon.
Rather than engage in battle,
he would retreat and retreat
until the enemy grew fatigued
and eventually made a mistake.
Although I abhor it
as a military strategy,
it is the basis for all of my,
uh, personal relationships.
So Avery is your enemy.
That sounds healthy.
You're in no position to judge.
Meeting someone in a hotel room
twice a month
is not a relationship...
just ask any hooker.
Oh, stop saying "relationship"!
I'm sorry,
I was going to say "climax."
Aah!
A line item budget.
Oh, I love this.
It takes people and turns them
into amounts of money.
Except for Tracy,
I'm the most person on the show!
At do we do now?
Oh, okay, well, Jack wants me
to keep the budget flat,
but I don't want
to deny people their raises.
You should fire grace
from wardrobe.
She doesn't do anything.
Fire grace?
Come on, you'd have to be
a heartless monster...
I'll do it.
Grace, your position
has been terminated,
effective immediately.
But I've been here
since the Jack Paar show.
Your health insurance will
remain in effect
until the end of this sentence.
Come on. Chop chop.
What a shank job.
Kenneth,
I knew you'd come back!
Let me smell your head.
Mmm...
Come on!
This is a woman's blazer
from a very expensive
blazer shop called Rico's.
I'm sorry, but my heart is
playing tricks on my eyes.
Just like my kidneys did
to my lungs that time.
Are you okay?
I keep hallucinating Kenneth.
Am I going crazy again?
Should I get my rainbow wig
out of storage?
No, Tracy, it's normal.
Kenneth was very special
to you, and now he's gone.
The next time you hallucinate,
just tell yourself,
"this is not real.
I am in control of this."
Like the world cup.
I'll try.
♪ ♪
No, this place is
too full of memories.
I gotta clear my head.
Okay, well, we've only been
back to work, like, an hour...
And bye.
Liz, get in on this.
Would you rather have to
start every sentence you say
for the rest of your life
with Urkel's catchphrase,
"Did I do that?"
Or be siamese twins
with Sharon Stone for a year?
Did I do that?
Carol!
So, Carol,
you ever join
the mile high club?
Try five miles high.
And no, I have not.
Did you ever see
a UFO up there?
No, but once,
when I was in the air force,
I saw Mr. t in a pizza hut.
Was the air force
like top gun?
Yeah, but with
a lot more volleyball.
You ever kill anyone?
Sucked a mechanic
into my engine once.
Are you on Facebook?
And these are for you.
Passenger left them
in the first-class lavatory.
Ooh.
Hey, I couldn't get a room
at any of the Starwinds
this weekend.
You think it'd be all right
if I stayed at your place?
Uh... uh, yeah. Of course.
I'll just have to
run home first
and take some plates
out of the bathroom.
But it would be nice
staying together
at your place, right?
Yeah, it'll be a fun...
Step for us.
I just can't believe that
every Starwind suite
in the city is taken.
Me neither. The lady said
they're all booked up
for something called jackfest.
How many rooms did you book?
It's for your own good, Lemon.
I just want you to have
what Avery and I have.
I am a grown woman.
I have been doing things
my way for a long time.
I don't like my life stuff
mixing with my dude stuff.
- A middle-aged woman
saying "dude stuff"...
is that on my sadness
scavenger hunt?
Why, yes, it is.
Carol and I enjoy
our separate-but-intersecting
lifestyles.
It's perfect.
I'm like that woman
on the food network
whose husband only comes home
on the weekends,
and she spends the rest
of her time
eating and drinking
with her gay friends.
Her name is
the Barefoot Contessa, Lemon,
and you will never be like her,
starting with
the barefoot part.
I'll have you know that
I wore sandals this summer,
over socks...In a dream.
Welcome to the late show
with David letterman.
Please have your tickets out.
And now, as with all
studio audiences,
we will sort you
according to attractiveness.
Front, front, back,
balcony, front, front...
Mr. Jordan!
No, you do not exist!
I'm in control of this!
Want to watch TV?
First thing you need
is tequila...
Stop. Wait. No.
The Barefoot Contessa...
I love this show.
Me too.
This is one of the three things
in the world I like...
Ina Garten, sweater weather,
and...
When Muppets present
at award shows?
- Wow, yes!
- Me too.
We really see eye to eye
on a lot of stuff, don't we?
Absolutely. I've never
met anyone before
who had the exact
same idea as me
about what to do
with Palestine.
- It would work, right?
- Of course it would work.
And don't you agree
that our situation
is perfect right now?
We have these great visits
together,
but then we still have
our separate lives.
We're like Jeffrey and Ina.
No, no, I can't...
I can't live like this anymore.
I'm not like Jeffrey Garten.
I'm not as strong as that guy!
Don't have too much fun
without me, okay?
I need to know where
this relationship is going,
and I can feel you
resisting it.
No, no...
It okay.
Don't be cry.
I'm a pilot, Liz.
You know, I've spent
my entire adult life...
just casual girlfriends
in different cities.
I... I can't go from woman
to woman to woman anymore.
How many women
have you been with?
I'd rather not say.
It's shameful.
I mean, I'm a pit.
Six.
Oh, that's not so great.
- I want grown-up love!
- Hello?
- Thanks.
Carol had a complete meltdown
about the state
of our relationship.
I can't believe I tried
to clean my bathtub for this.
No, this is healthy, Lemon.
Where is Carol now?
I finally got him to sleep.
I had to spoon him
for, like, an hour.
And I was the outer spoon.
Welcome to adulthood.
As for me, I have
successfully retreated
for another day.
When Avery got home from work,
I noticed that she had
some paint samples in her purse,
so I immediately asked her
if her sister had done
anything crazy lately,
and guess what...She had.
Avery talked about that
for about an hour,
her anger eventually
transforming
into some rather
interesting sex.
And now she's sleeping
peacefully
while Fabius has retreated
to his den,
where he is drinking scotch
and playing snood.
- Uh-huh. Does Avery's work
email go right to her phone?
- Why?
- Nothing.
Just sending her a link
to this cool site...
funkyvintagewallpaper.com.
Lemon, don't! She keeps
her blackberry in bed with her.
- And send.
- Damn it, Lemon!
It has to be elk tongue!
Oh...
Eww... No!
This Jenna promotion
is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
Do you understand how much
free time I have now?
Yesterday, I went to the gym.
And this morning,
I made love to my wife.
And she was still asleep,
so I didn't have to be gentle.
That's one of the most
upsetting things
I have ever imagined.
Are you sure?
Think about it again.
Yes.
Liz, the writers can't take
a car service at night anymore.
I've crunched the numbers,
and it's cheaper for us
to just replace anyone
who gets murdered.
So did Avery like
my wallpaper idea?
- She did. Heh heh.
- Huh...So why are you happy?
Because the Fabian strategy
is working.
Every new pattern
Avery showed me,
I would simply say,
"yes, I like that one too."
And she was so overwhelmed
with the choices
that she made a mistake.
She suggested that we consult
her old college friend,
who's an interior designer.
- Uh-huh.
He's coming here
to meet with me today.
His name is James.
Not Jim, not Jimmy...
Jamessss.
I get it.
She's sending her army
into unknown territory.
And I am flanking her...
With these.
Have you seen my eyes, Lemon?
Yep.
They're very blue.
Like a mikonos sky.
Mark Foley once
called them "piercing."
Hmm.
Avery has really made
a misstep here.
Do you know what a prize I am
in the gay community?
There's a term for it.
I'm a bear...And I'm a
I'm a daddy bear.
Just one hour
of flirty chatting with James,
and you know what I'll get.
Not a Glaad award, I know that.
Elk tongue.
Well, I'm glad to hear that
you've almost
vanquished your girlfriend.
Thank you.
And you versus Carol...
how's that going?
I don't know. We had
a pretty emotional breakfast.
He says he's leaving early now.
I don't know what to do.
I know it's difficult, Lemon.
But now you have
an adult decision to make.
Would you rather let go
of your precious autonomy,
and let Carol into your life?
Or would you rather
teach your cat to dial 911?
First of all, I'm tired
of playing "would you rather."
And second of all, you know
that I have life alert.
Oh, I pushed it.
I need a phone.
Mr. Jordan.
Mr. Jordan, please stop.
You're not real.
If I threw you
in front of a car,
it would drive
right through you!
No! No...Sir!
I am real!
Would an imaginary me know
that you have a mole
on your list of pets to get?
Or that your favorite color
is rainbow?
Of course it would.
It would know anything I knew
because it sprung
from my imagination.
Sir, it's really me!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no, I missed it!
Do it again!
I love you, Ken-word.
Why don't you come
back home to TGS
and pick the peas
out of my fried rice?
And the rice.
I just want carrots.
I can't do that, sir.
But don't you miss
rubbing my foot
back into the shape of a foot?
Of course I do.
But I'm real happy here at CBS.
They gave me a tote bag
with the mentalist on it!
- I guess this is good-bye.
Obviously, I'm going to need
the tote bag.
James, tell me,
which one of these do you like?
Because with my untrained eyes,
the strie is bland,
and the, uh...
Wallpaper just looks busy.
Oh...I don't know.
Do you see something, uh,
here that you like?
It's so frustrating.
♪ ♪
I think I found a way
to get the budget down
to where Jack wants it.
That's my girl!
You are en fuego.
I was looking it over,
and I've realized something.
There's one too many
producers, Pete.
Okay, I get it.
But please...
I have five kids...
That I don't want to be
at home with.
No, Pete, it's me.
As great as I am at this,
I'm not really necessary.
Hmm, the last time I said that,
I was in a three-way
with two of the backstreet boys.
No, Jenna, you can't quit.
I'll take a pay cut.
We can fire Liz!
This is hard for me too, Pete.
But it's because
I'm a genius producer
I know that you have to
fire me.
Take my producing fee
and amortize it
to cover the gaps
in transport and electric.
Hey, Liz, would you rather...
- Oh...
- Be with the person
you love forever,
but you always
have to wear a shirt
made out of their pubes,
or be alone
for the rest of your life,
but you get to wear
whatever you want?
Shirt of pubes.
I thought you left.
I came back.
I mean, I had to kick
an obese teen off the flight
to get a seat, but
I really wanted to talk to you.
Look, I'm not sorry
you saw me cry.
I'm an emotional guy.
That's actually not even part
of my personality.
That's just something
that happens to people
who change altitude
more than four times a day.
Is that also why you got so mad
watching the giants game?
No, that was because
why does Geico have
three different spokespeople?
They have the caveman,
the lizard,
and then the stack of money
with the eyeballs.
And the fake Rod Serling guy.
Oh, my God, right.
Thank you.
I mean, you see how good
we are together?
Look, Liz, I want this.
But if we're gonna go for it,
we gotta move forward a bit
with each visit.
Two minutes to air.
Cast, please set yourselves.
Look, you have to get back
to the airport, I have a show.
How do we move this forward
in the time allotted?
All right, let's each say
one thing about ourselves
that the other person
doesn't know
on the count of three,
all right?
Ready? One, two, three.
I'm on a waiting list
to adopt a kid.
Touched by a priest...
it's fine.
Wait, what?
Okay...
That was a step.
Yeah.
See you October 14.
Cast for "would you rather"
set yourselves, please.
I never thought you'd
make it this far, Lemon.
I know, season five... We were
supposed to get cancelled.
Not just the show, I mean you.
You're in an "adult dude"
situation.
You're wearing
a beautiful blazer
from Rico's husky-boy
collection...
Is that what
ragazzi robusti means?
I'm just saying
I'm happy for you.
Thank you, Jack.
And I'm glad that you're getting
to keep your wall "elk tongue."
Actually, no.
The fabulous James and I
came up with an excellent idea.
We're taking that wall down.
That way we can make the master
bedroom closet bigger
and gain a nice
architectural symmetry.
Huh. You think maybe that's
what Avery wanted all along?
Oh, my God.
Hannibal defeated Fabian
with a decoy army.
James was a plant.
The strie wall finish
was a decoy.
She hannibaled my Fabian!
Lemon, Avery and I are
perfect together.
Like...Whiskey and hunting.
"Soul mate" doesn't even begin
to do it justice.
She's my...
She's your pube shirt.
Pube shirt.
That's our show.
Good night.
Good night, Miss Maroney.
Good night, Mr. Jordan.
Good night, TGS band,
with your funny-smelling
dressing room.
Good night, bear!
Good night moon...Soon park
from accounting.
Good night, Miss Lemon.
Good night, Mr. Donaghy.
I lied to Mr. Jordan.
I miss you all so much.
Sir?
Is it really you?
Sure is.
Wanna go kiss in the prop cage?
What? No!
Sync by honeybunny
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net