We need to talk.
Right now!
We know Tracy is not in Africa.
He's hiding somewhere in New York.
- What?
- Don't play stupid, Walter.
We have ways of
making people talk.
By giving them
fresh apple slices.
Listen to me very carefully.
This show is my life.
I need Tracy back.
Where is he?
You think
we don't want him back?
Do you know how much
our Cobra payments are?
And he's the only one
that knows the combination
to the candy safe.
The worst part
is being able to see the candy.
All right.
But if I find out
you're holding out on me,
I will no longer allow you
to use my office
for your history club.
That's ironic, because
next week's topic is fascism.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
What about grizz and dot com?
They don't know anything.
Neither does anyone
Tracy's close to...
his wife, Charles Barkley,
Edward James Almost,
who is an Edward James Olmos
lookalike
- that Tracy is friends with.
- Kenneth talks to Tracy
on Skype, doesn't he?
Just call him.
It doesn't work that way.
Tracy only contacts Kenneth
on special occasions
like Bastille Day.
I'm going to go ahead
and assume
that Bastille is a stripper.
As well you should.
Now there's a chance
he may call tomorrow
because it's
his lizard's birthday.
Has it really been a year
since we were all at the Waldorf
eating that cake made out
of lizard meal?
Yup. Jeremy's almost 11.
For now, our only lead
is the pizza box
that we saw Tracy eating from.
We traced the phone number
to a pizzeria in Queens.
Listen to me.
I sound like Cagney and Lacey,
but without the slutty clothes.
You have to find him, Lemon.
Your show works with Tracy.
And this morning, I figured out
how to fix NBC.
We will only do shows
that work.
That's nonsense.
Do you know
what the business model is
in the entertainment industry?
Make ten shows and hope
that one of them works.
We produce more failed pilots
than the French air force.
$15 million so far
developing a show
called Who Nose?
about an investigative reporter
who can't smell and has to get
the story using only his eyes,
ears, and other senses.
You underestimated me,
congressman,
because I can't smell.
But you made one mistake.
You let me see the documents.
So from now on, no more
throwing good money after bad.
Only what works. $10 million
developing Dad 2.0?
Not on my watch.
Your father may be gone,
but before he died,
he programmed me
to take his place.
No. Shut it down.
This is terrible.
So what's going on?
Is Tracy coming back
or what?
Well, I don't know.
Well, what do you know?
What do you even do?
I'm the producer
of the show.
Right, that's what
your wife told me
in the shower this morning.
All right, well,
we're all having fun,
and it's important that we all
be able to laugh together.
Yeah, we're not laughing
with you.
We're laughing at you,
you bald bitch.
Yes, Reggie, I am bald.
I lost my hair
at a very early age
when I hit that Gypsy's kid
with my car,
but I am still your boss.
Hey, bald bitch.
Hey, that's you.
- No, I get it.
- He's being you.
Yeah, I get it.
I get it.
Listen up, fives.
A ten is speaking.
As you may have heard,
the Jennababy dolls
I've been selling on QVC
have been recalled.
Apparently
they were just being used
to smuggle cocaine
into the country from Mexico.
And that's caused some problems.
Let's just go
to soccer practice now.
I mean right now.
Yes. It's 4:00 in the morning.
Let's do it.
We own this town.
Jennababies were my backup
if TGS gets cancelled,
but don't worry because I have
a backup to my backup.
We don't ever worry
about you.
We don't think about you.
That's right, Frank.
I booked a movie.
It's called
Take my Hand.
It's kind of an artsy character
study about a young woman
who has a lot of holes
drilled into her head
by a deranged veterinarian
named Slaughterface.
Oh, so you're doing
a torture porn thing like Saw.
Exactly. In fact,
the producers of this movie
rented Saw
and watched it.
So let me know
if Tracy comes back.
Until then, I will be
in Stamford, Connecticut.
We're shooting there
for tax reasons.
On an unrelated matter,
does anyone know where I can get
intimate bleaching done
in Stamford, Connecticut?
Anyone?
I'm leaving to do a movie,
Pete.
What? No!
You can't do that.
That's what your wife told me
in the shower this morning.
Ha.
Can we order lunch
from Ikea?
What?
No.
I'm the producer.
I'm picking lunch today.
Okay.
We'll have a contest of strength
to decide who gets
to pick lunch.
Who's next?
Welcome to Federici's.
What can I get
for you guys?
Well, as hard as it is
to believe,
given our apparent ages,
this is my son.
- Seems about right.
- Okay, good.
My son is currently studying
at a local pizza academy.
Really? Which one?
New York Pizza Academy.
Well, then I hate you,
'cause I'm a Pizza Academy
of New York man.
Wonderful.
So what fraternity
are you pledging?
I'm not.
There are no fraternities
at New York Pizza Academy.
That's right. You correctly
answered my trick question.
Now I'm bound
by pizza academy tradition
to grant you any request.
Wow, this could not have gone
any better.
We need to see
all your delivery receipts
from the last two months.
Oh, you got that delivery
receipt exam coming up, huh?
What a bear.
Here you go.
Take your time.
I'll be in the back trying to
think of other ways to help you.
Well, this is obviously
a dead end.
Yeah!
Eat your weakness.
Congratulations.
According
to the transitive property,
you just defeated Muammar
Qaddafi in arm wrestling.
Yes!
This would have bothered me
in my 20s.
Pete, how are you so good
at that?
I don't know.
I never work out.
Paula!
Here comes the big girl.
She's got a clarinet.
Pete, lunch is your pick.
Takeout from Hooters.
What?
That makes no sense.
We'll know they touched it.
No one's coming to save you.
Oh, God.
Who are you?
Cut!
I just got a text
from the studio.
We're shutting down production.
- What?
- But I turned down Carousel
- at the Goodspeed for this.
- I'm sorry, Dana,
but our budget depends
on getting a tax break
from Connecticut, and they say
we're not portraying the State
in a positive light.
How are we not doing that,
Shawn?
I'm a little baffled
over here.
Yeah, no, it's just that
we're spending taxpayer money
saying there's a veterinarian
running around Connecticut
trying to make
a house out of breasts
for the Governor to live in.
But there's a positive message
at the end of it.
If you're a woman
in Connecticut,
Slaughterface will kill you.
This must be it.
Yes, ma'am.
There have been several
deliveries to this address
of Mr. Jordan's
signature order...
large cheese pizza
with one slice taken out
so I can pretend
I'm eating pac-man
like my hero
Blinky the ghost.
I hear someone coming.
Well, well, well.
You found me.
After I ordered Thai food
and gave you this address.
Yeah?
I'm sorry. I thought
my friend was living here.
And my best friend.
Oh, is this awkward?
Because I'm your best friend,
but you're not my best friend?
No.
No one living here.
At least not since we moved in
two weeks ago.
Wait a minute. Was that stuff
here when you moved in?
A copy of Black Yachts magazine
and a Rubik's cube that
has been smashed out of anger.
Mr. Jordan was here.
So what, Kenneth?
These guys have been here
for two weeks.
Tracy could be anywhere.
We're never gonna find him,
TGS is gonna get cancelled,
and then what?
Can I work here?
I'll do anything.
I'll get in my bra,
and you could throw nails at me.
I'll dance for you.
Miss Lemon.
Don't panic.
We have other options.
But for instance...
Mr. Jordan!
Where are you?
Come back!
For the love of God,
come back or we'll die!
Jack, can we talk?
One ten to another.
I'm an 11, but continue.
Me, my ass double,
and a drill that once appeared
on Home Improvement
are currently starring
in a feature film
called Take my Hand.
Really? Years ago,
Universal had a project
by that name.
It was a romantic comedy
with Reese Witherspoon
and Patrick Dempsey.
Reese Witherspoon's
just a likeable version of me.
Then she dropped out, and it
was rewritten as a buddy comedy
with Dempsey and Josh Hartnett.
But everyone fell asleep
during the table read,
so we moved it over
to Telemundo
where they tried to turn it
into a variety show
hosted by a supermodel and
a soccer ball with a mustache.
I met that soccer ball once
at a no-hands-allowed sex party.
Then after another round
of rewrites,
it was picked up
by our low-budget thriller,
high-budget porno division,
Splatterflix,
and now it's a horror movie
starring "any blonde actress."
Thank you.
Wait, that's our project?
This is exactly what
I was talking to Lemon about.
Three years,
millions on rewrites,
$20,000 in first-class flights
for the drill.
And we still have nothing
to show for it.
And we never will.
We just got shut down
because Connecticut's
being a douche bag.
They won't give us
a tax break
unless the movie
promotes tourism.
Then we make the movie
pro-Connecticut.
We are not losing any more money
on Take my Hand.
Okay, we just need to hire
some of those ugly people
who have the paper
and change the shapes on it.
Writers?
No.
We'll do the work ourselves.
Meet me in my dressing room.
I'll get a computer
from one of the ugly people.
And I'll bring the world's
greatest encyclopedia...
my mind.
Hey, is that a to-do list?
'Cause if your wife's on there,
I've already taken care of her.
I challenge you
to the wrestling of arms.
- What?
- Arm wrestling.
On the stage.
Midnight.
In front of everyone.
How about tomorrow?
Seems like it would be
more convenient for people.
I'll meet you
anytime, anywhere.
I just have to work
around a PTA meeting at 5:00
that I can't miss, 'cause,
this week, I'm snack dad.
Lemon, you look terrible.
And I once watched you eat
oysters while you had a cold.
We had him, Jack,
and we lost him.
So Kenneth and I had to spend
the rest of the afternoon
trying to think
like Tracy.
I ended up eating a swordfish
dinner at a strip club,
and Kenneth grabbed a cop's gun
and shot a blimp.
Well, tomorrow's another day,
so go home,
have a glass of wine,
and watch a show
about wedding cake disasters.
I can't go home, Jack.
TGS goes away
if I don't find Tracy.
I'm gonna wait up and hope
that he calls his lizard.
Did you make sure
that Tracy wasn't pretending
to be his own wax figure
at Madame Tussauds?
Yes.
There was some confusion,
and I ended up punching
the real Levar Burton.
I'm gonna go get Jeremy.
I hope he's not still in heat.
He has gotten
my top off before.
Here you go.
Did you know
that Connecticut is home
to the oldest public library
in the United States?
Huh. Could you use that
to motivate Slaughterface
sewing the sheriff's mouth
to his own anus?
Of course. Elegant.
Should vaginatorium
be capitalized?
Oh!
I cannot wait to humiliate
that guy in front of all
of his meathead buddies.
You're like a new man, Pete.
Yeah, I am.
Last night,
I had sex with Paula,
and neither of us
was wearing a walkman.
Oh, yeah.
Why are you
picking him up now?
I'm supposed to have him
till the weekend.
Shane wanted to come home,
'cause his dad's a loser.
Did your show
get cancelled yet?
We don't know, Stephanie.
We're waiting for Tracy
to Skype with Liz
and Jeremy the lizard.
You're a joke. David is taking
us all to Outback Steakhouse,
and we're getting appetizers,
'cause David can afford them.
Well, of course he can.
Mr. big shot pet photographer.
I hope he can sleep at night.
Never thought
I'd feel sorry for a guy
with a tattoo of a leprechaun
vomiting on a book.
No one's coming to save you.
- Oh.
- Because we're deep
inside one of Connecticut's
30 beautiful state forests.
30!
Oh, please,
don't kill me.
I still haven't tried
the famous seafood pizza
at Sally's in New Haven.
And cut.
Great. All right.
Let's move on to the scene
where Slaughterface centipedes
Jenna to the docent
of the Danbury Railway Museum.
Hold on.
I just spoke to Walmart.
They sponsor
wholesome TV programming,
and I've convinced them
to get into the movie business.
They will partially fund
this project
if we make it family-friendly.
I can never find stuff
to watch with my kids.
Thank you, Walmart.
This production
will be profitable.
Jenna, to your dressing room
to write.
It begins with the words.
Reggie.
I need to show you something.
Whoa.
Is that your deltoid?
I'm gonna beat you, Reggie.
But I don't want to.
I saw you in the lobby
with Stephanie
and Shane talking
about David and appetizers.
Look, I know what it's like
for your kids
to think you're a loser.
Which is why I'm gonna throw
the match.
Wow.
You would do that for me?
Know what your wife told me
in the shower this morning?
You're a good guy.
Oh, miss Lemon,
wake up.
It's him.
Okay, this is it,
Parcell.
We got to keep Tracy
on the line,
so draw him out.
Don't spook him.
Act normal.
Hello.
I'm a baby.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
- You got in my head.
- Hang on.
Something's not right.
Why is Jeremy acting so weird?
I don't like this.
- Hey, Tracy, don't hang up.
- Uh-oh.
Jeremy, call me
when you're alone.
I'm sorry, miss Lemon.
Don't be.
I know where he is.
Merry Christmas!
I practice abstinence.
Connecticut!
And cut.
We're not done yet.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Phil Rosenthal,
the creator
of the acclaimed show
Everybody Loves Raymond.
Last great sitcom.
Still does a 3.4 share
in Syndication.
I did okay.
I have a refrigerator
that's just for sodas.
Anyway, Phil is interested
in getting into acting.
- I got the bug.
- And has offered
to pay us $5 million
to be in the movie.
I'll rewrite the part myself.
You know what, why don't we
just get one as written,
and then we'll play with it.
You are a guest here, Phil.
Hello, Phil.
I never heard back
about my audition
for Everybody Loves Raymond.
I'd wondered
if you made a decision.
Yeah, 15 years ago.
We went with Doris Roberts.
But thank you for tying
your headshot around a brick
and throwing it
through my window.
Go ahead, bald bitch.
Go ahead.
Thanks for doing this.
I convinced my ex
to drop off my kid so
he could see me being a winner.
You rock.
No one's gonna know
that you did this
or that you're actually stronger
than me.
It doesn't matter.
All that matters
is I'm doing the right thing.
That's real strength.
Ha.
I beat you.
We're getting lunch
from Ikea.
- Ikea!
- Ikea! Ikea!
Ikea! Ikea!
That's fine.
Don't offer your guest anything.
Wax statue.
Darn it.
I thought we had him.
Are you kidding me?
You have been hiding
in my apartment
for the last two weeks?
What are you mad about?
I'm waiving the $60,000
you owe me
in appearance fees.
Did you really think
I wouldn't recognize
my college futon with its
trademark absence of sex stains?
This is the stupidest idea
you've ever had.
Really?
Think about it.
TGS is your whole life.
So where's the last place
you would be
if you were out
trying to save your show?
Home. Life lesson
from an unlikely source.
The only thing I do here
is sleep.
I know.
I seen you do it.
You're having a dream.
Is this your only mustard?
Huh? What?
Yeah.
You're the one who wrote
"every kind of mustard"
on my shopping list.
And yet you still don't have
the one I'm thinking of.
It's red.
It says ketchup on it.
Oh, I hear it.
That's on me.
Look, Tracy.
I don't know
why you're going crazy,
but I want to help.
Just come back to TGS.
You don't think I want to,
L.L.?
Then why are you hiding?
Oh, no, did you
also spill ice cream
on your mom's boyfriend's
record player?
As a time saver, I will refer
to the two of you as Klemon.
I wanted that next level,
Klemon.
Now, remember,
to save time,
you two are Klemon.
- It's a combination of...
- Just keep going.
I had everything I dreamed of.
Awards, respect,
Justin Long's autograph.
But I also got expectations.
People thought
I could change the world.
And it's too much pressure.
Like the time I got stuck in
Temple Grandin's hugging machine
at the Golden Globes party.
You pretended
to be in Africa
so that no one
would be disappointed in you.
I'm sorry I did this to you,
half of Klemon.
I had no choice.
Sean Penn wanted me to go
to Haiti with him.
And I'm not strong enough
for the pain
and the human misery
of a three-hour plane ride
with Sean Penn.
I'm tired of hiding.
I just want my old life back.
Then you need to get people
to stop respecting you
and start remembering
what an idiot you are.
You're off the leash,
Tracy.
It's not a leash.
It's a very long skin tag.
You want your old life back?
You're Tracy Jordan.
Hulk Hogan called you
a dirt bag.
The NAACP once hired someone
to kill you.
You wore a penis hat
to princess Diana's funeral.
Because I had worn it
to their wedding.
It was special
to the three of us.
You were the worst,
and you can be again.
You just have to go out there
and remind people
who you really are.
Go trash a hotel room,
expose yourself to Elmo,
visit OJ in jail again,
attack the Lincoln Memorial
with a hammer.
I have to burn
all my goodwill.
Then they won't expect anything
from me.
And you can go back
to your old life
and TGS.
Tracy Jordan
is off the leash!
Godspeed, Mr. Jordan.
♪ I'm the hero cop ♪
♪ and I'm here to say ♪
♪ don't do drugs ♪
♪ is what I'm here to say ♪
I can't believe
that amazing rap is available
now on iTunes.
Are you kidding?
No one's gonna pay to see that.
It doesn't matter, It's already
profitable. It works, Lemon.
To vote for Phil Rosenthal
text "Phil" to 62288,
Vote? For what? Isn't this
supposed to be a movie?
Again, it doesn´t matter. People will
just to anything to get 99 cents of text.
Well, I'm not letting Rosenthal win
I am voting for the muppet.
To vote for Liz Lemon
text "Liz" to 62288.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net