The writers put it on my door.
I don't know
what that's referring to.
It's referring to this one time
that I got a chemical peel
before work,
and I was wearing a red and
green sweater and a fedora.
But these douche-bs
have been doing this for weeks.
- "Lez Lemon."
- First thought.
"Winona Ryder
in a hundred years."
- Weak.
- "Fart Barfunkel."
- Indian food.
- "Paul Simon."
I don't get that, but it hurts.
Ok, I love a good joke,
but I am their boss,
and, at a certain point,
it crosses a line.
To quote Rodney
Dangerfield, "Hey, I...
Hey, I..." No, let's see...
Lemon, if you're about to say
that you don't get any respect,
you're right.
I mean,
in a post-apocalyptic world,
how would society even use you?
Traveling bard.
Radiation canary.
I have to run, Lemon.
I have an appointment
in Washington.
The hearings on the Kabletown-NBC
deal are underway,
and the company has entrusted
me to be their front man.
Hey, will you ask congress
where they put the USA network?
I've been trying to find monk
for, like, three months.
The only thing
I will be discussing
with the house subcommittee
on baseball, quiz shows,
terrorism, and media
is vertical integration.
What's vertical integration?
Imagine that your favorite
corn chip manufacturer
also owned the number one
diarrhea medication.
That'd be great,
'cause then they could put
a little sample of the medicine
in each bag.
Keep thinking.
Except then they might be
tempted to make the corn chips
give you...
Vertical integration.
Wow, that should not
be allowed to happen.
But it's my job to make sure
that it does happen.
Do you know who gets elected
to congress these days?
Former athletes,
washed-up actors, and women.
I'm locked and loaded
and ready for whatever
these beltway lobotomites
throw at me.
What if we have
to stay overnight
and there aren't enough rooms,
so we have to share a room,
and I forgot to bring
a shirt to sleep in
and the stores are all closed...
[Exciting jazz music]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Liz, quick question about
the Johnny Appleseed sketch.
Does it hurt it if we can't
call him Johnny Appleseed?
Yes. Why?
Well, Johnny Appleseed
was a real guy,
and his descendants
are very litigious.
So here is a list of the names
that legal says we can use.
Jerry Bananaseed.
And nothing else.
Great, so what are my choices?
Either I argue with legal
or I spend all day
writing something else?
Does anyone care how hard I
work... [Text message beeps]
Oh!
We can't use Jerry Bananaseed.
Someone with that name killed
a bunch of nurses in Portland.
[Sighs]
Kenneth.
You're back.
I need you to get me something
called vagitrax.
It's for dry knees.
I wish I were back,
miss Maroney.
I'm reapplying
to the page program.
But it's a lot harder
than my first time around.
It's gotten really competitive.
You shoulda seen what I saw
in Mr. Winerslav's office.
Well, your interview
will be Thursday.
Is there any a/v equipment
you'll be needing?
- Equipment?
- ♪ Inside Schwartz 21 ♪
♪ hill street blues,
wings is fun ♪
♪ golden girls,
quantum leap ♪
♪ outsourced
is the new friends ♪
The process used
to be dignified.
Now it's just a pageant.
Just a pageant?
That's like saying a guy is cool
because he has just a speedboat.
If you need help
winning a pageant,
you've come to the right place.
Well, if it'll get me back
into the page program.
When I was pageantizing,
my mother told me
there's only three things standing
between you and winning...
your breasts
and wanting it bad enough.
I'm not sure that applies...
we've already started.
And this deal will count
as a 39% bump
variable against an 11% increase
of synchronized flexibility.
Sir, my name is Rob Reiner.
And before I became a Congressman,
I dabbled in television,
won a couple of Emmys.
And I believe
that my experience out there
in hollyweird gives me
a special insight
into these types of deals,
particularly when it comes to...
Say it, meathead.
Vertical integration.
Ahh,
the dreaded V.I.
Bad for America, kills
innovation, drives up prices.
Is that it?
I guess
that's why big oil and Microsoft
are such great American
failures.
- What? - Dare I say vertical
integration drives down prices
by streamlining the process.
Consider the farmer.
He owns his land, the equipment
he uses to harvest his crops,
the truck that he uses
to drive that product
to the farmers' market
where he sells it
directly to the consumer.
Is that
not vertical integration?
1:32 P.M.
Mark the time, ladies and gentlemen,
that congress put a bullet
in the head
of the American farmer.
No! You win!
The acclaimed director of
when Harry met Sally
would never do that.
As always,
it's been a pleasure.
Mr.
Donaghy, one last question.
Why is NBC so racist?
[Tap dancing]
Horrible.
What else can you do?
♪ Oh, everybody ♪
♪ born before Jesus ♪
♪ is in hell ♪
♪ they went straight... ♪
Enough.
I'm gonna have to reinvent you.
Break you down completely
and build you up from scratch.
Just like Mickey Rourke
did me to sexually.
But miss Maroney, I don't want to
be reinvented I want to be me.
All right, first things first.
Can you lose that goony accent?
Well, I don't know, ma'am.
[Accent getting thicker]
You made me think about it,
and when I get to thinkin'
'bout it, it just get worse.
Mr. Donaghy,
I represent
Rhode island's first
congressional district.
It's a diverse community, from
the hard-working moms and dads
of Smithfield
to those spoiled jags at brown
to a thriving, flourishing
Italian criminal community
in Providence.
It's my responsibility
to make sure
that public airwaves represent
the face of my public.
Now, one question, why is it
that NBC looks about as diverse
as a Wilco concert?
I would point
to Sunday night football,
which features
many black players and coaches.
Oh, and we have
Anthony Anderson,
the star of law & order,
which is entering its 21st...
[whispering]
It's been cancelled!
What?
Why did we cancel that?
That doesn't make any sense.
Mr. Donaghy, this may just be
about money to you,
but, as a member of congress
and a black woman...
I don't really see color
or gender, Mr. Chang.
I feel I have an extra duty,
not just to my constituents,
but to future generations.
Now, unless I see
some serious change at NBC
and soon, I can guarantee you
this deal will not happen.
[People murmuring]
Rhubarb, rhubarb, rhubarb.
Peas and carrots.
Rhubarb. Rhubarb.
Rhubarb.
Dotcom, you run Tracy's
production company, right?
Yes. Dotcom productions.
That's Tracy Jordan
spelled backwards.
- Well, I need programming for
the African-American community,
and nobody knows that
demographic better than you.
Don't worry about it,
Jackie D, I'm on it.
Call Grizz.
I need someone around
who's not just a yes man.
Whatever you say, Tray.
Oh.
Come on, Walter.
What is going on?
Representative Regina Bookman
is using the Kabletown hearings
as a soap box
from which to complain
about a lack of diversity
on TV.
Well, she has a point.
I was reading the new Malcolm
Gladwell new yorker piece
on my kindle.
Did you really read that?
No, I did not.
I really resent
the congresswoman's accusations.
I've long been an advocate
for diversity.
It's made this nation great.
The Chinese built the railroads,
the Irish built
and then filled the jails...
A guy named Juan
built my armoire.
Diversity means new ideas
and new markets.
It is our best hope
for true innovation.
Did you tell all that
to congresswoman Bookman?
No, I was too busy
trying to remember
the name of the black kid
on community.
D'nall glover.
It wouldn't have mattered
anyway.
The whole thing
was just political theater.
You should have seen
her grandstanding.
The future and America.
Now I may have lost my train of
thought several minutes ago,
but if I continue
to talk like this,
no one will notice,
and when I stop,
you will applaud my energy.
Thank you.
[Applause] Thank you.
I can't let Bookman
jeopardize this deal.
Tell me about diversity
at TGS.
Well, Lutz claims to be inuit.
At least
that was his explanation
when I found his poem
about snow.
What about Toofer?
Is he any good?
I don't know if he's mentioned
this to you 100 times,
but he went to Harvard.
So we know he's smart and
superb at masturbation.
Ha.
Is there any way
we can give him a promotion
of some kind?
Sure.
Make him co-head writer.
I always figured he'd take over
for me when I die at my desk.
Really?
You're okay with that?
Oh, yeah. Let someone else share
the total lack of respect,
deal with the meetings,
the complaining,
the stupid Johnny Appleseed
sketch.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You are not doing a sketch
on the Appleseed family.
Monty Appleseed and I share
a liquor locker at the opera.
[Screams]
[Hoarsely] I forgot my doctor
said no more frustrated noises,
because it makes my vocal cords go...
[muttering]
Now it's gonna be
like this all day.
There you are.
I've got hair extensions
for you
and a body shaper
with a reinforced penile sleeve.
Miss maroney, please.
My feet are killing me.
I am trying to help you,
Kenneth.
Believe me, I wish you weren't
such a Houston foreclosure
of a human being,
but I need to tear you down
and turn you into someone that
can actually win this thing.
They hired keyboard guy?
He's not even recycling
properly.
Miss maroney, wait.
So what do we want
to see on TV?
I personally love cop shows.
I can't wait for law & order
to start back up.
Why?
It was a tentpole!
A tentpole!
Well, here's something
I've been working on.
It's called let's stay together.
After the Al Green song.
It focuses on an African-American
family in Detroit in the '70s.
Motown, the auto industry,
Vietnam, Watergate.
Let's stay together
is not just about a family
trying to stay together,
but also a nation.
What if there was
a talking dog?
I'd like to see that
incorporated into your rewrite.
Okay, meeting over.
♪ Thank you, NBC ♪
♪ for all the laughs and tears ♪
♪ once home to Kelsey Grammer ♪
♪ the golden girls,
my name is Earl ♪
♪ the a-team
and cheers ♪
♪ so shine on and thank you ♪
♪ NBC ♪
A top-ten network.
Smile.
Okay, let's dig in, cohorts.
It means the badger in Spanish.
I'm not sure who did it.
Toofer's got
a head writer sign on his door.
It's great.
Good for him.
Oh, God.
Tejon face.
Is this about the TV interview?
What TV interview?
It's nothing.
It's just a local cable show.
- Well, if my co-head writer is
being interviewed, then so am I.
Aqui viene el tejon!
- The only thing that worked in
the read-through was the dog.
- How's production going, Tray?
- Good.
And there's a lot of buzz.
Can you hear it too?
Or is my tinnitus acting up?
Hey! That food
is for Dotcom productions only.
TGS's food is backstage.
But they don't have
women's sports bars.
Men can have cramping too,
you know.
Mr. Donaghy, I have representative
Bookman on the line. Oh.
Representative Bookman.
Mr. Donaghy,
I'm in New York right now.
Some colleagues of mine and I
are taking meetings
on wall street
and then we're doing
a sex and the city walking tour.
Magnolia bakery?
Oh, sorry, hips.
But it looks like
I'll have time to stop by
and continue our conversation.
Good.
I welcome it.
As I was trying
to say the other day,
this company has
a long-standing commitment
to diversity and inclusiveness.
Yo, Jackie D, I had dinner
with don Imus last night.
He told the following joke...
- Good-bye, congresswoman.
I can't believe
they rejected me.
Well, of course they did.
The bridge was supposed to be
shuffle-ball-change,
maxi Ford, Cincinnati,
Cincinnati, double-time
shim-sham-shimmy, toe punch.
I don't know
what you were doing.
I'm sorry, miss maroney.
And where was your sparkle?
You embarrassed me in front
of all the other mothers.
If you think you're going
to sizzler tonight, Jenna,
you got another thing coming.
Oh, you'll be practicing
your steps in the garage
until the school boat comes.
If I hadn't seen you come out
of me in that parking,
I'd swear you weren't
my daughter.
Oh, my God.
What just happened?
I think you just turned into...
let me get there.
I've turned into my mother.
And I turned you into me.
You're welcome.
But it was wrong.
Well, to make it up to me...
let me get there!
To make it up to you, I am
going to get your job back
or my name isn't
Yustrepa Gronkowitz.
I mean, Jenna maroney.
Welcome to right on.
I'm your host, Rutherford Rice.
With me is my co-host
Shirley Thomas.
Our topic for today
is African-Americans
and their roles in the Mia.
Our first guest
is James Spurlock,
head writer
for TGS with Tracy Jordan.
- Good day, tri-staters.
- Co.
Co-head writer.
And also with us is someone
named Elizabeth Lemon.
Thank you, Rutherford.
It is a pl...
I can tell that you're off me.
Mr. Spurlock, do you think the
system is broken when it is news
that an African-American man
is a head writer
for a network TV show?
I think I can answer that.
Another question
that we could be asking
is why isn't it a big deal
that a woman is a head writer.
I would argue that TV is more of
a boys club than a white club.
I like your dress.
Do you have to wear
a bra with it?
I will let you get back
to Toofer.
Who's Toofer?
I don't know.
James, when people think
of TGS,
they think of Tracy Jordan,
Jenna maroney,
the mysterious crew deaths,
the Angela Lansbury lawsuit.
What they don't think of is you
working long hours
late into the night,
giving up any semblance
of a life.
Well, James Spurlock,
you can finally take your bow.
You are right on's
Arthur Ashe of the week.
Okay, you know what?
I get it.
I shouldn't be here.
I should have realized that
when I saw the masks
and the picture of black Jesus.
That's me in college.
All righty.
All right, I said
I was leaving.
You don't have to have your boss
come and...
that's a security guard.
That's not great.
Sir, representative Bookman
is on her way up.
Jonathan, what did we talk about?
But, sir,
I was born in Palo Alto.
[Indian accent]
I will go get her, sir.
A thousand apologies.
- Jack, it's an actor
me-mgency.
I want to get Kenneth
back into the page program,
but whatever this is
won't let me.
What? Who care Jeffrey,
just hire Kenneth back.
But Mr. Donaghy,
the only...
I don't have time for this.
Just do it.
Thank you, Jack.
- Mr. Donaghy. - Representative
Bookman, welcome to NBC.
This is the perfect place
to begin our tour.
Studio 6h, home to one of NBCs
biggest stars, Tracy Jordan.
Mr.
Jordan, Regina Bookman.
We met at the congressional
black caucus fundraiser
you crashed
your motorcycle into.
And thank you, representative.
What you're doing
is very important.
I can assure you
that NBC is committed
to making diversity a priority.
Then just walk away
and don't try to kiss her,
Tracy,
and don't say that last part.
Hey. You eat
from your own table, remember?
Our food is separate.
Separate!
I'll kill you, white devil!
[Screams]
Let's just head this way.
So how was your flight?
Congresswoman,
this is Jeffrey Winerslav.
He heads our diversity
and hiring initiative.
What's the latest
from H.R., Jeffrey?
Well, I'd like to tell you
that we filled the minority slot
in the NBC page program
with a native American fellow
named wants to get sandwiches,
but you made me hire
that guy instead.
Oh, brother.
Mr. Shoelace, you're being silly.
You call that a diversity hire?
Maybe.
That young man is a hillbilly
with a girl's middle name
and, because his county
never rejoined the union, a foreigner.
Now you're untied?
Have you two been talking?
There's James.
Attention, everyone.
Oh, give me a break.
I present you, James Spurlock,
with the 2010 Tavis Smiley
excellence in broadcasting
award.
Thank you for making us
all smiley.
[Applause]
Mr. Spurlock, how long have
you been head writer here?
- One day.
- Mm-hmm.
And who is the real
head writer of this show?
I am.
Ah. Tell me, you obviously
lonely and tired woman.
Do you have to put up
with this nonsense every day?
- Yes. - You know, they
say 90% of the work
is done by 10% of the people.
Thank you for being that 10%.
You're welcome.
After what I just saw,
you may be the only person here
I respect.
You get an "I met
a congresswoman" sticker.
Thank you.
Finally.
That's all I wanted...
This country was founded
on certain principles.
Oh, brother.
Freedom, troops, America, flag.
Now I might not ow
where I'm going with this,
but I know
we will get there together!
[Applause]
Who loves pizza?
[Cheers and applause]
Congresswoman, a word.
Okay, fine, I was putting on a show.
I was tap dancing.
But you made me tap dance.
Did someone say tap dance?
What was I supposed to do?
This is
a multibillion-dollar deal.
There are thousands of jobs at
stake, hundreds of second homes,
and your ridiculous grandstanding
could ruin the whole thing,
like luffing your spinnaker
during a yachting regatta.
I know I'm not helping myself.
Sorry.
Grandstanding?
Do you not think
I believe in this?
It's just political theater.
You're up for reelection.
Yes, maybe I get carried away
sometimes with my love
for this great country and the
troops and the flagtroops...
you're doing it.
And I apologize.
But I only talk this way
so I can get people to listen.
I care about these issues.
And so do I.
If you just give me a chance
instead of ambushing me
in front of the congress
and my own employees.
You think I don't take diversity
seriously?
Only a fool doesn't.
Diversity is the engine
that drives this country.
We are an immigrant nation.
The first generation works
their fingers to the bone
making things.
The next generation goes to
college and innovates new ideas.
The third generation...
Snowboards and takes improv classes.
We always need people
who are pulling themselves up
by their bootstraps.
I did it.
And it's my job to help others
do it too.
How do I know
you really mean that?
you're not just grandstanding?
Oh, I'll show you how.
Unless you give me
a real reason not to,
I'm voting no on this deal.
Then I've got three months
to change your mind.
I'll show you
that this company...
I'm cutting
that fat cracker's head off.
I'm part eskimo.
Hate crime!
- [Shouts]
- [shrieks]
Three months, congresswoman.
We were here first!
[Shouts]
Tray!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
They closed the plant.
I gave those people 30 years.
I didn't even get a watch.
All I got was this pink slip.
You think you got it hard,
I've got two dates tonight.
Stanley, even for a dog,
you are a dog.
Yes! Great fix, Grizz.
[Doorbell rings]
[Chuckles]
- Uh-oh.
Ain't life a bitch?
www.tvsubtitles.net