Alright!
Now that the popsicle's mounted,
we've got ourselves a tongue depressor
I want you to look at these
cold sores...
I get them when I'm stressed-out
Nothing to be ashamed of...
I get them from prostitutes.
It's been a hard couple of months,
Work has been crazy,
and I went through
a bad breakup.
And then there was
this plastic bag
that represented my death...
sounds like you could use
a little R&R...
Rum and ritalin.
Actually, I was hoping
you'd just have an ointment
- for my mouth.
- Gross.
'Cause I'm dealing
with the stress thing.
Over the break-up,
I'm renting a cottage
out in the Hamptons.
There's just four things
I want to do this summer...
be outdoors,
wear shapeless clothing,
do some mindless activity
like gardening,
and learn Spanish.
There are four things
I want to do this summer.
But they're roommates,
so it's tricky.
All right,
here is a prescription
for your cold sores,
and here's a blank one
for the weekend.
Now, one final thing.
Why aren't you wearing pants?
The other doctor told me
to take them off.
Other doctor?
That's my brother Randy.
Tomorrow he's going to jail
for the rest of his life.
Good one, Randy!
Hey, you want to go
to taco bell for lunch?
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
- Hey...
- Stop right there.
I know that people
are feeling sorry for me
because my wife was kidnapped
by Kim Jong-Il.
- I know...
- But I do not need your pity.
And I am tired of hearing
that tone of voice.
- Aw...
- Hey...
Hey, buddy...
Hey, I know what
you're going through.
I once kidnapped a woman.
I know...
- Stop talking like that, Lemon.
- I'm trying to,
but I'm kind of locked in,
sweetie.
The voice is
controlling me now.
Help me?
Look, obviously
this has been difficult.
I'm not sleeping.
Last night I sat
in front of the TV
and ate an entire carton
of foie gras.
I can hardly drink
my morning shower scotch.
I miss Avery.
It's the little things
I miss most.
On a day like this,
we would go to Strawberry Fields
in Central Park
and kick hippies' hacky sacks
into the bushes.
Look, you need to reset
and try to feel normal again.
Normal? I don't know
what normal is anymore.
"Normal" is a woman and a woman
getting married
and having a child.
- What?
- Is me being a bummer
helping you
feel like your old self?
- Keep going.
- Bush is a war criminal!
There's so much texting
going on these days
and no communicating.
Carbon tax!
Please leave!
That's the spirit.
Well, I'm off.
- Have a good summer, Jenna.
- Oh, I will.
Do you remember
when I performed
during halftime
at the Wool Bowl?
It was on ESPN-34.
♪ You can't spell "America" ♪
♪ without w-o-o-l ♪
♪ it's all better in wool ♪
A singer, everyone!
Woolly the wool mascot,
everybody!
The sponsors
were so happy with me
they're now naming me
the new celebrity face of wool.
How exciting!
Every year my aunt sends me
a wool sweater for Christmas.
We get it, Aunt Alice.
You're a sheep.
Also, this is very lucrative.
Paul and I can finally buy
that timeshare in Betasten Bos,
Amsterdam's premier
private sex garden.
They have
genetically altered men there
with minotaur heads that
chase you through the brambles.
Okay. Well, good-bye,
my closest female friend.
Oh, my God.
The season's over.
Why are you losers still here?
Final melee, Liz.
It's the last game
of the season
and no one wants to lose.
You have no summer plans?
Well, David Eggers and I
are designing a new font.
Ugh, shut up.
Frank, you have a girlfriend.
And Lynn wants me
to give up video games
'cause she thinks
I need to grow up.
How's this for growing up?
Last night for dinner
I put milk in my Apple Jacks.
Ha! I distracted you,
and you died.
- Game over.
- No, I shot my bazooka
at the ground to kill myself
'cause Toofer had me cornered.
Now I respawn and start over.
So you're killing yourself
rather than let
someone else win?
That's why everyone
has zero kills
and we've been playing
for 18 hours.
I'm wearing a diaper,
like a baby would.
Wow. I can't wait
to get out of here.
For three months.
It's gonna be glorious.
♪ ♪
Mmm.
Hi, neighbor.
II'm ina Garten.
You know,
my husband Jeffrey is away,
and I've got some bruschetta
and white wine open.
- Why don't you come over?
- I'm alive!
All I have left is to pay
the fine that I incurred
for committing a hate crime
against what the city is
now claiming was a Jewish tree.
And I'm free.
Have a great summer.
I'm not one
for good-bye speeches,
but I do feel...
Lutz, what are you doing?
Don't look at me.
Mm.
Jenna, this is a great day
for the wool council.
Well, I am very proud
to be your new spokeswoman.
You know, in the past,
I was the face of Clinique,
a French-Canadian
anal rejuvenation clinic.
And I was the feet
of filthylittlefeet.com.
Yes, well, about that.
Jenna...
Wool is a wholesome fabric,
which is why your contract
includes a morality clause.
You will be required
to conduct
your personal life in manner
which is consistent
with the values
of this industry.
Oh, of course.
We're just a little worried
about publicity like this.
No, Eugene,
that's not just some guy
I picked up at a dog bar.
Paul and I are
in a committed relationship.
Is he a cross dresser?
Goodness, no!
Paul is a gender-dysmorphic
bigenitalian pansexualle.
I see.
Maybe we should take a few days
and think about this.
No. Whenever men say that,
I never see them again.
You just need to meet Paul.
Our relationship is
everything that wool is about...
love, warmth,
chafed skin.
♪ Oh, noble sheep ♪
♪ we eat your babies ♪
♪ we use your brain ♪
♪ to fight off rabies ♪
♪ but the most beautiful
gift you give us ♪
♪ is wool ♪
All right, Jenna.
I'd love to meet Paul.
Let's say dinner tomorrow night
at your place.
I'll bring my wife.
Excellent.
I should warn you...
This had better be
a very normal dinner.
No hijinks, no farce,
and not just for the sake
of your relationship
with the National Wool Council,
but for the sake of my wife,
whose parents
were killed in front of her
while an episode
Three's Company was...
You know what? I'll let her
tell the story at dinner.
Wool-come, Jenna.
Sherry, who was at the door?
Kenneth, what are you doing?
Well, I know
your wife was kidnapped
by some
convenience store owners,
and I'm real sorry about that.
I'm not looking for pity.
Pity? Oh, sir,
back in Stone Mountain,
people lose their spouses
all the time.
Mumps, hill people attacks,
cave collapses,
both business and residential.
Continuing my list...
Kenneth, what do you want?
When someone needs help,
we don't waste time
feeling sorry for 'em.
We help them.
And you seem like you
could use a home-cooked meal.
Oh, that smells delicious.
It's an old
Parcell family recipe.
But I like to replace
the Union soldier meat
with boiled potatoes.
I haven't eaten at this table
since Avery's been gone.
That was her chair.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- No, please sit.
You two have
similar-shaped buttocks.
Deer God,
thank you for this venison.
Onion god,
thank you for these onions.
Carrot god,
thank you for the carrots.
Spanish for older women,
lesson 12.
Emergencies.
"Disaster approaching."
Desastre inminente.
Fore!
- What?
- Oh, my God!
Liz? It's Tracy!
From work!
What are you doing here?
I just bought everything
around this house.
It's supposed to be
a nice area,
except for the "new element"
everyone keeps talking about.
Look, I got a long night
of shooting guns in the air
ahead of me.
Do you mind
if I take a nap here?
Of course!
You're my neighbor.
I wanted a normal summer,
and chaos is my normal.
If I start screaming
in my sleep,
do not wake me up!
I will attack you!
Wake me up!
Free me from this!
Ah, Kenneth...
Thank you
for dinner last night.
It was nice to hear
a woman's laugh
in the house again.
You're bad.
I thought maybe
we could do it again tonight.
Oh, sir, I'd love to,
but I can't.
- Why not?
- Well, I have to work.
Now that the crew is gone,
I like to give everything
a good spring cleaning,
starting in the bathroom.
There's a lot of drawings
of Ms. Maroney eating celery
that men are giving to her
with their hips.
I see.
Well, another time, perhaps.
I'll just be alone...
In a house full of memories.
My house is full
of white cockroaches.
Hi, sweetie!
I got you
an early anniversary present.
It's a new leash for
when I walk you through the park
like a dog.
The weather's supposed to be
nice and muddy tomorrow...
- What's wrong?
- Look...
I'm the face of wool now.
I need to maintain
a certain image.
So, what,
we can't be ourselves?
Just not in public.
We can do whatever
we want here.
Except tonight.
Mr. Gremby is coming over
for dinner.
Eugene Gremby
from the wool council?
- Tonight?
- I just want him to meet you
and see us together.
Then he'll get it.
He'll understand what we have.
But the Grembys
are pretty conservative.
Maybe you should change.
Really? This is
a conservative top, Jenna.
And I hate to be
the stereotypical man,
but this is my home
and I wanna wear this blouse.
Paul, please.
You need to change.
Okay, I'll change.
And I'll cancel
the sitter for tonight,
tell him he won't need
to come sit on us after all.
Oh, you just made
a very dangerous enemy, Kenneth.
Thanks for the heads-up,
Jonathan.
Do you wanna come
to my birthday party?
What are you doing?
That's my job.
Uh, Jonathan
volunteered to clean up
so you could come over again
tonight, right, Jonathan?
But, sir,
it's not just the bathrooms
that need cleaning.
That's why
Jonathan's family is here.
Uh, Liddy goes down at 7:00,
so I'll see you then.
Oh, my.
Liz Lemon.
Any idea when your party
will be over, tray?
The party hasn't started.
That's just the guys
setting up.
Could I borrow a cup of sugar?
I'm trying to get a hummingbird
to drink out of my penis.
I can't do this, Tracy.
This is supposed to be
my vacation.
I wanted to spend it
learning Spanish,
not living next door to you.
I give up. Of course I'm not
allowed to be a human being.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You didn't wanna live
next door to your friend
after all I've done for you?
How many times have I come over
and painted your apartment?
Three! And by the way,
stop doing that.
Or maybe you're saying
we're not friends.
That's fine.
I don't think it'll affect
my behavior next season.
"The sad woman
has been trapped by the idiot."
La mujer triste...
We're friends.
Next year's gonna be fine,
'cause we're good friends.
We're sp...
spending the summer together.
Great! I'll come over
tomorrow morning!
Okay, well,
since you've just been staring
at me like that
for the last 20 minutes,
I'm gonna scoot on out of here.
Don't go, Avery.
Uh, I mean Kenneth.
Sir.
You called me "Avery."
That's your
kidnapped wife's name.
What a coincidence!
I haven't slept in days.
I'm not really feeling
like myself.
You know, in the evening,
Avery and I would
sit together and talk.
It was a nice way to unwind.
Well, I bet you miss...
Put on these earrings.
So...Tell me
about your day.
Well, I got
a soft yes from Jonathan
about my birthday party.
Then I went to
a very uncomfortable dinner.
Do you know what I did today?
Tried to be strong,
sat alone with my thoughts,
then...
I went to a wonderful dinner.
Then the dinner ended?
No.
So, Paul, what do you do?
I am in
the restaurant business,
and I really love...
Golf-playing.
Is that so?
What's your handicap?
Oh, well,
I don't have one myself,
but I do like a girl
with a limp.
Oh, Paul.
So, Mrs. Gremby,
you're also named "Eugene"?
Oh, no, dear.
It's "u" period "Jean."
My first name
is U. Jean
with a "u."
Oh, that's a nice blouse.
It definitely goes
with your eyes,
don't you think, Jenna?
Golf, blouses.
I'm just so impressed
with how normal
this dinner has been.
Very wool!
Greetings, slaves!
Who's ready to get sat on?
Uh, sir,
I don't know who you are,
but you are not wanted here.
Didn't you get my text?
I thought
it was part of the game.
We are good people
who have no interest
in being sat on!
So don't spew your statistics
on the health benefits
of weekly sittings
or its wide acceptance
in eastern cultures.
- Paul.
- We're normal!
And being normal is American,
and it's respectable,
and it makes us...
Happy.
Now get out of here.
Well done, sir.
Bravo.
You handled that pervert
with aplomb.
Very wool.
To tomorrow's photo shoot
and wool.
Shh! Shh, shh, shh.
Unbelievable...
you're still here.
It's still zero, zero, zero.
To zero.
I did it.
I spoke.
This didn't get mailed.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
out in the Hamptons
not getting invited to stuff?
I came back for the day.
Tracy lives next door to me.
I can't leave, I can't stay.
I'm trapped.
Speaking of trapped,
I got you, Lutz!
Nope, grenade.
Blowing myself up.
Oh, my God.
That's what I have to do.
I can be a normal person.
I have to blow myself up.
No, your honor,
I'm not disputing the fine.
I'm refusing to pay it.
Grenade, respawn.
Miss... I mean, ma'am,
read the fine print.
If you don't pay,
I can sentence you to
up to three weeks
of community service.
How about three months?
This is a sham,
your dis-honor.
Nay, a mockery!
I've put the system on trial.
You can't handle the truth.
I'm out of order?
You're out of order.
Victor Sifuentes!
Hoo-ah!
Gavel, gavel, gavel!
I lost my gavel
over the weekend,
but it doesn't mean
you can talk to me like that.
Talk to who?
I just see an empty robe.
Do you honestly not see me,
or are you being rude?
- I am being rude.
- That's it.
Twelve weeks
of community service.
You'll spend your whole summer
picking up trash.
Gavel, gavel, gavel!
Freedom!
For me.
Probably not you guys.
Mr. Donaghy,
where are my clothes?
Sherry must've put them
in the wash
while you were showering.
Now, give us a twirl.
This is not right, sir.
Now, what do you say you
put on some of Avery's perfume
and we head over
to Strawberry Fields
and whip pennies
at the drum circle?
I don't like to swear, sir,
but, no, thank you.
Now, maybe I haven't had a wife
who was kidnapped,
but I have seen the Brady Bunch
where Tiger runs away.
We've all been through
some bad stuff, Mr. Donaghy.
I had the perfect woman.
Gorgeous.
Brilliant.
Always let me be the hat
in Monopoly.
Why is this happening to me?
God, are you punishing me
because my hair
is better than yours?
All right, sir, enough.
You wanted me
to be Mrs. Donaghy?
Well, I know Mrs. Donaghy,
and she is mean.
She once made Rahm Emanuel
cry in an airport lounge.
So fine.
I will be Mrs. Donaghy.
And I'm gonna say...
Listen to me, Jack.
You don't want people
to pity you?
Well, they should,
because you're pitiful.
You think you're all alone.
"Boo-hoo, why can't my life
be the way it was?"
Well, it can't.
And you're not alone.
You have a daughter
you should be
spending time with
instead of being weird
to Kenneth.
He may be a chinless piece
of human garbage,
but he will never fill the void
that I left behind.
Oh, look, here he comes now.
He's gonna ask me
to go to his birthday party.
"Hi, 'Mrs. Don'gy.'
you wan' come on down
my birfday party?"
No, I can't,
but I know Jack can.
Kenneth, Kenneth, I get it.
Uh, Sherry?
Put Liddy's baby pantsuit on.
I'm taking her
to work with me today.
All right, Mr. Donaghy.
And, uh, thank you.
Avery.
Here's to you, Jenna Maroney.
Even with your back to me,
I can definitely tell it's you.
I'll turn around later.
Perfect.
I'll keep talking.
Mm, wool.
You know, my wife U. Jean
is out of town
visiting her parents' graves.
Maybe we could meet later
for a drink
and you could show me
your front.
We could do that...
Now!
Paul?
And Jenna.
Oh, my God!
I'm finally taking a stand...
After all these days.
You wanted us to be normal.
Well, this is our normal,
and this is what we think
of your morality clause.
Mm, give mommy some beard.
Ugh!
Oh, you got
some crumbs in here.
Oh, eat it.
Good God! Lemon?
Liddy, say
"good God, Lemon."
Goo gah, Lem.
I did it, Jack.
I got my dream vacation!
You're on a chain gang.
I'm outdoors,
I'm wearing comfortable clothes,
I'm gardening,
and I'm learning Spanish!
Uh, Liddy and I
just went to strawberry fields,
where she spat up
on a white lady's dreads.
It's nice to see
that we're back
to our version of normal.
- Jenna?
- Oh, Jenna, no.
There you are!
Bad dog!
You'll go in the crate tonight.
- Grr.
- Ew.
Hey, Jack.
Hey, Liz.
Ow!
Fore!
Hey, guys!
It's me! Tracy!
The black guy from work.
What are you doing?
I hooked a ball onto a truck
on the Long Island Expressway.
And Tracy Jordan
does not take Mulligans.
Good thing you had
to move out of that house.
Some idiot rammed his boat
that I was driving into it.
You see all the good
that is in them,
how much capacity for love?
Yes, I know.
I just need more time
with them.
Give me more time, Jacob,
I beg of you!
Go, I see you...
I'm killing myself.
Respawn.
Oh...
Dammit!
Hola, everyone!
Are you ready for Season 6?
And we moved the files from your
old computer over for free.
Oh, my God.
Wait...
How long have we've been here?
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net