Happy New Year, congratulations
on getting married, sir.
I know I didn't deserve to be invited
so I thought I'd give your gift now.
Not if it's a song.
It's not.
It's...
This belt.
Oh.
Well, the nuptials
were perfect.
We rented a villa
on St. Esclavage.
For my second wedding, I just
wanted a five-minute ceremony
surrounded by one giant party,
so the service was performed
by an exiled French
admiral/defrocked minister.
Well, I'm glad
it went smoothly.
- ♪ You and I... ♪
- Uh, the only hiccup
was that my best man,
deep sea explorer
and raconteur Bob Ballard,
took ill after eating
some bad toucan.
So, uh, Lemon filled in
as my best man.
This is from St. Esclavage.
It's my marriage certificate.
Oh, good God.
Liz Lemon,
I want it to be noted
that I'm here on time.
This is a new year
and a fresh start for me.
Now I got to go.
Where are you going?
I'm hosting the International
Pornography Awards.
And I have to go get
an insurance physical
so I can fly into the arena
in a penis-shaped parachute.
Hey, what is going on
with Jenna's dressing room?
Jack rented it out
to an I.T. company.
The Kabletown board
is meeting this week
to approve buying NBC, and
he's doing everything possible
to make us seem profitable.
He turned the green room
into an NBC experience store.
And we have to schedule
our rehearsals
around the bat mitzvahs
Jack has booked in the studio.
When Madison was born,
I said, "Rivka,
my schveltz is filled
with schpoinkis."
Okay, well, I'm gonna talk
to Jack about this.
I'm sure he's still in
a good mood from the wedding.
- Oh, yeah, how was that?
- Total chaos...
No rehearsal,
no program,
the bride wore
a black cocktail dress.
The airline lost my luggage,
and the only place
to buy anything on the island
was at the tennis pro shop.
Luckily, I had the essentials
in my carry-on...
toiletries,
closed-toe shoes,
and the state department-
recommended mosquito head nets.
I sense more complaining
in you.
Terrible flower girl.
At four years old,
you should know
how to pace
your petal distribution.
Hannah, petal, step,
petal, step.
Come on!
And don't even get me started
on the monkeys.
You!
It needs to see Mr. Donaghy.
It needs to see him right away.
Get us all our stuff back.
- Hey.
- Elizabeth, shut the door.
Lemon,
during my wedding ceremony,
do you remember being asked
a question by the minister?
Yeah.
It was something like...
And in spite
of not understanding,
you responded, "Oui."
Well, one of my new year's
resolutions is to say yes...
yes to love, yes to life,
yes to staying in more.
Do you remember signing
this document afterwards?
Yeah.
The minister told me to...
On the epouse line.
Witness.
Not witness.
No, Lemon...
Wife.
Mother...
Vous partagez?
C'est tres europeen.
Est-ce que je peux vous joindre
dans votre partage?
Oui.
They married us by mistake?
It is a clerical error
that will be rectified
immediately.
See, this is exactly the kind
of thing that happens
when there is no order,
no planning.
Hitler and Martha Stewart
would have hated that wedding.
Of course,
it's everyone else's fault
that the minister thought
the lady
in the white dress and the veil
was the bride.
It was a men's tennis shirt
and a government-sanctioned
head net.
You kept holding on to my arm.
It's hard to balance on sand.
Who wears shoes on a beach?
Only Rocky and Apollo Creed
during the training montage.
Who cares?
You're fixing it.
I'm sorry you got caught up
in another one
of Liz Lemon's adventures.
My adventures...
I am the protagonist.
Avery is in China right now
covering an economic conference.
She is not a spy.
I want this taken care of
before she gets back.
Divorce papers
are being drawn up.
Try to sign on the right line.
Whatever you say, dear.
Do not.
Don't forget, honey,
we have bridge
with the Cunninghams tonight.
Tracy, you are going to die...
What?
No!
When I tell you who I'm dating.
Squeaky fromme.
She is difficult.
Anyhoo,
I have the results
of your physical.
Tracy, you are going to die.
What?
No!
You have no reflexes.
Your blood tastes
like root beer.
And some of your bones
appear to have vanished.
Now, I've only ever seen
this kind of thing
on dead people
during operation Desert Storm.
I actually wrote
a report on it,
but my commander refused
to pass it on up to Saddam.
Kooky times.
But I can't die,
Dr. Space-Man.
Who will be there
to raise my kids
if I'm not around to pay someone
to raise my kids?
Look, making even minor changes
to your unhealthy lifestyle
would help,
like diet and exercise.
Well, we tried.
Oh, look, I'm sorry, Tracy.
But on the bright side,
at least your family's
financially set for life.
Now, this could
literally kill you.
Lollipop?
Thank you for taking
in Miss Maroney, Mr. Baker.
We would have asked you sooner,
but we forgot you worked here.
Thank you
for doing this, Danny.
It's gonna be fun.
Yeah.
It's like...
it's like we're married.
Now, don't you two
start bickering
like old married folks.
Are you okay?
It's just I got a haircut,
and you didn't even notice.
Sorry.
You get your hair cut
every week.
Excuse me?
I don't like your tone.
And I don't like
what you've turned into.
I'm not the one who forgot
our one-minute anniversary.
Finally,
as the merger progresses,
you'll notice some changes
to your benefits,
including
new health care options.
I'm sorry. That should read
"few health care options."
I've got to redo this.
You have to talk to Jack.
I can't lose my dental.
There's a hygienist there whose
boob sometimes touches my ear.
Yeah, go upstairs and tell
your boyfriend to help us.
Jack is not my boyfriend.
He is, dot-dot-dot,
my husband.
On your wedding night,
did he take you
in the French fashion?
No, there was a mix-up
in St. Esclavage,
and Jack and I
are technically married.
Oh, my God.
Did you hear
what I asked you before?
Liz, you should know
that NBC has strict
antinepotism guidelines.
If your husband is your boss,
then you're both going
to have to come
to my office and discuss this.
What? No.
It's not real.
- We're getting a divorce.
- That's what Ann Curry
and Subhas the janitor
tried to tell me.
That was five years ago.
No, it's a mistake.
We are signing something
tomorrow.
Wait, Liz, we can use this.
Jack needs a divorce.
You have leverage.
What are you talking about?
You don't sign
any divorce papers
until we get the studio back,
our full budget,
- our health insurance...
- Pete, I'm not...
They shut down
your secret bathroom
- to save on cleaning costs.
- I have to talk to my husband.
No, no, Bob,
we made it very clear.
You have to buy NBC
with everything else.
Then just don't watch it.
What is it, Lemon?
I'm trying to negotiate
a $30 billion deal.
That's billion with a "b."
Is that right?
That seems like way too much.
Yeah, well, my staff and I
are also trying
to do our jobs, but we can't
without studio space
or health insurance
or those vegetable chips
that I hate
and I keep telling Kenneth
not to get.
Let me show
you something, Lemon.
This is
our NBC priority pie chart.
The big red part you can see
is The Biggest Loser.
The yellow slice,
our number-two priority,
Make It 1997 Again
Through Science or Magic,
and the little green part
is everything else.
Request denied.
No.
Request denial denied.
You have to make TGS
a priority.
Your show netted $600
last year.
- Your parents had to buy an ad.
- I don't care.
If I don't get what I deserve,
I'm not signing
those divorce papers.
Are you blackmailing me?
You should think very carefully
about what you're doing
right now.
I am...
Lots.
Very well.
We'll do this divorce
the hard way.
But I'm warning you.
This isn't
my first rodeo, Lemon.
Well, I've been to a rodeo too.
It was a cat rodeo
in a gay guy's apartment.
Hey!
What happened to my poster
of the Montreal Alouettes?
It's signed by Marc Trestman.
Oh, it's tacky, Danny,
just like your mother's
stupid chain emails.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, my nails are wet!
Mr. Hornberger...
Do you and your wife
ever fight?
Not all the time.
After her hysterectomy,
she was in a coma briefly.
How do y'all make up?
Ah.
Look, Paula and I love
each other,
but two people living together,
it's unnatural.
And while our children
are basically snot silos
with bb guns,
they do come in handy
as a buffer.
Is that like being a fluffer?
Because I have done that
and did not enjoy it.
Blow-drying animals
at a pet salon is hard work.
No, a buffer
is a protective barrier.
Like pigs have around
their delicious testicle meat.
We can't fight around the kids.
You see them looking up at you
with their little faces,
their hair already receding,
and you bite your tongue.
A buffer.
What is it?
Thanks, Jack, for coming
to this emergency meeting.
I'm sorry I'm four hours late,
but my alarm clock
didn't go off
because it died
in a cockfight last night.
Tracy, what can I do for you?
Well, it's come to my
attention that I'm going to die.
Oh, please, you have nothing
to worry about.
We have Martin Lawrence
on a holding deal.
Look, I don't want anything
to happen to my husband.
But if it did,
we have a lot of expenses.
Estate planning is complicated,
what, with the government
taking half.
What?
That's double taxation.
I like you, Angie.
How can I help?
Well, to maintain
our standard of living,
I need to be able to earn
as much as Tracy does.
And if you need to make
millions of dollars
but have no real skills
or education,
the best place to do it
is in entertainment.
I mean, look at me.
I can't even find Mexico
on a map.
Things are a little tight
at the company right now,
but if you want to learn about
the entertainment business,
I can find you something.
Oh, yeah, I'm willing
to start at the bottom.
There's only one thing
I won't do,
and that's take orders
from anyone, ever.
Hey, Angie, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm not about to cancel
my hair appointment with D'Fwan
because I'm your new intern.
You need to light
some incense in here.
Okay, hang on.
Who said you're my intern?
It was Jack's idea.
I have to start a career.
But I'm gonna need next week off
to go skiing.
What?
Okay, I see what this is.
Jack's messing with me.
We're having a little fight,
- so he sent you here...
- Excuse me.
How is my being here
messing with you?
Do you have a problem
with strong black women?
No!
Don't you see?
That's the kind of exchange
Jack wants.
Angie, an intern's job
is to do things like make copies
and run errands.
So I'm like your servant?
No, because
you're not being paid.
You're really more like...
Oh, boy.
Look, Angie,
you don't want to be an intern.
Don't tell me what I want.
And I don't really have time
to mentor someone right now,
so I don't think
this is a good idea.
I don't understand.
That white girl just fired you.
Come on, D'Fwan,
be a buddy.
Hey.
Idiot, don't touch the...
Nothing.
Love you.
Look,
I made this picture of us.
Did you draw that?
You might need help.
That's awful for an adult.
Well, I think
it's great, Kenneth.
You should hang it on the wall.
Careful!
Don't coddle the boy.
He can do it.
Aah!
Oh, my bones!
- Now look what you did.
- You made him afraid.
Oh, did I also make you
half a man?
- You're ruining my life!
- What life?
My bones.
Lemon, why do I have
an appointment
with Jeffrey Weinerslav
tomorrow morning?
Every day
that I'm married to you,
my life gets worse.
That Angie thing
was real cute, Jack.
And some of your plan worked.
Yes, she hated me,
and, yes, I mentioned slavery
by mistake.
I knew I could count on you.
But you also made me her boss,
so I fired her.
She chased me around
for a while,
so I hid in a closet
down on news,
but then Subhas
and Ann Curry came in,
just going to town on ea...
- Damn it!
- Is this a game for you two?
I thought you were trying
to help my family.
My family!
I'm not a pawn.
I am a queen.
You all are trash.
And you know what Angie Jordan
does with the trash?
She drags it out to the curb
for pickup.
Angie, I did not mean...
- I will rip your weave out.
- It's not a weave!
- Oh, good God, Angie, no.
- Ow! She pulled my hair out.
I should never have made you
an intern.
- You're a star.
- That's right. I am.
Entertainment
is where untalented people go
to get rich,
and you have all the makings
of a reality superstar...
hair pullingness,
delusions of grandeur,
an insanely short fuse,
- catchphrases...
- It's my way till payday.
That's the t-shirt.
I should give you
your own reality show,
Friday nights...
11:00.
What? That is when TGS
or wrestling is on.
I guess I could reconsider
the time slot
in exchange for your signature.
Ugh.
You know what?
I'm calling your bluff.
You're not giving her
a TV show.
FYI, I am friends
with a hilarious fat girl
and a crazy-eyed,
divorced white lady
who wants to be
in the music business.
Oh, I'd watch that.
- Can D'Fwan be on it?
- Mm-hmm.
With his even gayer boyfriend.
Okay, fine.
Give her her own show,
and I will watch it
on our TV in our house, because
I'm not signing anything.
This is not over.
You think my meth-addict
nephew should be on the show?
Yes, please!
Pete,
you and Paula fight a lot.
No, I-I walked
into a door.
I'm so clumsy.
Jack is using TGS
as leverage in our divorce.
He says he's gonna replace us
with a reality show about Angie.
- Oh, I'd watch that.
- Obviously.
But how do I fight back?
Well, first off,
you can't back down.
If you do that, we get nothing.
I agreed
to go to a furniture store
instead of watching football
one time,
and I haven't seen
a game since.
Oh, I hear ya.
I mean, take Danny...
Please.
Then you got to hit them
where it hurts.
Find their weakness
and viciously exploit it.
That's what marriage is.
Don't even get me started
on marriage.
Thank you.
Kenneth, your Danny
has something to tell you.
What is it, Danny?
Well, sport,
I'm gonna be moving out.
I don't understand.
Well, sometimes two people
who care about each other
just can't live together.
Oh, no, I get that.
What I don't get is this
is Danny's dressing room.
I'm gonna be staying
at the "y."
It's that dark place
under the bleachers
that's shaped like a wishbone.
But you're my Danny and Jenna.
And we'll always be
Danny and Jenna.
We just won't be
Danny and Jenna together.
And don't think
for one second this means
we love you less.
Know that it means that.
Well, tell the board
we are currently in talks...
Hold on, please.
Jonathan, I have asked you not
to call me at home
after 11:00...
Or before.
She what?
My husband and I
are absolutely so pleased
to be underwriting
the Jack and Elizabeth Donaghy
High School for Teen Drama,
the Arts, and Feelings.
- Son of a bitch.
- As embarrassed Americans,
Jack and I pledge $5 million
to create a new generation
of choreographers
and puppeteers,
clunes, video artists,
and theatrical jugglers
who will ask the world,
"what is art?"
We know what art is.
It's paintings of horses!
Good morning.
How is the happy couple today?
Well, it's no surprise
we're sitting here.
You two have always thrown off
that "will they or won't they?" vibe.
And it's been a real hoot
to watch your courtship.
Okeydokey.
Now, when two employees
get married,
it is my job to make sure
that the employee
is not receiving favoritism
from his or her boss.
Favoritism? Really?
He's trying to cancel my show.
Uh-huh, and what about your
little announcement last night?
Do you know how many fires
I had to put out this morning
because of you?
And what was that voice?
It is my imitation
of Drew Barrymore's impression
of that crazy lady.
Let's keep this meeting short.
Our marriage is a technicality,
and it will be remedied.
Also, in order
for there to be favoritism,
we'd have
to actually still be friends.
All righty.
Let's just dive on in.
Does the employee spend
an inordinate amount of time
in the employer's office
compared to other employees?
Well, yes, I suppose,
but only because Miss Lemon
is incapable
of doing anything on her own.
Oh, please, half the time
when I go up there,
it's to help you choose a tie,
and they're all red or blue.
Where I come from,
if you have
more than two colors on a tie,
it means you're looking
for a certain kind of bar.
Are all workday conversations
business-related,
or do personal issues
often dominate discussion,
including but not limited to,
mothers, diarrhea,
having babies,
problems in the bedroom,
neckties,
food issues,
foot disorders,
- having it all...
- Okay.
Yes. In the past,
we have advised each other.
For instance, Jack taught me
not to wear tan slacks
with a tan turtleneck.
I thought it looked nice,
but he rightly pointed out
that it made me
look like a giant condom.
And Lemon is the only one
of my subordinates
who's not afraid to warn me
when I'm being
too authoritative or handsome.
Or when you have eye boogers.
Have you spent time
with each other's families?
Have you attended
special events together,
such as class reunions,
birthday
or holiday celebrations,
weddings,
or extended car trips?
Are you each other's
emergency contacts?
Do you ever drink together
at work,
perhaps while summarizing
what you've learned
over the day or week?
Have you shared
intimate details
of your fears, hopes,
and dreams,
both personal and professional?
Is this the longest and perhaps
most meaningful relationship
in your life?
Do you often find yourselves
thinking the same thing
and then saying it
at the exact same time?
- I apologize, Lemon.
- I'm sorry, Jack.
I never should have tried
to blackmail you.
I'll sign the papers.
And I shouldn't have
threatened your show.
I'll leave that
to the parental decency groups.
And I'll back off on the budget
and the bat mitzvahs.
Okay.
Now we're gonna do
word association.
Foreplay...
We're done, Weinerslav.
Uh, try to walk
like a woman, Lemon.
Your fly's open, Jack.
I'm Angie.
I think elegance and attitude
are the same thing.
And I have IBS.
I'm D'Fwan and I just want to be
accepted for who I am:
a sexual maniac.
And I'm Portia. I don't care
what anyone says.
I keep the 3D glasses.
I'm Randi, with an "i".
My ex-husband's new girlfriend
is cheating on him...With me.
Do you have any meth?
Or meth?
It's my way till payday.
www.tvsubtitles.net