- Where are Tracy and Jenna?
We're supposed to be rehearsing.
- Hey, L.L.,
sorry we haven't had
time to get into
our costumes yet.
- How are we
already behind today?
- Liz, women wearing
Men's watches is so over.
The New thing is
to get an Adam's apple.
- My mom just had
this fixed for me.
It was my grandfather's.
He worked for years
at union Station in D.C.
As a pickpocket.
- Hey, Hey, hey.
Card game, guys.
$20 per,
pot's $1,040.
Who's in?
- What is this,
jabba's pleasure skiff?
- It's the crew lottery, Liz.
You buy a card.
If it gets picked,
you win $1,000.
Get a tub of New suits
from the suit emporium.
Kabletown guys notice.
Your hair grows back.
Everything grows back.
- All right.
Anybody else?
- Fine, I'll take one
if it'll get everybody back
to work sooner.
- [scoffs]
- What are you doing?
That game is not for
softhands and faceworkers.
It's for
strongs and lifters.
- They hate
when one of us wins.
[crowd booing]
Your boos are not scaring me.
I know most of you
are not ghosts.
- Come on, my card
only has
a 1 in 52 chance
of getting picked anyway.
- How did you know that?
You're like rain man.
Quick, how many toothpicks
are on the ground?
- Zero.
- You need to go to vegas.
- Whoa, why is toofer
in the punishment corner?
- [BrItish pronunciation]
I said time to end the charade
and adjust my schedule
to buy a new vase.
- Ugh, you stay there.
You stay there until you die.
- Look up the pronunciation
for "schedule" on the internet.
- [Jack's voice]
Schedule.
- Ha!
Stay in the corner.
- Wait, that computer.
It's Jack's voice!
- [Jack's voice]
America.
Whiskey. Liberal.
- No.
That can't be Jack.
Why would his voice
be on some random website?
It's impossible.
- [Jack's voice]
Lemon...
lesbian...frankenstein...
wants her shoes back.
- Oh, my god.
It is him.
[exciting jazz music]
♪ ♪
- Come in, Lemon.
Just revisiting some old
g.E. Quarterly reports.
My first cover from My first
year at the company in 1985.
- Ah!
- Ha! Good times.
Just out of frame is
a wheelbarrow full of cocaine.
- So why the trip down
memory lame?
Ha ha!
High-fiving a million angels.
- The Microwave Division
quarterly report
comes out today.
It will probably be
my last with g.E.
Now that I'm transitioning
to kabletown.
I've been
a g.E. Man for 25 years.
And a g.E. Woman for one week
of corporate espionage
at revlon.
- So...
is there any way you could
possibly be the voice of
pronouncify.Com?
- What?
No!
- [Jack's voice]
Those bastards.
- Those bastards!
- Who bastards?
- Part of my princeton
Scholarship included
work for the linguistics
department.
They wanted me to record
every word of the dictionary
to preserve
the perfect American accent
in case of nuclear war.
Well, the cold War ended,
and princeton began
selling the recordings.
- So people can just
buy your voice?
- Oh, the things
It's been dragged into.
Thomas the tank engine.
Wu-Tang songs.
- [Jack's voice]
♪ Ah, yeah, just like that ♪
♪ make 'em clap,
make 'em clap ♪
- huh, I always forget
you used to be poor.
- Thank you.
But Yes, I've had
to work my entire life.
It began when my father left
and I started working
on the Boston docks
as a 12-year-old stevedore.
Bales up, you micks!
Bales up!
- You've been working
since you were 12?
- I had to.
Those jobs
put me through college,
But they also kept me from
having the college experience.
I was up early every morning,
working my way
through the dictionary
for the linguistics department
or sweeping the floors
at the princeton monkey lab.
It wasn't the feces
that got to you, Lemon.
It was the crudely scrawled
notes of "help me."
- Yeah, well,
college wasn't that fun, Jack.
I mean, sure,
the first two weeks are nice.
- Lemon, I really don't have
time for a long--
- the fall of 1988.
A young Liz Lemon enters
the university of Maryland.
Richard Marx haircut.
Pilonidal Cyst under control.
It was a magical time, Jack.
- Don't worry about
getting to your point.
I'm going to live forever.
- The registrar accidentally
gave me a handicapped room.
It was huge,
and for two weeks
it was party central.
I was popular.
People gave me nicknames.
A blonde girl high-fived me.
But then,
like all good things,
it ended
before it even began.
- Lemon, that's actually my
thoughtful Window-staring spot.
Visitors stare...over here.
- [quietly]
Okay.
[both sigh]
- All right, guys.
The moment
we've all been waiting for.
We're picking a Winner.
Here we go.
- This is the lucky one.
Four of clubs.
Paula's nickname
for my penis.
- And the winning card is...
the queen of spades!
- All right.
- Who's got it?
- Oh, brother.
- Queen of spades.
Who's got it?
- Aw.
- Oh.
- Come on.
- Boo!
- She sucks!
- Guys, guys.
I'm not gonna keep it.
I'm gonna take this money
and open a tab for all of you
after work at Hurley's.
- Wait, for real?
- You know it, arriflex.
Chris...is this guy.
- Now, that is really cool
of you.
[all cheer]
- Lemon?
Can you make sense
of this?
- Well, on some level, Yeah.
That's a four.
That's a nine.
- Something's wrong here,
Lemon.
According to these numbers,
the microwave division
had their best quarter
in five years.
- So?
- So they did it without me.
- No, they didn't.
I mean, you're still
the head of that division.
You hired everyone there.
If they succeeded,
it's because of you.
- Lemon, that's the smartest
thing you've ever said.
- Really?
What about three years ago
when I said
there Should be
more tv shows about cake?
- I'll drive out
to r&D IN STAMFORD,
congratulate my team,
make Sure everyone remembers
who got them there.
They'll probably give me
a crystal plaque,
and I in turn
will reward one of them
with a name remembrance.
Lemon, why does
your crew look drunk?
- I won $1,000 and I
gave them all a bar tab,
and they got drunk at lunch
and now they like me.
- Oh, Lemon, please.
Money can't buy happiness.
It is happiness.
- [Jack's voIce]
I love unicorns.
- I told them not to.
Let's get out of here, Jack.
- I'll tell you what.
Make me say anything you want.
Get it out of your system.
- [Jack's voice]
Obama is very presidential.
- All right, enough!
I was trying
to be a good sport,
but you should be
ashamed of yourselves.
A bunch of 30-year-olds,
sitting around
acting like college freshmen.
- Hey, I'm almost 46.
- When some of us had
to spend their freshman year
making those recordings.
And leading
a disastrous monkey escape.
Grow up...
you children.
- [Jack's voice]
That went well.
- Never did this before.
Say Hey, Willie mays.
You know, usually
everyone around here
makes me
feel like hitler.
But today I feel like
hitler in Germany.
- Aw, being popular must be
such a new experience for you.
- Well, it's not entirely new.
- Wow, I would experiment
with that girl.
- Too small.
- That's me
for two weeks in college.
I was popular
for one glorious fortnight.
And then it went away.
I don't know what I did wrong.
- You probably said
"fortnight."
- No, you didn't
do anything, Liz.
You were just you.
The cool people figured that out
and treated you accordingly.
- Well, ever since I gave
the crew that lottery money,
it's felt like
those two weeks again.
And you know what?
I'm not blowing it this time.
- Hang on, you know
[British pronunciation]
this charade can't last.
Just like in college,
Everyone here has their role.
I'm the hot blonde.
- And I'm the nerd
who takes off his glasses
and Everyone realizes
he's handsome.
- And you're the r.A.
- Only if r.A.
Stands for "really awesome."
- You are who you are.
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- [Jack's voice]
Hello, Pete.
This is Jack.
- Jack, hi.
Oh, okay, look.
What happened was
Suzanne from ad sales
got pushed into me
in the elevator.
I didn't try to touch her.
And the sort of
"unh" sound I made
was about something else.
- [Jack's voice]
Pete, will you be my friend?
- Your friend?
Sure, of course.
You know, whenever
I tell my wife a work story,
she pointed this out
the other day--
I always...
always smile a little
when I'm talking about you.
- [Jack's voIce]
I wish I was more
of a free spirit
like you.
Now freestyle rap for me.
- ♪ Rollin' with my homie,
me and Jackie d. ♪
♪ Bitches get ready
for a sex party ♪
[laughter]
- Hey, Liz, think fast.
[glass shatters]
- Okay,
this is why we don't
play football
in the studio, guys.
'cause it's too much fun.
- No, no.
Nobody high-five her.
- What?
It's me, the lizard.
You can start
calling me that.
- Look, we appreciate what you
did for the crew last night,
but you left some people out
and that's not cool.
- What are you talking about?
The Blizzard wouldn't do that.
That's another option.
- Yeah, the alcoholics, Liz?
How are they supposed
to enjoy your bar tab?
- I didn't forget
about them, Chris.
Their thing
just hasn't gotten here yet.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's a surprise.
And who knows
what it's gonna be?
Only the blizbian knows.
- All right.
- How long do you think
this can go on?
- I've got it under control.
- This is why I hated
my first two weeks
at the royal tampa academy
of dramatic tricks.
No one knew
who was the sluttiest.
But I showed them.
Oh, I showed them all.
And when we graduated
a week later--
- whatever. Jenna.
People's perceptions can change.
- Can they?
Look at me.
I'm ogbert the nerd.
Always have been,
always will be.
- Look, there is no cool Liz.
There's Only r.A. Liz.
- You're wrong.
- My glasses are dirty.
- Ogbert?
- Ah, the microwave lab.
Boys, I received our
quarterly report yesterday
and, uh--hang on.
Ajay, raj, ramesh.
What's going on here?
Where are dinesh,
Kumar, and sunavo?
- Sir, this lab
requires clearance.
- Clearance?
I'm your boss.
I'm Jack donaghy.
- I'm sorry,
your names all sound
the same to us,
John Donovan.
- I've worked here since 1985.
I spearheaded
the trivection oven.
- Trivection?
What is this, 2009?
[laughter]
The future is the tk-421.
- A new model?
How many vections
does it have?
- Five.
- [gasps]
- It's the perfect microwave.
It even has
a new voice feature.
- [Jack's voice]
Popcorn setting medium.
- My god.
- Which one?
- Gentlemen, I am still
the head of this division.
And no microwave ships
without my say-so.
And I guarantee you that without
my 25 years of experience
you did not build
a perfect microwave.
Now I'm going to find out
what's wrong with this machine,
and when I do,
you're going to wish
you'd never been born.
- Well, which time?
- [groans]
- Ah.
What are you
tinkering with, sir?
You know my uncle
was a tinkerer.
Until the FBI shot him.
- Every g.E. Product
has to be
no more than six sigmas
from perfection.
- Duh.
- So I'm taking apart
this piece of junk
until I prove that it
should never be released.
For the, uh,
good of the company.
- [Jack's voice]
Ready, ready.
- Is this about
the company, sir?
Or is it about you?
- I'm sorry, Kenneth.
What?
- Sometimes a place can be so
special to you
that it feels like it
couldn't possibly continue
after you're gone.
But after I left kentucky
mountain Bible college,
it still kept going.
Until it was shut down
because of the wolves.
Maybe this is really about you
not being able to let go.
- Tell me, Kenneth.
What did you major in
at that college?
- Television studies with
a minor in Bible sexuality.
- So not psychiatry.
Thank you.
But if you
really want to help me,
stick your hand in There
and see if you get a shock.
- Aah! My hand!
- Damn it,
it's supposed to do that.
- Everyone enjoying
the ice cream?
- Yes!
- Yeah!
- I don't even care
that we've taken
a 73-minute break
To eat it.
[dog barking]
- Oh!
Hey, somebody brought
a dog to work.
Oh, and it definitely
doesn't have
any of its own waste
on its feet--oh!
- Hey, why is Tony sulking?
- I couldn't go
to the bar
and now I can't
have any ice cream.
- I totally forgot, broseph.
You're a lactose-intolerant
alcoholic.
- I tried to forget too,
But Liz made me remember
in front of everybody.
- Poor Tony.
- Not cool, Liz.
- How not cool is this?
I remembered how special
Tony is,
and that's why
I got him this watch.
- Hey, you think
of everything.
- Lizard, lizard, lizard!
- Lizard, lizard!
ALL: Lizard! Lizard! Lizard!
Lizard! Lizard!
- [Jack's voice]
Pete, can I tell you a secret?
- Of course.
I told you about my blankie.
- [Jack's voIce]
I'm lonely.
Would you like to come
to my office
tomorrow Evening
and Hang out?
Bring your guitar
and some beer in Cans
and we will jam.
- Okay!
Yeah, great.
And with the kabletown stuff,
maybe we could
talk about some
new opportunities for me?
- [Jack's voice]
Yes, I will make
your dreams come True.
Make sure you wear one
of those mexican ponchos.
- Okay.
- Yes, nice.
- Yeah!
- All right, Kenneth.
Simulate a rainstorm.
- Sir, I was wrong
about the hypothermia.
I don't even
feel cold anymore.
I don't feel anything.
- Quiet.
Look.
The display
is malfunctioning.
- [Jack's voice]
Defrost. Power.
Time. Left. Pizza.
- Oh, really?
That's how much time is left?
Pizza?
- Mr. Donaghy,
I don't know
what point
you think you're proving.
Who would microwave something
in a freezing rainstorm?
- Why don't you ask choctee,
an inuit who wants
a hot bowl of naglak...
a man and food I just made up
to illustrate a point?
- Sir, you have to let go.
At least that's what
my Nana is telling me
from that tunnel of light
behind you.
- Kenneth,
I've told you this before.
Your Nana is an idiot.
- Liz, we're pranking Pete,
and It's going too far.
Please stop us.
- Why would I?
I love pranks.
I'm not the r.A.
- No.
[whimpers]
Ooh, But someone
has to be that person.
Hey. Everyone stop.
Listen to Lutz.
[all chattering]
- Hello, gentlemen.
Remember me?
- Yes, I had the greek salad.
- You know
I'm not a delivery man.
I'm wearing a suit
and carrying a microwave.
A so-called perfect microwave.
- [Jack's voice]
Start time. 1985.
- 1985. That's not a time.
I guess it could be a year.
The year I started
working here, actually.
That's interesting.
- [Jack's voice]
1985.
- Yes, 1985.
Thank you.
And since 1985
I have never allowed
a sub-par product--
- [Jack's voice]
stop.
- The point is,
my legacy here is--
- [Jack's voice]
over.
[microwave beeping]
Done. Over.
End.
Stop.
- That's my voice.
- You all sound the same
to us, jock dungaree.
- That was me...
30 years ago.
A young man who dreamed
of running this company,
who made a lot of sacrifices
in pursuit of that dream.
- [Jack's voice]
Goodbye. Potato. Goodbye.
- But he's right.
It's over.
Congratulations on making
the finest microwave
I've ever seen.
- Who ordered
the greek salad?
- Are we racist, or do
Those guys look a lot alike?
- You ready for this,
j-dog?
Jam out,
drink some brews?
Talk about everything
and nothing.
- After today, that is exactly
what I am ready for.
Beer me.
[sighs]
Sitting around drinking beer
while a guy in a poncho
plays guitar.
This is what I always
pictured college being like.
- I wouldn't really know.
I only had about
two weeks of real college
before Paula
got pregnant...twice.
She had overlapping pregnancies
five months apart.
- [sighs]
Hey, Pete,
do you know aqualung?
- [chuckles]
- ♪ Ba Ba BA BA ba ba ♪
- ♪ sitting on a park bench ♪
♪ neer neer neer ♪
♪ I don't know the words
except Park bench ♪
- Jimmy slice.
K-bone.
Mikey-Mike.
- Do not even use
my awesome nickname.
- What? Why?
Crisco?
- Did you give Tony
your grandfather's watch?
- No.
You can't prove that.
- Hmm. Ah.
Not stolen property
of adolf Lemon?
Why would you do that?
To get us to like you?
Are you that desperate?
- No, I'm not desperate.
I'm...
[stammers]
just tell me what you want me
to say and I'll say it!
- Liz, it's over.
They know what
you really are.
- Fine, you found me out.
I'm not a cool kid.
- You suck!
- You know who I am?
I'm the r.A.
And do you know what
the r.A.'s purview is?
Rules.
And guess what?
According to the nbc
employee handbook,
your little card game lottery
constitutes gambling.
So you're not doing it
anymore.
- What?
- Come on.
- Boo!
- Also, the next time
I see someone
throwing a football in here,
there will be fines.
And if I see that
filthy dog again,
I will put it down.
- [all gasp]
- I will put it down
with a smile.
Back to work, everyone!
[crowd booIng]
I love you too.
High-fiving
a million angels.
- Hey, Pete, how do I know
that the colors you see
are the same
as the colors that I see?
Maybe what I see as red,
you perceive as green.
- We should be writing
this stuff down.
- Oh, I didn't think
anybody would be in here.
I mean, I brought
you guys a pizza.
- Lemon, think fast!
- What is going on here?
- Join us.
Pete and I are having
a little college night.
- Oh, yeah?
Want to see me shotgun this?
- Oh, god,
she means the pizza.
- No, she's unhinging
her jaw!
- Come on,
we were just pranking Pete!
How long
do we have to do this?
- You wanted college
to go on forever?
You got it.
www.tvsubtitles.net