I never thought this
day would come, lizzie.
Okay, push.
Push, liz lemon!
Here comes your baby!
Congratulations.
It's meat cat!
the cheesy blasters mascot.
I'm what's inside ya!
Razzmatazz!
I got to eat better.
Oh, hello, mr. Hornberger.
I thought I was the only
one here at this hour.
No, this is just
my little ritual,
So I can have a moment
of peace and quiet
Between home,
where this happened,
And work, where...
I'm always being interrupted.
Oh, I get it.
A little pete time.
Pardon the familiarity.
Well, you just enjoy
your coffee, sir,
While I tell you a funny story
About my friend's cat.
His name is mr. Wiggles,
And his cat's name is benson.
Where's liz?
I need to speak
to her right away.
I guess that's the end
of pete and kenneth time.
Liz, she's here.
Verna's here.
My mother is downstairs.
Are you sure?
I didn't see her.
Security called.
She was trying to use
An oxycontin prescription
bottle as I.D.
That's verna.
Oh!
So is she coming up?
Are you kidding?
I told them to throw
her off the property.
But I'm sure she's down there,
Sitting on a curb,
chain-smoking,
And waiting for
me to come out.
Just like the day I was born.
Wow.
Look, jenna, I know
that she's no prize,
But no matter what,
verna is your mother.
Don't you want to have a
relationship with your mother?
This isn't a relationship.
This is some
woman who shows up
Every couple of years
to ask for money.
To her, I'm just a gorgeous,
Naturally-blonde atm.
You know, my mother and I
sometimes didn't see eye to eye,
But at the end of the
day, we always said
don't go to sleep
with a frown in your pocket
Ugh, liz, you don't know
anything about mothers.
Where's jack?
go into your yard
and tie it on a rocket
Both: shoot it to the moon
you'll be feeling better soon
don't go to bed with a frown
Yeah, there were firemen
there and everything.
Where?
- At my house.
I left my sith lord cloak
Too near my mom's
shrine to italian jesus,
And the candles
started a fire.
Were the firemen strong?
Were any of them the
ones from the calendar?
My mom's staying
with family upstate,
But I've got to find
someplace around here to crash.
I'm sorry.
Would you like to
stay in my guest house?
Yeah. Thanks.
When's good to go over there?
Oh, I'm not offering.
I'm just taking a survey
To gauge general interest.
But liz here has
a spare apartment.
Ain't that right, liz?
Well, it's not really spare.
I bought the place
upstairs from me
When I thought I was
getting a talk show.
But I'm gonna finish
the combination
As soon as I either
hit the lottery
Or get married.
Ugh. Fine. You
can stay with me.
But it's stuff like this
That makes me eat
things like this.
Thanks, liz.
Oh, I'd like to pre-apologize
For clogging your
tub, sink, and toilet.
Mothers.
You can't kill them...
Verna's been using me
my whole life, jack.
I never saw a penny from any
of the commercials I booked.
Keep you and your pets safe
With gator hater gator spray.
Sorry. Honey, you got to
get closer to the gator.
We drove eleven
hours to get here,
And you're not
getting any younger.
But when I wanted
to sing a duet
In a mother-daughter pageant,
She blew it off because
there was no prize money.
But today's different, jenna.
Today you break the cycle,
Because today you
are going to say...
I developed this
presentation in 2002
When colleen attempted
To lengthen her
christmas visit
To martin luther king day,
Or as she calls it,
"that day in January
When the post
office is closed."
I had to draw the line.
I had to say...
This word is your best friend.
Best friend with benefits?
Step one, say no.
Step two...
She will try to pick
a fight with you.
You will not let her.
She will raise her voice.
But I'm going to ask you to...
Always speak quieter.
Can I just tell you I'm
genuinely having fun right now?
If you raise your voice,
Emotions take over,
And she gets the upper hand.
But if you're calm and quiet,
You stay in control,
And it's on to step three.
And this is the
hardest one of all.
She will tell you how
disappointed she is in you,
And she will get up to leave,
And you...
Let her walk away.
It's simple.
Say no. Talk low.
Let her go.
Frank. Frank?
Do you smell smoke?
What the hell, frank?
Oh, man. Look, liz
How can you smoke?
It's disgusting.
And in my apartment?
Wow. An old white
lady yelling at me
While wearing
microwavable socks.
This is so different
than living with my mom.
Okay, so I smoke a little
as a stress release.
I never told you, 'cause
I knew you'd lecture me.
It is not a lecture
To simply point out to someone
That the episode
of diff'rent strokes
About dudley's dad
Has proven incontrovertibly
That smoking
destroys your health
And leads to
ridicule from willis.
Well, what about you?
You can't judge me
When you're eating
that garbage.
This is not the same
thing at all, frank.
Dr. Oz did a show
about junk food.
I saw it, 'cause it's on
a compilation dvd I have
Of fat ladies crying.
And this stuff will kill ya.
"manufactured in a facility
that also processes food."
This is what
meat cat spoke of.
So I guess I'll just get
One of those little
throat radios,
And you'll be buried
in a piano crate.
Goodnight, liz.
No, frank, that fire
in your apartment
Was no accident.
I know. I just wanted
to be in control!
It was fate!
We've been brought together
To help each other
stop being gross.
What do you say?
All right.
But if doing this
restores my sex drive,
The plus-sized ladies
in the mail room
Have you to blame.
Oh, there's my baby girl!
Hello, verna.
No. Low. Go.
Okay. I know.
Every time we see each other,
I'm always hitting
you up for money.
And I know that it's
always for something stupid,
Like paying the medical bills
That time that my boyfriend
Broke his tailbone
off in that cage match.
But this time it's different.
I said no.
Wait, what is this?
I'm trying to pay you back.
I'm trying to
make good for once.
Is this the fight?
I'm talking quieter.
I'm in control.
What's that now?
I'm the calm one.
Upper hand.
Jenna, why are we
talking like this?
Does somebody have a gun?
I'm going lower now.
Okay.
Well, I know you're busy.
I just wanted to say
this face to face.
I am so proud of you.
And I love you so much.
And I wish I'd said that more.
Don't go, mommy.
I'll stand closer
to the gator.
Goon!
Sorry I'm late,
mr. Hornberger.
funny story.
There was a guy on the subway
Who I thought for a second
didn't have any fingers.
But then I realized
He was holding
his hand like this.
Listen up, everyone.
Frank and I have some
exciting news to share.
I am quitting smoking.
And I am gonna start
eating healthier.
I signed up for a
service called "noofud"
That delivers
humanely-portioned organic meals.
And I took the elevator
all the way up here
Without losing my breath.
Liz, god knows you
should eat better,
But maybe now's not the time.
It's show week,
And I can't have
you melting down,
And junk food is
your stress release.
We all need a release.
I know, because kenneth
has taken mine away from me,
And I'm worried about what
I'm gonna do to replace it.
While you were talking,
I put a thumbtack in my neck.
Makes me feel something.
Well, don't worry
about me, pete.
I have a new outlet-
My delicious noofud.
Like my upcoming lunch,
Autumn tempeh risotto
With salmon-rubbed
streusel chunks.
Oh!
Jenna?
I just wanted to see
How it went with
verna last night.
Jack, it was perfect.
Like a john mayer song.
Good. So you said no?
I didn't have to. She
didn't want anything.
She's completely changed.
What? No.
People do not change.
In the late '90s,
I thought colleen had
become a better person.
It turns out she had a tumor
Pressing on her
brain's pleasure center.
A tumor those quack
doctors removed.
Jack, this is different.
She gave me money.
It's not different, jenna.
It never is.
You must be verna.
Oh, and you must
be jack donaghy.
Jenna, you were
right, darlin'.
He does look
like he'd be great
Between those two things
we were talking about.
Interesting earrings.
Oh, thank you. I
made 'em myself.
Something's killing all the
birds in my neighborhood.
Mom, I really wish you
didn't have to leave tonight.
'cause my birthday's
this weekend.
Oh, my god. I am
the worst mother.
No.
- Yes, I am.
Don't say that.
Could a bad mom have
raised a daughter
Who was engaged to a
congressman when she was 16?
Jenna to the stage, please.
Oh, that's me.
Oh, goodness.
Oh.
Blowing town tonight, huh?
I knew it was her birthday.
I'm throwing her
a surprise party,
And it's at a
fancy restaurant,
So wear something nice.
Like a pair of white jeans
And a dan marino jersey
or something, 'kay?
Hey. So how you holding up?
Terrible. I have a
headache, a stomachache.
Last night I spent an hour
Trying to remember how to
spell the word "heighth."
Liz, your body is crying out
For all the chemicals
it's used to.
You can't go on like this.
Here. Eat it.
Eat it. Come on.
You need your crutch.
Stop it!
God, your arms
are really weak.
What are you smiling at?
Aren't youiserable?
I have a very strong will.
Rossitanos have refused
to fight in seven wars.
I don't buy it.
There is no way that guy
Is stronger than me.
- Or me.
He's got to be
sneaking cigarettes.
You're the one
living with him.
Catch him in the act.
Yeah. I still have
his old cigarette pack.
I will leave it out
tonight as a trap,
And set up a video camera.
Good idea. Nanny cam.
Just like the
one our nanny used
To catch me
watching her sleep.
High five.
Hi. I was told I'd get paid
If I came here and danced while
the atlanta hawks eat dinner.
All: Surprise!
Oh, my god!
Mom, you remembered.
Well, of course I remembered.
Come here, sweetie.
I've seen this before.
Classic colleen move.
Whatever it is verna wants,
She's going to
ask for it tonight,
And jenna can't say no
In front of all these people.
My mother once
won a radio contest
To announce the starting
lineups at a red sox game,
And used the opportunity
To get me to promise
never to put her in a home.
What could I do?
Carl yastrzemski was
looking right at me.
This isn't about you,
So you need to get
over your issues
And try to be happy for jenna.
Speaking of issues,
I had a dream the other
night that we were married
And I gave birth to
a cartoon cat, so...
Could I have
Everybody's attention, please?
Thank you.
In my life, I've
been a lot of things-
A liar.
A dental hygienist.
But I haven't always been
A good mom.
Jenna, honey, I don't
know if you remember,
But when you were 11,
We were supposed
to sing together
At a mother-daughter
talent pageant.
I had completely
forgotten about that.
What betrayal?
Well, I was drinking
pretty heavily then...
On account of my bad knee.
And then I went
and drove my jet ski
Into that great
big bunch of moss.
So I did not make
it to that pageant.
Honey, I don't deserve
a single thing from you,
But I've got to ask one favor.
And it's a big one.
If you would do me
the very great honor
Of joining me?
Hit it.
do that to me one more time
once is never enough
with a daughter like you
do that to me one more time
I can never get enough
of a mom like you
oh
Both: kiss me
like you just did
How are you not moved by this?
Because I'm listening
to the words.
Both: do that to me once again
Verna.
Hey.
Nice office, jack.
I feel like I'm in
The martha stewart
section of kmart.
What can I do for you?
Oh, well, I just
wanted to thank you
For coming to the party.
It meant a lot to jenna.
And it was pretty
important to me too.
See, now you know what
the show would be like.
What show?
Jack, I did not drive my home
All the way to new york city
Just to kiss my
daughter's ass.
Thank you.
I want to do a tv
show about me and her.
You want to do a reality show?
Come on.
You see how good I am
At pushing jenna's buttons.
Yeah, this show will
have laughter, tears,
Topless arguments.
Infections caused
by jacuzzi water.
I knew it.
I knew you had
something up your sleeve
Besides a tattoo
with, let me guess-
It's a mermaid.
Doing it with captain morgan.
Now, come on, jack.
We both understand
the value of a dollar.
Oop.
Now won't you please
do me this favor?
Talk to jenna.
There's a lot more
where that come from.
Which is in my underpanties.
come in.
Jenna, I was right.
I was right all along.
What's that?
Oh. New earrings.
My mom just made them.
So they still might
have some pigeon mites.
But she said those can't
affect-affect humans-humans.
Yes, well, it
certainly is amazing
To see how your mother
has made this 180.
It's even better, jack.
She's made a full 360.
Well, I just wanted to come by
And make sure you're okay.
I'm glad to see
you're so happy.
I am happy.
Because now I have everything.
Good morning, dummies.
So frank can go cold
turkey but I can't?
Well, well, well.
Frank's old cigarettes.
When I went to bed last night,
There were 15
cigarettes in the pack.
This morning, there were 12.
What?
- J'accuse!
Look, I don't know where
those cigarettes went.
If only some genius
Had secretly videotaped
her living room last night.
Oh, wait. It did.
Hang on. You videotaped
your living room?
All night?
Sure did.
And as soon as I figure out
Which one of these things
Is the thingy...
Coming at you.
Gimme.
You didn't believe in me.
But I believed in myself.
Just like the last scene
Of all movies.
Okay. Here we go.
What are you wearing?
Both: They're
called night spanx.
I don't even
remember getting up.
What am I doing?
You're sleepwalking, liz.
It's a little-understood
parasomnial disorder.
That's gross.
She's not sleep walking.
Oh, my god. I'm sleep eating.
You tried to take
away your release, liz,
But nature finds a way.
Did you learn nothing
from jurassic park?
Why am I making a phone call?
Okay, I don't mean to be
the black guy at the movie,
But you better move, girl!
Uh-oh.
Oh, liz, you didn't!
I ordered a pizza?
Oh!
Oh, I don't want to see this.
Okay, fine.
I cheated in my sleep.
But frank folded too,
Because I am not making
it up about the cigarettes.
Any minute he's gonna- -
wait, what are you doing now?
No. No. Please, no.
Oh, god, liz. You
didn't smoke the
I'm eating it.
Okay, well, mystery solved.
Liz ate the cigarettes,
And I guess some of us
Just don't need a release.
So let's turn the tv off.
Hang on.
Oh, thanks, frank.
Oh, there's more.
Denise, I said wait upstairs.
My boss is asleep
in the other room.
I was told
You have a package
for the mail room.
Oh, come on!
This just got awesome.
I need you, denise.
I'm trying to quit smoking,
And my mom's not here.
I'm your mama now, baby.
don't go to sleep
with a frown in your pocket
go into your yard
and tie it on a rocket
This is the worst
thing I've ever seen.
you'll be feeling better soon
Both: don't go to
bed with a frown
I love you, denise mommy.
We all need our release.
Verna,
I want to be in
business with you.
Oh! Ho, ho, ho!
We are gonna be
swimming in green, jack.
Just like when I dye my
pool on st. Patrick's day.
I do have a couple of notes.
This project will not be about
Drama or dysfunction.
People are tired of that.
Well, so what's it about?
Redemption.
It's about a mother making
amends to her daughter.
And it's not a show.
It's four visits per year-
Christmas, mother's day,
Jenna's birthday,
and thanksgiving.
You treat jenna with
the respect she deserves,
You get a check.
You're trying to bribe me
Into being a good mom.
Well, it is all
just about money,
Isn't it, verna?
Well, maybe for me.
But this is emotional
for you, isn't it?
And I believe that
gives me the upper hand,
And you're gonna have to pay.
Big.
3 grand a visit,
And a rain tarp for
my washer and dryer.
Deal.
Verna, stop stroking my palm
With your middle finger.
This is a businessransaction.
Sorry.
Whoo-hoo, mr. Big stuff.
Dudley's father went outside
And lit a cigarette.
In the next episode-
Good morning, pete, kenneth.
- Liz.
If you are spending your
mornings with kenneth,
What's your release?
Uh...
Oh, I feel alive!
I've been biting my nails.
Oh.
Hey, liz.
Verna's coming back
for mother's day.
We're gonna do a duet
of I'll make love to you
At a children's hospital.
That's great, jenna.
Hey, jack, guess what?
Verna's coming back
for mother's day.
She is? What a surprise.
So I guess you were 100%
wrong about everything.
Think about that, jack.
You're a good
man, jack donaghy.
Thanks, meat cat.
I've got an idea for
a show called Doctor.
About Richard Doctor,
who's a piano player.
Remember that show
Jennifer slliped here.
Anne Jillian plays a ghost of a
hollywood starlet who helps teenagers.
With what? I don't know!
Some of those people on Magic
Cane were drunk... with power.
Did you know that Today Show
used to have a monkey on it.
Hasn't been this good since.
I think that chimp used
to drive a truck himself.
On you-know-what
and the bear.
www.tvsubtitles.net