Hey.
Could I get your
lucretia mott on this?
What is this?
Budget approval
for travel and hotels
for the moms.
The moms?
What moms?
The staff moms
that are gonna be
on the mother's day show
that nbc is making us do
after their ill-fated decision
to re-air the pilot
of bitch hunter.
Put the mimosas down!
[gun cocks]
Bitch.
Wait,
it's mother's day already?
Did you forget?
Colleen is gonna kill you.
There's still time.
Jonathan.
Jonathan, call the florist,
and order a dozen--no.
Necktie.
Too late, Jackie.
[Exciting jazz music]
♪ 30 Rock 4x20 ♪
The Moms
Original Air Date on May 6, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Hey, why isn't my
beautiful Frank up on the wall?
Ma, come on,
that's just for the actors.
Oh, here's a picture
you can use.
It's little Frankie
in the bathtub,
getting ready
for the senior prom.
Thank you.
Mom, what are you doing?
You don't have
to pay for the food.
Honey, nothing is free.
You remember that
when a man buys you
an expensive meal.
Yeah,
that's happening a lot.
Hey, verna.
Well, you must remember
my mom, Margaret.
Oh, yes,
we met a few years ago
when the girls
lived in Chicago.
You must have me
confused with someone else.
I have never been
to Chicago.
I sexually assaulted
scottie pippen in 1997.
There's my baby!
Oh, mommy!
Look, Tracy, this
mother's day show is tomorrow,
and we haven't been able
to track down your mom.
I gave Kenneth
her information.
"Her name might be Cheryl,
and she was wearing
a red shirt in 1984."
Look, I don't want you
to be alone up there
with all the families,
so what if I hire an actress
to play your mom?
Okay.
But whoever she is
needs to be someone
as amazing as I am.
I want to see a list of names.
Like when they was looking
for John mccain's running mate.
[Laughs]
I'm kidding.
This needs to be
taken seriously.
Happy mother's day,
Colleen.
I'm not here about
mother's day, John Francis.
You know who's in
my water aerobics class
down in Florida?
Yes, mother,
I've memorized the names
of everyone in
your water aerobics class.
Patricia goodband,
whose sister runs
the Friday night bingo game
at our lady
of reluctant integration
in waltham.
Turns out last week
that the game was won
by Anne o'connor,
who mentioned that her niece,
Nancy Donovan,
got divorced
and was running around
with a hotshot
in New York City
who pours scotch
like a woman.
If I don't always share
my personal life
with you, Colleen,
it's becse you've never
approved of any woman
I've shown an interest in.
Now, that's not true.
I'm not having this
conversation with you right now.
I have work to do, and
I'll be joining you for lunch.
In the meantime,
Kenneth here will entertain you.
Okay, Kenneth,
entertain me.
♪ Oh,
the fiddle's in the creek ♪
♪ and the frog's
in the kitchen ♪
I apologize, ma'am.
That is not a song.
You make me very nervous.
Oh, my God.
[Laughs]
Hey, lutz,
this is my mom, miho.
Oh, hi.
I didn't know
you were adopted.
What?
Thanks a lot, lutz.
[Both argue in japanese]
Mom, this is Lee.
He's the head
of our wardrobe department.
Well, hello, Lee.
Wrong tree, mom.
Gotcha.
So Lee's gonna take care
of your clothes for the show.
Oh, no, no,
that won't be necessary.
I brought some real cute duds.
I made us both
rompers to wear.
Excuse me.
My...Friend has to go
strangle her anxiety pillow.
Lee,
it's the bridesmaid's dress.
I can't breathe.
I'm gonna die in here.
Bridesmaid?
It's bad luck for a married
woman to be a bridesmaid.
It brings fever and disease.
Yeah, well, I'm not
actually married, so...
Not even common law?
How do you get credit
at a mattress store?
You know,
my Johnny's single,
and he gives
excellent backrubs,
I can assure you.
Thank you, Mrs. lutz,
and thank you, moms,
for your interest,
but I just haven't
met the one yet.
Oh,
for crying out loud, Liz.
You see?
That's what feminism does.
It makes smart girls
with nice birthing shapes
believe in fairytales.
Stop waiting
for your prince, Liz.
I'm not waiting
for a prince.
I'm waiting for
astronaut Mike Dexter.
Oh, sweet lord in heaven.
Who turns out to be
the secret king of Monaco.
Liz, you're almost 40.
You're not gonna find
some new kind of man.
Whoever the one is,
you probably already met him.
You're 40?
John is looking for a...
Greener banana, so...
Hello, verna.
Glad to see you're here,
upholding your end
of our bargain.
Oh, yeah.
I'm being a great mother--
listening, giving advice,
asking stupid questions
during movies.
But I need you
to hold up your end.
That money order you sent,
that was only for half.
That was a down payment,
verna.
You'll get the rest
after you've fulfilled
your mother's day duties.
That's kind of
a problem for me,
'cause I already spent
that down payment
on the first half
of my boob job.
It's not an implant.
It's just a little yank up,
you know?
I mean,
I got the meat, Jack.
Go ahead. Feel 'em.
Feel the difference.
Very different indeed.
Like a cantaloupe
and a ziploc bag
of mushroom soup.
But you're not getting
the rest of that money
until you give Jenna all the
mother's day love she deserves.
Whatever.
Narc.
Good news, tray.
We found a great mom
for you.
Her name is novella Nelson.
Novella Nelson?
Oh, wait, is she
aquaman's girlfriend?
No. She's a great actress
who lives in Brooklyn.
She looks like you.
That could be anyone!
We all look the same to me.
Is she famous?
You'd probably know her best
from a commercial
they air a lot
during the 3:30 A.M.
sportscenter.
Ugh, these overalls
are chafing.
I can't wear
these pajamas fishing!
Female announcer:
Pajamaralls.
Pajamaralways.
What about
the list I gave you?
Phylicia rashad.
Serena Williams.
They're too recognizable,
Tracy.
And Serena Williams
is younger than you.
Who cares?
She's awesome, and so am I.
I want Serena Williams
to be my mother.
We've already booked novella.
The woman's been
in the business for 40 years.
I think she's good enough
for the star of sherlock homie.
I know what you're thinking,
mother,
and we are not talking
about Nancy Donovan.
I don't want
to talk about Nancy Donovan.
I want to talk about
the little blonde girl
that you are sleeping with.
What?
A mother knows, Jackie.
Oh, hi.
Are you going up?
Down, actually.
Ugh, I forgot my phone.
[Elevator bell dings]
Two women, Jack,
at the same time.
What are you, Italian?
I didn't choose
for it to happen like this.
Be a man and pick one.
I can't. They both
give me different things.
One connects me
to the man I was.
The other...
Inspires.
Just listen to yourself,
Jack.
I know it's gay,
but it's my gay problem,
and I'm handling it.
We're ready to order now.
Just bring my son
one of everything.
That way,
he doesn't have to choose.
[Laughs]
Hey.
Um, why was I given this
to wear on the show?
Well, I loved your idea
that we both
wear the same outfit.
I just thought this one
might be more...Tv friendly.
You mean
instead of the rompers
that your mother slaved over.
Mom, this isn't Florida.
You're damn right it isn't.
In Florida,
everybody's always asking me,
"where did you get that?
You made it?
Holy crap!
Where do I commission one?"
Oh. This is about you
making money selling junk.
[Groans]
Verna, this is my job,
and I know
you don't understand that,
'cause you haven't
had a job in 15 years.
Because of my back.
Because of
the trampoline accident.
But I need to look
a certain way on tv.
You are nothing
but a spoiled brat.
You know what?
Here's what I think of you
and your fancy clothes.
That is quality stitching.
Damn the tiny, brown hands
that made this.
Oh, there you are.
Just thought I'd tidy up.
That's my computer.
Oh, no, honey.
A computer is a great big thing
with a green screen.
Mom,
do you think it's weird
that I'm still single?
Well, your standards
are very high.
As they should be.
I remember someone
who got a three
on her history ap test.
But do I expect too much?
Maybe the moms were right.
Maybe I should have
just settled.
I can't tell you
what to do, Liz,
but I know from experience
that that gu
that perfect guy,
is out there.
'Cause I know I found mine.
See, that's all I want.
What you and dad have.
Oh, I'm not talking
about your father.
What?
what do you mean
you're not talking about dad?
You love dad.
Of course I do,
but Dick lemon isn't ed.
Ed? Who's ed?
Ed was my true love,
sweetheart.
He was my steady
at montclair high.
The night before
he was shipped off to Korea,
I repeatedly lost
my virginity to him,
while Waldo,
the town perv,
watched from the bushes.
Wait, what?
Nothing, younger me.
It's fine.
He wanted to get married,
but when he was
invited to Houston
for his astronaut training--
he was an astronaut?
You could have been
an astronaut's wife?
It wasn't that simple, Liz.
I had just graduated
from secretary school,
and I got a job
at sterling Cooper.
I couldn't just
pick up and move.
I was already 26,
an old maid.
Different times.
Octomom.
So I settled
for a wonderful man,
and I have
never regretted it.
Not even when I watched
ed aldrin walk on the moon.
Wait,
your ed is buzz aldrin?
Yeah,
but I always called him ed,
because our town had,
like, five buzzes.
You could have
married buzz aldrin?
You should regret that, mom.
You should have followed him.
Laura linney
could have played you
in the hbo original movie
moon wives!
Where are you going, verna?
Oh, I quit.
I've been working my ass off
pretending to be a good mom,
but Jenna
doesn't appreciate it.
I see.
Well, then good luck
paying for that other implant.
It's not an implant,
Jack.
I mean, I got the meat.
Of course.
I apologize.
Verna, you have
a very simple decision to make--
quit, don't get paid,
and drive around
with one headlight out,
or, swallow your pride,
and get the money you need
tomorrow.
They said they were gonna
put a wig on me or something
so that nobody
would recognize me
as the pajamarall lady.
Like anyone
would recognize you anyway.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
You are way beneath me,
novella.
I am a movie star,
a television actor,
and a guinness book
of world record holder
for most car accidents
in a single year.
Maybe you wanted someone
more high-profile,
but I am what you got,
so, Tracy,
you better watch yourself,
or you may wind up
with no mother at all.
Fine. I'd rather be
up on that stage all alone
than to be with someone
whose resume has
"black judge" on it nine times.
And you think
I wanted a fake son
who recorded
an anti-condom psa?
I saved a lot of kids
from lame sex!
Little ingrate.
All right,
start with taxes,
then insurance, and change
this to "latin America."
I can't say Nicaragua.
Gah!
You must be Avery.
Yes?
I am so sorry,
miss Jessup.
Mrs. Donaghy keeps tricking me
and running away,
but not anymore.
Carl, they need you
out in the hall.
Yes, ma'am!
Mrs. Donaghy.
You must be Jack's mother.
Indeed, I am.
And Jack has told me
so much about you.
You're going to have
to work your backside,
because chest-wise
you have the measurements
of an altar boy.
I wish Jack had told me
you were in town.
Well, men have their
little secrets, don't they?
Especially Jack.
Secrets?
What I'm trying to say is,
if you're serious
about Jackie,
let him know now.
A man like Jack
has other irons in the fire.
I beg your pardon?
Oh!
Look at the time.
I've got to get back
to calling Kenneth "carl"
to see if he ever corrects me.
Carl!
Yes, ma'am?
[Laughs]
Lemon,
have you seen Colleen?<,
Kenneth was supposed
to be watching her,
but I just saw him
with his eyes closed
counting to infinity.
You want to talk about moms,
Jack?
Listen to this.
My mother could have
married buzz aldrin.
Oh, really?
I know buzz.
We met at a photo shoot
for vanity fair's annual
awesome gentleman issue.
My mom blew it, Jack.
She had true love,
and she threw it away
just because
it was inconvenient.
Well, lemon, if your mom
had ended up with buzz,
you would have
never been born.
Or I would have
been born Peter aldrin.
And I+d wait for a woman
with the right stuff.
Now, remember,
in this scenario,
I'm a man and my father
is an astronaut.
Well, lemon,
if you'd like to see
what your mom's life
would have been,
I can arrange for you
to meet buzz.
Are you serious?
He's in town.
I saw him last night at
Rupert Murdoch's twister party.
I mean, uh, regular party.
Tracy, this mother's day thing
is a disaster.
I hear you.
Because you're
talking in the ear
that I didn't
lose a button in.
I thought verna and I
had made this breakthrough,
but now we're just back
to fighting
about money and clothes.
Thank God Terry's dead,
or we'd be fighting
over him again too.
Boy, I thought I had it bad
with my fake mom.
Are you kidding?
At least your fake mom
has to act like
she cares about you.
Yeah, it's true.
And she is a good actress.
I bought those pajamaralls.
And you got to choose her.
No, Jenna, no one gets
to choose their mom...
Even when they're fake.
For good or bad,
we're stuck with them.
And you know what?
They don't get to choose
who we are, either.
And God knows
we're not perfect.
It's true.
Sometimes I sing
too beautifully.
What a nice surpri--
is there another woman?
What? How did you--?
Colleen.
Don't blame your mother,
Jack.
This is about us.
Oh, my God. Look, Avery,
you know how I feel.
So I'm gonna skip the part
where I deny anything.
Then you skip the part
where you yell at me.
And then we both move on
to the, uh, make-up sex.
Wow.
That is a swing.
Look, I assumed you and I
were exclusive,
but we never talked about it,
so maybe this is
partly my fault.
And I forgive you.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
But these tactics have worked
on stupider women.
If we're going
to move forward,
you better figure out
what it is you want.
Soon.
Excuse me, Dr. aldrin.
I'm sorry. There wasn't a door,
so I just...
I don't believe in barriers,
because I always break them.
You must be Liz.
Yes, sir.
I actually came about my mother,
Margaret lemon.
Well, you would have known her
as Margaret Freeman.
Maggie Freeman?
Of course I remember her.
Well,
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I can't help but wonder
what my mom lost
by giving up on you,
her perfect man.
Perfect? Sure,
I'm a famous astronaut,
decorated fighter pilot,
doctorate from mit,
but even I sometimes...
I see you.
I see what you're doing.
Return to the night.
You've no business here.
Are you yelling at the moon?
I'm sorry.
She and I just...
I get mad sometimes.
Sure.
Look, you want to know
what your mother missed?
Years of drinking,
depression, cheating.
I flipped over a saab
in the San Fernando valley.
I once woke up
in the air and space museum
with a revolver in the waistband
of my Jean shorts.
Oh, my God.
But you're--
a human being.
But I'm at peace now.
Sober almost 32 years.
But I would have put
Maggie Freeman through hell.
[Sighs]
The moms were right.
There's no such thing
as astronaut Mike Dexter.
What am I doing?
I'm sorry
if I've disappointed you.
Would you like to yell
at the moon with buzz aldrin?
Yes, please.
I own you!
You dumb moon!
I walked on your face!
Don't you know it's day?
Idiot!
Well,
I'm ready for the show.
Mom,
you're wearing my outfit.
Well,
a mother makes sacrifices.
Like those 16 hours
I spent in labor,
even though it was
Margarita Monday
at dockside Joe's.
Daughters
make sacrifices too.
Why are you wearing that?
Who's paying you?
No one.
I'm wearing it for the same
reason you're wearing mine.
Because I love you.
I love you too, baby girl.
Oh.
Why does your chest
feel weird?
Uh, because I love you
so much.
♪ Sincerely ♪
♪ oh yes sincerely ♪
♪ 'cause I love you
so dearly ♪
you look beautiful...
Mom.
Thank you.
Son.
I think I'm ready
for the sex talk.
♪ Oh you know
how I love you ♪
mom,
you were right to settle.
I'm glad you married dad.
So am I, dear.
Now, would you please
find yourself someone
and start a family
before my hereditary dementia
sets in?
Wait, what?
♪ Please say ♪
♪ you'll be mine ♪
you.
What is wrong with you?
I am 51 years old.
Do you not think
I can take care
of my own personal life?
Think?
I know you can't.
You do a lot of things well--
make money,
choose wine, wear ties.
But you and women?
Disaster.
Divorce.
Broken engagements.
I assume herpes.
And I wonder
why I'm like that.
Maybe it's because
you can't let go
of your precious Jackie,
so you undermine me
at every turn.
I'm not
gonna be around forever.
Don't pull that out,
Colleen.
And if I don't do something,
you will never
make a decision.
You'll just froufrou around
with Nancy and Avery
until they're both gone.
And then where will I be?
I'll be circling the globe
in my coffin rocket.
Something I saw on tv.
It's very expensive.
I'm done disapproving,
Jackie.
I'm just trying to help.
I need to know that someone
is looking out
for my little boy.
All right, Colleen.
Then I'm asking you,
for the first time in my life,
tell me what to do.
And I'm going to tell you,
for the first time in my life,
I can't!
[Door opens]
I--I did not lose her, sir.
Carl would never let you down.
Carl,
that does not sound right.
Kevin--no.
Who am I?
Is it Keith?
No, that's not--
yes, I'm Keith.
That's our show.
Thanks for watching.
But before you go to bed,
our moms are gonna tuck you in
with a special song.
♪ Don't go to sleep
with a frown in your pocket ♪
♪ take it to the yard
and tie it to a rocket ♪
♪ shoot it to the moon ♪
♪ you'll feel better soon ♪
♪ don't go to bed
with a frown ♪
all: ♪ don't go to bed
good night.
Stay tuned for a special
mother's day edition
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net