Previously on 30 Rock...
- So you're...
- In three weddings
On the same day, yeah.
Fate is telling us
we're each other's
Settling soul mates.
I've been seeing someone else,
And I think I'm in love
with both of you.
Jack wants me to stall?
So I'm gonna marry...
Japheth.
And we're gonna live in...
Nineveh.
And I'm gonna be a...
Prostitute.
Yes, I continued
to see other people.
One person, who apparently
you're also in love with.
It's possible. Haven't you
ever read Archie comics?
Jack, I got divorced.
I didn't know
if you would ever leave mark,
So I let myself
fall into something else.
You look amazing in that dress.
You look like a gay mortician
in that suit.
You know, Kenneth,
I have a thankless job.
For example,
I'm here on a Saturday
To show around
some Kabletown folks.
Chk-chk! Boom!
It's not real.
Point is, I usually only get
to deliver bad news.
But not today.
Kenneth, you are the new...
Junior in-charge boy
of the entire NBC page program.
Oh, my goodness!
This is my dream come true.
And to hear it from my best
friend in the whole world,
Comma, bald category.
Well, you start in two weeks.
And they'll give you some moving
money to help you get to L.A.
California?
I can't move out there
And be away from all of you.
No, thank you, sir.
I'll pass.
You can't pass.
Jack put you up for this.
If you don't want the job,
you have to talk to him.
Fine.
I will talk to him.
And Mr. Donaghy
will understand
'cause he's my best friend
in the whole world,
Comma, beautiful hair category,
parentheses, strong.
♪ and a man
must leave his mother ♪
♪ and a woman needs her bones ♪
What can I say, Nancy?
I want to be with you.
I want to take naps with you.
I want to watch you
watch a hockey game.
I want to find long red hairs
in my overcooked pot roast.
I love you.
I do love you,
Because you know
that what I really am
Is a poor mama's boy
from Sadchester, Massachusetts
Who had to wear his sister's
hand-me-down corduroys.
They were orange
and had hearts for pockets.
And you like me anyway.
Yeah, I get it, Jack,
But what are you gonna do
about it?
I can't share you
with another woman
Like you're that Mormon guy
on HBO
Who was in that Tornado movie.
The one with the girl
with the forehead
Who was married
to that Jewish guy.
What?
I'm a mom.
Give me a break.
I need to know right now,
Are you in or are you out?
In. Nancy, I'm in.
Okay.
Then I'm in too.
♪ sum of all his parts ♪
♪ there is a love ♪
♪ Floyd and Kaitlyn ♪
♪ there is love... ♪
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Paul?
What are you doing?
I thought you were going to get
Your hair done
for your friend's wedding.
I was, but I forgot
my bag of hair.
Is this who you're into now?
Cher?
You're being another woman
behind my back?
It's not what it looks like.
Oh, spare me your lame excuses.
Maybe I'm old-fashioned,
But when a girl dates
a straight man
Who impersonates her on stage
for mostly gay audiences,
She has certain expectations.
Fidelity, Paul.
It's not just the name
of a bank that sued me.
But I love you both equally.
I don't know what to tell you.
But you have to choose.
It's her or me.
Jenna, babe, wait.
I'm sorry.
That came out wrong.
Mr. Donaghy!
- Oh, God, Kenneth!
- I need to talk to you
About an urgent
page-related matter.
God, he came out of nowhere.
We can talk on Monday.
Ms. Donovan and I have an hour
between weddings to, uh--
- Tickle each other
like teletubbies.
That's how I used to explain it
to my kids
When they walked in on us.
But I don't want
my promotion, sir.
I want to stay here in New York
with all my friends.
I'm not going
to let you say no, Kenneth.
This is a promotion for you.
And, yes, it's difficult,
But today
is about pulling triggers.
It's about making bold choices.
It's about--
- Two spider-mans fighting,
And sometimes
they make weird noises,
But they're not hurting
each other.
How often
did they walk in on you?
A lot.
If you'll excuse me.
D'oh, bother!
Treble bother!
What is it?
My fancy dress slippers.
I left them in my office.
So go get them and meet me
at Cerie's wedding.
No.
When I was fired,
I vowed on the snipes name
I would never set foot
in there again.
Also Kevin in security
has a picture of me.
So, what, you want me
to go get your tuxedo shoes?
See?
Our minds are already one
As our bodies soon shall be.
There's the address.
Of course.
You work in insurance.
Specializing
in the transportation industry.
Fulfills my boyhood passion
for train accidents.
Fine.
I'll go get your shoes.
Farewell, my luscious plum.
- Oh, son of a--
- Why is your face like that?
California?
No way, Ken.
Look, you got
to tank this promotion.
Do a sloppy job,
and they'll leave you alone.
That's how I got out of doing
foreplay with Angie.
And my taxes.
That's not in my nature.
If you've learned anything
from me,
It's how to do a bad job.
Go. Honor me.
Save yourself.
But first get me a sandwich.
Get it yourself, Chubbs.
I'm on a coffee break.
That's my boy.
♪ ♪
Oh. I'm gonna hit
the ladies' room real quick.
You can never tell when one
Of these non-denominational,
goof-around weddings
Is gonna start.
- Jack Donaghy.
- Paul l'Astname.
I'm Jenna's boyfriend.
Oh, I've heard a lot
about you, Paul.
Well, it's all true.
I'm a native of Houston,
and I love to cook healthy.
And the female
impersonator stuff.
Oh, sure.
Of course.
It's actually been causing
some problems at home lately.
Do you think it's possible
to love two women at once?
I know it's possible.
But at some point,
you have to choose, Paul.
You can't delude yourself
with thoughts like,
"what if I could somehow combine
them into one perfect woman,
Like a s'more you could take
a shower with?"
But how do you know if you've
made the right decision?
You don't.
You'll always be wondering
What your life
would have been like
If you'd opened
that other door.
Like at a haunted house
sex party.
Exactly.
Thank you, Jack.
Come on, Jessup.
Get it together. No tears.
Everything all right in there?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Here.
You need this more than I do.
I never put my mouth on it.
- Thanks.
- You look so familiar to me.
Oh, I'm a financial reporter
for CNBC.
The hot box
with Avery Jessup.
No. You ever do a commercial
for overshoppe.com?
Oh, God, I did.
Oh, that was before I got rid
of my Maryland accent.
Does the "o" have it?
"o," we do.
Do you "o"?
"o," no?
Let go.
"o."
Ugh.
That accent's idiotic.
Anyway, nice to meet you,
Avery Jessup.
I'm Nancy.
Hi.
I'm not normally
this--ahem--overwhelmed.
I-I came here
to talk to my boyfriend
Or whatever he is.
I mean,
this whole situation--
Clamp down, Jessup!
Be a winner.
Oh, my God.
I can't drink this.
You wanna talk about it?
Oh, tuxedo slippers.
Give me a break.
Excuse me.
I'm supposed to meet you here?
Huh?
Are you Wesley?
I'm Carol.
I'm sorry.
What's happening now?
I'm supposed to meet a Wesley
About my insurance claim.
Wesley doesn't work here
anymore.
Are you serious?
I mean, I made the appointment,
Like, a month ago.
I rearranged my whole Saturday.
Are you a doorman?
Yeah, I'm a doorman...
To the sky.
I'm a pilot.
Oh, okay.
Well, look, it's a pretty
standard workman's comp claim.
I'm sure you could handle it.
I was flying at 7:00 A.M.
From Tampa to Louisville,
And we had
a two-hour weather delay,
So naturally
all the passengers got drunk.
Generally speaking,
if there's a delay
Of more than 20 minutes, I might
as well be driving a party bus.
It's just idiocy.
I don't know what's going on
in this country.
- I know. People wear flip-flops
to church.
And the NBA tattoo situation
is out of control.
Thank you. Anyway, we're about
a half hour into the flight,
I hear this commotion
behind me in the cabin,
So I exit the cockpit,
I go down the aisle,
And to my left, I see--
A terrorist?
No. I wish.
It's a drunk lady.
She's pulled her pants off,
and she's ranting.
She's complaining about
the in-flight entertainment.
So things got
a little heated...
And I had to implement sky law.
- What's...
- Sky law.
It's when I put on
the "fasten seatbelt" sign,
And no one's allowed to move
Till we've had ten minutes
of silence.
I made the whole thing up.
But, you know,
people are stupid,
So they don't question it.
That is awesome.
So what is the workman's comp
part of this?
Eventually, I flipped
the drunk lady off,
She bit my finger.
I know.
It was totally unprofessional.
But she was bagging pretty hard
on my TGS.
- What?
- TGS.
It's this late-night show
on NBC.
We run it in-flight
when we're northwest-bound.
Basically, the greatest thing
ever on television.
I don't stand for anybody
besmirching it on my aircraft.
Do you believe in fate?
Wait a minute.
Are you kidding me?
You write
for TGS with Tracy Jordan?
I'm the head writer.
I'm not
an insurance claims adjustor.
I'm just here
because my cousin...
Well, I mean,
it's my favorite show ever.
There's
the one fart doctor sketch
Where this fart doctor's trying
to figure out who farted
In the spelling bee,
and he's like...
"he who spelt it,
dealt it."
I wrote that.
I write all of the fart doctors.
I can't believe this.
Would you like to go to
a rich girl's wedding with me?
I don't know.
Does that sound like more fun
Than me eating alone
at the Laguardia chili's?
I won't leave you, sir.
No matter what it takes.
Good afternoon,
and welcome...Not.
We begin our stupid tour
Of this once-great network
Outside studio 6h.
Uh-oh. Ring-ring.
Hmm.
What's up?
Nothing. Just giving a dumb tour
to a bunch of uggos.
Let's meet up later
And smoke some drug cigarettes.
You're a pilot, huh?
I should pick your brain.
I'm developing a daytime talk
show with Sully Sullenberger.
Yeah, I met that guy.
He's not that great.
You know what a great pilot
would have done?
Not hit the birds.
That's what I do every day--
not hit birds.
Where's my ticket
to the Grammys?
Hey, what took you so long
in the bathroom?
The usual ladies' room
nonsense.
Girl with boyfriend troubles.
Someone forgot tampons.
Everybody's bad
at science and math.
You know the drill.
The ceremony
will be starting soon.
I'll get our table number.
You get as many drinks
as you can carry.
I'll see you
at the reception, Liz.
Jack.
Carol.
Get ready for some of this.
Later.
He's here with you?
Indeed he is.
I see that Nancy is still here.
You're welcome.
- Smug 40-year-old bridesmaid.
What a treat for everyone.
Yes, Lemon,
I am with Nancy now.
What made up your mind?
Well, I decided
that any decision
Was better
than no decision at all.
Huh.
I don't know, Jack.
I used to feel that way too,
but now I know.
You can't force your fate.
You just have
to let it wash over you,
Like a spray tan that won't take
because your skin is too oily.
That's absurd, Lemon.
The world is made
by those who control
Their own destiny.
It isn't made by those
who don't do.
It's made by those who do do,
Which is what made me
the man I am.
I do do.
Yeah.
Grow up, Lemon.
The point is I made my choice,
and I'm not looking back.
Period.
Avery Jessup?
Son of a--
What did you do
on your tour today?
Those were
the Kabletown executives.
Our new bosses.
Sir, I was just trying
to do a bad job
So I wouldn't have
to go to Los Angeles.
Everyone there smiles creepily
all the time.
And that's sort of my thing.
Kenneth, you're not going
To Los Angeles.
Oh.
Because they're making me
fire you.
You're fired.
Ready?
Here.
This is yours.
Oh, Nancy, I'm sorry.
This is
an embarrassing oversight.
Jack, this morning at church,
You told me all the reasons
that you loved me,
Some more graphic
Than were appropriate
for the setting.
Now I want you to tell me
What's so special
about this other woman.
Well, I like
how she's less hot than you.
I'm serious.
What can I say?
She's smart.
She's pretty.
She can tell you the Dow 40
in order of market cap.
She knows how
to field dress a deer.
Why do you--
- Go on.
Okay.
Her laugh is like music.
Really mean music.
And she always wears high heels
Because, according to her,
flat shoes are for quitters.
For God's sake, what can I say?
You'd like her.
So you weren't lying
When you said
you were in love with two women?
- No. I wasn't lying.
- Good.
Then I feel a lot better
about leaving.
- What?
- Avery's here, Jack.
And she's pregnant.
Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
Ah, it's fate.
You were supposed to be a dad.
And by the way, when I blew
your mind last night,
I was giving it about 50%.
Unhand my fiancee!
No, no, he's just a groomsman.
And a Somali pirate.
Careful.
You tried to end our engagement
With a textual transmission.
Your behavior as a fiancee
Has been as weak
as American tea.
There. I've said it.
Our first argument, everyone.
You're engaged?
What if the bachelorette party
theme was sluts?
No, the engagement is off.
You keep talking about how fate
is trying to push us together.
You know what, it is.
But not to meet you.
To meet the right man.
His name is Carol.
Like Carroll O'Connor
from Nick at nite.
Exactly, Cerie.
Thank you.
Carol is the one
that I was fated to meet.
And, yeah, I've only known him
for a few hours,
And maybe this sounds crazy,
But I already feel
like I could spend
The rest of my life with him.
He's the one
that I've been waiting for.
And someday, when Carol sees
my disgusting foot secret,
He's gonna be okay with it.
I can tell.
You were wrong, Wesley.
We don't have to settle.
The moms were wrong.
Stupid buzz Aldrin was wrong.
So thank you
and good-bye.
Praise to the universe.
Love is real!
Fine.
It's your loss.
There's only one Wesley snipes
in this world.
You know there isn't.
How much of that did you hear?
Well, you were engaged.
Apparently
you hate buzz Aldrin.
Foot problem.
And you and I are going
to spend
The rest of our lives together.
I see.
I'm sure you could
get a cab on Houston.
Yeah, I'm gonna depart.
On time.
I'm a pilot.
Jack.
Carol.
♪ in your eyes ♪
♪ there is a light ♪
Could you turn that down,
please?
♪ there is a light ♪
Mazel Tov.
I'm trying to tell you
I want to get married.
Oh, for God's sakes, Jack.
What do you think, you're just
gonna sweep me off my feet?
This pregnancy is two years
ahead of schedule.
I'm suing dodecacil.
I'm suing you.
I'm suing this baby.
You can't control everything,
Avery.
Sometimes it's just fate.
Ugh. Is their gay juice
in the champagne?
See.
I want you to teach our child
How to say awesome stuff
like that.
- I would be a kick-ass mom.
But if this is just you
trying to do the right thing--
- No. I want this.
I've always wanted this.
But maybe it's too hard.
The career, motherhood,
Keeping it tight
To stay camera-ready
for breaking news.
I mean, sure,
Soledad O'Brien does it, but--
- I wipe the floor
with that bitch.
Let's do this.
Love is patient.
Love is weird
and sometimes gross.
Love is elusive,
and you have found it.
So treasure it.
To Grizz and Feyonce.
On behalf of Grizz and Feyonce,
I'd like to thank Jack Donaghy
For letting us have
this reception here
After the other location
couldn't support the weight
Of Grizz's extended family.
Naturally, I blew it.
Now I'm alone in a dashiki.
I wonder what
that Somali pirate's deal is.
I could live on a boat.
I don't even know
where Paul went.
I guess he made his choice.
You know what?
Forget men.
We've got each other.
Yeah. Let's go lez.
No, I meant, like,
a book club or something. Jeez.
Right. Sisterhood.
That's something
we can count on.
I'll never--
is that Paul?
- You have a lot
of taped-up balls
To come here dressed like that.
Oh, my God.
If this is gonna work, Jenna,
It can't just be all about you.
- But...
- No buts.
I'm the man here,
and you're gonna respect me.
Yes, shma'am.
Lemon, you know that's
a young boy's puberty dashiki.
Wrong, Jack. It's
a warlord's concubine dashiki.
Avery, you're here.
I'm not surprised.
Why should I be?
And I'm pregnant.
Also not shocking me.
Reacting appropriately.
Lemon, I think your pilot
friend is looking for you.
So?
I thought he was gone forever.
I guess
I should go talk to him.
Carol, what are you doing here?
How did you get past security?
You walk briskly
in a pilot's uniform,
You can go
pretty much anywhere.
I've been upstairs
in the white house
While the obamas were sleeping.
I thought you had a flight.
Yeah, I do.
Those dirt bags can wait
On the runway
a couple more hours.
I hate people too.
Look, I'm 39 years old,
I'm single,
And lately I've been thinking
there's a reason for that.
I keep expecting people
to be perfect,
But nobody's perfect.
Yes. Exactly.
So if the worst thing about you
Is that you give
crazy speeches to fiances
And maybe you have
some kind of foot thing...
That was a joke.
I have medicine for it.
Why don't we give this a shot?
As long as you're not Jewish.
I'm totally kidding.
Yes.
Let's do this.
And honestly, Carol,
I am a very normal person.
Not a good time, guys.
Liz, Cher and me,
Paul, and I want to thank you
for being a part
Of our lives.
And for encouraging us
to be like this.
I can't believe I'm meeting
1 1/2 Jenna Maroneys right now.
Hi. Hi, there.
Hi.
- Carol.
- Carol. That's a girl's name.
It's a family name.
Hey, everybody.
I got fired today.
You won't have Kenneth Ellen Parcell
to kick around anymore,
So I want to tell you people
What I really think of you.
- Hey, this ain't the--
- No. No.
For four long years, I have
listened to you all complain
About your East coast
media elite problems,
Your apartment renovations,
And your overpriced
star wars memorabilia.
That doorman is hammered.
I have watched you
Throw away better food
Than my family eats
at Christmas.
And I have loved it.
You people,
you are my best friends,
And I hope you get everything
You want in life.
Kenneth!
So kiss my face!
That was actually really sweet.
I'll see you all in heaven!
Have a wonderful summer!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net