Hey!
Did you know
that everybody here
Went out last night without us?
Oh, nerds!
Nerds?
Nerds.
Yeah, Thursday night thunder.
That's been going on for years.
You know about it? How come
I've never been invited?
Don't you think
th's a little bit rude?
Well, I yelled "baba booey"
At Walter Cronkite's funeral,
So I actually have no idea
of what's rude or not.
- Yeah, well, let me...
- But I couldn't thunder
last night,
Because I had to take
Angie to the ER.
She had some complications
with her pregnancy,
So that kind of trumps
your little problem.
Ah, yeah, you're right.
How is she?
Well, she's fine,
and the baby's fine,
But they put her on bed rest
Till her blood pressure
goes down.
Well, listen, tray,
if there's anything I can do,
Please let me know.
There's one thing.
Could you take care of Angie
like a husband
Until this whole ass-ache
blows over?
Absolutely not.
What about you, k?
I'm on it, sir!
[exciting jazz music]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, my.
I haven't seen your brow
that furrowed
Since you saw that picture
of Helen mirren in a bikini.
How is it possible?
Is she a wizard?
A question
for another time, Lemon.
I was with Avery last night,
And I almost had
a Nancy-related incident.
Oh, Jack.
Oh, Nan...
Na.
What?
I was saying,
"oh, Nana."
Have I not told you
about my grandmother fetish?
Avery actually tried
to get on board.
Later that night,
She put some mothballs
behind her ears
And fed me peppermints.
She is in it to win it.
This can't go on.
I'm making a decision
about Nancy and Avery today.
I'm going in the bunker.
No distractions.
I had Jonathan remove the bar
And my collection
of 18th century french erotica.
I've had to make
some tough calls over the years,
Switching sheinhardt's
wig production
To 100% chinese cadaver hair,
Turning down Dick Cheney's
offer to become king of Iraq,
Selecting
the brand-new logo for NBC.
[NBC chime plays] it's fresh.
But this Nancy-Avery thing
Is the toughest decision
I've ever had to make.
Well, I'm glad
you're taking it seriously.
Although, sometimes when
you try so hard to find love,
You can't see that it's been
standing in front of you
The whole time.
Oh, good God.
[laughing]
What did you
come in here for?
[sighs]
Last night, I saw
my entire staff out at a bar.
They go out every week
and I'm never invited.
Do they not even like me?
Oh, don't worry.
It's healthy.
Bosses need to keep
their distance
From their subordinates.
Mr. Donaghy, I have to
run out to Mr. Jordan's house.
I'll call you when I get there
so you know I'm safe.
No! I don't care
if you're safe!
I love you!
After four years,
I thought I was close
with these people.
I thought we were a family.
Don't say family.
Then I see them
out at a bar without me,
Giving each other
windmill high-fives?
Like in top gun.
But this is your staff.
You can't let it bother you.
You could always come up here
and have a drink with me,
A fellow manager.
Oh, great,
that sounds really fun.
I'll just pour myself a drink.
Oh, I dropped my glass!
Is that supposed
to be a broom?
Anchor the handle.
Yeah.
There it is.
[cell phone vibrates]
This better be important.
I'm in a meeting.
Mr. Jordan,
The situation here
has deteriorated.
Great update, Ken.
Thanks for checking in.
Talk to you later.
Actually, sir,
I think you should come home.
***
If she sees me again.
She wants you to come help her.
What? But why?
You're much better
at that serving stuff than I am.
Well, your wife thinks
Taking care of her
should be your job
And I have to agree, sir.
You made a promise
to care for her
In sickness and in health.
Don't you remember
your wedding vows?
To be honest, I couldn't
really understand anything
Rick James was saying.
Come home, Mr. Jordan.
Mrs. Jordan needs you.
Fine, I'll be there soon.
And if you get hungry,
You can help yourself
to anything in the fridge,
And once I'm there,
I'll determine
how much to charge you.
[phone beeps]
[exhales]
Hey, buddies.
Anybody do anything fun
last night?
What about you, Frank?
What did you do?
I, uh, had a...
Doctor's appointment.
Oh, really?
For what?
Oh, uh...
Oh, God, it looks like
the underside of an octopus!
Hey, Liz, can I talk
to you and Jenna in...
The office where everyone
clips their toenails?
Not cool, guys.
As you guys know,
I'm getting married
on may 22nd.
You are? Still?
Well, it was off for a while,
Because my fiance
was on his dad's yacht
And got captured by pirates,
But now,
thanks to the a-team, he's back.
Sure.
He has
a different energy now.
He's quieter.
But we're getting married.
And are we still
in the wedding?
Of course.
The bridesmaids are you guys,
Andy roddick's wife,
My dutch cousins,
And Penelope cruz's
hotter sister Monica.
You're gonna be
so out of place, Liz.
Anyway, my mom said
that if you guys
Are gonna
throw me a work party,
It has to be this week.
- Oh, no! Really?
- Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
It's just that the schedule's
really filling up
Now that aris
is finally getting over
His Stockholm syndrome.
Oh, that reminds me.
You guys may have to walk
down the aisle
With some pirates.
It's just, I don't think
I can plan a party this week.
I'm doing a juice fast,
And it's making me
really grouchy.
Aah!
You know what?
This is perfect.
I'll have that party...
Tonight,
And it'll be fun,
And you'll all see
that I'm fun.
So screw both of you!
And screw everybody out here!
Liz Lemon is having a party!
[rapping] * and they're
ain't no party *
* like a Liz Lemon party *
* 'cause a Liz Lemon party
is mandatory *
All right, Donaghy,
Follow your heart.
"hard equations
and rational thinking."
Damn you, heart.
[panting]
I'm sorry, sir.
There's
a minor janitor problem.
I apologize for letting
a kashmiri
Into your office.
I just need five minutes
of your time, Mr. Donaghy.
[speaking hindi]
Now would be a good time,
actually,
To handle
the janitor situation.
- But, sir, what about...
- I always say bosses
should stay
Deeply involved
with their subordinates.
Does this mean you're coming
to my cabaret?
Jonathan, close the door.
Please.
So what can I do for you?
It has been a week,
And I've heard
nothing from you, sir.
Have you forgotten
our agreement
About me taking over 11:30?
I'm sorry. What?
Five years ago,
I threatened to quit
Unless you got me
out of the late night shift.
Wow, other than
some notable recent exceptions,
Nbc never guarantees
employment terms
Five years in advance.
I have a contract.
That is my signature.
You signed it
on April 22, 2005.
Okay, in my defense,
every April 22nd,
I honor Richard Nixon's death
by getting drunk
And making
some unpopular decisions.
Well, I want
the earlier shift.
It's better pay
and more prestigious.
Ever since I am a little boy,
I am dreaming
of hosing the tonight shift.
Okay. Uh, calm down,
Uh, Khonani.
I understand
that I made you a promise,
And we're going to keep it,
because this is NBC...
[NBC chime plays]
the biggest loser network.
So you'll fix this?
Today?
Well, this is
a janitor emergency,
And I really have no choice
But to make it
my number one priority.
Good. Thank you.
Can I have those pictures
For a special book
the janitors keep?
Absolutely not.
[dog snarling]
Aah!
Good monster!
Good scary monster!
Hey, Ken, isn't that
a fun place to stand?
Oh, I forgot to warn you
about my dog, Tracy senior.
I trained him
to hate white people,
Because, not to profile,
But most ghosts are white.
This is my boy here.
And look what Angie did to him.
She set up an invisible fence.
He gets shocked if he tries
to leave the property,
Just because he'd run away
and cause car accidents
And impregnate
neighbors' horses.
He's trapped here just like me!
Sir, you're not trapped.
Mrs. Jordan just wants you
to be here for her.
I'm trying, Ken,
And I want to be responsible,
But I've been me
for a long time.
Well, Mrs. Jordan
isn't asking for a lot.
Right now,
she just has a craving
For a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
No, we're not supposed
to do any sex stuff
While she's on bed rest.
Oh! Like a real one!
I'm on it!
Maybe this'll get Angie
To stop calling me
irresponsible.
Just stay focused
And take this sandwich
to my wife.
Nope!
I'm in a strip club!
My bad!
Hey, Jenna, if I'm expecting
about 20 people tonight,
How much ice should I get?
Oh, you don't want
to mess with that stuff, Liz.
Ice has caused a lot of ods
in the porn community.
Oh, you mean frozen water?
I don't know.
Well, I just don't
want to forget anything.
Don't worry.
No one's expecting a lot.
No, tonight
is gonna be different.
There's gonna be booze
and a karaoke machine
And that Black Eyed Peas song
They wrote for bar mitzvahs.
[on speaker] Jenna Maroney
to the floor.
Sure, it will.
Hello?
Lemon, you know Subhas,
The current
first-shift janitor?
Uh, kind of.
According
to the janitor community,
You call him frequently
Regarding
home toilet situations.
No, it's not that.
We're dating.
Lemon, please.
Look, I just need
his phone number.
What does this have to do
with Avery and Nancy?
That is taking a backseat
To this janitor situation
right now.
I need Subhas to step down.
But Subhas does a great job.
Look, five years ago,
I promised Khonani
the earlier shift.
Why would you ever
promise that?
Honestly, these immigrants
have a tough life,
No health care,
And I kind of just thought
he'd die
Before it became a thing.
Are you sure that
you're not just using this
As an excuse to avoid
your real problem?
Lemon, this is
a janitor emergency.
I need that phone number.
Okay, let me find it.
Subhas...Scrolling.
- I know you know it by heart.
- 917...
All right, Khonani,
If I've learned anything
from recent experience
It's that we have to handle
this next step
With Subhas very delicately.
Oh, don't worry.
Subhas will want to leave,
Spend time on his hobbies.
He collects classic car...
[coughing]
Cardboard.
Classic cardboard.
[dog growling]
Ken!
Why did you let me
go to a strip club?
I tried to stop you, sir,
But you threw your dog at me!
This is bad,
because I can't change!
I'm like a chameleon,
always a lizard!
[cell phone vibrates]
This better be a meeting,
'cause I'm important!
Tracy, it's Liz.
I want you to know
that at my party tonight,
You're off the leash.
I want to see the behavior
That got you kicked out
of the inaugural ball.
I can't, l.L.
First of all,
the secret service
Never gave me back
my t-shirt cannon,
And second of all,
I gotta stay home
and take care of Angie!
What? No!
Come on, you have to come.
I need you.
This party
has to be off the hook.
People don't say
that anymore.
They say
"surf party, usa."
Tracy, this is important.
I have to prove
to my co-workers
That I am not some angry,
un-fun woman,
Who doesn't deserve
to be included.
[speaking german]
Look, Liz Lemon,
I know your feelings are hurt,
But parties are like frisbees.
If you throw them
the wrong way,
They'll veer off
in a bad direction,
And then your kid
will fall into a quarry.
What?
Don't throw
a party for vengeance.
It will turn on you,
Like your wife after your kid
has fallen into a quarry.
You know what? Fine.
I don't need you.
I am gonna crush
this party Liz-Lemon style.
I don't know what to do.
A party's in trouble,
And I'm the only one
that can save it,
But your wife and
unborn daughter need you here.
- I'm torn, k-pax.
I know I should be here,
But my body's gonna
take me to Liz Lemon's.
What do I do?
[dog whining]
Put the electric
dog collar on me.
It would be my honor.
Subhas, thank you
for coming in
And for showing me
your, uh, special book.
More men in it
than I would have expected.
Book is book.
Indeed.
Uh, Subhas, you've
been with us a long time,
And you've
done great work here,
But we need some new blood.
I've decided that it's time
for you to step aside,
And Khonani will take over
at 11:30.
No! I'm in a union!
Well, I have a contract!
Meeting over!
No, no, hold on.
There's always another option.
What of we re-invent
the way people
Think about
their nightly trash removal?
No, thank you.
What if the night shift
just got a whole lot earlier?
Gentlemen, there is a way
For everybody to get
what they want
And for me to look
like a genius and a hero.
You're bullcrapping us.
No, I am not.
I am "innoventing."
A word that I just innovented.
[laughs]
NBC.
[NBC chime plays]
It's fresh.
Man, Tracy senior
took off fast.
He did not want to live here.
Sir, far be it from me
To question a plan
this well thought out,
But what's going to keep you
from just taking the collar off?
You're gonna pour glue
in the lock.
That's how my kids keep me
out of the liquor cabinet.
And, of course,
I'll be here to help.
No, Ken, there's something
else you have to do...
For all of us.
Unfortunately, there's
only one Tracy Jordan,
But sometimes
he's needed in two places.
You're Tracy Jordan now.
Go.
Go save that party.
Yes, sir!
Wait. I don't walk
that well.
There he is.
How's your first day going?
Oh, I don't know.
You tell me.
Khonani, I don't know
enough about being a janitor
To understand
what you're trying to tell me.
There's no trash, Jack.
Ever since you moved Subhas
to 10:00,
He takes all the trash.
No trash left for Khonani.
Okay, well,
there's a solution to this.
What if you and Subhas
share 11:30?
No, I wouldn't do that
to 11:30.
What are you talking about?
What
are you talking about?
There are two people
who want the same thing.
They can't both have it.
You need to make a decision.
I can't.
Damn it, I can't.
Don't you think
I know what it's like
To have two amazing people
Who both want the same thing?
I do!
And with Nancy and Avery,
I'm the thing, Khonani.
I'm the trash shift.
That sounds very difficult.
It's impossible.
It's paralyzed me.
I just want everyone
to be happy.
It doesn't work that way.
One person's heart
is going to be broken.
You have to choose.
I'm sticking with Subhas,
Khonani.
I'm sorry.
Okay. I know
that was hard for you.
And don't worry.
I have a job
for me at fox... [coughing]
Woods.
Foxwoods casino.
My cousin is
head janitor there.
You ought to get
that cough checked out.
[telephone rings]
This better be meetment,
I'm importing.
Mr. Jordan,
it's Kenneth Parcell,
From work and friendship.
Key, Ken.
With all the excitement,
I forgot that Mrs. Jordan
Had asked me to get
her blood pressure medicine.
She left it in her car.
But, sir, her car is parked
out on the street.
Oh, my God.
I know. It's outside
the electric fence.
Oh, my God!
I just didn't want
to go outside!
It's chilly!
I can come back.
This is all my fault.
No. This is something
I have to do myself.
You're a good husband,
Mr. Jordan.
[dog barking]
Sir, is there any chance
Your dog followed me here?
Yes. He probably
picked up your scent
And is hunting you.
I suggest you cut off a finger
And throw it in the river.
[dog barking]
Wow, Liz.
Good work.
This looks
like the post-coital suite
At the nba all-star game.
Thanks, Jenna.
Well, so now that
everyone's here,
Maybe someone should
say a few words.
[amplified] Absolutely.
* Jimmy crack corn
and I don't care *
- What are you doing?
- Juice fast delirium, Liz.
Um, I'm glad
you could all make it
To cerie's party.
I don't have a lot to say,
Just that the bar is open
And the karaoke machine
is ready to go.
Karaoke, awesome.
Yeah.
You think I don't know
what that is?
I know about
Thursday night thunder
And I know
that I'm not invited!
- Uh-oh.
I deserve to be loved!
Oh, no, she's going wide.
I am a proud, single woman!
How did it become about this?
Go out the window!
Save yourselves!
I may not have a real family,
But I thought at least
I had one at work,
Which is not what I wanted
for myself, by the way.
You think when I was a kid,
I dreamed of someday
paying $1,200
For a karaoke machine
To impress
a bunch of pasty losers?
And a professional singer,
Who's beautiful,
but doesn't know it.
So now let's
all go around the room
And apologize to me!
- Oh, my God,
this is the worst...
- [whimpering]
I had nowhere else to go!
- [barking]
- dog!
Dog attack!
[screaming]
[exhales]
Hmm.
Maybe this doesn't work
on people.
Aah! Aah!
Oh, my neck!
My swan-like neck!
Aah!
Oh!
Must...Fight...Through it.
Also must...Weed...Lawn!
[gasping]
I made it.
I'm on the other side.
I'm free.
I can go anywhere I want...
Like Liz's party
Or one of those places
Where you skydive
over a huge fan.
[truck door closes]
Hmm...Maybe it doesn't
work on people any...
Aah! It still does!
Aah!
[screaming and dog barking]
Why is that thing
following you?
Hunting me!
Electric collar!
[dog barking, door thuds]
There's no fire escape
in this room!
Why are we even here?
You make us show up,
you start yelling,
And then we get attacked
by a dog!
And Cerie didn't even come.
That's just
a cardboard cutout of her.
But I rescued her.
[door thuds and screaming]
Quiet! Quiet!
Everybody shut up!
We need to figure out
what we're gonna do.
[dog growling]
Oh, really?
Now I'm a part of the group?
Now you like me
because you're in trouble
And you need someone
to bail you out?
Yes, that's exactly
why we like you.
We love you.
You solve our problems.
That's what you're good at.
So what if you're
not fun at parties?
Yeah. You know
who's fun at parties?
Paris Hilton, Andy Dick, Tracy,
And they're all
gonna burn in hell.
Oh, God!
If you deliver me from this,
I promise every Sunday
for the rest of my life,
I'll go to...
Huh?
I'm through it.
Pizza Hut.
I'll go to pizza hut.
Ha!
Look, if this is a family,
That makes you the mom,
And you don't want to go out
drinking with your mom.
You want mommy
to make the monsters go away.
[door thuds and screaming]
- Oh, please
- come on!
[dog barking]
Everything's
gonna be all right.
Oh. Okay, Tracy senior,
Let's see what you've got.
[gasps]
[dog barking]
Aah!
Oh! Aah!
Run! Run, my losers!
[panting]
Aah!
Great party, Liz.
Everybody take some cupcakes!
[dog barking] Aah!
Hi, Subhas.
I have an extra headshot
I was gonna throw out,
Unless you want it
for something.
No!
You're not book!
Why?
What am I doing wrong?
Wanting to be book
is not book.
Mm...
So you solved
your janitor thing.
Now back to Nancy and Avery?
Top gun high-five
for courage?
Only because you look
like you need it so badly.
I'm fine with that.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net