Hey, liz, my daughter's
selling valentine cookies
For a school fundraiser.
Valentine's day is a sham
Created by card companies
to reinforce and exploit
Gender stereotypes.
Evelyn, this is the lady
I was telling you about.
I like valentine's day.
Tommy reticker gave me a card.
Ha. Learn from my sexual
misadventures, evelyn.
Last valentine's day,
I watched my boyfriend drew's
Mother/grandmother die.
I met floyd on valentine's day,
But he left me for the ty of cleveland.
And forget about dennis!
That pervert would always
just try to get me drunk-
All right, so zero cookies.
No, I'll buy some cookies.
But not for valentine's day.
Instead, these cookies celebrate
The February 14th birthday
Of anna howard shaw,
famed american suffragette.
Happy anna howard shaw day to you, evelyn.
Come on.
A happy anna howard shaw day to us all!
Lemon, which one of these ties
do you find more attractive?
- The red, definitely.
- Thank you.
I've got to look camera ready tonight.
I'm being interviewed on cnbc.
Have you ever watched
The hot box with avery jessup?
No, cnbc gives me a headache.
I get all my money advice from pbs.
Where should I put my money:
In tech stocks or the housing market?
Tech stocks, foxy moneybags, tech stocks!
Sir, your reservations are
all set for valentine's day.
And just to be clear,
are you and I exchanging-
No.
Why do you have valentine's plans?
What about nancy?
Nancy knows that I'm
here when she's ready.
But after what we went through,
our marriage,
The way that it ended between us,
It was, uh, very intense.
Like when you think
there's one more stair,
But there isn't.
And all of the sudden, you're, like, "whoa!"
Exactly.
So for now, I just want
something fun and easy.
Frankly, I could use a win. - A win?
What's with the euphemisms, jack?
Why don't you just say you want some...
- Is that sex, lemon?
- Is the way I do it.
So who's the lucky lady? - I'm not sure yet.
I have three dates set up across the city,
And I hope one of them works out.
How are you gonna handle
three different dates?
Well, I have a system for first dates.
At the appointed time, jonathan calls me
And tells me that I have a conference call
With the geneva office.
If I don't like the woman,
I have an excuse to leave.
If I do like her, I loudly tell jonathan
That I'm doing something more important.
The woman is suitably impressed.
And I'm guaranteed to see some underwear.
Perhaps a, uh, bra with a front clasp.
What?
What are your plans for
valentine's day, lemon?
I am taking myself out
of the equation entirely.
I scheduled a root canal
for February 14th, jack.
I will spend half the day in twilight sleep.
Then I will go home and watch
the lifetime original movie
My stepson is my cyber-husband.
Wow. That is inspired.
You are truly the picasso of loneliness.
Or I am that painting
elephant of being awesome.
Oh, kenneth, have any
packages come for me today?
No, miss maroney.
Well, that doesn't make any sense.
Valentine's day is always a huge deal
For maynard roger hoynes.
That's my stalker.
You have a stalker?
It's a real problem in
the celebrity community.
But if beyonce simply answered
one of my letters,
I'd stop trying to break into her house.
So if you haven't heard from him,
Isn't that a good thing?
Kenneth, the celebrit
y- stalker relationship
Is very special.
Maynard's debilitating devotion
Validates how wonderful I am.
But what does it say about
me if he's moved on?
Maybe to one of my peers like julia roberts.
I'm sure there's a reasonable explanation,
Miss maroney.
Hey.
Has anybody heard about any
cool new sex positions?
My girlfriend's visiting for valentine's
And I want to keep things caliente.
Oh, my god, lutz.
Are you still pretending karen exists?
She's real.
Would a fake woman have a personal web site
At jdlutz. Com/karen/proof?
Oh, good grief.
My cousin set me up on a
blind date for valentine's,
And I just found out the girl is... Well...
Urban.
Are you saying she's black?
I don't know how to get out of this.
Dude, come out with me.
You know that load with the messed-up teeth
Who cleans the urinals?
She'll only go out with me
If she can bring her ugly sister.
Wow, I can't believe you guys
Are letting valentine's day win.
Not me. One word. Oral.
Two words. Oral surgery.
I'm having oral surgery and
skipping valentine's day.
Doctor's orders.
Oh, that reminds me, dr.
Kaplan's office called.
They want to know who's picking you up
After your procedure.
- What?
- Yeah. It's an insurance thing.
Any time they have anesthesia,
Someone needs to bring you home.
Hey, that stuff messes you up.
When I had my wisdom teeth out,
I tried to get in the bath with my mom.
Okay, is there any chance
that you could take me home?
Sorry.
Every year, paula and I rent
this big suite up at niagara.
And then she takes the kids there
And I stay home and get wasted in my garage.
It's what keeps the magic alive.
Welcome back.
I'm here with sheinhard
t- universal vice president
Jack donaghy.
Thanks for sitting in the hot box, jack.
My pleasure, avery.
Also joining me, walter stein,
Whose bow tie tells us he works
for some liberal think tank.
And the food in his beard tells us
That he purchased a snack pack
On the train from new haven.
Ooh, that's got to hurt, walter.
Let's get to the countdown. First topic.
Prime minister wen wants a weak yuan. Do we?
China needs to transition
to a spending economy.
After dubai,
what's the next credit crisis?
The baltics or women's tennis.
Do we need a second bailout?
- Absolutely... Not.
- I love it.
Try to get in there, beta dog.
- I am trying.
- On three.
Who will be thnext president
of these United States?
Three.
Both: Mitt romney's oldest son jezba.
- Dennis kucinich.
- Okay, that's sad, walter.
Just sad. Jack, back to you.
Who's number one on your speed dial?
Blackberry, warren buffett.
Iphone, jimmy buffett.
- Favorite movie.
- Tie.
The fountainhead or uncle buck.
i>- My wife and I just saw the
yellow handkerchief.
Just sit a couple out/ stein. God.
All right, karaoke. Go to jack. Hit me.
- Nitty gritty dirt band.
- Oh, I rock the brothers.
Hey, let's grab a drink after this.
You read my mind.
We'll be right back after this ad
Aimed at the elderly.
One second.
Hey, tray,
I really need a ride home from the doctors
On valentine's day.
- Can't do it, li
- lem.
On valentine's day,
Angie and I rent a room
with a heart-shaped hot tub
And cook chili in it.
Then we take it to a soup kitchen
And that's where it
starts to get sexy.
Hey, jenna, please tell me
You haven't already concocted
Your usual valentine's day drama.
Can't talk, liz.
I just got my stalker's work
address from his parole officer.
And I'm gonna confront him
about why he's ignoring me.
Hey, kenneth. Are you free on valentine's?
No, miss lemon. I'm sorry.
I will be attending an al
I- day abstinence rally.
You're welcome to come.
I think I've got an extra
Gender-neutralizing hood.
- No. Thanks. God.
- Hey, liz!
- Hey.
- The answer's no.
Hello, maynard.
Jenna, you shouldn't have come here.
Well, what was I supposed to do?
It's almost valentine's day
And I haven't heard anything from you.
Has the dog who gives you your orders died?
No. Brandon's fine.
Jenna, we need to talk.
I don't think I can stalk you anymore.
No. You don't mean that.
Look, I have a new therapist,
I'm taking my meds.
I can't even see electricity
Shooting out of your head any more.
Well, is there someone else?
It's one of those kids from glee,
isn't it?
Jenna, please, don't make a scene.
I always knew this would end someday.
I just thought it would
be with me in the trunk
Of a rental car.
So, uh, where did you go to school?
Choate, then yale,
Then two years in africa
with the peace corp.
The peace corps. That's surprising.
Oh, no, the peace corp.
Lawrence peace's corporation.
We drilled for oil in gorilla habitats.
Oh, of course.
I learned to talk to gorillas
when I worked for ge medical.
Uh, we're going to test poisons on you.
Oh.
So, uh, are you seeing anyone?
Not for a few months.
You remind me of him, actually.
I have a thing for commanding
salt and pepper types.
I don't know why.
I think it started when
I walked into my parents
Doing it the day reagan was shot.
- I wouldn't over-analyze that.
Hello.
I am calling about the mad
e- up conference call with geneva.
I love having secrets with you.
One time, I ran over an old lady in arizona
And just kept driving.
Yes. Damn it. Geneva.
Well, cancel the conference call.
I'm doing something far
more important right now.
And more beautiful.
You're kidding, right? I mean,
that's your move?
- I
- I beg your pardon.
It's 3:30 in the morning in geneva, jack.
Who's your call with?
The hooker working the corner
outside of raiffeisenbank?
Oh, well, it is February.
And in switzerland,
that is night business month.
- Okay.
- All right, I'm sorry.
I forgot who I was dealing with.
Stay and just have another drink.
Look at me, jack.
Look how my body goes with this dress.
I don't need to be dealing with amateurs.
Listen, frank, I really need
a ride home from the doctor
On valentine's day.
Are you free?
No. That cleaning lady finally agreed
To go out with me.
We're gonna pick up some pierogies
And then eat them at her husband's grave.
you thought you
were so much smarter than us,
Didn't you?
But now you're in the exact same
Crappy valentine's day
boat everyone else is in.
No, I'm not.
I just need a ride home, not a date.
They're completely different situations.
How's that?
All we want on valentine's day
is to know that someone cares
Even a little about us.
Aren't you lookivg for the same thing?
In fact, yours is worse.
If you don't get that tooth fixed,
The infection will
probably move to your brain
And kill you.
Yeah, well, if I die,
my ghost is gonna haunt you.
Then your ghost is gonna see
Some disgusting stuff.
Lemon, look at this.
It's from avery jessup.
Oh, it's set to the wrong time.
It's set to geneva time.
Last night, avery saw right through
My conference call move.
Today, she sent this.
"hopefully you won't make
the same mistake again,
Mon sel et poivre. "
That means "my salt and
pepper" in swiss french.
She's hitting the ball back, lemon. Game on.
Wow. Avery jesvup. She's hot.
She was on maxim's "
I'd rape that 100."
I know. And besides being beautiful,
Avery is smart and doesn't suffer fools.
And when I eventually seduce her,
It's going to be... Very satisfying.
Well, great.
I hope you enjoy your weird game
Of sexy one-upsmanship.
Meanwhile, the male escort that I hired
To take me home from surgery
Has had a chlamydia flare-up, so-
Uh, lemon, I wish I could help you,
But I have to concentrate on avery.
Uh, I need a big next move
and you have a show tonight.
I've invited her to be my guest at the tgs
vip room.
We don't have a vip room or vips.
Get jon bon jovi.
He's nbc's current artist in residence.
What is that?
i>- A not stupid program that I came up
with.
Bon jovi is under contract
with us for a full year
And scheduled to appear across a variety
Of programming platforms.
Okay, fine. I'll set it up.
Thank you.
Because tonight, she's going to get
The jack donaghy "a" game.
Ooh. She's getting the
jack donaghy "a" game.
Hope she can keep her clothes on.
Lemon, your hair looks very nice today.
You should wear it like that more often.
- Oh, my. Well, I-I never, uh...
Oh. Ma'am, is something wrong?
- Maynard left me.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
Look at this.
It's the first letter he ever sent me.
"jenna, I was in your bedroom last night.
I left a gift in your toilet.
You will be my bride someday. "
Oh.
How can you be upset about
losing a guy like this,
Miss maroney?
Look, I know it's crazy.
Maynard is a weirdo.
But that weirdo loved me unconditionally.
You know what I realized?
He's the longest relationship I've ever had.
Except, of course, for doug.
Please do not say what doug is.
Doug is my vibrator.
This is the worst valentine's day ever.
Hello, this is elizabeth lemon.
I have surgery scheduled tomorrow.
And I am not embarrassed to tell you
That I don't have anyone to pick me up
And I will be leaving alone.
Ma'am, you really need someone.
i>- No, I don't. I don't need anyone.
Because I can do every single thing
That a person in a relationship can.
Everything. Even zip up my own dress.
Hmm.
You know, there are some things
That are actually harder
to do with two people
Such as... Monologues.
i>- Look, if you really
don't have anyone,
You can sign a liability release,
Then you can leave alone.
I'll fax it to your office. - Great.
Thank you for looking out for a sister.
In a feminist way, not because you're black.
Although it doesn't matter
because I'm black too.
No. You're gonna meet me. No, I'm not black.
Thank you for setting all this up, lemon.
Grizz, dotcom, thank you for pretending
To be bouncers.
Maybe some day we'll live in a world
Where you ask us to
pretend to be scientists.
Jon. Thank you for coming.
Oh, no problem, jack.
What do you need, arena rock anthem,
Power ballad?
Actually, I have a date coming by.
So if you can come over at
some point and say hello,
That would really impress her.
Oh, sure. That sounds
like an appropriate use
Of my time and talent.
Liz. The doctor's office
faxed this to you earlier.
Hey, when are you going to set up that cool
Vip lounge?
Thank you, cerie.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You shouldn't sign anything
without reading it first.
I made that mistake once
And I ended up nbc's artist in residence.
Oh. Okay.
Give me it.
I have an honorary degree
from monmouth university.
Hmm.
"I, the undersigned,
"henceforce known as the alone,
"hereby state that on February 14th,
I have absolutely no one in my life. "
You're alone on valentine's day?
It's not about a date.
I just don't have a ride home
from the doctor's office.
But isn't that the same thing?
I mean, isn't it about
having somebody out there-
Yeah, I get it, bon jovi,
It's already been explained to me.
"I, the alone,
otherwise known as jane sadwoman,
"release dr. Kaplan's office
Of all legal responsibilities.
"will likely die alone eaten by house cats. "
Boy, this seems like a lot of unnecessary-
Forget it. I am not signing this.
I reject the idea that there's some stigma
To being alone.
All rit, then what's the plan
If you don't sign the release?
I'll just tell them that my "boyfriend"
Is gonna pick me up.
And then after the surgery,
I'll make a run for it.
So you're going to invent a boyfriend
On valentine's day?
That is the lamest thing
I've heard since... This.
I'm tyke myson, baby boxer.
I wrote that.
Hey, jack, who's this lovely-?
Excuse me, bon jovi,
I'm in the middle of a conversation here.
- Yeah, but you said to-
- uh, thank you.
- I hate it here.
- Wow.
That was a lot better
Than your little conference call move.
Can I get you a drink, avery?
Or we could just get out of here.
Yes. We could.
Hello. Elizabeth lemon.
Do you have your release?
No, I don't need it because my boyfriend,
Astronaut mike dexter,
Will be picking me up...
On his motorcycle.
- Mm
- hmm. Take a seat.
* I will *
* remember you *
* will you remember me? *
Oh. Oh.
Ah.
* *
* that we had *
maynard?
* I will *
* remember you *
You know, I don't think the "anastacia"
Actually "affectored" me.
Oh, my god. What are you doing here?
We knew you'd need a ride home.
What do you mean we?
You can't leave without a ride, dummy.
Happy valentine's day.
Oh, you have some dried blood on your teeth.
You're here.
You're all here because you didn't want me
To be alone today.
Oh, floyd, I still think every day
About what would've happened
If I had gone to cleveland with you.
And even you, dennis,
Watching the color purple
drunk with you
Was one of the funnest nights of my life.
And drew, so handsome.
So, so stupid.
Seeing all of your beautiful faces
And dennis' jean jacket,
I know that I don't need anyone,
But I do want to be loved.
We all do.
And if it didn't work out between us,
It's just because I'm not
finished becoming me yet.
But I will find love someday.
Because I am a sailor
On the sea of the human heart.
Okay, this bitch is tripping her ass off.
Well, what do we do with her?
I got a date tonight.
I say we order us some
pizza and lock her in here
For the weekend.
I'm gonna start dialing numbers
Till somebody pick up.
What's that, bon jovi?
You love me too?
Hey. You want to grab breakfast?
You're sweet, jack, but let's not pretend
This is anything more than it is.
I'm sorry?
Look, despite what happened
in the shower last night,
I'm a pretty traditional girl.
I mean, I want a husband
someday and a family
And men like you don't.
"men like me"? That isn't fair.
I want a family.
A son I can throw a ball to
And when he's older,
have power struggles with.
Jack, you don't have to lie to me, okay?
I love guys like you.
You're great! For one night.
Look, avery, I admit, this isn't
What I was looking for
going into this weekend.
But you're an amazing woman.
Lemon, I c-oh. You're kidding.
Okay. I-I-I'll be right there.
Uh, I need to go.
Jack, the phone trick again?
I mean, I'd be insulted
if I wasn't so impressed
By your assistant.
This isn't a trick.
I have to pick up a
hallucinating employee of mine
From the oral surgeon's office.
Well, that's at least creative.
Look, cancel your walk of shame.
Come with me on a car ride of proof.
oh, my god.
Who did this?
I don't know.
I guess some weirdo out there loves you.
Thank you, kenneth.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Happy valentine's day.
What hotel is this?
Uh, would you just keep an eye on her?
I'm gonna turn down her bed.
i>- I was sure he was making this up.
Yes, you're a very pretty doggy.
Hey, what do you think about jack?
Who, jacky? He's the best one.
I don't know
what I would do without him.
Yeah, he is pretty great, isn't he?
bon jovi.
- Um...
- Uh, no, no, no, no, lemon.
It's time for bed. It's time for bed. Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net