I wrote that! I'm Liz Lemon.
"If your man is over 30, and still wears
a name tag to work, that's a deal-breaker."
But not you, Mike.
That's not you.
Mike, leave my cutout alone.
Okay, you know, I'm gonna do
the same thing to your cutout.
Oh, wait, you don't have
one, because you're nobody.
Blam-O! Another successful
interaction with a man!
30 Rock - Season 4 Episode 02.
Edited by He7LOW0RlD
Yes, Mr. Geiss, of course.
Well, I'll only be in D.C. for
the day, but if I find time,
I'll be sure to go see Fonzie's jacket.
You sit on it as well.
Hey, if you're going to D.C., I lost my
retainer there during a junior High field trip.
What can I do for you, Lemon?
Well, I wanted to give
you a copy of my book.
They used your blurb.
"Lemon numbers among my employees.
"Sir, your bus to Washington
leaves in half an hour.
You're taking a bus?
I have to.
Ever since these buffoons from
Detroit took private planes,
the rest of us have to put on a show.
And now, your president-who, by the
way, is Kenyan and smokes cigarettes,
has created an industry task force
for microwaves and small appliances.
Why? Do you need to be bailed
out with my tax dollars?
Even if they wanted
to, I wanted take it.
It's corporate welfare, Lemon.
Granted, the microwave industry
isn't what it used to be,
and the American love affair with the microwave
oven has cooled since its postwar heyday.
* and she told her daddy she
was doin' the microwave ?*
* do the microwave?*
Did that happen?
But, unlike Detroit, we don't
need handouts or regulation.
I'm gonna go down there, talk
circles around these hacks,
and catch the afternoon
bus back to Chinatown.
Now, where was the last place
you remember having your retainer?
I took it out to eat astronaut ice
cream at the air and space museum.
Air and space...
If your man collects action
figures, that's a deal-breaker?
What? Oh, yeah.
Last weekend, I picked up this girl after
practicing Jedi moves in prospect park.
Also a deal-breaker.
I took her back to my house on the handlebars of my bike.
As is that.
Snuck her inside, past my mom.
Wow, that's four. She sees my mint-condition
Hellboy figurine and starts quoting your dumb book!
Also, my girlfriend is mad.
In Canada.
Ms. Lemon, would it be all right
if I only worked 20 hours today?
I'm volunteering at an
animal shelter later on.
Oh, of course. I didn't
know you did volunteer work.
Oh, yes. I also help out at the pants
for zoo animals program and big brother.
Really? I did big sister in college. That
little girl taught me how to use tampons.
Oh, no, this big brother isn't
affiliated with the mentoring program.
It's an organization that secretly watches
people and makes sure they're behaving properly.
Liz, I don't if you saw the
crawl on the TV guide channel,
but I've agreed to star in a sexy, supernatural
thriller in the vein of twilight and true blood.
Oh, that's good. The vampire
movies are hot right now.
This is actually a werewolf picture that,
for tax reasons, is shooting in Iceland.
I play a moon scientist who's trying
to get to the bottom of things,
and who-spoiler alert-may
herself be a werewolf.
We start shooting tonight.
You can't leave. You
have rehearsal tomorrow.
Oh, well, why don't you get the
New cast member to cover for me?
Okay.
Look, I know that you're mad about
Jack's decision to bring in another actor,
and you want to punish me.
Punish you? Please, Liz.
I've just always wanted to shoot a
student werewolf movie in Iceland,
where I'm filling in
last-minute for Victoria Beckham.
Or we could sit down and
talk about this like adults.
Liz Lemon! You booger face! I'm
gonna kill you with a bazooka!
I bought my wife that dumb book of yours, and the
more Angie reads it, the madder she gets at me.
Well, maybe that's on you, tray.
No, it's off me!
A book hasn't caused me this much trouble since
where's Waldo went to that barber pole factory.
It's on you Liz Lemon.
And you will be punished.
This'll take ten minutes.
Let's hit the meadowlands
racetrack on the way home.
I've got a betting system
based on horse penis size.
Is it true, Mr. Donaghy, that your executives routinely
used company helicopters to dry their home tennis courts?
Yes, and no. yes, that did
happen. No, it didn't not happen.
And that G.E. kept a party clown on
retainer with a six-figure salary?
When silly Willy's fee was amortized
over all birthdays company wide-
I'm being told that company money
is being gambled at racetracks.
Yes, but I have a system.
In 2007, a G.E. officer used corporate funds to throw
a cabaret-themed Halloween party on fire Island.
As I recall, that was you.
Mr. Donaghy, I am overwhelmed by
the negligence and incompetence.
It is an affront to your shareholders
and, frankly, to the American people.
Listen, Banks!
Mr. Banks, you go and tell
your president the truth.
We don't need the government
telling us how to run our industry.
I've heard enough.
Why do you have a gavel? This
isn't the congress.
I brought it from home.
Congratulations, Liz Lemon.
Now Angie wants a break.
So instead of going to a hotel, or
my houseboat, which I cannot find,
I'm staying with the woman that
started this problem in the first place.
What? No. Tracy, that is not fair.
Oh, yeah, there's a garbage bag in
the hallway with a reef shark in it.
Just put him in the tub with a reef.
What's for dinner
tonight? I want pierogies!
Unfortunately, we're not gonna be able
to find homes for all these animals.
But, uh, you know, the
most important thing is that
you not become emotionally
attached to any of them.
I grew up on a pig farm,
sir, where all the animals,
even the birds that cleaned our
teeth, were workers, not pets.
I never even had a dog, 'cause, as
my mom would say, you can't eat love.
And as my mom's friend Ron
would say, "the donkey died.
You're the donkey now, Kenneth.
Just another animal.
Might as well be a rat.
An adorable rat, who shows you it's
okay to be scared during a thunderstorm.
Why, it seems crazy to me to
even give a dog like this a name.
For example, bandit.
And that's Reggie,
and up there is digger,
well, the dogs scheduled to be put
down today have red tags on them.
I will adopt all of them.
Jonathan, call don Geiss' office and
Les Winkler in corporate communications.
Tell Susan Cunningham,
Alan Junkin, Mark-Jack.
What took you so long?
Banks, you son of a bitch.
You know, revenge is a
dish best served cold, Jack.
Like...sashimi. or pizza.
You prefer cold pizza?
The morning after, it's the best.
Better than hot pizza? That's insane.
You don't tell me what
kind of pizza to like.
You don't tell me
anything anymore, Jack!
It was a year ago that
you kicked me to the curb.
I began plotting my
revenge that very day.
I knew that I had to align myself
with something more powerful than G.E.
And since American idol is not on till
January, that left the United States government.
So I spent all last fall raising money,
worming my way into the Obamas' inner circle.
Oh, my god, Malia, he did not say that!
Let's text him now.
After the election, I could have
had any ambassadorship I wanted.
Even to the world's
gayest country, Ireland.
Instead, I suggested that
I take on this task force.
See, I had you in my
sights the whole time.
What kind of gun was that?
It's a laser gun. It’s unstoppable.
You listen to me, Banks.
You keep your spray-tanned
little hands off this company.
Too late.
Your testimony's gonna make headlines in
every paper across the country tomorrow.
But...it wasn't a public hearing.
Somebody must have "weaked" it.
You did. You "weaked" it!
And I'm just getting started.
By the time I'm done, you're gonna make AIG
look like the Lehman brothers of microwaves.
You would destroy an entire
company just to get me?
Think of the pensions, the employees, the
kittens we use to test microwave strength.
Enjoy the view while you can, Jack.
You'll be here for
about three days, tops.
Oh, that's all I'll
need, Banks, you watch me.
I'll make this company profitable so fast, the only
headline will be, "Donaghy saves G.E., marries your mom.
“See you in a couple days, Jack.
Laser shield.
Tracy and Liz's
residence. Tracy speaking.
Tracy, it’s Jenna. Is Liz there?
It's Jenna, from work.
Jenna, it's 2:00 in the
morning. What’s going on?
Night stalkers has encountered some production
speed bumps that are complicating my schedule.
Well, I need you back by
Friday. What kind of speed bumps?
Well, Iceland appears to have
a different sun than America,
because this one is not setting.
Ugh, yeah, of course,
'cause it's so far North.
And you probably don't know this,
because you've never played a moonologist,
but werewolves only come out at night.
Yes, I remember that
from the thriller video.
Too soon.
What is your plan, Jenna?
Well, evidently, as it gets later in
the year the sun will start to set.
I'm told tomorrow night we may get
as much as a minute of darkness.
Really? So you're gonna shoot this movie
one minute at a time, just to punish me?
Liz, I don't even know
what you're talking about.
What New cast member? Bye.
No, you...
What's wrong, roomie?
Well, two of my coworkers are driving me insane,
so I'm gonna kill them in their sleep tonight.
Tracy and Liz's. Tracy speaking.
Tracy, put Lemon on.
Hello?
Okay, as a single woman, would you be
more inclined to buy a New microwave
if it could be programmed
to ask you about your day?
Before you answer,
consider your loneliness.
I'm hanging up now.
Now that we're all up, you want to
talk about the elephant in the room?
No, I don't. I don't even know
why you brought that thing.
I mean the figurative elephant!
Liz, I been reading your book.
Now I see why Angie's mad at me.
"If your man has seven cell phones,
but won't give you any of the numbers,
that's a deal-breaker?"
"If your man owns a diamond
necklace that says open marriage,
that's a deal-breaker!"
Liz Lemon, every little
thing I've done is in here.
You used me to write your book!
What? No, maybe some of
it is inspired by you.
You stole my life.
And you're gonna pay for it.
Really?
You're gonna make my life
worse than it is right now, how?
I'll take all of them.
Tracy and Jenna are like children.
And like children, you can't
reason with them when they're upset.
All you can do is turn the heat
up, pour some whisky in their juice,
and wait for sleep to save you.
Well, that's not gonna work for me,
because Jenna is immune to whisky,
and Tracy is afraid of juice.
Oh, and not to add to your
problems, but Paula read your book.
Attention, creative
types. Brainstorming Session.
Let's try to stop
mouth-breathing for one minute.
What is this?
It's an idea. An idea that started
this company, changed the way we live,
and made this country
great. This is Dinesh Mehta.
He's a design engineer
from the microwave division.
All Dinesh and I need from you is one
idea that is as good as the light bulb.
What?
I have two days to make
people buy a lot of microwaves.
Well, it's kind of annoying when
you're microwaving, like, a burrito,
and the burrito won't
rotate because it's too big.
It just gets caught against the
sides and the tray under it rotates,
but it doesn't rotate.
Bigger ovens. Americans
like big, yes. What else?
What if microwaves broke down more easily, so
people would have to buy New ones more often?
Yes, shoddier, excellent.
Bigger and not as well-made.
Wow, that sounds exactly like the philosophy
that almost destroyed the U.S. auto industry.
This isn't the auto industry, Pete. The auto
industry was run by a bunch of out-of-touch
White guys selling consumers
a product they didn't want.
We're G.E., damn it.
And we're gonna make a
giant, flimsy microwave.
Frank, I can't! If I make it any
bigger, the door will be too heavy.
Fine! Forget it.
Wait.
Say that again.
I said forget it.
For...get it.
Four smaller doors.
We'll crack this yet
"We’ll" crack this yet.
Wheel. Put wheels on it.
Nice.
Donaghy
Okay, it's go time. Are you ready?
I'm in character and everything.
All right, let's do this! The sun
is setting! We get one shot at this!
Thank you.
And action!
Claire, I'm sorry. Which hand did I have
the flashlight in when we were inside?
The right! You had it in the right.
Thank you.
Cut!
Great day, everyone.
You guys are the real stars.
Since I have neither the time nor the energy to
even pretend that your situation is a real problem.
She doesn't like to refill the Brita.
I will cut the baby in half.
And I will take the top half. For
that is the part with the face.
Lemon, you wrote about
Tracy's life for your own game.
Tracy should be allowed to
use your life as he sees fit.
I'll have Jonathan call legal and
get a life rights contract drawn up.
Wait, what do you mean? Tracy
will own my life story?
What are you gonna
do with my life story?
Something humiliating.
Thank you, Jack.
Thanks a lot, Jack.
It's your only move, Lemon.
Sometimes the way back up down.
Let me tell you a story. It's 1994.
I went ice climbing,
and I fell into a crevasse.
I hurt my leg, and I
couldn't climb back up.
So fighting every natural instinct, doing
the thing that seemed most awful to me,
I climbed down into the darkness.
And that's how I got out.
And when I got back to base camp,
I went and found my fellow climber,
the one who had cut me loose after I fell, and
I said, "Connie Chung, you did the right thing.
Thank you.
Climb down, Lemon.
Climb down.
Hey, you're back.
Night stalkers is taking
a brief, permanent hiatus.
Well, maybe now we can talk.
Jenna, I'm your friend, no
matter what, and I will always
oh, Liz, I would really love to do this.
But I have to go home for the day.
Gotcha. So you're sticking with
the passive-aggressive acting out.
No, it's not acting out.
I have Mercury poisoning from
obsessively taking my rectal temperature.
And cup holders. Everyone
loves cup holders.
Okay, I've been up for the last 50
hours, but I think this is a good idea.
Let's get rid of the oven entirely
and replace it with an AM/FM radio.
Okay, it's a car. We’ve
invented the Pontiac Aztec.
Thank you, Subhas.
You are the deal-breaker!
This is a Bill.
Tracy.
Hey, roomie. Did you order
pay-per-view at my apartment?
I'm willing to go splits-ies.
I'm not paying for any of this. You
ordered six adult movies in two days.
"The curious case of
Benjamin Butt." Lovely.
"I'm a do us?" What does that even mean?
That's a pun on Amadeus, dummy.
I will not be judged by you.
You caused this whole folderol.
Until you're adequately debased, you will
subsidize my predilection for erotica.
Oh, yeah, and I used your credit card to buy
a vocabulary course from the teaching company.
So you're saying once you
figure out how to get back at me,
you and the dogs will
leave my apartment?
Affirmative.
I have to climb
down...into the darkness.
I know what you should
do with my life rights.
Pete, keep tours out of the
studio for the next couple days.
I need you to build a set that looks like my
apartment and get all the hand sanitizer you can find.
Wait, wait, why do you need Tracy
is producing a porno based on my life.
And I'm writing it.
I didn't think it would
end like this, Jonathan.
Not with a bang, but with a whimper
a whimper indeed, Jack.
I only came by to wish you
luck on your New venture.
What do you think that'll
be? Selling fake weed to NYU students?
I'll have you know that Barry Diller and I
are working on a whole New approach to media,
combining the digital - God!
Just let me drink.
See you around, Jack.
Thanks for letting me be such a big
part of you hitting rock bottom, huh?
Not yet, Banks.
I can go lower.
Into the crevasse.
What?
You played this all wrong.
You want to humiliate
me? You want to destroy me?
You should have walked
in here with a check.
Again, what?
Sure, maybe you've ruined my
career. Maybe you'll never see me again.
But if you had forced me to take
government bailout money, you'd be my Boss.
Oh, my.
You'd have to come down to Washington.
Report to me, like
a little school boy...
Your hands sticky from candy.
And the worst part is, I
wouldn't even want the money.
No, you wouldn't. Jack Donaghy
taking welfare? It'd kill you.
With so many jobs at stake.
You'd have to take it.
I'd make you. I'd make you take it all.
I'd roll over and let you give it to me.
I'm honestly not trying
to make this sound gay.
No one is. It’s just happening.
One word to the president, and I own you.
I own this office.
I own that...fancy
little fellow outside.
It'd kill me.
But I'd do it for the company.
Hey Sasha, is your dad home?
What? You have to invite everyone
to your party? Even Zach S.
Everyone settle.
And action.
It's not just about the new cast member.
When you always put the show ahead of me,
it makes me feel like we're growing apart.
Jenna...you're my friend.
No matter what.
I will always look after
you. That's not going to change.
Oh, Liz, thank you for giving
me the hotter porn Lady.
Okay...we should get out of here.
Yeah, we should.
Everything good with Tracy?
Yea, I think so. And Jenna and
Frank and even Subhas. And you?
I live to fight another
day. But at what cost?
Oh, boy, I know the
feeling. What a week, huh?
Lemon, it's Wednesday. But
it's not all...
Bad news.
My retainer. Now my
dad won't be mad at me.
Take it out, Lemon!
You take it out, Donaghy!
Everything good with Tracy?
I think so, and Jenna too,
and Frank, and even subhas.
And you?
I live to fight another day.
But at what cost?
Boy, I know the feeling.
What a week, huh?
Lemon, it's Wednesday.
But it's not all bad news.
My retainer.
How will I ever thank you?
And cut. This is disgusting. Shut it down.
www.tvsubtitles.net