I'd like to welcome everyone
to this NBC employee
town hall meeting.
And thank you for taking time
out of your busy schedules.
Yeah, I'm supposed to be
drinking a soda right now.
A special thanks to those
joining us via simulcast,
Particularly you gentlemen
in the Tokyo office.
I know it's late there.
I don't know why you're wearing
girls' pajamas,
But I'm sure it's cultural.
I'm here to address concerns
regarding the acquisition
Of our company
by Kabletown.
With a K.
This is an exciting time
for NBC.
Not Seinfeld, Friends, E.R.
exciting.
More like 3d episodes
of Merlin exciting.
But I believe
this is a great opportunity
For all of us because Kabletown
is a great company.
Even if it is from...
Philadelphia.
Go Eagles!
How did you even get
a snowball?
Philly rules!
Cheesesteaks! Bobby clarke!
Will Smith!
Your town sucks.
You do not want
this argument, Lemon.
Boston is the greatest city
in the world.
Boo.
Boston tea party.
Boston cream pie.
Boston Rob Mariano.
Birthplace
of Benjamin Franklin.
Yeah, then he looked around,
realized it sucked,
And moved to Philadelphia!
Oh, did you just whip
a battery at me?
Mr. Donaghy, I'm sorry,
can we get back to the meeting?
Of course. My apologies
to our friends
[laughing] from the great city
of Los Angeles.
[laughter]
Hey. Stop laughing.
L.A. Rules.
Michael Bay, freeways,
Legoland.
Before I take
your questions,
I'd like to say few words
about Don Geiss.
The world has lost a giant.
He built G.E.
into the greatest company
on earth,
And the earth into one of
the top three planets
In the universe.
For those of you wishing to pay
your respects,
There will be an episcopal
cryogenic freezing service
Open to all six sigma
black belts and higher.
That's the craziest thing
I ever heard.
Episcopal!
Now the floor is open
to questions.
I would be remiss if I didn't
honor our fallen leader
With a song.
This is for you,
Dan Goose.
♪ amazing ♪
♪ gra-♪
[exciting jazz music]
30 Rock 4x16
Don Geiss, America and Hope
Original Air Date on March 18, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
So how was your second date
with Wesley?
Ah, well, you know
that scene in Notting Hill
Where they have the romantic
date in the garden?
Well, I would have rather
watched that terrible movie
Five times than have hung out
with Wesley.
So he's not
your future husband?
He's not my future anything.
You gave it a shot.
Good riddance.
Nope.
I'm seeing him tonight.
You are? Why?
Well, this morning I was
buying an advanced ticket
For the truffaut
retrospective
At the anthology
film archives--
One for the 8:00
hot tub time machine.
Liz?
Are we both seeing
hot tub time machine tonight?
How does this keep
happening?
If there is a god, liz,
I think that she...
Ugh.
Is trying to tell us
something.
It's like the universe
keeps pushing us together.
We can't shake each other.
I had a thing where I kept
running in to michael douglas.
But then I realized
it was just some old lady
Who lives in my building.
Lemon. A moment.
We have a Tracy problem.
Okay.
Escaped exotic animal
Or did he swallow
another firecracker?
I wish.
Our old nanny wrote
a tell-all book about me.
Oh, no.
It's bad.
I just got the call
from a friend at little brown.
The publishing house?
No, the premier talent agency
For black dwarves.
Tracy, we need to start
doing damage control on this.
What does she reveal
in the book?
Everything. My addiction
to prescription glasses.
The fact that I suffer from
attention deficit disor--
Jack, your shoes are shiny.
And worst of all,
she revealed the fact
That I've never cheated
on my wife.
Okay, well,
that's not true.
Actually it is true.
Tracy shared that with me
last year.
What?
What about the strip clubs
And the disgusting stories?
Your ben & jerry's flavor
is called adulteraisin.
That's all for show.
I love my wife
and only her.
Okay, and how is that
a bad thing?
My wild and sexually
adventurous image
Is how I make my money,
Liz Lemon.
I start losing my endorsements,
Angie's gonna be madder
Than a bat in a suitcase.
Uh-oh.
Which reminds me.
Gordon. Gordon.
[bat squeaking]
Gordon!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
You have a problem
With the science
of hot tub time machine?
Not the time travel.
It's the hot tub.
You don't just turn one on,
and it's immediately hot.
I should know. I've been
in a hot tub two times.
Well, I don't question
everything.
Except for the snacks
I got for us.
Yeah.
Seltzer and Mike and ikes.
What did you want?
Popcorn?
Yes.
Popcorn? At the cinema?
And, by the way,
your food obsession
Is not as endearing
as you think it is.
It's like being
in a cathy cartoon
That just won't end.
Oh, my god,
I want to smash your face.
[laughter]
I don't think
we were meant to be together.
So why are you in my phone
as future husband,
and why am I in yours
as future wife?
I guess we'll never know.
At least we'll always have
Dr. Kaplan's recovery room.
It was our Paris.
huh...to bad we can't go back there.
Look at all these books, sir.
Feel like I'm back at school
learning about the dangers
of book readin.
This is all research on
Kabletown.
I'm trying to learn everything
I can about our future owners.
G.E. gave me the finest
education know to man.
I learned to develop
new products,
innovate new technologies.
We brought good things to life.
and bad things to Chinese Rivers.
G.E. is a great company.
Second only to the company
of great friends.
I thought I would workphone
at G.E. forever.
But my future opportunities
at the company died
With Don Geiss,
I have to accept that
And move on to
this exciting new challenge.
A friend of mine
has been worried
They'll be bringing in
new page rules.
Like age limits
and age verification.
Truth be told,
I haven't learned a lot
About Kabletown.
It's a whole different
business model.
My cousin in Atlanta
is a business model.
She holds up staplers
in catalogues.
But later today, I'm meeting
with an old colleague
Who left G.E. For Kabletown
five years ago.
I'm going to pick his brain
and learn how Kabletown works,s,
So I can prove
that I am the man
With the ambition,
the talent,
And the looking-at-my-watch
skills to run this company.
[gasps]
terrific, sir!
So all we need you to do
Is to put us under
anesthesia again.
Wesley brought his video camera.
In England,
we call it a film pod.
No.
And that way, afterward,
we can watch the tape
And figure out
what our connection was.
Would you ask a cardiologist
to do something like this?
I am a real doctor.
Yeah,
but a cardiologist is...
I know
what a cardiologist is.
My brother is a cardiologist,
and I'm just as good as he is.
We drive the same car.
So what if his wife
is more attractive?
But Dr. Kaplan,
this is for love.
It's like that brilliant film,
uh, Notting Hill.
I'm british and charming,
and she's...
Got certain angles
that work for her.
Really?
You think you found "the one"
In my recovery room.
Let me show you
what happens in there.
We are gonna hang out
so much after this.
I want to take you
to the big apple circus
'cause we're best friends.
I don't think
there was any connection.
It was just the anesthesia.
Well, liz, I wish you
all the best.
But future wife deleted.
It's a good idea.
And if my heart surgeon
brother is so great,
How come so many
of his patients have died,
But I've only killed
one guy, huh?
Say it ain't so,
tray.
What about the Seattle
Seahawks cheerleader?
That one
kind of thick rockette?
That blind woman
In the business class
bathroom on the acela?
Were those all lies too?
But, Frank, I still party.
I'm still terrible at my job.
I looked up to you.
Now I hate you.
Tracy, I know
what you're going through.
I got a lot of flack
After I ate the pig
that played babe.
I learned you have
to go on the offensive.
Start denying this stuff.
I did, j-mo.
I held a press conference
this morning.
I'm here to announce
that I'm leaving show business
To spend more time
with my stripper.
But it's like
a black barbie doll in Arizona.
Nobody's buying it.
Well, we lost
another one, tray.
I just got off the phone with
the people
From horny goat weed.
They're dropping you
as their spokesman.
But John Edwards and I
were supposed to ride
On their cinco de mayo float.
Yet another
black superstar
Taken down
by his personal life.
Just like my favorite golfer
OJ Simpson.
[laughs]
Remember how you tricked
the owner
Of that toaster company
into thinking
You were his dead son?
And he sold you the factory
for $1.
You are an animal.
Dave "the animal" hess.
I was only as good
as my mentor,
The man who taught me
how to bait the enemy,
Jack "the master baiter"
Donaghy.
So, dave, tell me
all about Kabletown.
What's their business strategy,
revenue streams?
Do they have a preferred side
of the head
For parting your hair,
because I've been continental
For years,
but I'm willing to go western.
Whoa, relax, buddy.
Your job is secure.
I just want to understand
the operation
So I can contribute
right away.
Well, that's the beauty
of it, Jack.
You don't have to.
The cable's already laid--
I don't understand.
There's always room for growth,
For innovation.
No, there really isn't.
It's brilliant.
And this is the goose
That lays the golden eggs--
Channels 500 through 600.
Oh, good god.
Ass-atar.
The lovely boners.
The hind side.
Fresh-ass: Based on the novel
"tush" by assfire.
It's all pay-per-view porn.
Do you know
how much of our profit
Comes from men
ordering adult movies?
91%.
They churn this stuff out,
People at home push a button,
And we make money
off it.
We don't do anything.
Then what do you want
with NBC?
Why do you even want me?
Well, buying NBC counts
as a charitable donation
For tax purposes.
And as for you,
You're the classic
american executive.
You will look great
Standing behind our ceo
at press conferences.
You are kidding me.
I went to Harvard
business school.
I'm the reason
the microwave tray rotates.
Jack.
I make things.
I build companies,
innovate products.
Don't fight it, Jack.
It's the perfect business.
The war is over,
and we won.
"and Alexander wept
For there were no more worlds
to conquer."
Hans Gruber, Die Hard.
Hey, I know
you're off-duty,
But is there any chance
you would take me
To the upper west side?
Okay.
Oh, good catch.
Thank you so much.
[tires screeching]
[crash]
ow.
[drivers argue
in foreign language]
Bloody hell!
No, no, no,
not again.
That's not him, is it?
Okay.
That was almost--
Gangway for footcycle!
[gasps]
Come on!
I said gangway for the...
[gasps]
you witch!
No, no,
I am walking away.
Wait, Liz, wait.
Look, I wasn't even supposed
To ride
my footcycle home today.
Stop calling it that.
Yeah, fine, my velocipede,
but I did ride it
Because the universe wanted me
to run into you again.
And I finally think
I know why.
Commencing
eye-roll sequence.
The universe wants us
to settle for one another.
Well, there has to be
a reason
This keeps happening
to us, Liz.
I think fate is telling us
This is the best
we're ever gonna get.
We're each other's
settling soul mates.
Settling soul mates?
That is grim.
And I've played
Monopoly alone.
Well, I know
it's not ideal,
But we'd both benefit.
I mean, I could open jars
and kill bugs for you,
And you could make me look
less gay at work functions.
Look, I happen
to believe in roma--
Don't even say
romantic love.
How many couples do you know
that are actually in love,
That don't completely annoy
one another?
Okay, what about them?
You wouldn't be complaining
If you wore the shoes
I bought you.
You're an old bitch.
Why fight this?
Grow old with me, Liz?
In separate bedrooms?
No way.
Have a nice life.
Think about it, Liz.
It's what the universe wants.
You'd have someone
to tell you
When you're about to step
in something.
Ah, nerds!
Okay, mentor time.
I need a pep talk.
Lemon, I'm not in the mood
to solve your lady problems
Or listen to a story
about whatever escapee
From the island of misfit toys
you're currently dating.
No, this is
a Liz relationship emergency.
It's a Liz-aster.
[sighs]
Okay, Lemon.
What is it?
[sighs] okay.
Ever since I was little...
No, faster than that.
My whole adult life...
No!
Oprah says...
You have ten seconds.
Okay, this guy Wesley
Thinks we should get married
Because it's time for us
to settle.
Now that's completely
and totally wrong because...
Is it?
Maybe you should settle.
Everybody settles.
What?
Look at me.
At one point,
my obituary was going to read,
"CEO of G.E. dies violently
in a casino orgy."
Now what's it going to say?
"middle manager
of a Philadelphia
Pornography distributor
never wakes up"?
What are you talking about?
Kabletown.
It's a mousetrap company.
And you cannot build
a better mousetrap.
Wait--Kabletown makes
mousetraps?
Kabletown
doesn't make anything.
Maybe it is
the perfect business.
A perpetual motion machine
endlessly satisfying
Every human need.
Soon you won't even have
to leave your house.
That sounds pretty good.
They don't need ideas,
They don't need innovation.
In other words,
they don't need me.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going to bury Don Geiss,
America, and hope.
[knock at door]
hey.
I saw some women came forward
to say
You didn't have sex
with them.
It's gotten worse.
Somebody leaked my voicemails.
Hey, baby,
it's your husband.
So I'm at Bed Bath & Beyond,
And I can't remember,
Did you say to get metal
or wood shower curtain rings?
Oh, you're calling me
on the other line.
I can't wait to talk to you.
I love you.
How does angie feel
about this? Is she mad?
She says I better have
an affair and quick
Before it tears
our family apart.
I wish I could help you,
But I can't sleep
with a black guy.
I'd lose my endorsement deal
with NASCAR.
That's the problem.
Who's desperate enough
to have sex with me
At this point?
Come on.
You're still Tracy Jordan.
There's got to be
some skank around here
Who's made it very clear
she wants you.
Go save your career
And give her
the thrill of a lifetime.
Hello, Elizabeth.
May I offer you
a succulent fruit?
What? No.
Why are you in here?
Let me do a dance for you,
my lover.
No.
No, this is wrong.
I can't have sex with you,
Liz Lemon.
I love angie too much.
Wow. Okay.
That was not gonna happen
for many reasons
Besides you loving your wife.
Reason one: I am conscious.
Reason two:
You smell like icy hot.
Reason three--
I'm sorry, L.L.
I know how much you wanted this
to happen.
I'm disappointed in me too.
If I can't have an affair,
Tracy Jordan is finished.
Stop it.
Just embrace the fact
That you are lucky enough
to be a happily married man.
I mean,
I'm actually jealous of you.
You've got stability,
a great marriage,
Devoted kids.
You know what I have?
A sims family
that keeps getting murdered.
So quit whining
and be grateful.
I am lucky.
Thanks, Liz Lemon.
You're welcome, Tray.
Hey, you know what, one day
you will have what I have
Because you're an amazing,
strong, and intelligent woman
Like Hilary...
From Fresh Prince of Bel-Air.
Thank you.
That's a very good pep talk.
Ugh!
I'm sorry.
I was still riding the vibe
from earlier.
[somber G.E. Jingle playing]
♪ ♪
Welcome, all,
to the memorial service/freezing
For Donald H. Geiss.
You were the last
of a dying breed, sir.
I'll never forget the first
thing he ever said to me.
"these are all hookers.
Pick one."
Then after we picked our hookers
and the plane took off,
He told me
his business philosophy.
There's always
an untapped market.
Don was the one who realized
there was a whole segment
Of consumers not buying
light bulbs.
The asleep.
That realization led him
to develop the nightlight
And the marketing campaign
aimed at making children
Afraid of the dark--
a monster under every bed.
Don said that no business
is ever done evolving.
But there are always
opportunities for innovation,
That you can always...
You can always find
new customers.
I'm sorry.
But I just had
an amazing business idea.
You'll have to excuse me.
[applause]
[ave maria]
♪ ♪
I know it's not my place yet
to call a meeting
Of Kabletown
senior vice presidents,
But I have something
I need to share with you.
Gentlemen, there is
a giant segment of consumers
Who are not buying
our most lucrative product.
Three words:
Porn for women.
Jack, women hate porn
Almost as much as men hate
going to outlet malls.
Yes, women hate porn.
Our porn.
But women do have
one insatiable need.
To jabber.
And it doesn't matter
if you have a headache,
Or you're not in the mood,
Or you're about to go
to Don Geiss's funeral,
They barge
right into your office
And start complaining
about a boyfriend
Or a coworker.
And you're supposed
to sit there and nod
And tell them they're right.
And the more you give it
to them, the more they want it.
I'll tell you, sometimes
my wife will be blathering on
About something,
and I'll think,
I'm more
than just a pair of ears.
You know, I'm a person
Who thinks about sex
every seven seconds.
Exactly.
So what if women had
a pay-per-view channel
Featuring handsome men
patiently listening to them?
What if they had...
Porn for women?
Okay, but where does
that content come from?
From us.
We make it.
Jack.
We don't make...
Hear me out.
Yes, I'm talking about
Doubling pay-per-view
profits
While cutting out the middle
man, but I'm also talking
About american businessmen doing
what they were born to do--
Make things.
We've stopped making
And become a country
of consumers.
Well, I, for one,
am done consuming.
And I'm ready to make.
Liz?
I don't believe it.
Hello, Wesley.
Don't you see this is
just gonna keep happening?
You can't fight the universe.
No, this isn't a coincidence.
I wanted to see you,
and I figured
You wouldn't miss a tasting
of the white wines of Scotland.
Most restaurants refuse
to serve them.
Oh, yeah, you've only told me
that, like, nine times.
So does this mean
you've come to your senses?
Are you ready to settle
and become Mrs. Snipes?
No. I wanted to tell you
to your face
That I know
that I can do better than you.
And I am never gonna be
Mrs. Snipes.
Hang on, is your name
Wesley Snipes?
That is insane!
No, it's insane
That the actor Wesley Snipes
has that name.
If you saw a picture of him
and a picture of me,
And you were asked, "who should
be named Wesley Snipes?"
You'd pick the pale englishman
every time.
Every time, Liz.
Frankly, you should be having
this conversation with him.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go do that.
I give you two months
before you give up
And decide to settle!
I'll see you in May!
For sweeps!
That's what we call
spring cleaning in England.
[groans]
[flipping channels]
Hello there.
Well, hello.
How was your day?
Do you need to talk?
'cause I'll just listen
patiently and say things like,
"uh-huh,"
"how annoying,"
"she's clearly
jealous of you,"
And "well, it's his loss."
You're a great woman.
You deserve a great man.
For just $24.95 an hour.
Yes, please.
It's the yellow button,
sweetie.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net