- Earl, can you break
some 20s?
The big spenders at table two
Wanna split their
$11 check three ways
Even though one person
did all the eating.
- I was in a three-way once.
Same thing happened.
- Max, table ten
would like the check.
And don't forget to pick up
customer comment card.
Customers very important.
It's all about the fans.
- Yeah, I'm not a fan of
hearing what people have to say.
For instance,
what's happening right now--
Not a fan.
- Max, feedback from customers
is very important business tool.
Perhaps we'll pump the brakes
on sour waitress attitude.
- There's only one tool
that can change my 'tude,
But I'm gonna need
two double-a batteries
And a 20-minute break.
- ¶ ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ¶
[cash register bell dings]
¶ ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ¶
- Welcome, everyone.
Thanks for coming
to very important
First official diner meeting.
- This ain't right, man.
2:00 a.M. Starts earl time.
- Earl, here's your brandy.
- Okay, we're good now.
- If I knew we were gonna have
staff meetings after work,
I would've taken job
at t.G.I. Friday instead.
Over there,
they roll fast and loose.
- Well, this is how I roll.
- Yeah, short and slow.
- No, I roll fast and furious.
Tokyo drift style.
- Han, I'm starting to drift.
Can we get to the point?
Max and I still have to get home
and bake cupcakes for tomorrow.
- We received so many excellent
comments from customers tonight.
Okay, first comment.
"dark-haired waitress..."
- hey!
- "was very rude.
- Hey!
- Max, customers are giving
Their honest opinions
about diner.
We need to take it seriously.
"i'd like to ride the blonde
waitress like a tilt-a-whirl."
- Shout out!
- Next comment.
"why does cashier
wear earphones?
I thought he was a dj."
Both: ¶ go, earl,
go, earl ¶
- Holla!
- Moving on.
"this meatloaf tastes stale
and dry."
Both: ¶ yeah, oleg
yeah, oleg ¶
- It also says that cook
could wear deodorant
And shirt that covers armpit.
- This is on card?
- Yes.
- You are lying.
- Remind me never to be a spy
with han.
- So this is how you tell me
what you think of me?
You hide behind outdated
method of feedback?
- What, I should've posted
twitpic of my face like this?
- Maybe I will send you
a twitpic of my meatloaf.
- Can you twits pick
another time to do this?
I've gotta go home.
- I have to go home too...
And cut the remaining sleeves
off of all my shirts.
And then go buy more shirts
And cut the sleeves
off those shirts.
- You must wear sleeves.
- Do not tell me what to do.
I was working here
when you were still a dumpling
On your father's chopstick.
- Now this is starting to sound
like earl time.
- Did it light?
- No.
Try another one.
The gas is on.
Ah!
- Why are we throwing fire
at an oven?
Is this a poor people game?
- Yeah, it's called light
the broken pilot light
Without
blowing our faces off!
- This is ridiculous.
My heart is pounding.
I didn't know baking cupcakes
was an extreme sport.
It's like the deadliest batch.
- See? A slight hint of gas
in the air
Makes everything funnier.
Now there's too much gas.
If we threw a math
in there now,
I'd be out a nose or a pair
or a pair of eyebrows
And I'm not living through
that again.
- Again?
- When I was a little girl,
I was trying to make
a hungry man dinner
And I lit the pilot light
too soon and whoosh!
No eyebrows.
Had to draw them on
in magic marker.
Only mexican girls
would talk to me.
- Max, we have
a cupcake business.
We have to tell the landlord
we need a new oven.
- We can't ask the landlord
for a new oven.
Then he'll ask us stuff like
"who are you?
"why is your name not
on the lease,
And where's the rent?"
- Well, I'll buy us one.
- Really? You're gonna buy us
a whole oven?
We're so poor I have a sock
that I refer to as my good sock.
- I've been saving something
for an emergency,
Like a burst appendix
or a first date bikini wax.
- I knew it!
You have a secret stash of
your father's missing billions.
We're rich!
Wait, it's other people's money.
Yeah, but I didn't steal it.
We're rich!
- They're my expensive rings.
- So if these are
your expensive rings,
What's all that other stuff
you wear?
- Cheaper copies.
You never wear the good stuff
out in public.
- Got it, kind of like
hiding the banana republic
And wearing the gap.
- See how special?
They're all one-of-a-kind
from thomas aristotle thomas.
T-a-t.
Tat.
- What?
- Tat rings.
You've never heard of tat rings?
- Oh! Tat rings.
No.
- I guess it's the kind of thing
That only people
in the know know, you know?
- No.
- Make all the jokes you want,
But I only have to sell
one of these
And I can get us a new oven.
Any ideas what kind
we should get?
- Uh, yeah, you're not the only
one with a secret stash.
It's the bluestar.
It's the tat rings of ovens.
In purple!
That's right, I said purple.
It's the muscle car of ovens.
It's bad-ass!
It's so bad-ass
when I do karaoke
I change the lyrics from
purple rain to purple range.
- Great, we'll get this one.
- Uh, we can't buy that.
It's too expensive.
This is just something
you fantasize about.
It's kitchen porn.
- Fine.
Tomorrow we'll go
to the cash for gold store
And get a regular oven
and get cookin'.
I think the funny gas is gone.
- Must be time.
I'm going in.
Let me do it, my eyebrows
need to waxed anyway.
- Hurry up! The gas is on!
Throw the match in!
- Did it light?
- No, but my foot is on fire.
I'll do it.
[both scream]
Both: You're good.
- I'm sorry, but how much longer
do we have to wait
To get cash for our gold?
- I told you before
I'm on the phone.
Sit down, shut up,
don't be rude.
- I thought she'd be nicer
from her picture
On the bus stop bench.
- Yeah, and where
are the dollar signs?
- Let me see, which ring
should I sell?
So much history in my lap.
- I don't even wanna tell you
about the history in my lap.
- My father got me this one
in london.
I got this one in paris
to reward myself
For not crying during
the turbulence
On the flight to paris.
- My mom got me a fresca when
she hit me with her car once.
- I got this one
when I was 18.
It was my very first tat.
- Okay, stop!
This was a bad idea.
Let's get out of here.
- I told you before.
I'm on the phone!
Sit down, shut up,
don't be rude.
- I'm only sitting down
because look.
She has her hand on a gun that's
strapped under the counter.
She is dying to plug us.
- Max, what are you
talking about?
Why is this a bad idea?
- I don't want you sacrificing
your precious rings, frodo.
Because if the business
doesn't work out,
It'll be my fault
you have nothing.
And call me selfish,
The only life I wanna ruin
is my own.
- Max, the business
will go up and down.
That's natural.
But this ring is about more than
the day to day of the business.
It's about us...
And our future together.
- Yo, did you just ask me
to marry you?
- You could do worse.
- Now, ladies, gold.
Now.
- Come on.
It's only one ring.
And when it comes to us,
I'm in this for the long haul.
- Or until this lady shoots us.
- Hi, I'm here to--
- come on! Let's go.
Don't push me
I'm out of nicorette.
- Well, you're all business,
aren't you?
I can respect that.
I'd like to exchange
a tat ring.
- I've never heard
of a tat ring.
- Thomas aristotle thomas?
World-famous designer?
- Yeah, talk down to me.
That'll make the price better.
All right, I'll weight it.
- What's that smell?
Is someone making soup
in the back?
- None of your business.
I will give you $275.
- It's worth $2,500.
- Where? In 2005?
- You're just taking advantage
of people
Because the world economy
is crashing.
- It's called cash for gold,
not sympathy for flat chicks.
- You know what?
This is inappropriate.
All right, I'd like to see
your business license.
Maybe I'll make a call
to the chamber of commerce.
- Oh, you will, huh?
- Duck! Here comes the gun!
- Maybe I'll make a call
to my boys in the back.
Sal! Richard!
- Oh, hello.
Let's get out of here.
- Are you sure? Because
I'm kinda feeling richard.
- Max, I was just
in the ladies' room
And I had a thought.
- Why am I doing my lipstick in
a mirror that says "die carlos""
- I know how to get
the full value of the ring.
We just have to take it to
the store where they sell it,
And return it.
- Uh, and why didn't that
occur to you before?
- 'cause I don't have
the receipt.
And I bought it
three years ago...
From another store...
In another country.
- The customer asked for crust
off of a turkey club.
- Did they say that
or is this something you say
That they said?
- They said it.
But I say I see "screw the bos""
sleeveless tee.
- I'm sorry,
someone call ripley's.
There is
a small mouse speaking.
- And I bet for sure
it comes with stinky armpits.
- Why don't you see
for yourself, ratatouille?
- I've gotta go.
Fight's starting.
- You are stinky.
So stinky my mother in korea
called me and said,
"what is that smell?"
- I am surprised you're upset
by man smell.
Most women like you
enjoy it.
- Yo, max,
I got 20 bucks on han.
He's scrappy.
- Your english is terrible.
- My english is less terrible
than your terrible english.
- What? I couldn't understand
a word you said.
- What? So sorry I couldn't
understand a word you said.
- Excuse me,
regular-sized people.
I am on break until
he apologizes.
- I think the round's over.
I couldn't understand
a word they said.
- He needs to apologize.
I'm the boss.
- Don't let him get to you,
han.
Every woman knows
size doesn't matter.
- I like your shirt.
Reminds me of the side of
the van I lost my virginity in.
- That little man
disrespect me.
He insult my food, my english,
my "hyjane."
- Is there anything I can do
to cheer you up?
- A hug would help.
- If I hug you,
will you go back to work?
- Yes.
- Two-second hug.
I'm going in.
- Aww.
- How did you do that?
Your hands never left my back.
- I am david blaine
of zippers.
- I was trying to cheer you up.
- You did.
- Wow, it's so surreal
being back here.
I grew up here.
It was like camp for me.
I learned who all the best
designers were,
How to color coordinate,
how to ride a bike.
- They let you
ride a bike here?
- Bitch, I owned this piece.
- If there's not
an iguana in here,
This place is stupid.
- Oh, my god.
They are such gorgeous
tat rings.
- Thanks!
- Hate you! So jealous!
- Bye!
- Seeing you in your natural
habitat is truly disturbing.
- Hi! Can I help you?
- Hi! I'd like to return
a ring I got as a present here.
- Tat rings are so amazing.
I can't believe you want
to return it.
- Well, this one's from a guy
I'm no longer with,
So it's painful
to even look at.
- I understand.
But I couldn't take it back
without a receipt.
- The thing is
he used to hit her.
- Max! You did not!
- Caroline,
it's not your fault.
- That's awful.
I understand why
you wouldn't want this ring.
I'm sure there's something
I can do.
It's not our fault.
I mean...Your fault.
- Caroline channing?
- Jeffrey!
- Surprised to see me
working here?
Well, I got fired from
that other store
Whose name I will never
mention again
After last year's
cigarette butt incident.
- I'm so sorry.
I had no idea those menthol
slim 100s were yours.
I just thought so many butts
on the ground
Outside the store was gross,
so I said something.
- Well, that one comment
from the great caroline channing
About those butts
fired my little butt.
You'd be happy to know
that I quite smoking
After you got me fired.
Couldn't afford it.
I also couldn't afford
my gym membership.
Which is why my fired little
butt got massive,
Why no one wanted to date me,
and why I spent gay pride alone.
Fortunately, I wound up
working here.
- Yeah, it all worked out.
Your butt looks tight.
- It's halfway there.
- So I got the price
on the ring.
- You're buying a ring?
A tat ring?
- Actually, I'm returning.
- Oh, can I see the receipt?
As manager
of the jewelry department,
I couldn't possibly return
a ring that you bought
At least three years ago
without a receipt.
You wouldn't want me to lose
my job again, would you?
I got this, donna.
And so sorry to hear about
your father being a criminal
And you being penniless
and all that ugliness.
But it is kinda karma.
You are where you are now,
and I'm back on top.
- Look, jeffrey,
I know we just met,
But there's no way
you're a top.
- Now what are we gonna do?
- We should hunt down that super
fake jealous lady
Who hates you.
Maybe she'll buy one.
- Max, that's brilliant.
If anybody's gonna
buy a tat ring,
They're already in the store.
We can have a pop-up sale!
- A pop-up sale?
- You don't know
what a pop-up sale is?
- You didn't know
what a pilot light was.
[elevator dings]
- it's the new trend.
Mini stores pop up
and sell stuff,
Then they're gone.
- That's not a new trend.
Drug dealers have been
doing that for years.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
- What are you doing,
beautiful mind?
- I'm mentally scanning
the layout of the store
For security cameras.
I knew coming here and not
going to parks as a child
Would pay off.
Okay, there's only one place
we could pull it off
Where there are no cameras.
- Where?
- Pop-up sale
in the ladies' room.
That's right, ma'am!
I said pop-up sale
in the ladies' room.
- I don't do improv.
[elevator dings]
So did we sell the ring yet?
Those women weren't our
target customers.
We're looking for
a very specific type.
Too much style
and money to burn.
- [speaking arabic]
hold the elevator!
[speaking arabic]
and I love new york!
Both: Pop-up sale
in the ladies' room.
- I'll take you in
two at a time.
Let me go check
with my associate
And I'll be right back
for adin and lublubah.
- Such a good memory.
- Hard to forget
such beautiful names.
Ready?
- We have a pooper
in stall two.
- Who shops and plops?
I mean, really.
- Trust me, I smell the match.
Classic shop and plop cover-up.
- Where are the two kit kats
we got from the vending machine?
- I told you I was hungry.
- Arabic women expect a gift
when they buy something.
- Well, stall number two
Will probably supply
a little present.
- Hi, are you here
for the pop-up sale?
- No, I just have to pee.
- Oh, geez.
Come on,
don't waste my time!
One stall's open--in and out!
Running a business!
- That woman pushed
ahead of us.
Do not sell her
my tat ring.
- It's fun.
You're here to pick up
She's here to drop off.
Open the shop.
We're a good team.
You set 'em up,
I knock 'em down.
- Why is [indistinct]?
- I don't know, it just is.
Are you here
for the pop-up sale?
- A pop-sale in the bathroom?
So lame.
- So lame.
Caroline?
- Jen, robin!
- Oh, my god.
- Oh, my god!
- Excuse me.
When will pop-up sale start?
We have lunch reservations for
five at four seasons at 3:00.
- Why are you asking me?
- You two are doing
pop-up sale, no?
- No.
I have nothing to do with this
pop-up sale in the bathroom.
- So lame.
- So lame!
- Come to lunch with us.
- Oh, I've already eaten.
- Our treat.
- We are not taking no
for an answer.
- They're not taking no
Sell the ring.
- Where is she going?
I thought you two were a team.
- Apparently not.
- So sorry.
I got caught up in a hostage
nicoise situation.
How'd it go?
Did you get full price
for the ring?
- Oh, do you know me?
Because I couldn't sworn
you didn't know me.
My new friends adin
and lablueballs
Thought it was weird
that you just bailed on me.
- Max, I panicked
in the moment.
I didn't want those girls
telling everyone
That caroline channing was in
a bathroom selling her jewelry.
I'm barely back on my feet
after the whole scandal.
I just couldn't bare it.
- Here.
I didn't sell them
because I didn't buy the whole
"in it for the long haul"
thing from the beginning.
And I was right
because I'm always right
About people
in the long haul.
- Max, I'm talking to you.
- It's cool.
We don't need to talk.
- Max, about the rings,
I'm sorry.
I don't know what else
to say.
- You don't need to say
anything.
You already said a lot of words
about the future and us,
And then next thing I know,
you were "oh, my god!"
Off to lunch
with your friends.
- Max, I am in this
for the long haul.
Isn't there anything I can say
to convince you of that?
- Nope.
And it's fine.
It's not you, it's me.
I'm the idiot who actually
believed for a minute
That we had a future.
But it's okay.
We'll just keep getting by
like we are, for the short haul.
Cool?
- Max.
Hey!
- Hey.
What's that smell?
- I'm making cupcakes.
- You lit the pilot light?
- Didn't have to. Look.
- No way!
The bluestar in purple?
What the--
how did it get--
How can--
how could you afford that?
You sold your tat?
- Sold them all.
Spent it on the oven, next-day
delivery fee and installation.
- That woman gave you
a better price?
- No, she pulled a gun on me.
So I went to every gold store
in brooklyn,
Leveraged their offers
against each other
Until I got enough to buy
the bluestar.
- You didn't have to do that.
- After what I did,
there were no more words.
Only ovens.
And our future means more to me
than rings from my past.
I told you, I'm in this
for the long haul.
For the record, I hated lunch
with those girls.
I'd rather split a kit kat
in a bathroom with you any day.
- I'm sorry
I wasn't listening.
I was staring at my new
boyfriend over there.
I wanna make out with it!
[giggling]
Ooh.
Ow! Hot!
[oven dings]
There's not a ding!
- There's a ding.
My rings bought a ding.
You wanna hug me, don't you?
- Yeah.
- But you're not gonna.
- Yes, I am.
If you unzip my shirt,
I'm gonna be pissed!
Impressed, but pissed.
www.tvsubtitles.net