hi.Wow.Good morning,indeed.
You just missed a fascinating
hour on megalithomania.
Oh.That's my favorite.
Um,actually,could I talk to you for a minute?
Well,yeah.For you,I have more than a minute.
Well,I don't know how to say this,except.
being with you last night reminded me
of how much it hurt when you dumped me.
Oh,I--I prefer to say,"broke up with.
" See,and I can't get
my heart broken again,ricky.
So it was fun.
- Nina.
- Hey.
You take care of yourself.Ok?
Nina.Come on.
Nina,come on.
Are you happy now,darling?
As if that's possible.
Honey,you want a glass of wine?
No,thanks.
Makes me sleepy.
Melinda,you can't stay awake forever.
And lookin' at these masks is
not doin' you any good right now.
I'm just trying to figure out which mask the guy's wearing
in one of my dreams or memories,whatever they are.
I know,but maybe you should take a break.
I don't know.
Uh,maybe help kate cross over.
Staying away from that one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Payne doesn't want my help.
He seems to think this is
his chance to get back at her,
and she doesn't wanna
go anywhere near a light,so.
yeah.I get it.
Mel,I'm worried about you.
You hardly get any sleep these days.
And when you do,your nightmares are getting worse.
The only way it's gonna stop is if I can figure out
who this mask guy is and what he's trying to tell me.
I'm pretty sure it has something to do with my father.
Well,do you think you should talk to a professional?
I don't need therapy.
No,I mean,do you think you should
talk to a private investigator?
Remember my cop friend,carl neely?
It's what he does.He moonlights.
I mean,he could tell you how your
dad died,when,where he's buried,even.
You want me to call him?
Ricky.
- Hi.
Hi.
What are you doin' here?
Uh,I'm sorry about the hour,but,
uh,it's just-- can I come in?
- Uh,no.
- No.
Um,I'll come out.
Look,uh,I-- I don't,uh,blame you.
I wouldn't really trust me either.
But you need to know this.
I had--well,I had my heart
broken,twice,as a matter of fact.
I mean,once when kate died,and then
another time after she was already dead,
I found out that she had an affair.
I'm sorry.I--I didn't know.
I'm much more sensitive to people's
hearts since my heart has been ripped out
and kicked around like a hacky sack.
And the fact of the matter is we
really had a good time last night.
Yeah,we did.I know--
'cause if you're in town for a week,
we should make a go of this thing,
I mean,go have lunch.What's lunch?
Nobody ever got hurt by a lunch,unless
of course there was a food-borne illness,
and-- why are we whispering,exactly?
You're not alone in there,are you?
No.
But it's not what you're thinking.
Mom,who you talkin' to?
Just a friend,baby.You go back to sleep,ok?
"Mom"?
I usually detonate that bomb on
the third or fourth date,but yes.
I have a son.
His name is elliot.
And since I would have to bring him
to lunch tomorrow,you can flee now.
No.No,I'm not fleeing.
Oh,no.
You-- you should bring him to lunch with us.
I love kids.What kind of a guy doesn't like kids?
I hate kids!
Maybe "hate" is a strong word,but
I have a profound lack of understanding
for the need to breed.
Plus,all kids are just filled with snot.
So it's a nonstarter for you.
I just think single moms are dicey.
None taken.
What?
I was just hopin' you'd throw a "no offense"
my way,but guess I gave you too much credit.
Oh,no,no,no,no,no.But your son ned,he's different.
He's a-- he's a teen or
tween or whatever they're called.
Teen'll do.
He's a teen.
And look,he's interacting.
Cyclical conversation.
He's fine.
He's self-sufficient.
Nina's son isn't going to be self-sufficient,and
he's gonna be a complete germ bag,for crying out loud.
Hey.You are a mom.
You could help me.
You--you can watch this kid while I go to lunch.
Oh,sorry,but I am taking my
son on a dicey single-mom lunch.
Let's go,ned.
- So what's the deal with that guy?
- You don't want to know.
Don't even look at me.
Hi,guys.
This is elliot.
El,it's professor payne.
Hello,young man.
How are you?
Hello,professor payne.
Please,call me,uh-- actually,
call me professor.That's good.
Hi.Elliot,I'm melinda.
Some people think dust is
mostly flakes from human skin.
Elliot.
A-actually dust is a lot of things.
Could be pet dander,pollen.
It could be soot.
Yeah,but its overall makeup
depends on where you live.
I think the human skin thing
was started to sell dust spray.
Are you an academician?
Oh,spare me.
Nobody but rick's that pretentious.
As a matter of fact,I am.
Why would you ask me that?
So's my dad.
You see,his,um,dad's
not really in the picture.
He's-- he's on an extended sabbatical in india.
They can't get text messages there.
Mind if i take a look at your victrola?
No.Go right ahead.
Uh,elliot,how old are you exactly?
Almost 10,sir.
That's a decade.
When's your birthday?
August 27.
I'm a virgo.
And we broke up in.
this isn't happening.
Maybe it's not what it seems.
Can I talk to you alone?
I just remembered we've got a,
uh,thing we're gonna be late for.
El,baby,come on.We gotta go.
Nice to meet you all.
Bye,guys.
there's no way I'm that kid's father,right?
Well,ignoring what she's
already told him about his dad,
the fact that he seems
to have your dna,math--
you're not helping.
You asked.
I know I asked.
You could always take a paternity test.
And confirm something
that I don't want to be true?
She hasn't exactly demanded one.
It's my own darn fault for chasing after her.
I--I didn't want kids when
I was married,let alone now.
Oh,neither do I,not yet anyway.
Why don't you want kids?
Do you mind me asking?
I do mind,actually,but I will answer.
It's your porch.
Kids are a huge responsibility,
and,uh,I'm selfish.
What's your excuse?
I'm afraid of juggling,you know,
the-- the feeding and the diapers
while dead people harass me.
You win.
I can't be a dad.
Look at me.I'm not father material.
I'm a miscreant of epic proportions.
Well,that's true.
All right.
Besides,we don't even know
if this is what nina wants.
Who knows what nina wants?
There's one way to find out.
I--you know what?
I hate talking to you.
I promote to a knight.
I found out I was pregnant after
you left,and I was so scared,ricky.
And I was gonna tell you,but you were.
already with kate,happy.
From the sounds of it,you've
all but told him I'm his dad.
No.I just kind of,you know,
dress it up a little.that way,
if he ever does find out,
it won't be such a shock to him.
Doesn't he have a right
to know who his father is?
It's complicated.
- Check.
- What again?
Oh,nice.
And he's mine.
He's brilliant.
He didn't get it from me.
Don't underestimate yourself.
I,uh-- I tried to enroll
him at archfield academy.
That's good.That's a good
school for pint-sized mensas.
Eh,it's not gonna happen
wait a minute.This kid could get into yale.
There's no way he didn't get accepted there.
Eh,he did.
It's just they-- they only
have 2 financial aid slots open.
He seems to be doin' ok at public school.
Public school?
Nina,no.
No,this kid's a genius.
You put him in public school,it's
like putting raw meat in a piranha tank.
They'll eat him alive.
You can't do that to him.
I don't sell enough
antidepressants to pay for it.
When kate died,I got a call
from my life insurance company.
Here's my wife of 8 years
dies in a freak accident.
Now they just wanna cut me a check.
I felt pretty awkward about it.
I didn't know what to do.
I never invested the money.
I just kept it in my savings account.
Bottom line is I'd like to use
that money to pay for elliot's school.
No.
Ricky,that's too generous.
Now,I didn't come here to ask you for money.
I didn't come here to ask you for anything.
I know that.
I'm pretty sure that's
what kate would have wanted.
You should move your pawn.
Don't count on it.
I don't need you to teach
me how to play chess,kid.
I'm just saying,if I were
you--I'd sacrifice my pawn.
Ah,he really is a chip
off the old payne,isn't he?
Alexander,you mind if I cut in?
This kid's too smart for me.
Well,don't blame it on him.
It's just his dna,I guess.
Unbelievable.
Do you mind if I finish his game?
Sure,professor,but you'll lose.
Whoa!
How 'bout you and i start from scratch?
Honey,I'm home.
Oh,how many times have I told you
about leavin' your shoes in the foyer,kate?
You know,kate,the scientist
in me is very intrigued,
but the human being in me has hair standing up in places
that I didn't even know that I had hair.
Come on,kate!
Is that the best you got?!
All right.
Getting better.
Oh,honey,that is such a textbook haunting.
A screw.
Are you tryin' to tell me something?
Ok,fine!
You wanna have this out!
Let's have it out right now!
You cheated on me with one of my colleagues!
So what right do you have to be mad at me?!
You think this is about infidelity?
What was that,honey?
I didn't quite hear you.
payne,where are you?
Here's something I never thought
I'd say-- I'm in here under the piano.
Oh,my.god
are you ok?
Well,not to be captain obvious,but not really.
There's an 800-pound baby grand on my back.
Can you feel anything?
Yes,jim,I can feel everything.
Thank you.
I'm gonna get the car jack.
I'm so sorry.
How's that?
Ahh.It only hurts when it hurts.
We're gonna have to get this x-rayed
and get you to the emergency room.
So you gonna tell me what happened?
Well,I was drunk.
I came home.
I decided to plow through my own
bookcase,swing from the chandelier,
and then me and the piano
rolled around on the floor-- all right.
I got in a fight with kate.
Yeah.She's obviously trying to tell you something.
Right.
It's like ghost charades with props.
You know,she seemed pretty upset
the day that you met elliot.
Is there something you're not telling me?
Well,kate wanted kids,and so did i
for a brief,brief moment of insanity,
and we tried everything,all the fertility drugs.
It was killing kate that nothing was working,
and I told her,"don't worry about it.
I don't even want kids," but you know the way i have
that great talent for saying things the wrong way.
It just--it got ugly.
Now you have one,a kid.
And she doesn'T.
That hurt?
Ah,compared to being under a piano,it's ok.
Do you think that's why she's
upset,because of elliot?
Well,I think it's only gonna
get worse until she crosses over.
Well,look,I don't speak ghost,
and I don't do humility very well.
Would you please talk to her,mediate,whatever?
Yes.
- Hey.Please?
- Ok.
Just stop baiting her.
I will not bait her anymore.
What's that look?
Nothing.
- Hey.
- How is he?
Lucky.
His foot's pretty banged up,but,uh,
hairline fracture of the tibia,
\and he broke his little toe.
He'll be fine.
Look,uh.
I heard you two talking about how
much payne's wife wanted a kid.
- And I hate to bring this up again,but
- I'm so sorry.
Could you just hold that thought?
I always do.
Maternity Ward
Nursery
Labor & Delivery
You could have killed him.
I lost my temper.
He has that effect on me.
And anyway,I thought he
could stand to suffer a little.
Hasn't he done that already?
I mean,it's been 3 years,kate.
It's time for you to let him move on.
The way he's let me move on?
He told me you wanted a baby.
Oh,I know what he told you.
I'm a ghost,darling.
I can go places,hear things.
It's the only upside to an otherwise lousy state.
I'm sorry.I really need your help.
I was here first.
Sorry.
That happens all the time.
Look,obviously you're upset that he has a child.
- Ok,it doesn't seem fair,and I get that.
- Do you?
She shows up here with this boy and plays her
sad little violin about needing money to
get him into some special school,
and he's all too ready to just write her a check
for my life insurance money,no less.
Seems a bit sketchy to me.
So you think she's playing him.
You're a clever girl.
Figure it out.
Hey,you.
What happened?
Broke my vestigial appendage.
- I'm fine,though.Can I talk to you?
- Yeah.
- Yeah,but just let me go first,ok?
- Ok.
All right.Um.
I thought about your offer to pay
for elliot's school,and.
I accept.
And then I--
I swear we'll go back to the city,
and you'll never hear from us again.
I've been thinkin' a lot about it,too,
and I don't wanna be a checkbook dad,nina.
So the offer's no good anymore?
No,the--the offer still stands.
I just wanna sw-sweeten the pot.
I-I've thought a lot about it,and that is,I-if I'm...
ok,if I'm going to be elliot's dad,
then I wanna be elliot's dad.
How would that work exactly?
Well,we could take it slow.
You don't have to tell him right away.
You guys can move in with me.
Oh,r-ricky,wait.Slow down.
No,uh,it's not-- you know.
I have lots of space,lots of space,
and you and I,we don't have to
be this instant couple right away.
We don't even have to be a couple at all,
even,you know,but,um,
there's a great satellite school that the
college offers for gifted children.
We could enroll elliot there and--
I just--I don't know.
I think I'm ready.
I'm really ready to be a dad.
At least,I'm ready to give it a try.
So,uh,how is this all goin' over at home?
Well,you can tell that jim wants to talk about it.
I keep sidestepping.
I mean,what's the big rush,right?
There's gotta be some huge compromise
somewhere between forever and right now.
Yeah,except for men pretty much have forever,
and women don'T.
I'm still young.
ish...Ok?There's plenty of time.
Besides,I have to cross kate over,
and I can't do that until I find out
if nina's telling the truth,
which means you should stop changing the subject.
You know,you could always get that P.I.
you hired to help you out.
And distract him from getting me
more information on my dad?
I don't think so.
You know what I really need to do is
just yank a hair right out of payne's head
and then do my own paternity test.
You know,as much fun as that sounds,
I have a simpler idea.
Ready?
Hello.Yes,
is principal stickley available for dean
julia marlowe from the archfield academy?
It's regarding elliot haley.
I'll hold.
This sleuthing stuff is kinda fun.
You're oddly good at it.
Yes.One moment,please,for dean marlow.
Hello.Principal stickley.
Yes,we did receive elliot's application,
but the birth certificate,though,
I-it was a fax of a fax,
and so you know how that goes.
We really need to get the father's name.
Pen.
Yes.
Thank you so much for your trouble.
Damn.
I think you're just beating yourself up
over an accident.
Your time here earthbound,
it's about your redemption.
You did that.
You made that sacrifice.
But is it that simple?
It is if you can see the light.
Yeah.
Yeah,it's-- it's on the other side of that car.
What do I do?
Go into it.
Sort things out on the other side.
- Another one.
- Yep.
Just a random ghost.
Sometimes I wish they'd just leave me alone.
Yeah,you and me both.
So what am I gonna do?
I mean,am I gonna talk to rick,am I gonna confront nina,
or am I gonna just move to canada?
You'll figure it out.You always do.
That was really helpful.Thanks.
You want my real opinion?
I feel like you should tell rick first.
Why?
'Cause you guys have so much in common,
I think he'll be relieved that the kid is not his.
So that's why you're being distant.
We've talked about this.
Yeah,I know.We've talked,and we've talked,
and,melinda,I gotta say sometimes
I feel like you use your gift as an excuse
and that you care more about the dead than--
that is not fair,ok?
I'm just not ready to have a baby.
I'm beginning to wonder if you ever will.
I mean,we've been married 3 years.
Yeah,and we're still young.
Yeah.
So were payne and kate.
Look what happened to them.
- I gotta go to work.
- Yep.
Let me know how it goes with carl.
Have to tell you up front,melinda,
your father left a pretty cold trail.
Since 1989?
Uh,'91,2 years after you said
he left you and your mother for good.
Drained his bank account.Cashed out his ira.
Went back to the woman in colorado he had a son with.
Gabriel,my half-brother.
Other than that,the only record I have of him
is workin' as a short-order cook at a debby's in arizona.
What?
I mean,my dad was a lawyer.
That doesn't make any sense.
It does if he was on the run from somethin'.
The run from what?
Melinda,when you first asked me to look into this,
you told me your father was dead.
You were pretty certain of that.
Yeah.I guess I have...
been telling myself that for so long
that I started to believe it.
There's no record of his death?
Not that I could find.
No burial.No cremation.
The list of john does in this country's huge,
and without dental records or dna,
it's a needle in a haystack.
Look,I have some other leads,but--heh.
I'm startin' to feel guilty takin' your money.
You found out more than I ever could.
Well,it's your call.
Just don't give up,please.
I really need to know.
So I guess the final question is just do
I make the check out to archfield academy,
or,I mean,I could make the check out to
the school that's here in grandview.
I'm not tryin' to force a decision.
I know.
I'm just gonna need to take some time
to think about it,so.
maybe if you just make the check out to me,
I can put it into elliot's school fund.
That way,I can prove I can afford
whichever school he applies to.
What are these,professor?
Those are my fetishes.
Ricky?
He's 10.
I know he's 10.
That's actually what they're called.
They're called fetishes.
They're carvings from an ancient
zuni tribe from new mexico.
They carve each animal,
and they think that there's a spirit inside them,
giving each one a very specific power.
Why don't you pick one up and give it a try?
Ah.The wily fox.
He keeps his owner safe.
What you do is you put his nostrils in your mouth--
Inhales And you inhale.
Go ahead.Give it a try.
No,thanks.It's still flu season.
Hi,everyone.
Hey.
Actually,I'm here to see nina.
- You are?\n- Yeah.
Who's brian dobbs?
Who?
He was on the birth certificate as the father.
- How did you f
- I made a phone call.
And I can make some more.Yeah.Do I need to?
- It's not what you think.
- It's exactly what I think.
The question is are you gonna tell payne,or am I?
Hey.
- Sorry I'm late.
- No.Right on time.
Technically I should have them stored in cornmeal.
That's what they eat,and the more they eat,
the better they are,and the more power they have.
Uh,nina said that is was ok for delia
to take elliot for some ice cream.
Ok.What's going on?
Come on.
We'll be in the cafeteria.
Brian dobbs?
The guy that used to hang out in the
laundry room of our building,brian dobbs?
Anyway,he was nice to me.
After you started hangin' out with kate,
I saw the writing on the wall.
So he took advantage of you.
After you left,I found out I was 3 months pregnant.
When I told brian,he demanded I take a paternity test.
Kind of backfired on him.
He hung around for about a year.
Then he split.
Then what happened?
Bastard stole my social security number.
All of a sudden,I've got all these--
these credit card bills piling up.
I find out he's drained my savings account,
and I haven't heard from him since.
He left me with a one-year-
old and buried under a mountain of debt,
and I've been killin' myself,
tryin' to pay it off for years,
and now it's gonna cost my son his school.
I've never done anything like this before.
Why me?
Why'd you start with me?
I just thought the rick payne I remembered would.
give me money to make the problem go away.
I never in a million years thought
you'd want to be in elliot's life.
So I'm sorry for what I did.
Mostly I'm sorry I underestimated you.
Well,you're not half as sorry as I am.
I think you should go.
Yeah.I think you should go.
Kate.
Are you here?'Cause he really wants to talk to you.
Spooky.Is that it?
I bet you feel really stupid now that
it turns out the kid isn't even mine,don't you,honey?
Ask him how he thinks it makes me feel to watch him,
a man who told me flat out he
didn't want to have children with me,
become completely and utterly destroyed
over some kid who wasn't even his to begin with.
She's a little angry at how upset you were
when you found out that elliot wasn't yours.
What's that got to do with us?
I'll tell you exactly what that's got to do with us,
you miserable little.
I will not repeat that,and,you,calm down.
Why?What happened?What did she say?
She's angry.
because she thinks you didn't want a baby with her.
Wow.She thinks I didn't wanna have kids with her?
Kate,I--that's not what I said at all.
- Yes,you did,repeatedly.
- And I never once made this about you or about me,
- and you wanna think that I'm selfish.
- "One more year.
We have so much time,and look what that got--" .
child,elliot,and you wanna think that you're suffering.
- I'm the one that's suffering.
- You have no idea how much.
You don't even know the damn truth!
All right,enough!
She started it.
I didn't get any of that,nor did I want to,
but I did hear you say something about him not knowing the truth.
When we were trying to...
when I thought he wanted children as much as I did.
we were doing in vitro,fertility injections,and.
were you gonna tell me,rick?
I need a little more here.
The dean called.
Your grant's been approved.
2 years in peru when we're
trying to get pregnant,
and you didn't tell me.
Move over.
Come on.
Look,I am nowhere near ready
to have a child now,ok?
But we've very young.
We have lots of time.We have
all the time in the world,so...
it's ok.
Professor payne.
Sure.
It's the fertility clinic.
I know all this.
They called.
They said her eggs were not viable,
and she accused me of being relieved.
We fought.Blah,blah,blah.
I lied.
The doctor said we were good to go.
That was my one chance to get pregnant,
but because I knew he didn't want it.
I lied.
Few weeks later,I was dead.
What is it?
She lied.
She lied to you because she thought
you didn't want children.
The doctor said it was a good time.
She thought it was her only chance.
I didn't know.
If she lied,why is she mad at me?
I'm angry because you knew I wanted children.
and you said you wanted that,too.
Then every time I brought it up,
you just pushed me away.
But that didn't make it stop.
Even now,it.
I know it's not possible,so why
does the ache only get worse?
It hurts so much.
How can you make that go away?
I can'T.
But you have to move on now.
I mean,you know that.
You know I can'T.
Kate,please don't go.
oh,my god.
What is it?
Well,kate told me about her death,
but listen to this old article.
"A construction crane plummeted 8 stories "
at a brookside office complex
late yesterday morning,
"crushing to death a motorist
who was making a u-turn,
"the victim later identified as katherine payne.
Payne died moments before her body was freed.
" That is awful.
How random.
Just making a u-turn.
Hi.
I'm sorry just to show up like this.
- No.No.
- No.
What's goin' on?
Go on.
I took this from professor payne.
My mom wants you to give it
back to him for me and.
tell him I'm sorry.
Look,I may not be the world's best role model,
but I'm trying to raise an honest kid here.
No.You know what?
maybe you should do this yourself in person.
Pretty sure ricky never wants to see me again.
I think you might be surprised.
Are you crazy?
I told you I never wanna see her again.
That's why I put you in a moving
car before I told you.
Why don't you just waterboard me instead?
Wait a minute.
This is where kate died.
I hate this place.
Why would you bring me here?
Trying to kill 2 birds with one ghost.Come on.
Well,thanks.
What is it?
The fox fetish is in there.
I took good care of him just like you said.
You took it from me without asking?
Yeah.
I'm...I'm sorry.
I just thought it'd keep my mom and me safe.
Ok.
I thought you'd be here.
Seems like I'm always here.
There's this constant pull.
I...it's because this is
where your time was cut short.
You know,I don't normally
reward thievery,young man,
but I'm gonna make an exception.
I want you to do me a favor,elliot.
I want you to take this box,
and I want you to keep it,
because that way,
you'll always know that somebody's lookin'
out for you and your mommy,ok?
- Damn him.
- All right.
Listen,go,uh...
why don't you go wait in the car or somethin'.
I have to talk to your mom,ok?
Thank you,professor.
Well,if I felt stupid before,
I really feel stupid now.
He really got accepted to archfield academy?
Yeah.
Yeah.That much is true.
That's good.
I'm proud of him,and I'm still paying for it.
You don't have to do that,ricky.
I know.That's why I'm doing it.
And for the record,after that first night,
I wasn't gonna go through with it,
but then you just surprised me.
And I started wishing it was true.
My grandma used to say,"wish again,
'cause you got bad luck on that last one.
There's another reason why
you keep getting dra here.
Wn I think it's what you're really mad about.
You wanted more time,and you were mad at him,
because he always promised
that there would be more.
It's not his fault.
Well,I don't have to guess who
you're talking to,do I?
Hello,kate.
Hi.
She says hi.
I don't want you to be mad at me,but I...
I can't stand the thought of that little
boy not getting what he needs,
whether he's my son or not.
She doesn't seem angry.
I'm sorry the guy I was
didn't wanna have kids.
It's 'cause I was selfish.
I just wanted you all for myself.
Think I needed to believe that
elliot was my son,because.
I don't have you anymore.
I'm sorry I didn't forgive you.
I forgive you.
But I couldn't before,because
I wasn't ready to let you go.
Oh,crap.
- You see it,don't you?
- Yeah.
It's magnificent.
Tell him I said I still love him.
and I think he'll make a
wonderful father someday.
I promise.
Good-bye,rick.
Tell him he should put his
ring in the sock drawer.
That way,when he opens it,
he'll think of me every now and again.
Hey,mel.I'm home.
You've got the.wedding china out.What's,uh...
what's the occasion?
Just celebrating life.
That's all.
Look,I'm sorry about today.
I...I'm not mad if that's
- what this is about.
- No.
It's not,not at all.I...
was just thinking about
what you said,and you're right.
I mean.
we never know what's gonna happen.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
Let's have a baby.
Uh,look,don't do this just for me.
- I'm...
- no.
It's for us.
Life is too short.
You know?What the hell are we waiting for?
Oh,god,I love you.
I love you.
Don't answer it.
Oh,no.It's carl.
I told him to come by.
- He wanted to
- ok.
- All right.I'm
-all right.
Look,I'm gonna go in the shower.
Hold this whole.
- hey.
- Hi.
Uh,look,I'm sorry.
This is it,everything
I could find on your father,
which isn't much.
Sorry I couldn't find more.
Are you ok?
Um,sorry.
It's chilly tonight.
Here.
What are these numbers?
I don't know.Must have pulled an old file folder.
It's not my handwriting.
Carl,I just saw you write them down.
I'm sorry,mel.I have no idea
what you're talkin' about.
Good night.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: Dylan
Proudly Presents
www.tvsubtitles.net