Previously on 24.
You have already been briefed
on the Cordilla Virus
that's now threatening our cities.
A vial of that virus has
already been release.
We discovered the identity of
the perpetrator.
His name is Stephen Saunders and
he is a former MI6 agent.
In 32 countries across the
Middle East and Asia,
your government employs
intelligence consultants.
Theyre spies.
In 45 minutes, I want a list of
their identities.
If you fail to comply,
I will release 2 vials of the
virus in major cities.
Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
A daughter?
We know she is 19 years old, she goes
to school in Santa Barbara.
I was just about to call the Santa
Barbara office to have her picked up.
Tony, thats not the right play.
If you want to grab her for questioning,
you are going to have to do it
without him knowing,
which means we have to conduct
a plain sight swap.
Switch her out with one of our own agents.
Ok, lets see her.
Kim, you are not going to fool anyone
who knows Jan Saunders up close
I know.
Clear
You think I am playing a game here with you?
Hundreds of thousands of peoples
lives are on the line.
You have no idea how far I am willing
to go to acquire your cooperation.
Where is your father, Jane?
I don't know.
Could you help me find something on this aisle?
Yeah, no problem.
Call for help and I will kill you right now.
Kim?
Damn it.
Saunders is going to know we have his daughter.
The following takes place
between 8:00 am and 9:00 am.
These are the quarantine zones
that were set up an hour ago.
Since then, 2 new symptomatic patients were discovered
at an ER in Silver Lake and one in Hancock Park.
Those 2 cases engendered 5 new quarantine areas.
Thats 3% of the city.
If containment isnt total,
it will grow exponentially.
All right, thanks Adam.
We are all tired, I know that.
And some of you have been working
for 24 hours straight.
I dont have to tell you how serious
the situation is,
but we can't drift.
If there ever was a worst case scenario, this is it.
We are in it.
Everyone has to stay on point.
We have switched from prevention to containment.
The virus is out.
You all right?
Yeah, I am fine.
I am sorry it had to go down like this.
The man I shot, is he dead?
Yeah.
What's going to happen now?
Saunders is going to know we have Jane.
This is Jack.
Jack, its Forrester.
The Saunders girl is calmed down.
You can try talking to her again.
Ok, thanks, Rachel.
We will see what we can get from the daughter.
I understand that, Tony.
So you'll tell him?
Yeah, I will tell him.
I want every precaution taken.
I'll get back to you.
Yeah.
What's going on with Jack Bauer?
The operation wasn't completely successful.
Now, David, they do have Saunders daughter,
but they were unable to remain covert.
So, Saunders knows we have her?
No, not yet, but CTU is estimating he
will find out within the hour.
What's Jacks plan?
Use Saunders daughter, try to locate him.
David, listen.
The deadline for his next demand is
gonna be up here in about 15 minutes.
Now, giving this guy a list of every foreign
operative on our payroll is an act of treason.
I know that.
But he will release more of the virus if we dont.
So what do you want to do?
I want to see what Bauer gets out of
Saunders daughter first.
You know what just happened?
A man who your father hired to protect
you just tried to kill one of my agents.
So, you killed him, right?
A man that worked for my father.
You are a smart girl, Jane.
Look out in that room.
Everyone here is a federal agent whose job i
t is to protect the lives of American citizens.
Jane, I know how hard it must be for you to believe
everything that everybodys been
telling you about your father.
But I am going to show you something
that will change your mind.
And the sooner you stop resisting me,
the sooner you can help us start saving lives.
Why are you putting all this on me?
Because you are Stephen Saunders daughter.
And unfortunately, you are the only
leverage we have against him.
You cant just say these outrageous
things and expect me to believe you.
I know.
Truth is, I know your father.
I worked with him.
He was a good man.
He was a brave man.
But something has happened to him.
All I care about right now is stopping
him from doing what he is doing.
I can't do that without you.
I need your help.
Palmer still hasn't sent the list yet.
He has 15 more minutes.
CTU has been trying to use IP locators
to get at your through the domain name.
We've protected it though, right?
Yes. It's a dead end
Good.
Thank you.
I am going to show you who your father really is.
These photographs were taken over 8 years ago.
Your father told your mother that he
was going to Europe on a fact finding mission.
But the truth of the matter is,
we were both part of a special forces unit
that was dispatched to Kosovo to
kill a man named Victor Drazen.
This is where the mission ended, Drazens hideout.
When I left Kosovo, I believed your
father had died in the blast.
The British government told your mother
that thats where he died, too.
But recently,
we discovered through phone records
that your father had contacted you 4 years ago
to tell you he was still alive.Is that right?
Yes
A couple of months after my mother died,
I get a call from him.
He said he was living in Europe
under an assumed name.
And that nobody knew he was alive.
And for his protection, I couldn't
tell anyone that I had spoken to him.
Did he ever tell you why he had contacted
you after so many years?
Yes.
He missed me.
I understand that.
Over the last 3 to 4 hours,
we have been pooling data from Interpol.
Here are some more recent images.
This is your father with Sayed Ali,
a known weapon dealer in the Middle East.
Here you see his meeting with Ari Consul,
a biologist from Jakarta
who is now spending the rest of his life in prison
for the manufacturing of illegal biological weapons.
This doesn't prove anything. He could have been
meeting with these people for any number of reasons.
I will play you an audio file, one of three
that we got from your father earlier today.
This is your father talking to the
President of the United States.
...Working against these countries at
the behest of the American military machine.
In 45 minutes, I want a list of their identities
sent to me by way of a website, sylviaimports.com
If you fail to comply, I will release
2 vials of the virus in major cities.
2 more vials of the virus.
He has already released one.
This is a live video feed from the
Chandler Plaza Hotel in Los Angeles,
where your father ordered the release of
one if the vials of the virus
into the ventilation system of the hotel.
The people that you are looking at will
all be dead within the next 2 to 3 hours.
There is almost 800 of them,jane
This is how they will die.
I don't want to see any more.
I don't want to see any more, either.
You can help us stop this, Jane, please.
Please.
I have a phone number.
He told me to call it day or night
if I ever got in trouble.
Have you ever used it before?
No.
We need it.
It's a mistake.
I am ok.
I don't have any infection.
No. Don't take me in there with those people.
I don't want to die.
Please.
Michelle, I just got a call.
Your lab results are on the way here.
I am sorry to interrupt, Mr. President.
What's this? Aaron?
Our bureau chief just informed me that
NHS believes Los Angeles is no longer safe.
We would like to move you out of the state.
I appreciate your concern.
Tell Chief Kurtzman,
I'd rather manage matters from here.
Sir, I am afraid this isn't a request.
Excuse me.
Secret service is invoking section 32.
For your own protection, we are requiring
you to accompany us to Air Force One.
You are ordering me?
Yes sir. It's for your safety.
Wayne?
I don't know the specifics of the code,
but secret service is invoking it.
And here in LA, the threat is serious.
It's serious everywhere.
At least here, we know what we are facing.
Who has to sign off on this, Aaron?
Chief Kurtzman and myself.
I'd like a word in private with you, Aaron.
Sir, I am sorry for appearing to overstep my bounds.
But it's my job to protect you.
Listen, Aaron.
You have been with me from the beginning.
You don't have to apologize for doing your job.
But this crisis will end.
And the people in this city and this country will be stronger,
knowing that their president stood by them shoulder to shoulder.
I am asking you as a friend and a fellow citizen
Protect me, but here in Los Angeles.
Can you do that for me?
Yes, sir. For you I can.
Thank you
Yes, sir.
Mr. President the conference call is about to begin.
Jack, you there?
Yeah, I am on.
Mr. President?
Mr. Almeida, I understand.
We may have a way to locate this man,
Stephen Saunders.
We do, sir. However, my technical staff just informed me that
to do this properly, it may take 15 minutes, possibly longer.
So there is no way we can get to
him in the next few minutes?
No, sir. There's not.
Ok, gentlemen, time is upon us.
Having considered all the possible scenarios,
I see no other choice than to draw our line in the sand.
I will not give in to Saunders' latest demand.
Mr. President, I hope you understand
that leaves us with only one option.
That's to use Stephen Saunders' daughter
as a hostage and hope that will stop him.
I understand.
All right, gentlemen, get to it.
Yes, sir.
David, are you sure we are doing the right thing?
The only thing I am sure of is we can't let
this country be taken over by this madman.
Jack, how do you want to do this?
How long do we have to keep him
on the line so we can run a trace?
About a minute.
Ok, we need to cover our bases.
We will use Jane to try and keep him on the line.
If we have to jump in, we will.
All right, look, I will initiate the trace.
You tell Jane what we need her to do.
I will get back to you.
Damn it.
What's happening?
We have run out of time.
We need you to call your father.
And tell him what?
Anything. We just want you to
keep him on the line.
For how long?
At least a minute.
Do you think you do that?
I need to think about it.
Jane, we don't have anymore time.
Your father just threatened to release more
of the virus in the next few minutes.
Is the list up, yet?
No.
Well, his time is up.
Yeah?
It's me.
Release San Francisco.
That's my daughter's line.
Ian, wait.
I will call you right back.
Find out where this is coming from.
Jane?
Yeah.
Hi, Dad.
What's wrong?
I told you only to use
this number in an emergency.
I want to see you. I am scared.
All the airports are shut down, and the news
channels are talking about the alert level being raised.
Just, just stay where you are, honey.
You'll be fine.
Someone is monitoring the call.
Hang on a second, honey.
Are you sure?
Yes
The signal is splitting.
They've got her.
Jack, we just got a hit on the trace route.
He knows we are on the phone.
What do I do when he gets back on?
Nothing. You are doing great.
Just keep talking.
Jane.
Yes, Dad.
There's a man named Jack Bauer
with you, isn't there?
What, Dad?
Hand the phone to him.
Dad
You heard me.
I am on the line, Stephen.
Jack, you know how many vials I have,
and what I am capable of.
And you know what I am capable of, too.
Did you get a lock on the signal?
It's dead. We are negative
for passive triangulation.
Tony, did you get him?
We are working on it, Adam?
I have got 2 microwaves that can give me a
longitude reading, but I don't have the latitude yet.
Here, try this.
Adam?
I am trying, Tony. I am working on it.
Ok, here it is: 21904 Collins.
We have got him, Jack.
We will send teams from here.
Ok. Patch the location through to the chopper.
We will be airborne in minutes.
Get me Chase.
We got a location. Tell the chopper to come in.
I want you to assemble the team.
Take Jane back to CTU.
I want her fully protected.
What are you going to do to my father?
I am going to stop him.
I want you to go with her.
Michelle
The test results, they just came in.
Thank you.
Almeida
Honey, it's me.
What's going on?
I am ok.
I am not infected.
Are you sure?
Yeah. They did AA swab and a
blood test and I am going to be fine.
I am going to be fine.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, sweetheart, that's fantastic.
Look, I want you to get out of there right now.
Ok? Away from anybody who's infected.
Oh, no, no, no, sweetheart.
They said those of us that didn't come down with
the infection, that we have an immunity to the virus.
Well, where are they taking you?
Downtown, to NHS.
They want to keep us under watch for 18 hours.
But they said it's just a formality.
All right, look. I will get
there as soon as I can, all right?
No, no.
Stay where you are. They need you at CTU.
I can work from downtown.
Honey, you don't have to work.
We can handle it from here.
I want to help, Tony.
Ok
Michelle
Yeah
I can't believe I almost lost you.
I almost lost you, too.
But we are still here.
Yeah.
I have to go.
I will call you from NHS.
Hey...
I love you
I love you so much.
Excuse me, everybody,
can I have your attention, please?
The President has asked you to this informal setting
without cameras or recording devices
to tell you what relationship, if any the outbreak at the Chandler Plaza Hotel has with the airport closures.
Was the Chandler Plaza the reason yellow level was raised?
The President will deal with that in his statement.
So Saunders knows we have his daughter.
Yeah.
Found out about 5 minutes ago.
How did he react?
He broke off communication.
The good news is, CTU has position of Saunders,
and they are sending in teams now.
What's our confidence level?
David, this man knows our system, our protocols.
He is going to be tough to corner.
Stay on top of our emergency response teams.
The abduction of his daughter
may have made things worse.
The President of United States.
Please be seated.
As you know, this morning our
alert level was raised to red.
We do have information regarding a
possible biological attack on American soil.
We have maximized our preparedness across the nation.
Now the best way for our citizens to
insure their own safety is to stay home.
If you are at work, go home.
That's the message I hope the media can convey.
Mr. President, we have heard reports that the local
British intelligence office was attacjed a couple hours ago.
Is that related?
I can't release any details on that right now.
I am sorry. Mr. President, the people of the
city of Los Angeles are starting to panic.
And information is not
following from this office.
We have had major outbreaks, we have had
quarantines, and now a hint of biological terror
Carol, Please
No. Gerry, no. The President has
got to be more forthcoming.
It's ok
The President has to be in control,
and so do you.
If you want to help the public and do your jobs best,
sit quietly and listen to what I have to say.
Biological agents do their worst damage
where large groups of people congregate.
The best defense we have right now is to encourage everyone
to go home and stay home and await further instructions.
Chase, it's Jack. Are you en route?
Yeah, I am a little more than 10 minutes out.
Jack, what are the chances Saunders
knows we have his location?
Not likely. Saunders will think he had 90 seconds more
of talk time before we could ever lock onto this location.
Look, I want you to move your teams into position
and remind local law enforcement to stay out of sight.
We can't tip him off.
Done.
Adam, I want you to keep an eye on the satellite, track anyone coming in and out
of that building, and feed all that information over to local law enforcement.
You copy?
I am watching the data now, Jack.
Ok, plug Chloe into it, too.
Yeah.
Listen, everybody, this is our time. Get it right.
Stephen, we have to leave.
We are not leaving.
Why not?
You said they probably have our location now.
Not probably. They do.
I don't understand.
They have got us on satellite.
They will pick us up if we try to leave now.
So we sit around here and
wait till they surround us?
Exactly.
The more bodies they send,
the easier it will be for us to disappear.
No. I am not waiting around to get caught.
Osterlind
I am leaving, Stephen.
Yeah.
Has she left, yet?
No.
She will.
Stay on her.
We are going to need to do this soon.
Ok
Where are we going?
Los Angeles.
I thought your father said
there was an outbreak there.
Where we are going,
it'll be safe. Don't worry.
Where in Los Angeles are they taking me?
A place called CTU.
CTU?
Yeah.
Counter Terrorist Unit.
I still can't believe this.
That my father is a terrorist.
4 years ago, when I found out
he was alive after all that time, I was so happy.
I had a father.
I let myself believe all that he wanted me to.
That he was this wonderful man.
How often did you see him?
Couple times a year.
Sometimes he'd surprise me.
And he'd always bring me something
And it was always perfect.
Like he knew.
Maybe he did know.
What do you mean?
He had people watching you, Jane.
He knew more about your life
than you are probably aware of.
What am I supposed to do with
all these feeling for him?
The person I love doesn't even exist.
What's going to happen to him?
My dad's going to try and bring him in.
Adam, it's Jack.
What's the status of Saunders' location?
I am watching it now, Jack.
No one's left the building.
Who's working with us?
LAPD has set up a staging
area about a block away.
They have surrounded the area
and are hidden from view.
Ok, good work.
Tell them I will be there in a few minutes.
All right.
Yeah.
You're absolutely sure.
Thank you very much.
Tony, I need to talk to you.
Yeah, just a second.
Why don't you go ahead and put
these simulations on my system.
I need to talk to you right now.
I will catch up. Go ahead.
What's it?
I have been working on the tented
quarantine area, you know.
And?
I have been going over the list of people who
have been isolated and I found a familiar name.
And?
One of them was Sarah Kaufman.
Who is Sarah Kaufman?
Adam's sister.
You are sure it's Adam's sister?
Yeah. She tested positive in the medical sense.
She's going to die.
All right, thanks.
You are not going to tell him, are you?
Yeah, I have to.
But we still have a lot of work to do.
I mean, how can he concentrate knowing
that his sister gonna die in a couple hours?
Did you ever think about that?
Chloe, I am getting real tired of your personality.
I am just trying to help.
You want to help? Get back to work.
Adam, could you come with me a second?
I am sitting on these satellite
feeds for Jack right now.Can it wait?
No, it can't.
Chloe will watch it.
Fine. What is it?
Tony, I really have to stay on this.
It's personal. Just come with me.
Tony, whatever it is, just tell me.
Did I do anything wrong?
No.
I am afraid I have some bad news for you.
Your sister, Sarah,
is in one of the quarantine zones.
What?
You have a sister named Sarah, right?
Yeah.
But how can they be sure that it's her?
There have to a hundred Sarah Kaufman.in Los Angeles.
Chloe confirmed it.
Have they kept her away from
the people that are infected?
She's infected.
What are you saying, Tony?
Are you telling me that
Sarah's going to die?
It looks that way, yeah.
I am sorry.
Oh, my god.
Adam, I am going to give you a chance to talk to your sister, but
then I am going to need you to stay on until the crisis passes.
You think you can do that?
Adam
Because we need you here.
Yeah.
All right.
No, I am completely surrounded.
How do you know?
There was a security guard across the
street making his rounds every 15 minutes.
He missed his last rotation,
which means CTU has taken over that building.
What are you going to do?
I am going to wait until Bauer gets here.
Baker and his team are running
operations from behind the building.
They will move when we tell them to.
LAPD set up a perimeter here,
here, here and here.
We got SWAT teams moving in
this way and from over here.
Snipers on the roof.
Nobody goes until we give the word.
Understand?
What's the situation?
We have taken over building on either side of him.
We got snipers on the roof, ready to go.
Phones?
We didn't jam the area.You said he'd know.
What about infrared?
We can't get through those walls, Jack.
He knows we are here.
What makes you say that?
Because I would.
You think he's still in there?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't he try to escape?
I don't know
All right, on my signal move
your teams into position.
Minimum 3 men per exit.
Remember, no one goes into the
builder till I give the order.
We have to assume Saunders
has taken defensive measures.
Everybody ready?
Let's go
All team move into first position.
This is a go.
Repeat, this is a go.
- positions all set
- Let's go
Stephen Saunders
This is Jack Bauer.
You are completely surrounded.
The President is refusing to
capitulate to any further demands.
I need to remind you that we
still have your daughter.
Stephen.
It's over.
The only way you are getting out of this thing alive is
coming through the front door with your hands on your head.
That's not exactly true, Jack.
Adam
Not now, Chloe. I am running
comm on the Saunders pickup.
I know what you are doing
Robin, take over Adam's screen
for a minute. Come here.
Why? Chloe, this is really not a good time.
Tony, I need you to hear this.
What?
I have to report some bad news.
Field ops lost 2 satellite feeds
because Adam forgot to segregate the channels.
What are you talking about?
It's true. I checked your system.
I had to reinitiate everything.
You touched my system?
Tony, let's face it.
Adam shouldn't be here.
He's under duress because
his sister's going to die.
I did not forget to separate
those channels, Tony
Yes, you did.
All right, look,
we don't have time for this.
We have teams on the ground
that are depending on us.
Did you back up the satellite data?
Yes. I reprogrammed almost everything.
We lost about 30 seconds.
We didn't lose it, Chloe.
I can prove it to you right now.
I thought that I ¡­
Chloe is right.
I forgot to separate them.
All right, look.
You made a mistake.
But what I need to know is if can you get through
the rest of the day without making another one.
Adam?
I'm fine, Tony.
Ok
I want you to know that I don't
agree with Tony's decision.
But since you are going to stay, I am going to double
check your logs every 10 minutes in case you screw up again.
Jack, what do you want to do?
If he's not in there, we are wasting
a lot of time we don't have.
Just have the men maintain their position.
This is Bauer
Congratulations, Jack
You found me.
Stephen, it's over. Come on out.
It would suit me better if you
came in here and got me.
I'd hate to be in the crosshairs
of all those unstable CTU snipers.
Come out the front door with
your hands on your head.
I assure you, you'll be fine.
11 more vials, millions dead.
That doesn't affect your nerves a little bit?
The President has made himself clear.
He's not following orders from you anymore.
I work for him.
Well, if that's the case, you won't
mind if I take a few minutes to think things over.
While you are thinking things over, you might want
to take a second and think about your daughter.
Tony just confirmed that he's in the building.
All teams hold your position.
We got confirmation.
Is it done?
Yes
All right. Stay on the line.
Almeida.
Listen to me very carefully, Agent Almeida.
Who's this?
It's Stephen Saunders.
Before you make any tactical errors,
I'd like to give you an update on the situation.
I'm listening.
I need you to move to a private area
that has direct comm. with your teams on site here.
And why would I do that?
Open a web socket to ip 257.211.16.5,
and you will find out.
That's ip 257.211.16.5
Just trust me.
Do it.
By the way, Tony. I'd like to offer you congratulations
on your wife eluding infection from the virus.
How do you know about my wife?
Get on that site.
I don't know exactly what
they are doing to her, Tony.
But I did instruct them to leave her
barely functional so that we can return her to you.
I'll kill you, son of a bitch
I will rip your dam throat out.
You hear me?
I am low on time, so I am sorry
if I brush past that remark.
Because in 15 seconds, Michelle will
be dead if you don't do what I say.
There are 5 agents watching the
northeast exit of this building.
4 on the ground, a sniper on
the rooftop next door.
I am assuming they are operating
as a single unit.
I want you to give them a code 9,
send them to the front entrance.
Now.
Jack Bauer's running the operation.
I don't have the authority to do that.
No authority?
Really?
Kevin, is Michelle still conscious?
Yes
Take an eye out.
No, wait, stop
Kevin, hold for a second.
It's gonna take me some time.
You have 30 seconds.
Gerry, we are talking about mass
hysteria spreading out all over the place.
Now, we are not in any position to mobilize¡­
It doesn't matter.
Our position is to let the public
know what is going on.
This is Baker.
This is Tony Almeida.
Switch to channel 3
Go ahead
We need you to code 9 your team
I want you to use a controlled
channel in case Saunders is listening.
What are we doing?
Move everyone to the front now.
I have been monitoring all channels.
There's nothing going on in front.
We just got a new SAT feed that
Jack doesn't have yet.
Looks like Saunders is on the move in a blind spot.
Get there now.
Roger that. 4 CTU personnel
diverting to new mark.
No, Baker. Negative.
No, not just CTU personnel, everyone.
Police control included. Get there now.
Unit 4, we have a code 9.Repeat, code 9
Everyone to the front of the building now.
Get in your car, move to
the front of the building
Down, down
www.tvsubtitles.net