Previously on 24.
Tony, its me. We have a problem.
We just determined a man who was
exposed to the virus got out of the hotel
Son of a bitch. Howd that happen?
He must have slipped out right
before we reinforced the perimeter.
Its likely he had no idea had been exposed.
If we dont find this guy before he becomes
symptomatic, we might be looking at an outbreak.
What do you want?
To give you your next assignment.
There is a man named Ryan Chappelle,
regional director of CTU.
I want him killed.
This man Saunders has proven that
he will use this virus
to inflict mass casualties if you
dont do what he says.
How long am I supposed to let
him hold this country hostage?
Until we catch him.
Saunders called in with another demand.
What does he want now?
He wants you killed.
Hes threatened to release the virus into the main
population unless we deliver your body by 7:00 a.m.
My god, jack
He has proven he will use the virus.
The president didn't have a choice.
Ryan, I think we found Saunders.
45 minutes ago he made a call from an
apartment not far from here.
Chase is leading a strike
team over there now.
Good, Jack.
No one is here.
Saunders, why are you doing this?
Even if I told you,
you wouldnt understand.
A van will be arriving shortly.
Leave Chappelles body with the driver.
I am sorry, Ryan, we got to do this.
Get on your knees.
I am sorry we let you down, Ryan.
God forgive me.
The following takes place
between 7:00 am and 8:00 am.
He is clean. There is no tracker.
If you try to follow us,
Saunders will release the virus.
Wayne Palmer.
This is Jack Bauer
Chappelles body has just been
picked up by Saunders' people.
Thanks Jack.
Ryan Chappelle is dead
I ordered the death of one of
our agents, one of our finest.
As unthinkable as that was,
I had to buy some time in order
to protect civilian lives.
I will not cave in to any more
of this terrorists demands.
David, unfortunately we are vulnerable as long as
Saunders has his virus and is willing to release it.
So far, over 700 people have been
infected, and they're all gonna die.
Now, unless you are willing to accept more
loss of life, I dont know what else we can do.
He has us in a corner, David.
Convene the Cabinet.
Yes sir.
What did you find?
We worked up the money trails
that Chappelle had on his system.
Stephen Saunders has been sending
$10000 a month to his daughter Jane.
He has a daughter?
Yes. Right here on the screen.
She is 19, she lives in Santa Barbara.
She goes to school there.
All right, find out where she is now.
Call Santa Barbara PD (Police Department),
make sure they are on standby.
Almeida.
Tony, its Jack.
Jack, what happened?
Chappelle is dead.
Saunders people picked up his body.
4 men all wearing hoods,
black van, no plates.
All right, look,
I will see if we can SAT track it.
I already put Adam on it.
Do we have any idea why
Saunders wanted Chappelle dead yet?
I was just about to call you.
We found a thread that Chappelle
was working up on his own.
Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
A daughter?
Yeah, the money trail Chappelle
was following leads to a Jane Saunders.
What do we know about her?
We are still digging up information.
We know she is 19 years old,
she goes to school in Santa Barbara.
Is she still there?
Yeah. I was just about to call the Santa
Barbara office to have her picked up.
Wait, Tony, Tony, dont.
Thats not the right play.
Why not?
Think about it.
We dont know anything about this girl.
We dont know if she even
knows who her father really is.
And obviously Saunders is going to
everything he can to protect his daughter.
So someone is watching her.
If you want to grab her for questioning,
you are going to have to do
it without him knowing.
Which means we have to conduct a plain sight
swap, switch her out with one of our own agents.
Jack, I dont know that we have the time.
We are going to have to find an agent that
looks like the girl within the next half hour.
Right now Saunders is calling all the shots.
If we dont do something soon,
we are going to be completely paralyzed.
All right, I will get started.
Chloe, we need to find a
Jan Saunders look alike.
I need you to abstract a physical description cross
referencing with our CTU agents in regions 2 and 3.
Ok, when do you need it?
Right now.
I just started the file on her.
Chloe, just do it for me, please.
Dessler.
Hey, its me.
Did you get the test results?
I wont know if I am infected
for another hour.
Whats taking so long?
They couldnt interpret the result here.
They had to send everything back to the lab.
How are you feeling?
I am, I think I am ok.
No nose bleeds?
Nothing on your skin?
No.
Look, NHS has everything under control here.
I want to keep busy.
How can I help?
Adam is working on a citywide containment.
I will have him split off some
of his workload on your system.
Open a socket, you can help
with NHS deployment.
I will call you later, ok?
Yeah, ok.
Michelle is still at the hotel.
I just told her youd send over some of
your system updates for her to work on.
Ok, I will send them right over.
Where are we on this guy who
escaped from the hotel?
His name is Bill Cole, he is
an insurance sales rep.
We contacted his wife by phone,
but she wasnt being very cooperative.
We did manage to get from her that Cole
came home unusually late and left early.
For work?
Probably, but his office
doesnt open for another half hour,
so we are looking for him now.
NHS has just arrived and they will
quarantine the house and test the wife.
Who are we sending over there?
Chase. He will be there soon.
Agent Bauer,
I have the President for you.
Patch him through.
Jack
Mr. President
Stephen Saunders, the man who is in
control of the virus, you know him, correct?
Yes sir. I worked with him a number of
years ago on a mission that you sanctioned.
The Drazen mission in Kosovo.
The last conversation I had with him,
he said there would be other demands.
His exact words: the main event to come.
You have any idea what he means by that?
I wish I could tell you, sir.
Right now Stephen Saunders is
in a vengeful state of mind.
Any demands that he makes will
be detrimental to American security.
What I am asking, Jack,
is what will he do if I say no to him?
Mr. President, when I worked with Stephen Saunders,
I never thought he was capable of mass murder.
Today we know he is.
He still has the virus.
If you dont meet his demands, sir, I
believe that he will continue to release it.
Thank you, Jack.
Yes, Mr. President.
Here is the list you wanted of the top ten
agents that could double as Jane Saunders.
None of these are in Los Angeles.
I know. The closest is CTU San Francisco.
Did you put together a 2nd tier list?
Yeah.
You sure this is right?
Yeah, I double checked when
I saw the results.
Kim Bauer.
Yeah, Kim, could you come up
to my office, please
Sure.
Thanks.
You are not thinking of using her?
We dont have a choice.
Shouldnt you talk to Jack first?
Chloe, I will take care of it,
all right? Thank you.
Why dont you sit down.
Ok.
Kim, we need to question Jane Saunders
without her father knowing about it.
The problem is, we are pretty
sure he has somebody watching her.
Fine. What do you need me to do?
Well, you are the same age,
similar body types,
your facial fertures are different, but no so
different that we couldnt disguise it from a distance.
You want me to pose as Jan Saunders.
Well, we have better matches, but
they are too far away from this office.
So, the bottom line is,
you are our best chance.
Now, we dont have much time.
We are still in the early
stages of planning this mission,
but if all goes according to plan,
it shouldnt be too dangerous.
No, I am not going to
order you to do this.
I know, and I know whats
been going on today.
And if you had a better option,
I know youd take it
So, I am fine and I will do it.
You sure?
Positive
Chloe, I am leaving for
Santa Barbara in a few minutes,
so you are going to need to transfer
all my stuff onto your system.
I know everything thats happening,
I already pulled your data.
Good.
I think its only fair that I tell you.
I told Tony I didnt think you should do this.
Field work isnt learn as you go.
I am not doing this to be a field agent,
Chloe, there is no one else.
Yeah, thats why I didnt fight Tony harder.
Not that he would listen to me anyway.
I am not so out of it that I dont know he
doesnt respect my opinions on tactical matters.
Ok, look, I have to go.
Ok, I just wanted to let you know how I felt,
and I want you to know that I am behind 110%
I really hope nothing bad happens to you.
Listen, Chloe, are you coordinating
this operation from inside?
Of course.
Ok, maybe you should start prepping, because I bet there
is about 2 dozen agents still waiting for comm. Codes.
I like your energy, Kim. Use it.
Adam, could you send me a list of all the
personnel working on the Jan Saunders operation?
I cant do it right now, Chloe,
I am monitoring Chase.
Did he find Bill Cole?
Not yet, he is interrogating Coles wife.
This thing is out of control.
I already told the people on
the phone that Bill isnt here.
I know, I know,
but when he was here,
did you notice anything
out of the ordinary?
Was he bleeding from
the nose for instance?
No, not that I saw.
What about rashes, skin irritation,
anything of that sort?
No. Why would you think that hed be sick?
He came in contact with some people who
are sick at the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
When was he at the Chandler Plaza?
Earlier this morning.
No, no, he wasnt.
He was with a client at the office.
He did it again, didnt he?
That bastard did it again.
Maam
Then I hope he did get something.
I hope that he dies.
Please, Mrs. Cole, I need you
Get out of here. Get out of my way.
Mrs. Cole
Get out of my way
Mrs. Cole, you need to stay calm,
because I cant let you leave.
Agent Edmunds
Yeah
One of my men just found this.
Where?
Wastebasket in the bathroom.
Blood is tacky, which means its fresh.
Then Bill Cole is symptomatic.
Yeah.
I need you to contact every urgent
care facility in a 30 mile radius.
Yes sir.
Excuse me.
I have had a nose bleed
for about an hour.
I cant seem to stop it.
Did you put ice on it?
Yeah. Didnt do anything.
Try an ER, get it cauterized.
That will take too long.
I got to go to work.
We dont have anything here
that will stop that.
All right. Thanks.
Excuse me.
The swap will take place at
the campus library.
She works there in the mornings.
This is a file of
relevant personal data.
All right.
Chloe, where is Tony?
He is in the teleconference
room with Kim.
Why isn¡¯t she working the
satellite track with you?
Uh, you might want to
talk to Tony about that.
When you get into the position,
just act naturally
Try to look up a place.
Hey, Jack.
What are you doing with Kim?
Chloe came over a list of
potential matches for Jan Sanders.
Good, so we have got one?
Well, you are not going to like it.
It¡¯s Kim.
My Kim?
I am not crazy about it either,
but she is the only one that matched
both physically and geographically.
You are not sending her into the field.
She can handle it,
plus she has a safety net.
Find someone else, Tony.
Jack, you said yourself, we need to get
Saunder¡¯s daughter without him knowing.
Kim is our best shot at doing that.
She is not doing it.
It¡¯s not up to you, it¡¯s her decision.
Fine.
I will order her not to do it.
She doesn¡¯t work for you, Jack
She works for me
Don¡¯t...
Dad
Get out of here.
Please don¡¯t do this, please
Get out of here now.
Or I will throw you out myself. Move
Jack
You talk it over with your father.
If we have to abort this,
I want to know now.
I will be outside.
I know you think you are doing the right
thing, but this is not going to happen.
Somebody has to do it.
Someone will, not you
I am the best match
You are not a field operative
I have weapons training.
This is decoy work.
Saunders¡¯ people won¡¯t
even come close to me.
Kim, you don¡¯t know what
you are talking about.
If everything was to go right in this scenario,
which is not a chance I am willing to take
You are not taking it, I am
The reason why you have got this job,
the reason why I gave you this job is
so that I an make sure you¡¯d be safe.
I took this job because I wanted it,
not because you wanted me here.
I know that this is hard for you,
but this is not your decision.
This is my job, better yet, my duty.
I am going to be safe,
but I am doing it.
They are ready to go
All set
Ok, now as soon as we get there, they are
going to deal with your hair and makeup.
Remember, we are not trying to
fool anyone at close range.
You will be in a position where Saunders¡¯
people can only view you from a distance.
Yeah.
Is your comm.
unit getting a clear signal?
Oh, it¡¯s fine.
Kim
Yeah?
This is a gun I got for you.
I don¡¯t think you are
going to have to use it,
but if you do, don¡¯t hesitate.
Ok
Come on, let¡¯s go
Please be seated.
Thank you for assembling
on short notice.
You have already been briefed on the Cordilla
Virus that¡¯s now threatening our cities.
What you don¡¯t know is
we have 2 new developments.
Wayne.
First, a vial of that virus
has already been release.
The Chandler Plaza Hotel, here in Los
Angeles, was the site of the first attack.
That situation is being addressed.
Secondly, we discovered
the identity of the perpetrator.
His name is Stephen Saunders
and he is a former MI6 agent.
Now, apparently, Mr. Saunders has at least 11 more vials and
is threatening to release them unless we meet his demands.
Mr. President, what are those demands?
So far there have been 2.
The first was for the President to use the phrase
¡°the sky is falling¡± in a press conference.
He then demanded that we
terminate one of our own agents.
One of our agents? Why?
Well, we are still looking into that.
What was his response
when you didn¡¯t comply?
It devastates me to tell you
that I had no choice but to comply.
A half hour ago,
we delivered this agent¡¯s body
to one of Saunders¡¯ representatives.
My God.
Millions of lives are at stake.
I am going to need each of your departments
to open your files to CTU Los Angeles.
Give them whatever they need.
Tony, I am trying to get into some DOD files
for Jack, I need authorization from Cahppelle.
When is he going to be back?
He is not.
What do you mean?
Could I have everybody¡¯s
attention, please?
I am sorry to tell you that,
Ryan Chappelle was killed in the
line of duty about a half an hour ago.
I can¡¯t give you any more details,
but I will be assuming Ryan¡¯s responsibilities
until we hear from Brad Hammond at division.
Now, there will be an opportunity
to pay proper respects to Ryan,
but now is not the time.
Tony, it¡¯s Chase on line 5.
Thanks
Almeida.
Yeah, it¡¯s me.
I am at Cole¡¯s house.
We found evidence he is almost
certainly symptomatic.
All right, how many people did
he come in contact with over there?
Just his wife.
NHS is moving her into
isolation right now.
All right,
I will let the teams know.
Tony, transfer me to Kim.
She was running a simulation for me.
Yeah, I gave that to Adam.
Kim is out on assignment right now.
What kind of assignment?
Well, we are pretty sure that Saunders
has his daughter under surveillance,
so Kim is gonna take her
place when we grab her.
Kim is not a field ops
What the hell is she doing out there
I don¡¯t want to hear
about it, chase, all right?
Kim was the only match
we had available.
Tony, there is got to be other
agents you can use for this.
What the hell are you thinking?
No, there aren¡¯t
Back off, Chase
Where is she now?
She is on her way to
Santa Barbara with Jack.
Jack signed off on this?
First of all, it¡¯s my call.
Secondly, yes, Jack did, but most
importantly, Kim accepted the assignment.
Now, I am gonna transfer you over to Adam.
Fine.
Look, I am sorry about what
happened earlier about grabbing you.
I didn¡¯t mean to scare you.
I just don¡¯t think what
you are doing is right.
But I need you to understand something
in the field I am in command.
You do what I tell you to do.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand me??
Yes
Ok, good
My nose has been bleeding for almost
an hour, and I can¡¯t get it to stop.
All right.
Have a seat and fill this out.
How long will that take?
There are a couple patients ahead
of you, it shouldn¡¯t be too long
Thanks
TV: As to how serious this illness is,
we have no new information and
the authorities are not commenting.
We can¡¯t verify this but we are hearing that
whatever is infecting the people of this hotel,
it¡¯s very serious and possibly deadly.
Body bags have been spotted, and rescue workers
are positioned around the Chandler Plaza.
Authority do not give any
information regarding the estimated...
Hey
One minute, sir.
No, now.
I need to see a doctor now.
I was at that hotel. There is
something seriously wrong with me
Oh, my god, you are him
Dr. Joyner.
The man we are supposed to isolate, he is here
Yes
We have just identified the body
And it¡¯s Chappelle?
It's confirmed. The thumbprint
matched the one in his file.
Good.
Dump the body.
Yes, sir.
You take care of your problem?
Yes, Chappelle is dead.
But CTU is still gonna try to
find out what he was working up,
so tell Lennox to stay alert,
make sure he doesn¡¯t let
Jan out of his sight.
Yeah
Any problems?
No. She is leaving her apartment now.
She is going to work.
All right, stay with her.
The next few hours are crucial.
I will be here.
Mr. President, we have started down a
slippery slope here, and unless we are
Cut the euphemisms, Jeseph.
What are you trying to say?
Sir, we are concerned about the fact that you ordered
the death of a high ranking member of our intelligence
I don¡¯t think we are here to second
guess actions that have already been taken.
Joseph, no one is more aware than I am
of the moral ambiguity of my decision.
I did it to buy CTU more
time to find Saunders
and to delay for as long as
possible the slaughter of millions.
I made the decision to
protect their future
not mine
Saunders.
I have to take this.
Yes
I have confirmed the identity of
Chappelle¡¯s body, Mr. President.
It will be disposed of respectfully.
We know who you are, Mr. Saunders.
Whatever you are trying to
accomplish, you are going to fail.
Your only chance is to relinquish
the virus and hope we don¡¯t find you.
That¡¯s not going to happen.
What is it you want?
To make America clean again.
You see, Mr. President
the world hates America
and for good reason
I won¡¯t bother going into the details, you know
better than I the atrocities your nation commits.
But we are going to change all that.
You and I, together, are going to dismantle the military
machine that exports its ugliness across the globe.
And how are we going to do that?
We will start where the work gets the
dirtiest, something I know a little about.
Covert foreign nationals.
In 32 countries across the
Middle East and Asia,
your government employs grade A
through H intelligence consultants.
They are citizens of the
countries in which they reside.
They are spies
Working against those countries at the
behest of the American military machine.
In 45 minutes, I want a list of their
identities sent to me by way of a web site
Sylviaimports.com
If you fail to cmply,
I will release 2 vials of the
virus in major cities.
And this time,
they won¡¯t be in hotels
where they can be contained.
Agent Bauer, Rachel Forrester.
This is Agent Kim Bauer. She is
gonna be doubling for Jana Saunders.
We have already set up a staging area
outside the library where she works
Is it a safe distance away?
Yes, we won¡¯t be detected.
Is she there yet?
No. She will be in a few minutes.
Let¡¯s go ahead. Let¡¯s go.
Make sure everybody on the block is
contacted and nobody leaves their house.
Sheriff¡¯s department is sending officers over
to patrol a 3 block area until they get here.
Use your men. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Edmunds.
Yeah, we found Bill Cole.
- Where?
- He is at an urgent care center not far from you.
Laurel Canyon and Moorpark
Yeah, I know where that is.
I want you to get over there,
get as much as you can off of Cole.
He is pretty agitated, you are
gonna have to help him focus.
Tony
Yeah
Is Kim in play yet?
No. She just landed in Santa Barbara.
All right, I will call you.
Where is Jane now?
My people have her under
surveillance in the library
working behind the reference desk.
How crowded?
10, 20 people
Well, one of them belongs to Saunders,
and their orders are gonna be not let her
out of their sight, not for one second.
I know. We have taken over
the surveillance cameras
and we have narrowed down a
list to about 5 probables.
Ok, get that intel over to
Tony Almeida at CTU.
Ok, let¡¯s see her.
Ok, now remember, Kim
You are not gonna fool anyone
who knows Jane Saunders up close.
I know
The staff knows what¡¯s happening
But I want you to stay at least
10 feet behind the counter,
and I want you to keep your
head down as much as possible.
the wig looks darker than
Jan¡¯s hair color.
That¡¯s the best we could
do on such short notice.
You are gonna have to match every detail as
closely as possible, her life depends on it.
Mr. Cole, when you were inside the
store, who did you come in contact with?
What do you mean, contact?
Who did you talk to?
Just the pharmacist
behind the counter.
How many others?
Customers?
Yeah, there were some
other people there.
How many other people were there?
Bill
If we do not identify and track down everyone you have
come in contact with, we are gonna have a citywide epidemic.
So how many people?
I, I don¡¯t know
Think!
That¡¯s it. We are now patched
against security.
No audio from the system
Nothing on B
Go ahead, try six
This screen go ahead isolate front desk
5 is good
Thank You
Oh
I am so sorry
You are not supposed to
have drinks in here.
I am sorry, I will throw it away.
It¡¯s ok
Start tracking that man
in the red shirt.
I want to know everything that he does.
Yes Sir.
Subject is on camera 4 right now.
I was just about to replace those.
Here you go.
Clear
What the hell is taking her so long?
Checking all surveillances now
Nothing on 1, nothing on 2
Come on
Sir, she came out from 4
Kim
There is a man handing
towards the bookcase
at your 3 o¡¯clock, red shirt
Might be one of Saunders¡¯ men.
I want you to angle away
from him slowly.
Good
We just got off the phone with
Chase who is with Cole right now.
After Cole left the hotel,
he went to his house in Burbank.
He stopped at a gas station
on Riverside Drive
But it was self service
and according to what he told the urgent care unit what his wife
confirmed, he didn¡¯t become symptomatic until after he got home.
The nose bleeds and the sweating?
Right
Here is where the ripple
effect starts.
At 7:20, he stopped at a pharmacy
and asked the pharmacist Sam Tyler for
some medication to stoop the bleeding
There were 3 other people inside
that pharmacy at the same time
Right. One of them, Anne Schwartz.
She¡¯s has been going to the pharmacy for
years, so they had her address on file.
We have sent NHS people to her house.
She has a husband and 3 children.
What about the other 2 customers?
ID is unknown.
These people could be anywhere, spreading the
disease to anybody they come into contact with
It gets worse.
At the urgent care facility
in Studio City
there were 6 patients in
the waiting area
when cole came in, who left before
the quarantine was put in place.
We are tracking them down
But between then and the
staff at the facility
We could be looking at
up to 75 people
Just in their immediate families. If any of these people
are in a supermarket or a mall when they become symptomatic
This thing is going to be
impossible to contain.
We need to identify and
find them now.
Also, I need you to coordinate
with NHS and HazMat.
We have to set up a quarantine in 2
neighborhoods in the Burbank Studio City area.
Department heads report to Adam.
Looks good, everybody, it looks
like this worked.
- Maintain monitering Kim. Come get me if anything happens.
- I got it.
Thank you, good work
What¡¯s going on?
who are you?
My name is Jack Bauer,
I am a federal agent.
You are not in any danger
What do you want?
We need your help
We need to get in touch
with your father.
Then get in touch with him.
What do you need me for?
We don¡¯t know where he is
and we think you do.
What¡¯s this about?
You don¡¯t know who your
father really is.
First of all, I hardly know my father.
And whatever this is,
I know it¡¯s illegal.
You have no right to keep me here.
Release me now,
I haven¡¯t done anything wrong
You¡¯d better listen to me
very carefully, Jane.
Right now your father is engaged in terrorist
activity against the United States of America.
This morning, he killed hundreds of people,
and he is threatening to kill thousands more.
Now, I can only imaging how difficult
this must be for you to believe,
but trust me, you are going
to cooperate with us.
There is a lot at stake,
and there is not a lot of time.
I am not going to do anything.
I want to talk to a lawyer.
There is no lawyer.
There is just you and me.
I don¡¯t know anything
about my father.
He comes into town twice a year.
I have dinner with him.
I don¡¯t even know where he lives.
How do you contact him?
I don¡¯t. He calls me.
You are lying to me, Jane.
I¡¯m not
Don¡¯t try to protect him. You are just
going to get yourself in a world of trouble.
You are the one in trouble here.
You are the one breaking the law.
You think I am playing a
game here with you?
Hundreds of thousands of people¡¯s
lives are on the line.
You have no idea how far I am willing
to go to acquire your cooperation.
What are you threatening to do to me?
Where is your father, Jane?
I don¡¯t know!
Where is your father?
Somebody, help me, pleaase
Jack
What?
Red shirt is approaching her desk.
What¡¯s going on?
He¡¯s at the desk.
Kim, don¡¯t turn around.
Just stay where you are.
- Where the hell is the librarian?
- Alice, get someone to the reference desk now
Excuse me
Just a minute
I, I need some help with, finding a book
Just one second
- Ok, sweetheart, you are doing great..
- Jus stay calm, until we check this guy out.
Give me a close up on the gentleman
in the red shirt at the desk
Can I get some help here?
I'll be with you in a minute.
Ok, Kim, I want you to slowly get up and try to
make your way to the bookshelves in front of you.
Stay out of his eye line until
we find out who this guy is.
- Maintain a constant visual on her from monitor 3.
- Get camera 3 on Kim
We are panning off her.
Get me another angle.
There is no other angle.
- What¡¯s going on?
- Jack, we had her a second ago. Camera 3 should be panning back on her in few seconds
You work here, don¡¯t you?
Yeah.
- Could you help me find something in this aisle?
- Yeah, no problem. What is it that you need?
You call for help,
I will kill you right now
Who has Jan Saunders?
I don¡¯t know what you
are talking about.
Where the hell is she? Kim
Damn it
Team two, go, go
Get down, get down
Kim
Kim, step back, step back
Radio back. Tell them
the subject is down.
Are you ok?
Yeah, fine.
Saunders is going to
know we have his daughter.
www.tvsubtitles.net