Previously on 24.
Alan Milliken's prescription bottle turned up with Sherry's fingerprints on it.
I can call Foxton.
He can make this all disappear.
All you have to do is give me the ok.
David put you up to this, didn't he?
Sherry, I¡­
The police think I killed Alan
Well, I told you to keep your mouth shut
It's nobody's fault but your own
Oh, my God. Sherry.
No.
You committed treason. You facilitated the escape of a man
who is responsible for the death of Ryan Chappelle and almost a thousand civilians.
With luck, the best you can hope for is 20 years
Tell me how to find your couriers, Stephen
Or I am going to put her in that building
You wouldn't dare. She has nothing to do with this
Neither do the people in those body bags
When your daughter is infected, I am going to make you watch her die
Dad, stop them
Stephen, you are out of time
Stop, stop, stop, I will tell you
Where's the 11th vial?
Los Angels
What's the target?
His instruction were to select a public place where maximum casualties would be inflicted.
The target has stopped moving
The target has stopped
Drop the bag
Get on the ground, now. Don't move
Where is it?
Where's what?
- Where is it?
- Where's what?
Chase
What are you guys doing, what's going on?
I have got the signal.
What are you looking for?
It's just a transmitter
He's put it on an innocent. This man is not Rabens.
Shut the station down now
The following takes place
between 12:00 pm and 1:00 pm.
This is Dessler
Michelle, it's Jack
We just lost Rabens
He dumped the GPS beacon onto an innocent.
Which means he still has the virus?
We have to assume so. He couldn't have gotten very far.
We are sweeping the station now.
We have locked down the entire building
We are gonna start moving passengers through monitored checkpoints.
How will you find Rabens?
We still don't have a sketch on him.
We need Saunders to make an I.D.
I want you to move him over from holding to Chloe's station.
We are sending up a live feed, you should have it in a few minutes.
Ok, we will be ready on our end.
Michelle, Gael Ortega's wife Theresa is here
All right, Jesse, send her in
According to Chloe's statement, you were working in parallel to bring down Saunders,
even while you were complying with his demands.
Yeah, that's right
I, I gave Chloe a recording of a conversation between Saunders and myself
Chloe also said you intentionally scrambled the voice to slow down her progress.
Tony, did you put Michelle's life ahead of public safety or national security?
Yes, I did
They said he was exposed to a virus
Yeah, that's right
Did he suffer?
No, no, he went quickly
Gael
He was a hero
He tried to stop the virus from being released,
and when it was, he just kept working
Till the end.
Thank you
Can I pick up his things
Of course
I will go see what I can do
Ok
Wait here
Kim
Yes, Michelle
That's Mrs. Ortega. Gael's wife
I need you to take her to his station, pick up his personal belongings.
Sure
Thank you
Sit him down
Hello
Kim, I need you
Saunders is here to I.D. Rabens.
Well, I am with Mrs. Ortega.
Michelle said I could reassign anyone I wanted to help me,
and I want you, so please don't make me ask again.
Fine. I will get Barry to watch her
Barry
Yeah
Please watch Mrs. Ortega while she gathers Gael's things.
Sure.
Take as much time as you need.
Thanks
Excuse me, Barry
Can I get a signature?
Oh, sure
Thanks
Anything else?
No, that's it
Sir. If you will just step up to the line
Right here
Chin up, please, sir
Chin up.
Move in closer on 2A
Yeah, Jack, it's me
Any matches, Michelle?
No, nothing yet
- How far have you got?
- 4C
So far, we have gone through the 1st 2 sets of photos.
Next group is uploading now. Stand by.
It's not him.
Is there anything on this page?
3B, closer up
No. That's not him
No
Station 3, do we have a match?
It's a negative, Jack
I don't see him anywhere
Head up, sir.
Bring up 5B
No, he's not, he's not here
All right, bring up the next page
What about this one?
He killed my husband
He killed Gael
Michelle, what's going on over there?
Saunders has been shot.
What are you talking about?!
Who shot him?
Gael's wife
Hold on, Jack. I need medical here now
Michelle, what is his condition?
Looks critical.
You do everything you can to keep him alive.
He's our only connection to Rabens.
Chase
Yeah
Jack
Talk to me
He didn't make it
Son of a bitch
We will get back to you
Saunders has just been shot.
He's dead
Don't move, madam, don't move
He killed Gael
Between the information we've gotten
from the captured couriers and our own intelligence,
We've been able to confirm that Saunders
was the sole architect of today's actions.
If we catch this last man
Arthur Rabens
that'll be the end of the threat
And if not, we are back to square one
And the virus is back on the market.
Find him
- Hello, Wayne.
- Joseph, could you give us a minute??
- Thank you, Joseph
- Mr. President
Well, did you get the prescription bottle from Sherry's house?
?
Yeah
Well, that's good
David...
something horrible happened and I don't¡­
Sherry is dead
What?
How?
ulia, she came in and she...
she killed her, and then she turned the gun on herself
They are both dead?
Yeah
Listen, I am not going to try to pretend that we can just put this behind us
but the fact is¡­
The fact is that politically, we are free of everything
Free of Milliken's extortion, his death
free of Sherry's involvement.
You are thinking of the politics of this?
The mother of my children has just been murdered
And the woman that I love just killed herself in front of me.
I understand how you feel
But there's a story here, David.
There's a story that can tie this all together
Alan Milliken was having an affair with Sherry.
Julia found out, and then she killed them both
No, no, no, I don't want to hear it
- Your emotions are clouding...
- No!
David, please, just listen to me.
Leave me alone.
David, please!
Jeanie
Yes, Mr. President?
Would you get my son and my daughter on a conference line
We are going to separate the crowd into units of 10.
I want an officer assigned to each unit.
That officer's gonna be responsible to make sure that no one leaves that unit
unless authorized by me or another CTU agent
I understand
We are also going to search every passenger
and I mean every briefcase, purse and pocket.
And we are gonna verify their identification.
We will be here all day
- Not if we find him
- Yes, sir
I want you to initiate another search of the station
including the tracks, a mile in each direction.
Thank you
Yes sir.
Jack
We are locked down
We got 2 men at every exit
Good
Is there anything else we can do right now?
No, not until we get an I.D. on Rabens.
Jack, listen,
about Mexico...
I hope you know I understand you were just doing your job.
Look, it took me a long time to understand that if you want to do this job well
you have to stay detached...
If you can accept that, you will be fine
Yeah
Well, I have accepted it
That's why I am thinking after today, I am done
I don't want to be detached, Jack
Not from Kim, not from my daughter
I am going to request a transfer to the floor
You sure about this?
I'd still be serving my country,
and take care of the people I care about
I owe them that, Jack
What did Kim say?
I think she's willing to give it a try as long as I am not in Field Ops.
What do you think, Jack?
I am the last person you should be asking
This is between you and Kim
Whatever you choose, I would support
You are a good man, Chase
Let's go, let's go
Moving in, form a line here, sir.
Please, fast, we'll be checking your belongings and your identification
You only have 9 people in your unit,
Where is the man in the brown jacket?
I don't know
Chase, we have a passenger unaccounted for
This is Jack Bauer, we have 2 LAPD officers down at the northwest exit.
I need transportation to meet me on the corner.
I am a federal agent. Did you see what happened here?
A carjacking
- Get a make on the car?
- No
This is Jack Bauer, we have got a civilian casualty on Hope and Seventh
Did you see which way the car went?
Yeah, yeah, he went straight down there
I need that transportation now
Michelle, this is Jack
Rabens is out of the station.
I repeat, Rabens is out.
He was headed east on 5th street less than 5 minutes ago
I need to I.D. a stolen car
I want you to get me a DMV readout on a¡­
- Frank Kassar
- ...A Frank Kassar
Then I want you to set up roadblocks in a 5 mile radius
and coordinate SAT surveillance, traffic cameras,
everything we have got
Yeah
Fred, it's me. I need to talk to you now
All right. I will be right out.
I need to step out
Brad, Rabens is gone
He got through the perimeter at the MTA station
How the hell did that happen?
It doesn't matter how it happened, it happened.
We identified the vehicle he carjacked as a light blue Malibu.
We set up a roadblock and uplinked traffic cams and satellite sweeps
But I need Tony to coordinate the data flow with tactical.
There's no downside here, Brad
You know he's not a flight risk and he'd be a major asset to the operation.
- I could be brought up on charges if I let Tony out
- We can't lose Rabens
So unless you want to take responsibility and run tactical yourself...
You are wasting time, Brad
We need you on the floor.
Come on, Chloe, where's Rabens?
Just a second, Jack
I think I have got a match
A light green Malibu, intersection of Fifth and Vanowen.
Ok, we are only a few blocks away, we are gonna head over there now.
Adam, get me a closer shot of that plate.
Doing it now
I am back in play, Jack, Michelle got me up to speed
Tony, how long till the plate's I.D'd?
Adam, do we have a match?
Yes, it's him
Jack, it's him
Which direction is he headed?
East on Del Mar, just past Franklin.
It's this block
Right there, right there
Tony, we got him. He's headed south on Manning toward the Chatham Center.
We are going to need backup
Copy that
Tony, where's that backup coming in from?
From the east and from the south on a reciprocal course.
Ok, we just made a right.
We are headed west on De Soto
Get that thing out of here now
Tony, we have been cut off.
He made a right on to Lawndale. He's headed north.
We are about 3 blocks behind him
Yeah, Jack, we have 3 vehicles in the area
ready to cut him off.
Jack, we got him pinned on Chamberlain, just north of Palm
Keep him there. We are 2 blocks away
He's running into the middle school on Chamberlain, main entrance.
Tony, we are coming up on the middle school now.
Tony, he's in the school. Gotta get back to you.
Tell the arriving teams to secure the exits
We can't evacuate this school.
We run the risk of losing him. Let's move.
Hayes, cover the west exit.
- You got anything??
- Nothing
Cover your exit. No one leaves this buildin
Chase, take your men and search the auditorium
All teachers and students are instructed to remain in their classrooms and lock their doors.
I repeat: remain in the classrooms and lock the doors
It's all right, children
Chase, it's Jack
Second floor is clear. Do you copy?
Chase?
No,Chase, just lay still
Everything's going to be all right
This is the only thing I could do to keep him from escaping with the virus.
Don't waste your time, it's not coming off
What are you talking about?
Rabens didn't even try to remove it
If he could unlock it, he would have
Tony, Rabens is dead
The virus is in our possession.
But the dispersal device has been activated.
I don't see a timer£¬I have got no idea how long we have got
All right, Jack, I need you to find a secure container.
Anything airtight.
I can't do that£¬the device is attached to Chase's wrist.
What?
I will explain later.
Right now I need you to put me in touch with one of the teams
that's been able to disarm the device already.
All right, I will get back to you.
Hurry
Just support the device
Jack, I don't know how this is all going to turn out,
but I want you to tell Kim that I am sorry.
You got to tell Kim, you tell her yourself
We're going to get through this. You just stay with me.
We are going to get through this.
- Jack, I am patching you through
- OK
Roger Summers here
Roger, my partner had to fasten the dispersal device to his wrist
to stop the courier from escaping with it.
I need to figure out how to disarm the timer or remove the clamp
Forget about the clamp. It's titanium£¬
And it's also wired into the tamper proof mechanism.
Fine, then let's disarm the timer. What do I do?
There's a plate at the opposite end of the clamp
You need to open that up.
Ok, I see it
Chase, stay with me. Stay with me
Ok, I have got the timer.£¬
3 minutes, 51 seconds, counting down.
You should see 6 wires to the left£¬separate them from each other
Ok, done
Ok, the furthest to the left should be red.
Cut it without making contact with the others.
You ready?
I cut the red wire, but the timer is still counting down
That's ok. The timer will stop with the next cut
Locate the green wire. It's in the group to the right
Roger, I don't have a green wire.
What color wires do you have?
Orange, yellow, black and purple
Jack, the devices don't match
Don't panic, and don't cut any more wires until we can figure this out on our end.
Hurry. We are running out of time.
Jack, you need to go
I am not going anywhere without you.
Do it
- They are going to call back
- You have to
They are going to call back
It's ok
This is Jack Bauer. We have a man down on the 3rd floor science lab northeast corner of the building
requiring medical assistance
Emergency, now
Could you give us a minute, please?
What's going on?
I am back in custody.
Hammond's taking me down to Federal.
No, no, they can't do this
Not after everything you have accomplished today.
Michelle, I put your well being above the country's
Nothing anybody can say will ever change that fact.
But they can't£¬they can't put you in prison.
Yes, they can
And they will, for a long time£¬believe me.
- Tony, don't talk like this. I
- Michelle
I can't, I won't give up on you
Michelle, come on. Please, Michelle, don't do this
Baby, you are alive
And nobody else got hurt because of what I did
And that's more than I hoped for
I can live with that
Even in prison
Tony, it's time
- This is Bauer
- Agent Bauer, please hold for the President
Jack
Mr. President
I wanted to thank you personally
Not only for what you have done today,
but for everything
This country continues to owe you a great debt of gratitude.
Thank you, sir.
I put you in an unimaginable position earlier today,
when I asked you to take the life of one of your colleagues.
Please forgive me for that.
Mr. President, there is nothing to forgive.
It's what had to be done
It wasn't the only sacrifice made today
I understand
How's agent Edmunds doing?
He's in surgery now
It's going to be a few days before we know whether or not he can use his hand
Well, when he's strong enough to talk,
I'd like to thank him personally.
He would appreciate that, sir.
You know, Jack, men and women like you,
your courage and level of commitment humbles me.
Thank you, Mr. President
I will let everyone know at CTU that you appreciated the job they did
Jack, there's one more thing
and please don't discuss this with anyone until it becomes public
But I wanted you to hear it from me, personally.
I have decided not to seek reelection.
This will be my only term
Mr. President, I hope you don't mind me saying so,
but I think you're making a mistake.
Well, mistake or not, it's what I have decided.
When I am a private citizen, I hope we can become better friends.
That would be an honor, sir
Thank you, Jack
Thank you, Mr. President
Come
Mr. President,
the motorcade's ready
Thank you, Eric
Thank you, Wayne
- Dad
- Hey
Is Chase going to be ok?
The doctors are very optimistic.
They got him into surgery very quickly
Oh, thank God
Come here
I hear you and Chase are going to make some changes.
I am very happy for you
I thought you were going to be upset about it
I am so proud of you
I am sure whatever choices you make will be the right ones.
Thank you, Dad
Thank you
You going to be ok?
Yeah, I am going to be fine.
There's something I have to deal with
But I am going to be fine
You are going to wait here for Chase to get out of surgery?
Yeah
I've gotta leave for a little while,
- but I will be back
- Ok
I love you
I love you, too, Dad
Jack, you there?
Jack?
This is Jack
I just got a call from District
They have started interrogating Saunders' courier.
We could use your help
- Jack?
- Yeah
Jack, did you copy?
I am on my way.
www.tvsubtitles.net