Previously on 24.
Mr. President, with respect to the
death of Alan Milliken, I know you lied.
You told the police Sherry was with you at
the time of Milliken's death.
Her fingerprints on this prescription
bottle prove otherwise.
What do you want?
Your resignation.
Without this, Sherry's got nothing, right?
Now, I can call Foxton, and he
can make this all disappear.
You mean steal evidence.
Jack, I just heard Tony took Jane Saunders
out of the building without authorization.
Saunders has Michelle.
He wants to trade her for his daughter.
Tony, put that gun on the dash
You help me make this trade, I will turn myself in.
Go to prison, whatever is gotta happen.
We don't have a visual on Saunders.
I repeat we don't have a visual on Saunders
Keep your teams down. Stay down
I can't
Jane, it's ok, come here
Team A and B move
Move now
Stephen
I am pinned down
Saunders has a helicopter
Call in air support now
11 vials of the virus are unaccounted for.
Where are they?
It's not going to be that simple, Jack
This is Jack Bauer
Saunders is in custody.
The following takes place
between 11:00 am and 12:00 pm.
We just got verification from Saunders' computer.
There's 11 vials across the country
How long till you can give us their location?
I am not sure I can.
Saunders applied a sophisticated decryption overlay.
An unauthorized access will auto
erase the file structure.
- I will keep trying
- Ok
Where are the 11 vials?
You are wasting your time, and I am not foolish
enough to have that information in there.
Where are the vials?
In the hands of dedicated men, true believers.
Believers in what?
That's the greatest threat to world
peace comes from this country.
There's a hotel not far from here where 800
innocent people are dead or dying because of you.
Were they a threat to your world peace?
The United States must be forced
to retreat within its own borders.
Those people are simply the first casualties of war.
What happened to you, Stephen?
I was abandoned by the people I worked for
As you will be some day
But my message will be heard in less than 1 hour
What are you talking about?
My couriers have been instructed
to release the virus at noon.
They are in fail safe mode and they can't be recalled.
Tell us where they are, we will stop them.
That is possible, but only if you agree to my terms.
What are your terms?
I have a private jet waiting at Van Nuys airport.
I need to be on it with presidential
guarantee of safe passage to North Africa.
Never going to happen.
Then hundreds of thousands will die.
I know what you are thinking, Jack
But the Bosnian secret police worked on me
for 2 years and couldn't break me
Do you really think you will be able
to do it in less than an hour?
Get me on that plane, Jack
You don't have a choice.
Bring me Jane Saunders.
I'm gonna need your gun, Tony.
Frisk him
Hey
- You don't have to do that
- I have got my orders.
- You take it easy. He's one of us.
- Not any more
What's going on?
My orders are to take Almeida into custody.
That's straight from Brad Hammond at Division.
I am sorry, Tony
There's nothing we can do right now
Just take care of business, Jack
I'll be all right
He said you wanted to see me?
I need you to speak with your father.
What do you want me to say?
Try and make it personal.
Try to connect with him.
Tell him you are scared that you don't want him to do this
I will try
I know what's going to happen, and I know you can stop it
Please
I wont let them use you to manipulate me
Despite everything that's happened
I love you
And I asking you, please don't let this happen
This doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't make any sense to you because
you haven't seen what I have seen
You don't understand
I know you think what happened to you is
the governments fault, and maybe it is
But the people who are going to die are innocent.
Ant that's tragic, Jane.
But it has to happen for things to change and they must change
How can you do something like this?
I am doing it for your sake
For my sake?
For you and your children
And after it, the world will be a better place
Please, Dad
Please
Please, don't do this
Jane, I don't expect you to understand now.
But one day you will
And you will look back and you will
thank me for what I have done
Yeah
Oh, my god
Jane
We are on the move, get the choppers ready
Hello
Sherry, Its David
Hello, David
I have been thinking things over
What Keeler offered you, how did you put it?
A seat at the table?
Yeah, something like that
Well, there my be a seat at my table.
Its a little too late for that, David
Sherry, I think its in both our best interests
for you to hear what I have to offer.
All right, I am listening
No, not on the phone
In person
Where, then?
The Oakcliff Building, downtown
I know it
Good. I will meet you there in 25 minutes.
That's a short notice, David
But you will be there
You are in no position to be making demands here
Sherry, I have a schedule to keep.
If I start changing things around, it will attract
attention and I don't think either one of us wants that.
All right, David
I will hear what you have to say
Fine
Yeah
She should be leaving soon to meet me
I know shed go for it
Oh, she's enjoying having me over a barrel.
I could hear it in her voice
Don't worry about that, David
If we can find this prescription bottle,
all her leverage is gone.
How long will you need in the house
The more time we have, the better
our chance of finding it
I will do whatever I can to keep her there with me
All right
Wayne, find it
Take a look at your handiwork
You murdered these people, Stephen
Whole families
Sometimes a fire needs to be lit
in order to put out another fire.
I don't want to hear your justification
This is over
You are going to tell me how to find
the rest of the vials now
Or you'll send me inside the hotel?
I am prepared to die for my cause, Jack
Yeah, I know
Chase
Yeah, Jack
Come in
Copy that
What are you doing, Jack?
Why did you bring me here?
Ask your father, its up to him
Dad?
Tell me how to find your couriers, Stephen
Or I am going to put her in that building
You wouldn't dare. She has nothing to do with this
Neither do the people in those body bags
I am going to do everything I have to stop you
from releasing more of this virus.
How could you do this?
I am going to give you one chance
You are not
Tell me how I find them
You know you cant do this, Jack
You are a government agent
Send her in
Take her inside now
No
Dad, stop them
Stop it
Dad, please
No, no, no
Everything that happens to your daughter is because of you.
Dad, stop, no, no, no
Get her out of there, Jack
Jack, get her out of there
Where are the vials?
Get her out of there
How do I find the vials?
Dad
Let her go
Do as I say now, Jack!
When your daughter is infected,
I am going to make you watch her die
Bauer, let her go
Let her go
You are running out of time, Stephen
Stephen, you are out of time
Stop, stop, stop, I will tell you
Just don't harm her
How do I find the vials?
Each one is tagged with a GPS locator chip so that I can
track them right up until t he moment they are released.
Where are the locator codes?
In my head
You memorized all 11?
Yeah, get her out of there
Bring Jane out from the tunnel now.
Let's go
Jack, we have picked up 10 of the 11
GPS signals coming off the vials.
Why are we missing a signal?
I don't know. I gave you the correct codes.
Where's the 11th vial?
Los Angels
What's the target?
His instruction were to select a public place
where maximum casualties would be inflicted.
What's his name?
I know him as Arthur Rabens.
But I am assuming that's not his real name.
We need a description
Take him back to holding over at CTU.
I want him working with a sketch artist immediately.
What about Jane?
She stays here
Kaufman
Adam, its Jack
I need you to do an all agency search on the name Arthur Rabens.
Saunders believes it might be a alias
Ok, I am on it, Jack
Has district sent anyone over to replace Tony?
Actually, yeah, Brad Hammond just got here right now
Ok, let me speak to him
One second
Mr. Hammond
I have Jack Bauer for you on line 6
Good, thank you
Jack
I have been briefed on CTU activity to this point
We are relaying the coordinates of the 10 vials
to local police, NHS and HazMat across the country
But we still cant lock on a signal from the 11th vial
The 11th vial is in Los Angeles.
The couriers name is Arthur Rabens
Although Saunders believes that that might be an alias.
There's no predetermined target
Did he tell you the truth
Yeah. Right now he thinks we are willing
to kill his daughter if he doesn't cooperate.
But our best bet is to lock on to that signal.
I understand everyone in comm. is working on it
Brad, I know you took Tony Almeida into custody.
But now that his wife is safe,
I think he might be a real asset to us.
I am sorry, Jack, but there's
not going to be any special treatment.
For Gods sakes, Brad
Four and a half years ago, I was put in the
exact same position as Tony's been put in today.
Victor Darzen kidnapped my wife and daughter,
and I went outside of CTU to get them back.
And no one put me in prison.
The circumstances were different
And the outcome will be the same, we will prevail.
The entire operation was put at risk because of what he did
This operation started a year ago with Gael, Tony and myself.
Gael gave his life, I became an addict just
to maintain my cover, and now you are sending Tony to prison?
Its wrong
Brad, its wrong and you know it.
You should be putting a medal on him not handcuffs.
Jack, you can testify at his hearing.
Right now, we have got work to do.
Where's Michelle?
She's here
Can I talk to her, please?
First thing first
Plachecki's coming over from the attorney
Generals office to take your official statement.
You are entitled to have a lawyer present.
Look, I don't need a lawyer, Brad
I did what I did
What you did, Tony, is punishable by the death penalty.
Death penalty
What did you expect?
You committed treason
That was not my intent.
You facilitated the escape of a man who was
responsible for the death of Ryan Chappell
and almost a thousand civilians,
who was contemplating killing millions of others.
Then you tried to neutralize the only leverage
we had over him, by giving him back his daughter.
So what's the bottom line?
I will testify to the fact that your service
record is long and for the most part, distinguished.
With luck, the best you can hope for is 20 years
Sherry should have left by now
Yeah, well, she's taking her time
So she can make the President wait.
Wayne Palmer
Wayne
I told you not to call me
I don't have anyone else
I am sorry, but I cant help you right now
The police are coming back to arrest me,
Wayne, for murdering Alan
Because they don't believe that Sherry was here
I know what happened
Then why didn't you tell them the truth?
My lawyer says that the President is backing Sherry's story.
Is it true?
Is your brother covering for Sherry?
I don't know, Julia.
Don't lie to me
Listen, I am sorry, but there's nothing
I can do for you right now.
Please
Just don't, don't hang up.
I will call you as soon as I can, I promise
Wayne
I am so scared
I know, I know
We loved each other once
Help me
I have to go, Julia
Wayne
I am sorry
Chief of Staff to the President of the
United States and I am committing a burglary
It's an historic moment
Foxton, Sherry can never know we were here.
You do what I say, and she wont
Lets get to work
Jack
This is the tactical feed from San Francisco
They are apprehending Saunders courier.
He's not breathing
He's been neutralized
Sniper took him down with a head shot.
We have got it
The vial is intact.
Repeat, we have the vial
One down, 10 to go
You check the kitchen?
Yeah, for the second time
There is nothing there
Well, it looks like Mrs. Palmer
believes in better living through chemistry.
But none of the bottles are Milliken's.
Damn it
Relax
If she's hidden it here, well find it.
How can you be so sure?
Because she's not a professional, and I am
Sherry
David
Lets take a walk
Well, actually, I just wanted to get to the point
What is it that you have decided?
I decided to give you what you want
A place in my administration
Well, that's what you implied over the phone, but I thought
I was here so that you could be a little more specific.
You will be my de facto right hand,
involved in all major decisions.
Involved how?
On everything from ambassadorial appointments
to legislative proposals,
you will be one of my primary consultants.
One of your consultants?
Right
Good-bye, David
Why? Where are you going?
Back home, because this conversation is over.
Why?
That's just not good enough
I am not going to be relegated to some informal
role so that you can ignore me whenever you choose.
Why don't you just tell me what you want?
I want a permanent position, David,
in your administration and in your life.
I don't understand
I want to be your wife again
You what?
I don't expect to have the kind of physical
intimacy that we used to have,
although maybe in time that will come,
but I really want be Mrs. David Palmer again
The first lady, right by your
side in Washington wherever you go
Sherry, I don't know what to say.
You can start by saying yes
Or I walk for good
Are you prepared to have me be your wife again?
Yes
Really?
Oh, David
Oh, God
We should talk about the details.
Work out a timeline
How we expose this to the public
Wait a minute
I know you a little better than this, David
Something's not right here.
You are making this all too easy
There's, there's something else going on
I am giving you what you asked for.
No, no, no, you are not
You are toying with me
And I don't know why, and frankly, I don't care
You just consider my offer rescinded.
John Keeler will be the next
President of the United States.
Yeah
She's on her way back
David, we need more time
We haven't found anything yet
Look, I tried to keep her here as long as I could,
but she knew something was wrong
Wayne, you should leave
We are not done
She will be there soon, you have no choice
David, hold on
There's a safe
David, we found a safe in a hidden cellar.
Can you open it in time?
Can you get in?
Its an Evans Stoller, so forget about cracking it
All these electronic safes have
manufacturer override codes.
I have a guy who can get them for us.
One of them will work
How long
Depends on how long it takes to get him on the phone
David, we may have just found a way.
You'd better. You are running out of time.
The suspect has used a titanium clamp to
secure the device to a railing.
We are defusing on the site
Wilson, what's your status?
The suspect's in custody
New York Times' men's around. Virus is contained
Yeah
Seattle, Las Vegas' secured,
suspect's taken down making a phone call
Ok, hold on
Jack, we got the couriers in Las Vegas
and Seattle without incident.
But Saunders man in Denver was making
a phone call when he was killed.
Did he complete the call? Did he warn the other couriers?
We don't know
We got to find that out
Chloe, I am getting a level 2 SAT
transmission from the LA grid
Are you sure? What are the coordinates?
Alpha 1733 at Delta 401
That's downtown. Lock in on the SAT field
Its done
Transfer to my screen
Ok
This is Jack
Jack, its Chloe
What do you got?
Saunders is telling the truth
Rabens is in Los Angeles.
Where?
He's on south Flower heading northwest.
We got a location
I want you to extrapolate his path.
Cross reference it with a list of probably public targets.
Already done
The most likely match is the California Center.
A mall makes sense.
I want you to get units over there to
evacuate and secure the area. We are on our way.
I just tried to see Tony
Security said you are denying me access.
He's a prisoner, Michelle.
I'm his wife. He did what he did to save my life
I am aware of that
And because of that he's being charged with treason.
Treason?
Brad, look, I know that he broke protocol
by taking Jane Saunders out of CTU,
But he would never have given her up
Because of him, we were able to catch Saunders
We had Saunders 2 hours ago, and Tony let him escape
No one told you?
We had Saunders trapped in a building downtown.
We were ready to drop the net, and Tony pulled
unites out of position so Saunders could get away.
Brad, it was an impossible choice
No, it wasn't
Tony has a sworn duty to protect the people of this country
Putting your life first was treasons
And he's going to prison for it.
Brad
I want you to put yourself in his place, Michelle.
If you would have made the same call,
you should resign right now.
The target is still moving north at 40 miles per hour
How long until we intercept?
About a minute
How are we doing on the other vials?
They got the Flagstaff couriers and
the other 2 in Washington.
Rabens is the last one.
Ok, make your next right.
You should be coming up right behind him.
Ok, I am turning right onto Flower.
The target is less than a block ahead of you.
You should have a visual.
Chloe, there's no vehicles within range.
Are you sure the targets still in the vehicle?
Of course, he's traveling 40 miles per hour
You are closing
Target is less than 50 feet ahead of you
There's no cars in front of us, Chloe.
You need to recheck your signals.
Its not possible
Yes, it is
He's underneath us
Chloe, the targets on the subway
Can you access the MTA's disaster response system?
Yes, we can access their control center directly.
Ok, we need to stop the train in the
tunnel before it hits the station.
Logging onto their system.
Has Adam been able to turn up a photo on Rabens yet?
No, and Saunders hasn't completed the identity sketch.
Ok, they're accepting my request to stop
the train in the tunnel just short of the station.
Do you want me to tell MTA to close the station?
No, absolutely not.
If Rabens notices anything out of
the ordinary, he might release the virus.
I am going to need 20 personnel undercover
and a backup HazMat team ASAP.
Okay, we've got men nearby.
I will tell Hammond to order the redeployment.
Yeah, Foxton here.
I've got this codes for the safe.
Ok, give me the first one
That didn't work
Got another one?
Come on, come on, come on
Did you hear that?
There's a car coming
no
Sherry is here
Look, I need you to be quiet
We need to get the hell out of here
Quiet
The next one
Damn it, Foxton, come on
Got it
Its not here
All right, come on.
That's it, lets go
What?
I didn't come this far to leave empty handed.
Wayne
What's going on here?
Answer me. What?
Oh, now I understand why David wanted to meet me.
But I am so surprised to find
you here doing his dirty work.
I have never done anything to hurt you, Wayne
David put you up to this, didn't he?
Sherry, I¡­
Answer me, David put¡­
There will be a short delay
due to a stalled train ahead.
Chase, what's your location?
I am covering the east side of the tracks
Copy that.
Chase, I've got a visual on you coming down the stairs.
Everything in place with the MTA?
They are ready to move the train into the station.
Team A and B, are you in position?
Roger. We are in position.
Rabens' description
white male, dark hair, brown eyes, none descript
Chloe, release the train
Release the hold on the train, release the train
Train doors are opening
The target is moving off the train
North or south?
North
Target is moving north
All teams remain in your zones.
- Chloe
- go ahead
can you check the altitude on a GPS signal?
If I triangulate.
Positive, target is changing altitude.
Target is moving upstairs.
We have got 10 remaining white males.
Target is now moving west
Team A, split off and maintain pace.
Target is now moving south.
Target is now descending.
He's heading to the Seventh Street exit
Coming right towards you, Jack
Target is heading south
I got a visual. 4 white remaining males.
I want all teams to start closing in.
I repeat, all teams start closing in
What have you got, Chloe?
Target is now moving west
Target has stopped moving
The target has stopped
I have identification on the target
White male at my 6 o'clock.
He's looking at the map
I am initiating takedown
Drop the bag
Get on the ground, now. Don't move
What's going on?
Where is it?
Where's what?
Chase
What are you guys doing? What's going on?
I have got the signal.
Should we wait for HazMat
No, its either in the vial or
we are already contaminated.
What is this?
Those aren't mine. I don't even¡­
Shut up
Son of a bitch
Its just the transmitter
This isn't Rabens.
He knows we are on to him
He's still got the vial
Shut the station down, now
Julia
Stay here, I will be right back
Where are you going?
Just stay here
Julia, what are you doing here?
The police think I killed Alan
Well, I told you to keep your mouth shut
Its nobody's fault but your own
What are you doing with a gun?
You don't want to do this
I am going to jail for the rest
of my life because of you
Julia
That isn't true, Julia
No, wait. Relax. We're alright here.
You got to put that gun down
No, no, she's the one who should be going to jail
My life is ruined, don't you understand that?
Julia, please, we can, we can work this out
He's right
We can work it out
Shut up, shut up
You have been lying your entire life
You are not going to lie your way out of this
You are right
But right now, Julia, I am telling you the truth
I will go to David and he will pardon you.
Now, I was just with him, just now
I am going to be his wife again.
He will do whatever I say
I promise you, you will not spend one day in jail
Isn't that so, Wayne?
Julie, listen, you will have everything you have always wanted.
You will have your freedom, you'll have Alan's estate.
You just think about it, sweetie
I promise, you will be set for life
Good, good. That is real good
That's good
My God. Sherry.
I am so sorry
No!
Oh, God, no, please
Take up position at the end of the platform.
Jack, we have detained everyone in the station.
We shut it down in time
No ones left since the train came in
Ok, set up a team and start searching the tunnels.
www.tvsubtitles.net