Previously on 24.
I just got off the phone with one of
my sources over at Keeler's headquarters.
Sherry was there meeting privately with Keeler.
Meeting Keeler about what?
He didn't know. David
I came here because I can guarantee you a win in November.
David Palmer is an accessory to murder.
David lied to the Chief of Police last night
in order to provide an alibi for me.
Why are you lying to me?
I screwed up earlier.
The SAT transmission on my system
was forged by my own people.
Making a mistake is one thing.
Covering it up is another.
I can't let you stay in place.
I am taking over command of CTU now.
I made a mistake, Jack
No, Tony
You made two
I am going to let you speak to your husband
Tell him that you are ok and
you are being treated well.
Are you all right?
I am fine
Don't let them do this, don't let??
If Jane is not release when
I order it, your wife dies.
That's all you need to know.
Are we clear?
From this point on, I am assuming control of CTU.
Tony Almeida has stepped down.
We are taking Jane Saunders to Division.
Here's the order.
- We are leaving right now.
- Ok
Going out this way right here.
Where are all the guards?
We don't need those guards anymore.
Jack, Tony locked me in here
Saunders has Michelle, he's using her as
leverage to get his daughter out.
This is Almeida. We are out. I have got her
I will give you further instructions in 20 minutes.
Exit security, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida
The following takes place
between 10:00 am and 11:00 am.
Excuse me
Chloe, I want you to pull up all the
surveillance tape from every exit in this building.
I want you to focus on the last 10 minutes.
Adam, have you linked up with
traffic surveillance yet?
I'm working on top chance.
Jack, I just heard Tony took Jane Saunders
out of the building without authorization.
- That's right
- Why?
Saunders has Michelle.
He wants to trade her for his daughter.
Jane Saunders is the only leverage we have.
Trust me, Chase. I know that.
I got him. He left the building 3 minutes ago,
and drove off the premises 90 seconds later.
Adam, he's in a silver SUV.
Chase, I want you to prep the tactical team.
- Be ready to move as soon as I give you an order.
- All right.
I got him, Jack
He's on 5th about half a mile
from here, heading east.
I will call you from the car.
Son of a bitch
Are you ok?
It's just traffic.
You have been acting all wired since we left.
Yeah, well, there's a lot going on right now.
You never really explained why you wanted
to transfer me to this division place.
I told you.
I know what you told me. It doesn't make sense.
Yeah, well, I don't have the time
to explain it to you right now.
Almeida got my daughter out of CTU.
You need to be ready to move the moment I tell you.
When are you calling Almeida with instructions?
15 minutes. I will be with Fredrick.
At least 700 people are dead or
dying in the Chandler Plaza Hotel
because Saunders released a weaponized
virus into the ventilation system
What the media is reporting is a cover story.
They are deflecting the truth to avoid mass panic.
You will be infected along with everyone else
No matter what he's paying you,
it's not worth losing your life
Jack is in pursuit of Tony. Move out
as soon as we get a location on Saunders. Understand?
Good
- Kim
- Yeah
What are you doing?
I am working with a team that's monitoring my father.
I thought you were setting up a tactical unit.
Yeah, I am
We have to wait until we get a location on Saunders.
Until then, we are pretty much on standby.
- All right
- Listen
Before I have to go back out there,
I want to talk to you.
About what?
About us
I need to know whether there's going to be an us.
Look, I have been thinking about it a lot, and...
the baby changes everything.
It doesn't change the way I feel about you.
Look, let's forget about me for a second.
You have a daughter and a job
that won't let you be with her.
Is that you talking, or your father?
My dad would be the first one to admit it.
He wasn't the greatest dad.
And it wasn't because he didn't love me.
I know he loved me.
It was because of his job
If I transferred out of Field Ops,
would you consider staying with me?
I want to stay with you,
and I would raise a child with you, Chase.
I just won't raise one for you
Adam, is he still on 5th street?
No, I lost him
He must have turned between Jarvis and Hill.
Widen the search
I am
Ok, Jack, I have got him
He's going south on Vine, 2 blocks below Hill
- You can save some time by...
- Ok, I got it
He's hit traffic at Fillmore.
You might be able to intercept on Grant.
Look, I know you are lying to me
I know you are not taking me to division.
You will be fine, Jane. All right?
At least tell me where we are going
Where are you taking me?
Back to your father
My father?
Why?
He's holding my wife hostage,
and he will kill her if I don't take you back to him
So, basically, you are kidnapping me.
I am sorry
After everything he's done,
how can you be sure he'll do what he says?
How do you know he won't kill your wife, anyway?
I don't have a choice.
I wish I did, but I don't
Tony, put that gun on the dash
Put that gun on the dash, now!
Slowly get out of the car
Jane,
stay where you are, everything is going to be fine.
Saunders has Michelle.
I know
He wants to make a trade, Michelle for his daughter
I know. I can't let that happen
Look, I almost lost her once today, Jack
I am not losing her again.
Tony, listen to me
I understand exactly how you are feeling.
I have been there.
And you handled it just like me,
you kept everyone outside of it.
Tony, this is different.
Millions of lives are at stake
Oh, rules apply to other people
But not to you, right, Jack?
Tony, just calm down, ok? Come on
You help me make this trade,
I will turn myself in.
Go to prison, whatever is gotta happen.
I can't do it
We need Jane to lure her father in.
Even if it means Michelle's gotta die.
Michelle doesn't have to die.
We can string Saunders along.
I need you to start working with me
Chase has already got a strike team mobile.
No, no, no, no
Saunders sees I brought CTU into this,
he kills Michelle
He's not going to know we are there.
Tony, where are you meeting him?
Tony, you don't have a choice right now
You've got to work with me on this
Where is the meeting?
Come on, where are you meeting him?
He wants me to be at a public pay phone
at the corner of Taylor and Vine in 5 minutes.
He'll give me further instructions from there.
Thank you
You are doing the right thing
The quarantined areas are circled in red
Now, as far as we know, we have containment.
We are still not certain?
No. But we can't really be certain for hours.
Maybe days.
David, listen
The press is breathing down Gerry's neck pretty hard.
Now, he thinks we should release a statement.
I already have.
I have closed down public transportation and
I have told the people to stay in their homes.
We have F18s patrolling the skies.
Yeah, but we haven't revealed the exact
nature of this threat and the press is picking up on that.
We have 10 million people spread
out over 4000 square mile area.
If even a small percentage decide to leave at the same time,
it will ignite a public panic
beyond anything we could control.
The right thing to do is to withhold the
truth until we are sure the virus is contained.
I will tell Gerry to hold off
on the press as long as he can.
Mr. President
Yes, Jeannie.
Senator Keeler's here to see you
Have him brought in
Yes sir.
Hello, John
Mr. President
Please take a seat
Thank you. I will stand
You can imaging my surprise when
I was told that you wanted to see me.
Are you withdrawing from the race?
Mr. President,
with respect to the death of Alan Milliken,
I know you lied to the police.
Excuse me?
You obstructed the investigation of a capital crime.
That's a baseless charge, John.
Though I have come to expect this
kind of recklessness from you
No, sir, it's neither baseless nor reckless.
This is a photograph of the nitroglycerine
medicine that would have saved Milliken's life.
If it hadn't been kept from him
You told the police Sherry was with
you at the time of Milliken's death.
Her fingerprints on this
prescription bottle prove otherwise.
Now...
the last thing this country
needs is to have its President...
dragged through the mud for complicity in a murder
Why are you showing me this, John?
What do you want?
Your resignation.
Not immediately, of course.
But once this crisis you are dealing with is over,
you can resign with whatever
face saving reason you want to give.
Get out of here.
I am offering you the chance to leave office with honor
to control how your legacy is written.
It's a good deal, David
You should take it
He's going to call in one minute.
I should go to the phone
Ok, as soon as Saunders tells you
where he wants he exchange to take place,
you need to reject the location.
We need to force him into picking a secondary
location so Chase has time to embed his teams.
If I don't show up where and when
Saunders wants me to, he's going to kill Michelle.
Not as long as we have his daughter.
What if he doesn't go for it?
Don't give him a choice.
You have got some leverage here, Tony, use it.
All right. I need to go.
My father kidnapped his wife because of me?
Something like that.
And now you want to use me as bait to get to him.
We are going to do whatever we have to to
stop your father from releasing this virus.
Stay here. We'll be right back
Where are we meeting?
First, let me speak with my daughter.
No. You can talk to her when we make the exchange.
All right.
Bring her to an industrial pack 3 miles
north of where you are, on Maltin Road.
A car will be waiting at loading dock 22.
Choose a new place. That doesn't work
Make it work
You have got 10 minutes to get to the
industrial park or your wife will die.
If we meet there, we all die.
Really?
CTU has redundant satellite surveillance of that area.
They are dedicating all their resources
to finding me right now
If you want your daughter back safely,
you pick a new spot.
I am not negotiating terms, Mr. Almeida.
I have planned too long and too hard for this day
and I will do whatever it takes
to make sure nothing interferes.
Even...
even if it means sacrificing my daughter.
You need to understand my commitment, Mr. Almeida
What the hell are you doing? He wasn't going for it.
He is testing you. He's heard what you had to say.
He'll phone back. Now hang up the phone.
How you know?
Because right now he thinks
I am going to kill his daughter.
The only reason why he exposed himself
is to make sure she's still safe.
Maybe that's what you'd do, Jack
But you are not Saunders.
No matter how well you think
you know this guy, you are not him.
This isn't a game, Jack
We are talking about my wife.
Michelle's got a better chance of surviving if we control
the ground where the exchange is supposed to take place.
But protecting her is not your priority, is it?
If she were to get killed, that would
be an acceptable loss, wouldn't it?
My god, Jack,
Didn't you learn anything from what happened to Terry?
Shut up, Tony
Shut up
Tony
Just because you sacrificed your wife for
this job doesn't mean I am going to sacrifice mine.
I am here
Make no mistake
This is your first and your last accommodation.
Just tell me where you want to make the exchange.
Downtown, under the 6th street bridge.
Under the 6th street bridge.
Be there in 30 minutes
But if I see that you have brought anyone else into this,
I will kill your wife.
You did great
Tony Almeida's going to make the exchange,
but until we get confirmation that Saunders is on site,
we stay invisible.
I will assign positions on the way out. Let's go.
What is it?
Satellite pictures of 6th street bridge.
I asked for a real time feed, Kim
We will have it, too, by the time we are on site.
What about air support?
We are coordinating with the Marines.
They will move on your order.
Look, Chase, please be careful
Don't worry about me. I will be fine.
Chloe, how much time before you can setup
a real time satellite feed for the 6th street bridge?
Do you really think Chase is going
to quit field ops to start a family?
He won't
I don't know where you are getting this from,
but it's none of your business.
I have known Chase for 3 years.
You have been dating him for 3 months.
And your point being?
He might be a great guy, but he's just like your father
They are both the same person.
So if you are expecting him to leave this
for the suburbs, you should revise your expectations.
When can you uplink a satellite feed?
10 minutes
Then do it
I am just trying to be a friend, Kim. That's all
Hello
You have gone too far this time, Sherry
You know, I thought I might be hearing from you, David
You sent Keeler over here to blackmail
me into giving up my presidency?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down
You mean Keeler paid you a visit?
You know damn well he did and you know why
Only one person could have given him that
prescription bottle and that's you
Ok, supposing that was true.
What then?
You should go to jail for murder.
You should go to jail, too, David
You lied to the police.
You told them that I was with you all night
Withholding evidence, obstruction of justice.
Those are serious crimes
I knew you always wanted to
go down in the history books, David.
But I am not certain like this. Am I right?
What did Keeler offer you, Sherry?
Exactly what you should have offered me,
respect and a seat at the table,
but instead you called me up when you needed me
and then after I did your little dirty work,
You threw me out like an old pair of shoes.
You know me, Sherry,
better than anyone, and you know I won't be bullied.
So before this goes too far,
you better ask yourself a question.
Are you willing to go to jail?
You know, David, I have asked
myself that a million times
and the answer is yes, I am willing to go to jail
The question is, are you?
I didn't think so.
I want the strike teams split into 2 groups
Group A can take cover here, group B back here.
I want them briefed and
ready to go as soon as we get there.
If Saunders sees anyone other than Tony or his
daughter, he's not going to make the approach.
What's the response time for air support?
30 seconds, after I give the order.
I will relay the coordinates.
I will see you at the bridge.
You got it
I know my father released the
virus in the hotel that people died.
But do you really think he'll do what he's saying?
Release it all over the country?
If we don't stop him, yes.
Why?
There has to be a reason he's doing all of this
When I worked with your father, he dedicated
himself to saving the lives of innocent people.
Something has happened to him
I don't know what
But now he believes our government's betrayed him
Is he right?
There's no easy answer to that.
The work that your father did often demanded that
he make seemingly impossible sacrifices.
Whatever happened to your father in Bosnia
was obviously a sacrifice he wasn't willing to make.
I am sorry
No
Shut up! No one can hear you.
Shut up now
No
No! Oh God
I said stop, stop screaming
Look at me, I have been infected.
Help me, help me, help me¡­
Help
We got a problem here
What's going on?
She has it
She has the virus
What are you talking about?
She's bleeding, she must have caught it at the hotel
They wouldn't have release her without testing her
It's a trick
She did it to herself
Kevin, are you there?
Kevin
All right, take the east corridor
Stop her from getting aboveground
But do not shoot to kill
(No Service)
CTU, O'Brian
It's Michelle
Hello?
Chloe, can you here me?
Whoever this is, I have a really a bad connection.
I have got a lot of stuff to do right now
Chloe
So what did Keeler want?
My job
He has proof that Sherry was at Alan Milliken's tonight
What?
What, what proof?
Alan Milliken's prescription bottle turned up
with Sherry's fingerprints on it.
How did he get a hold of this?
How do you think?
Sherry
I talked to her a few minutes ago.
She didn't even bother to deny it
David, she's got to be bluffing
I mean, if this gets out, she goes to jail.
So will I
She figures I have more to lose than she does
And she's right
What does Keeler want you to do?
Withdraw from the race for whatever reason I choose.
The party gets thrown into chaos,
whoever takes my place won't
have a prayer in the election,
and Keeler becomes President.
Oh, my god
This is all my fault
Hey, look
We both made mistakes
I am the one who called Sherry
There may be a way out of this
How
Without this, Sherry's got nothing, right?
What are you suggesting?
That we take away the only leverage she has.
You mean, steal evidence.
My god, Wayne
Before you say no, you just think about this, ok?
Now, I can call Foxton,
and he can make this all disappear.
All you have to do is give me the ok
- Stay with her
- Yes, sir.
Is your strike team in place?
2 minutes, they will be ready
You sure they will be of sight?
They will be invisible, Tony
Ok
I am gonna back Tony up here at the 6th street bridge.
We should get in position now.
Jack, priority call from Kim
This is Jack
Dad, I got Michelle on the line
Is she with Saunders
No, she said she get away from him.
Patch her through
Hold on
Michelle, go ahead
I got away from Saunders, but he's still after me
Michelle, it's me. Where are you?
Wilshire, a block east of Olive
Chase, send your strike team in now.
Chase, don't
What are you talking about?
Michelle, I want you to listen to me very carefully
I want you to let Saunders catch you again.
What, are you crazy?
We have to let the exchange go down
It's the only way we are gonna catch him
You want me to give myself up?
Yes, the exchange site is secure, I will send our
people in as soon as we know he's there.
- Chase, redirect your people now.That's an order.
- Chase, don't!
Jack, stay out of this
You are not in command here
Get him out of here, now
Jack, Jack, that's my wife, Jack
You son of a bitch
It's my wife
Jack
We need this exchange to go through
Everything depends on it, do you understand me?
Michelle, if he doesn't have you for trade,
he won't go through with the meeting
Look, we are not going to get another chance at it
Do you understand, Michelle
Yes
We are gonna do everything we have to
to make sure you come out of this ok
But we have got to move now
Let's get our teams into position
And I thought your brother was the kind of
politician who would never lower himself to my level
I need to recover something that
could cause him a great deal of trouble
What is it?
A bottle of medicine was taken from a crime scene.
Has it been admitted into evidence?
No.
It's in the possession of Sherry Palmer,
the President's ex-wife
I have a pretty good idea where she is right now, and I can
partially reconstruct where she's been since she stole it.
What kind of time frame are we looking at?
Hours, Foxton, not days.
Has this operation been authorized by the President?
What difference does it make?
You will get your money
I am not worried about that,
I just need to know who I am working for
My brother knows what you are doing
Not that I don't trust you, but ...
I'd like to hear it from him
Fine
That's proof enough
Let's go
Chase and his men have Saunders yet?
No one's coming yet
Look, Jack,
promise me you won't make a move on
Saunders until Michelle is safe.
We are going to move as soon as we have
got a visual on Saunders, Tony
That's the way it's got to go
I know
I am just asking you to do what you can
You know I will
We have got 3 cars headed in from the west
Tony, they are coming. Are you ready?
Yeah
The windows are tinted. I can't see inside.
Give her the phone
My preference is to turn you over to your husband unharmed
But I will kill you if anything goes wrong
Yeah
When I see my daughter, you will get your wife
All right
Jane, I need you to get out of the car
Ok, everything is going to be ok
I want you to walk over to your father's men
Where's my father?
We don't know
Listen, we have to do this, Jane
I am sorry
Look, Jane, you have got to trust me on this
Please go. Come on
Jack, send your men in now.
We don't have a visual on Saunders.
I repeat we don't have a visual on Saunders
I can't
- Hey, come here
- Jane, no, turn around
Jane, it's ok, come here
Team A and B move
We've got a visual on Saunders.
Move now
Stephen
I am pinned down
Saunders has a helicopter
Call in air support now
I repeat, call in air support now
We need air support
I have got a flight of 2 US Marine F18s
Just off the marine.
Call sign Guardian Angel
Copy that
Guardian Angel, Guardian Angel, this is Watchdog.
We've got a hot on to victor bravo tango
Jack, the Marines are coming in.
Take cover, I repeat, take cover.
Chopper's been taken out
You ok?
Don't move
11 vials of the virus are unaccounted for.
Where are they?
It's not going to be that simple, Jack
Stephen, it's over
No, it's not, Jack
It's just the beginning
Where are the vials?
You can waste time trying to break me and kill millions of people
Or you can give me what I want.
This is Jack Bauer
Saunders is in custody.
www.tvsubtitles.net