Previously on 24
What if I can get us a copy
of keeler's playbook?
What exactly do you mean
by "playbook"?
His entire prep for tonight's debate.
- Damn it, I told you to drop that.
- Will you just listen to me?
There is something you need to see.
There's nothing i need to see.
It's about anne. It's something that
we didn't know about her.
Something that could damage all of us.
- Can I talk to you now?
- Yeah, Of course.
Kim, what's up?
Chase and I have been
going out for a while,
and it's starting to get serious.
I really care for him, dad.
- So what do you think?
- I don't know what I think.
We want the release
of ramon salazar.
If you refuse to comply,
the virus will be released.
It looks like the virus was delivered
in a crystalline form.
Maybe what you're looking for
is a white powder.
It would look like a bag
of cocaine or heroin?
Yeah, that may even be the strategy.
Someone thinks they're selling a bag of coke.
when, in fact,
they're handling the virus.
- Where did you get that money
- It doesn't matter.
Okay, we needed it.
I got it.
So this is how you're
going to help you're family?
By dealing drugs?
I'm not dealing them.
It's a stupid delivery.
That kid's walking around with a bag
of cocaine that's got the virus in it.
He doesn't know it.
I need to find him and stop him
from putting it into circulation.
You didn't shoot up, did you?
Why? You think you can hide it?
I'm not trying to hide it from you.
I'm trying to quit. / Okay.
People don't just quit, jack.
I am not.
going on record with this addiction.
Do you understand me?
You're the only person who knows
about it, so it's going to stay that way.
Give me an update.
Kyle's still in his house.
What about the package?
It's with him.
- And ramon?
- Just waiting to come home.
Good.
The following takes place
between 3:00 p.m and 4:00 p.m.
Adam, have you downloaded
everyone's folders for the meeting?
Not yet. I'm still pulling up some of the
medical details about the virus.
Don't waste a lot of time on that.
The only thing our people need to know
is that it kills within 24 hours of exposure
and we believe Kyle Singer
is transporting it.
I got all that.
What about our approach to Singer?
Jack's going to meet nicole duncan,
head of health services, los angeles.
They're going to take a haz-mat
team over to Singer's apartment.
He's waiting for her now.
영어'類
김선임(sunim113@lycos.co.kr)
자막편집/싱크
남효주(hyojunet@nate.com)
한글번역
(http://club.nate.com/24)
제작지원
박창희(jfpark@nate.com)
Hi, Jack.
How you doing?
I'm okay, Nicole.
How have you been?
Until this afternoon,
I was doing fine.
You know, I, uh...
I tried to reach you
after I heard about Teri.
Yeah, I know.
After that, I kind of withdrew.
But I appreciated the calls. Thanks.
We should get going.
I just finished running Macer's
epidemiological model.
Her estimates were off.
Better or worse than we thought?
Twice as bad.
She had nine percent of the
population infected within a week,
but it's closer to 20%.
And the infection-to-mortality rate
is higher than her estimate.
Almost 95% lethal.
I've been hunting germs for 12 years
and I've never seen anything like this.
Great.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah. Why?
You're perspiring.
I've been non-stop since noon.
Look, we're going to be
about eight minutes out.
It would be great if we could go over the
quarantine protocols before we get there.
- No problem.
- Good.
If you refuse to comply,
the virus will be released.
I want the release of Ramon Salazar...
Gael.
Here, take a look at this.
Closing in on the point
of origin of this call.
You see this code artifact here?
- Yeah.
- I found a few more on this recording.
I think it's coming from
a domestic switching node.
You think the call was made
from inside the U.S.?
Maybe. I'm piping it
over to your system.
See if you can find a match.
- Okay.
- But do it after the meeting.
What meeting?
Tony's shifting resources
to help Jack in the field.
He's closing in on the virus.
- Gael.
- Yeah?
Jack needs that audio feed in place
when he gets to Kyle Singer's apartment.
I know, but Tony needs me to
take care of something right now.
- I'll get it to you after the meeting.
- I need you to do it before the meeting.
Jack's on his way there.
So come do it now.
I can't! Stop bugging me.
I'll get it to you.
Fine.
Have you thought about how it will be
when Ramon comes back?
How it will be?
Like it was before.
Things have changed, Hector.
Nothing's changed.
He's only been gone three months.
You've changed.
You've been in charge
while he's been in prison.
Are you willing to give that up so easily?
What is it?
Bauer's telling CTU he's
about to intercept the package.
- How?
- I'm not sure. I'm about to find out.
- Is Gomez still on Kyle Singer?
- Of course.
Then we're fine.
Hey, how was the interview?
Fine.
What's up, dad?
Your mother told me you paid the rent.
All three months we owed.
Yeah. I came into a little money.
How does a 19-year-old kid who doesn't
have a job come into a little money?
Tim and I, we went down to
the track the other day.
He knows this guy
over at the stables, so, uh,
- we got a tip.
- Where did you get the money?
Dad, what does it matter?
Honestly, the rent's paid
for three months. All right?
The pressure's off us now.
Did you do something illegal?
No.
I told you we went to Santa Anita,
and we got lucky.
I didn't do anything illegal.
Don't lie to me.
I've got enough to worry about.
Now, this is my house.
I pay the rent!
I take care of you and your mother.
And when you get that job,
you go ahead and
pay me back, huh?
Wait a second.
We're not done here!
No, we're done here.
Don't walk away from me!
You should be thanking me
instead of crawling up my ass.
Kyle!
Open the door!
His name's Kyle Singer.
We think he's transporting the virus,
although it's likely he doesn't
realize what he's carrying.
How could he not know?
Health Services believes that the virus
was made to look like heroin or cocaine.
We know that Kyle Singer was hired to deliver
a package from Mexico to a dealer in LA.
He thinks he's smuggling drugs.
That's the working theory.
Now, here's the thing.
Once Singer delivers that bag of powder,
it gets cut up and distributed
throughout the city.
At that point, it becomes
impossible to contain.
Was LAPD grabbing Singer?
No.
Why not?
Can't they get there faster?
LAPD is not trained to handle haz-zone.
Jack Bauer's going to go in
with a team from Health Services.
We're going to run
the operation from here,
updating the president in real time.
Now,
we have to approach
Singer with care.
He has no idea how
deadly this powder is.
I'm not fighting.
I'm just asking the questions.
- He should respect us.
- Of course he does...
now will you please calm down?
$1,800 is...
He said he won the money at the track?
He could come up with
a better lie than that.
Well, maybe he's telling the truth.
Oh, come on, Helen.
- Where you going?
- Wherever.
What's in the bag?
- Some clothes.
- Well, open it.
What?
Open the bag.
I'm warning you: Open that bag
or I'm going to open it myself.
Mom?
- Kyle, listen to your father.
- It's none of his business.
As long as you're living
in my house, it is!
Your house?
This isn't your house.
You can't even pay the rent.
Oh, Kyle...
Come on, will you
quit snooping, please?
Don't even think about it.
What is this? Huh?
Coke? Heroin?
- Give it back, dad.
- What did you say?
- I need it.
- What do you mean, you "need" it?
What are you, some kind of junkie?
No.
I'm just delivering it to this guy, okay?
And if I don't get it to him...
Who?
- It's just a guy, okay?
- Who?!
Give me a name.
Kyle, answer your father.
You just give it to me, okay?!
Stop it!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
Both of you!
Stop! Sam!
Sam, don't, Sam!
Kyle!
I can't reiterate this enough.
This is a credible threat.
Salazar's people will release this
virus if we don't find it first.
So lets get going.
Okay, we're going to need a white room
with full audio and video capability.
Get me 3b if that's available.
Log him in.
I'll be there in a minute.
I thought you were supposed
to be with my dad.
I was. He sent me back here.
Why?
To question Parker.
Parker? He already turned in Kyle Singer.
What else are you going to get from him?
Nothing.
And that's the point.
- I don't understand.
- Your dad's sidelining me, Kim.
He's making me sit out.
Why?
Why do you think?
Because of us?
- Chase, I'm sorry...
- He says he's protecting me...
but I'm not the one
he's trying to protect here.
You're not blaming me, are you?
Look, all I'm saying is,
we shouldn't have told him.
What were we supposed to do?
Keep sneaking around
until someone catches us?
We could have waited.
Until when?
He'd have the Same response
no matter when we told him.
I got to deal with this kid Parker.
Jeffery.
The food's exceptionally bad today.
Aren't there laws in this country
for cruel and unusual punishment?
Tell Annicon, I'm ready to talk.
Bauer couldn't tell me,
but Salazar's got some kind of leverage.
Enough to get him released.
I'm not about to let this son of a bitch
erase the last two years of my life.
Call your friend at the state department,
see what he can tell you.
Annicon.
- Mr. Annicon?
- Yeah.
This is Jeff Benson,
Salazar's guard.
I know who you are.
Sir, Salazar asked to see you.
Why?
He says he's ready to talk.
I'll be right there.
University of Southern California
Don't ask me why, just do it.
I hope you can get a refund.
A refund?
From whoever sold you
that load of crap.
David,
Keeler is going to use
this against you in this debate.
Now, ignoring it's
not going to make it go away.
Neither will dignifying it with a response.
He's going to claim that Anne perjured
herself, which, in case you've forgotten,
- is a felony.
- Anne is no felon.
The allegation itself
is enough to damage you.
Now, come on, David please, think.
You know you can't go into this debate
without some kind of response.
What do you propose?
Talk to Anne,
make sure she's told you everything.
She has told me everything.
Are you sure?
Ever since I started seeing Anne,
you've taken every chance to
undermine our relationship.
- Just because you don't like her...
- You're absolutely right, I don't like her.
This isn't about me and Anne.
It's about you and Anne.
Now, if she's got nothing to hide,
fine, David, she's got nothing to hide.
But you'd better find out before you
face off with Keeler on national television.
Did you ask your friend
Jack Bauer what's going on?
You did, didn't you?
But he wouldn't say.
Must be very frustrating,
Luis, being kept in the dark.
You have something to tell me?
- I asked you here, didn't I?
- Then start talking,
because you used up
my patience an hour ago.
you are dog with a bone, Luis.
Once you bite down, you don't let go.
When I'm out of here,
I don't want you on me anymore.
When you're out of here?
You were right.
In a few hours, I'm going home.
Really?
And how will you manage that?
Hector's a good brother.
Unless he's got a key to this place,
- you're not going anywhere.
- But he does have a key.
And when he turns it,
the last two years of your life,
all the hours you've spent
away from your family,
all the work you've done
to put me in here
will go away...
...just like that.
I wanted you to hear it from me, Luis.
I wanted it to be the
last thing you ever heard.
Your son will be
returned to you now.
I'm just saying that Kyle
is in over his head.
We're not calling a lawyer.
- He hasn't even been arrested.
- Not yet.
Maybe he won't be.
If we leave it alone,
don't do anything,
maybe this whole thing
will just go away.
- You can't be serious.
- Why not, Sam?
Why do we have to let anybody know?
- Because it's against the law not to.
- What are you suggesting we do,
call the police?
Maybe they'll give us a reward
and then we can pay our rent.
All right, that wasn't fair.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my god!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm going to get rid of it!
- You want to visit your son in jail?!
- Wait a minute.
Helen!
- Get back! Get back!
- Who are you people?
Where's Kyle Singer?!
- Kyle Singer!
- He's not here.
Isolate him and draw blood for
a full panel. Get an oral swab.
Seal off all these windows and vents.
No!
in here! In here!
- No!
- Put her in quarantine.
Tony, the virus is out.
I repeat, the virus is out.
Copy that, Jack.
Where is it?
In the sewage system.
Get DWP to shut down
the lines from ground zero.
It might also be airborne.
Get the fire department and
LAPD to set up a perimeter.
Tell them we've got
a level-three hot zone.
Copy that.
Come in.
Wayne said you wanted to see me.
What's wrong?
Keeler.
He's bringing your
ex-husband into this debate.
The SEC's investigation into his company.
Well, Ted was convicted,
and served his sentence.
You know that.
I know what you told me.
I told you everything there is to know.
Ted's company was introducing
a hypertension drug...
- and you reviewed the research.
- Yes.
Which later turned out
to have been fabricated.
Which Ted knew at the time,
and I didn't.
Now Ted's claiming that you both knew.
He can't reverse himself 8 years
after giving sworn testimony.
Well, he is.
And he's willing to go
on record with the press.
I don't know what to say,
except he's a liar.
It's your word against his.
David...
you have reason to be suspicious.
God knows,
you've been betrayed by some of
the people you've trusted most,
but I'm not sherry.
I told you the whole truth once.
I'm not going to defend it.
Because if there's anything less
than complete trust between us...
I do trust you, Anne.
You should.
Yes.
We need to talk, David.
I'm with Anne now.
Ah, let me guess…
She denied everything.
I believe her.
Yeah, well, listen, I might be able to make
this whole thing go away.
How?
Meet you in the auditorium...
alone.
All right.
So have you had a chance to take
a look at Nicole's field report yet?
Yeah. I'm almost done.
What are your impressions?
Based on what I've read
so far, I'm optimistic.
So you think we'll be able
to contain the virus?
At the very least, we should be
able to limit the casualties.
Even though the virus was airborne?
Well, there is some risk of it spreading,
but Nicole's team acted fast.
They evacuated and sealed off the apartment
building and quarantined the Singers.
- When do we get the test results?
- Five minutes, ten tops.
So looks like we lucked out, huh?
- Yeah, we deserve a little luck.
- All right, look,
I got to go. Make sure you keep me
in the loop, all right?
- Okay, you do the Same.
- Okay.
Tony, LAPD's setting up the perimeter, but they
need wind vectors for the last 15 minutes.
Call meteorology.
Extension 212.
Tony, local news picked up
the story about the dead body
being dumped at Health Services.
Great.
They want a statement.
What do you want me to tell them?
Nothing.
Tony, warden Mitchell is on the phone.
He's calling from the prison.
He says it's urgent.
Almeida.
Mr. and Mrs. Singer?
What the hell is going on here?
Because this is not about drugs.
We think you've been
exposed to a virus.
- A virus?
- It's called Cordillera Virus.
We believe that your son carried it in from
Mexico this morning without knowing.
What do you mean "carried it in"? How?
He thought he was carrying drugs.
So, we've been exposed?
I'm afraid so.
Wh-what does that mean?
Are we sick?
We're going to have to keep you quarantined
until we get the results back from your tests.
Excuse me for one moment.
- Yeah, this is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Tony.
Tony, I think Kyle Singer's
been exposed.
Yeah, we've already got
an all points out on him.
Have you set a perimeter?
Yeah. We're doing everything
we can to contain this thing.
All agencies and departments are
in the loop on a need-to-know basis.
- Okay, good work.
- Listen, Jack,
I know this isn't a best time to tell you, but
I just got some bad news.
I figured you'd want to know about it.
What's wrong?
Luis Annicon was murdered.
- Murdered, how?
- Salazar's guard.
We've got him in custody.
He claims that ...
Salazar had a son kidnapped
and threatened to kill him if he didn't do it.
Jack, I'm sorry. I know you
two worked closely on this case.
- Tony, I'm going to have to get back to you.
- Is everything okay?
- I'm going to get back to you.
- Jack?
- These results can't be right.
- They are.
- Check it again.
- I have.
Blood and saliva, atmospheric and
surface tests, they're all negative.
We can't find even a…
a trace amount of this virus.
What the hell are you doing?
You haven't showered down yet.
We're not at risk.
What are you talking about?
- I watched the powder get out.
- It's harmless, Jack.
Some form of silicate, but that's all.
- What?
- There is no virus in the powder.
We tested five Samples.
There weren't even trace amounts.
Atmospheric and surface
analysis also came up negative,
and Kyle's parents
tested negative, as well.
You're sure about this?
The only thing I'm not sure about
is if we're on the right trail.
No. No, the body that was dropped off
at Health Services was linked to Kyle Singer.
Why would Salazar's people pay him
to bring across a bag of worthless powder?
Fine, Jack, but where do we
even start looking?
I don't know.
Wait a second.
Macer said the only way to transport
the virus was in crystalline form, right?
Yeah, that's the only way it can
survive outside a living body.
What if it was never
outside a living body?
What do you mean?
What if the virus
was transported in a living host?
What if Kyle Singer was infected earlier
this morning in Mexico before he even left?
But Salazar has no leverage if Singer
was walking around, infecting people.
That's the point.
He wouldn't be contagious yet.
The incubation period is 14 hours.
Right. Think about it.
We know for a fact that Kyle Singer
was in Mexico 11 hours ago.
Hector Salazar hasn't threatened to
release the virus for another three hours.
The math adds up.
We need to find Kyle Singer.
- Hello?
- Linda.
Kyle, I told you, I have
nothing to say to you.
No, listen to me, okay?
I'm in trouble.
Yeah, because you're dealing drugs.
I need your help.
What happened?
My dad found the stuff.
We got in a fight,
I split, but he's still got it, okay?
And I got to get this them, all right?
These guys are hard core.
I got to make it right.
Make it right? How?
I know, I was thinking,
you know, maybe,
maybe I could pay them enough,
you know, just
- to keep them off my back. - You want me to give you money?
No, no, no, just borrow.
How much?
It's about 20 grand on the street.
I don't have that kind of money, Kyle.
Didn't you say your dad keeps
some cash around the house?
- Not that much.
- Linda, listen to me!
These guys...
they will kill me if I don't
give them something.
Please... please, anything
will help right now.
Now you want me to
get involved in this?
Just... please let me borrow
something, anything.
I'll pay you back,
I swear to god.
- Where are you?
- I'm at the mall.
- I'll get there as soon as I can.
- Thank you.
CTU knows the powder is not real.
Now they're going after Singer.
What do you want me to do?
Stay with him,
and as soon as he's alone,
- Grab him and take him into containment.
- Done.
You can't let the cops get him.
We need Singer to make this work.
Of course there's no way
we'll ever release Salazar.
CTU is very close to
containing the threat.
Yes, that's right.
All right, Stan.
I'll make sure you're kept in the loop.
What have we got, Wayne?
I just talked to Anne's ex-husband.
Now, listen, all Ted Packard
wants is money.
If we pay him off, he'll
recant before this debate.
That's blackmail.
- That's business.
- I don't think so.
David, it's a hell of a lot cheaper
than trying to defend against this allegation,
which is going to hurt you.
I've faced down worse lies.
I think I've earned some credibility.
You read the polls this morning?
Because Keeler is closing the gap,
and this race is much
closer than it should be.
And listen, I know
it's distasteful there, but
in cost-benefit terms,
it's a no brainer.
Anne won't think so.
- Anne doesn't have to know.
- I can't keep it from her.
Well, that's your choice.
But if this comes out,
Anne is going to find herself on the front
page of every single newspaper in this country,
and David, she's not Sherry. She's not
equipped to handle that kind of scrutiny,
and you will not be able
to protect her from it.
Now, between this debate
and the threat of this outbreak, you have
enough on your plate to worry about.
Don't be a martyr.
Keep it simple.
We could have the money
within the hour.
Do it.
What's going on?
They don't have their suits on.
What does that mean? Are we okay?
Yes. The powder was harmless.
Oh, thank god... then you put us
through all this for nothing.
- You scared the hell out of us.
- Mr. Singer, we still need to find your son.
Is there anything that you
can tell us that would help?
Why? You just said
the powder was harmless.
We believe that your son was infected
with the virus in Mexico earlier this morning
before he came home.
We have three hours to find him
before he becomes contagious.
What are you saying,
that our son could die?
- Yes, that could happen.
- Oh, god.
I know how difficult this must be for you,
and I'm sorry.
But we need to find your son,
we need to find him now.
- Have you tried his cell phone?
- Yes. The line's been disconnected.
No, wait. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
- He took my phone this morning.
- What's the number?
818-555-0103.
Okay.
I'm going to need
one of you to call him.
This is my fault.
I never would have done any of this
if I couldn't take care of my own family.
- No.
- Yes. You know, it's true.
Tony, it's Jack.
Yeah, Jack, I just spoke to LAPD.
They've got a priority APB on Singer.
Okay, good.
I think we've got a number on him.
All right, look,
we'll thread the line
through a tracing matrix.
Okay. The number is 818-555-0103.
I want you to route the call
back to my cell phone.
You got it.
I want you to trace that number and
reroute the call to Jack's cell phone.
I'm going to need one of
you to make the call now,
I need you to keep him on the line
as long as possible so we can trace him.
What am I supposed to tell him?
The truth.
Tony, you set?
Yeah, we're ready.
- Linda.
- Kyle, it's your father.
Dad?
We need to talk.
Look, I don't know what
you want to talk about.
I already know how
pissed off you are, okay?
Look, um,
whatever you did...
I know you were just trying
to help out your mom and me.
Yeah, well, look, unless you're willing
to give back the stuff you took,
I got to deal with the situation, okay?
Kyle! Please, don't hang up.
Please! Listen.
Listen to me.
What I'm telling you is
important. Please,
you have to come home.
Dad, why do you sound different?
I need you to trust me onsomething I'm about to tell you.
Dad?
You may have gotten a virus,
something you picked
up in Mexico.
How'd you know I went to Mexico?
It doesn't matter.
But you may be sick.
And if you are, then you need
to get checked out by a doctor.
Dad, I don't know what you're
talking about, all right?
- But I feel fine.
- I know it sounds crazy,
but it's real.
Now, there's e some people
here who are trying to help.
- Cops?
- No
Tony, have you got
a lock on this trace?
- We're going to lose this kid.
- How much longer?
I've got the cell tower, but it's
covering a three-mile radius.
I can't believe this.
This fight, one minute you
tell me that you love me,
the next minute, you're
selling me out to some cops.
They're not police, Kyle.
They're just trying to stop this virus
before it becomes an outbreak.
Dad, I already told youI feel fine, all right?
They're saying that you're not going to
start feeling sick for another few hours.
- But by then, it's going to be too late.
- Tony, have you got a lock yet?
How much longer?
10 seconds.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to turn myself in?
Because you may be sick.
And if you are, other people
are going to get infected.
- Tony...
- We got it, Jack.
He's at the Los Feliz Mall,
between Vermont and Sunset.
Okay, get his photograph
over to mall security.
Tell them not to approach him.
Look, Jack,
you're 20 minutes away by car,
I can land a team there in ten minutes.
Fine.
Tony, I don't want you taking Chase.
- Why not?
- I just don't.
Thank you very much.
We'll notify you as soon
as we have him in custody.
Please, help our son.
We will.
O'Brian.
Chloe, I'm not sure you've heard yet,
But Tony's heading off site for a while.
He is?
Yeah. I'm taking over for a few hours.
- Okay.
- Let people in your area know.
- Okay, I will.
- Thanks.
What was that?
Michelle. She's taking over CTU
for a couple of hours.
Where's Tony?
They have a location on Singer.
Jack can't get there
in time, so Tony's going.
What? Tony's not field ops.
Seems like they're really going out of
their way to cut you out of the loop.
Did you do something
to piss off Jack?
Bad idea, Chase. You're just
going to make things worse.
Tony...
I just heard they found Kyle Singer.
Is this for real?
We'll see. I'm meeting Jack
over there right now.
Look, I'm done with this kid Parker.
He's said all he's gonna say.
- I want back on the case.
- Yeah, well,
we're handling it now,
Chase, all right?
Because Jack doesn't
want me there, right?
Did he tell you why he's cutting me out?
I don't really care.
He's your boss, it's his call.
This isn't right.
Did he tell you this is because of Kim?
He found out we were seeing each other,
and this is how he's going to make me pay for it.
Take it up with Jack.
Just want to keep the line open for Tony.
Leave a message for Jack Bauer.
Damn it, Jack.
Chase.
Look, I know my dad can be hard,
but he will come around.
How do you know?
Because I know my father.
Maybe you don't know him
as well as you think.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
It's okay. Forget it, Kim.
Don't you think I feel
bad enough already?
Because I do.
We shouldn't have told him.
Well, the only other option I can think of
is for us to stop seeing each other,
which as far as I'm concerned,
is not an option.
Or is it?
- Chase, what do you want?
- I want to be able to do my job.
Kim, we need you at your station.
Tony's about to land.
Tony Almeida, CTU.
I think we found
the guy you're looking for.
He's in the rotunda.
- Bronson, lock down the east exit.
- Yes, sir.
Pierson, I want you to run point
from the security office.
Alright.
How long have you been using, Jack?
What?
I did a rotation in rehab. You learn to
pick out when someone's using.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You know exactly what I'm talking about.
How long?
For a while now.
It was the only way I could maintain
my cover with the Salazars.
- Are you high now?
- No.
- It's empty, Jack.
- Nicole, I told you I'm fine.
- I'm not so sure.
- If you're not so sure, then turn me in.
I don't want to turn you in, Jack.
I'm worried about you.
You don't have to be.
I've kicked it.
I have a responsibility to stop this virus,
and I am taking a calculated risk that
you are more of an asset than a liability.
Just please don't screw this up.
I won't.
- Yeah?
- Hey, Jack,
Security found Singer.
I'm about to pick him up.
Okay, where are you?
Second floor rotunda,
top of the north escalator.
Where are you?
We're coming into
the loading dock, north entrance.
- Have you got a visual?
- Yeah, I got him.
- Where have you placed your men?
- We posted at all the main entrances.
Okay, good.
We should be there in a minute.
All right.
Have your men cover
all the parking level exits.
Let's go!
I don't want to cause any kind of commotion.
- Yeah?
- CTU's here.
They're about
to move in on the kid.
Just stand down.
It's too hot.
This is my only chance.
We can't let the kid get caught.
- No, no, wait.
- I can't wait. Gomez!
Wait here, I want to make a clean grab.
Yes, sir.
Kyle.
Who are you?
My name's Tony Almeida.
I'm a federal agent, but
I'm here to help you.
What your father told you
about your being sick is true.
I don't believe you.
You come with me,
I'll prove it to you.
Get out of the way! Move!
Nicole, he's been hit in the neck!
Jamie, give me your walkie-talkie.
We have an officer down.
Kyle Singer is not in custody.
I repeat, Kyle Singer is not in custody.
Maintain cover on all exits.
www.tvsubtitles.net