Previously on 24
Tony Almeida from CTU
has just informed us
that they were unable to confiscate
this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
This man Amador,
where is he now?
Latest working theory is that
Amador has this virus,
and is headed back
here to Los Angeles.
I let you live.
Tell me what you know.
Any time Amador does business
on the west coast,
he washes his deal through
a man named Alvers.
How does Amador contact this Alvers?
I don't know.
I've never met him.
Hello?
Marcus, it's me.
I'll be there in an hour.
Got the virus?
Yes.
Just be ready.
I will be.
I got to go see Julia Milliken.
No. I don't want you to go
anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
Julia...
My pills.
No, don't.
- What are you doing?
- Don't.
- Sherry?
- This is your way out.
- We killed him.
- No.
There's one thing you're
going to have to be really clear about,
when the authorities come
around questioning you.
I was never here.
The following takes place
between 2:00 a.m. and 3:00 a.m.
Point Mugu Naval Air Station
I got her.
- Agent Bauer.
- Yeah?
I'm Jason Carusone from Division.
These men will be escorting
the prisoner back to CTU.
She doesn't leave my sight.
I know. You can accompany her
in the lead van.
Let's go!
This is Carusone.
Yeah. Yeah, he's right here.
Agent Edmunds.
It's Chloe O'brian from your office.
Hey, Jack, I'll take another car.
Okay.
Yeah, Chloe?
Chase, they found out.
Who found out what?
Everybody here
found out about Angela.
They all know she's your daughter.
What? How?
The baby-sitter flaked. She had
a family emergency and brought her here.
You brought Angela into CTU?
What was I supposed to do?
Your sister's out of town.
There is no one else.
You have no idea what I've been
through in the past couple of hours.
Okay, okay, okay.
Chloe, thank you for covering.
I appreciate it.
But where is Angela right now?
She's downstairs with Marcy
until you get back.
Did Kim find out?
Chloe, did Kim find out?
Yes, yes, Kim found out.
How did she react?
Uh, gosh, Chase, I think
she's kind of pissed.
All right, listen.
I'm coming back to CTU right now.
I'll take care of everything.
Bye.
Here's the situation:
We believe Michael Amador is
in possession of the Cordilla virus.
We believe he is either headed to
LosAngeles or he's here already.
We estimate he has enough of the pathogen
to take out a major metropolitan area.
Our only lead is Nina Myers, who's
being brought back to CTU right now.
She thinks Amador is meeting
with a man here in Los Angeles
by the name of Marcus Alvers.
Adam's done a workup on him.
We have some background, but there's nothing
that places him definitively in Los Angeles today.
That's it?
What about interpol?
What do they have on Alvers?
Our data tracking's a little behind,
so we weren't able
to access that report.
Why are we behind?
We didn't update the European
contact logs while I was down.
Michelle,
you were the ranking agent.
I didn't think Europe was a priority.
Obviously it was.
There was a lot going on at the time.
All right.
Let's get back to work.
And let's try to ease up on the
mistakes for the rest of the night
as there are millions of lives
depending on us.
Michelle...
Come.
I just got off with CTU.
What's the status on the virus?
Well, it's not good.
The limited intelligence they have
supports their original suspicion.
It's on its way to Los Angeles.
David, it may already be here.
Then we should be prepared
in case they target other cities.
Our people in the security
envelope have been alerted.
Trust me, it's being handled.
Now, why don't you try
and go get some rest?
I'm on this.
Mr. President,
Mrs. Palmer's here to see you.
Send her in, please.
Start waking people up.
Set up a conference call with
the appropriate cabinet members:
Homeland security, FBI,
National Health Services.
We're going to need
everyone on this one.
Yes, sir.
Wayne?
Sherry, I asked you here to help me,
not make things worse.
I did not want you going
to Alan Milliken's house.
Well, relax, David.
I didn't go there.
- You didn't go?
- No.
When we spoke on the phone,
you told me it was crucial
that you speak to Julia in person.
Yes, and I changed my mind.
I-I spoke to her over the phone.
About what?
About Kelly's disappearance.
I asked her if she would check
Alan's cell phone and
see if there were
any recently made calls.
And?
She wouldn't do it.
You don't take no
for an answer, Sherry.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing, David, I swear.
What have you been up to since we
last talked if you weren't at Milliken's?
Making calls.
You could have made
them from here.
Yes, but I didn't.
I parked on the side of the road,
I started making calls
because I didn't want to wait.
I told you we have a small
window of opportunity here.
I wanted to exploit the fact
that Milliken may not have had time
to cover his tracks
when he had someone grab Kelly.
All right.
I have other things to attend to.
Okay.
Is there anything else?
That's it.
Hello, Nina.
Take her to interrogation 819.
Yes, sir.
What's the security configuration?
Don't worry about it, Jack.
We're handling Nina.
Ryan, you know
what she's capable of.
That's none of your
concern right now.
I'm sending you to medical
to get checked out.
I'm fine.
I don't think you are.
What's this about?
We found evidence
you've been injecting heroin.
Tell me I'm off here, Jack.
Tell me I'm wrong.
I didn't think so.
Ryan, I haven't missed a step.
I'm fine.
I have to cover my ass.
- I need to get you checked out.
- You're wasting time.
- Kim.
- Yeah?
I thought you'd want to
know your dad's back.
What about Chase?
Uh, he's a few minutes behind.
Thank you.
Kim.
Dad.
Oh, god. Hi.
She's here.
I know, sweetheart.
I know. Come here.
Look, I have to debrief Chappelle.
I'll see you in a minute, okay?
Dad, I know about
your drug problem.
Why didn't you come
to me with this?
Come here.
I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry.
I was embarrassed.
And it wasn't your problem,
and it still isn't.
I didn't want you to worry.
Well, is it over?
No, not exactly.
I think I'm going to have to go into
a program, and get some help.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
Chappelle wants me to go into
the clinic and get checked out.
- We'll talk about this later, okay?
- Okay.
Don't worry.
- I love you.
- Me, too.
Okay.
Jack.
I'm glad you're back.
It's been difficult without you.
Thanks, Chloe.
- Chase.
- Yeah.
- Need to talk to you.
- Okay.
Why don't you take a few minutes
and come to my office.
Yeah, sure.
Mr. Milliken?
Mr. Milliken? Oh, my god.
Mrs. Milliken!
Come quickly!
Quickly!
Hey.
How's the hand?
It's fine.
How'd Chappelle find out?
I don't know,
it doesn't really matter.
What's going on out there?
Almeida's going to be
interrogating Nina,
and I'll follow it from a feed.
Okay, good.
Make sure Tony puts double
security on the doors.
Get back to me as soon
as she gives you anything.
Agent Bauer, keep pressure here.
Sure. Thank you.
Jack,
you're about to find something out about
me that's not going to make you happy.
What are you talking about?
Excuse me. Do you mind?
I've got a daughter.
- A daughter?
- It was sprung on me a month ago.
Her mother dropped her off,
and she split.
It's a long story.
Does Kim know about this?
Yeah.
From you?
I haven't had a chance
to talk to her myself yet.
You square this with her, Chase,
you understand me?
Just make that right.
And get back to me as soon
as Nina gives you anything.
I will.
Are we up yet?
Yep. Video's piped in,
voice analysis,
vitals, transcription.
- We're all set.
- Nick, do you copy?
- Yeah, I read you.
- We're ready to go.
All right, recording
to hard drive now.
So, Tony's doing this?
Yeah.
Is that going to be weird for you?
What do you mean?
Didn't-didn't he and Nina go out?
Yeah.
We set?
All right.
I want you to do
a hi-res on her eyes.
She's tired.
We might be able to pick up a tell.
Okay.
So, we all right?
Yeah. We're fine.
All right.
Let's do this.
I got the hi-res on monitor two.
Tony.
Didn't know I was gonna
see you today.
You know what we want.
We need to find Michael Amador
before he unloads the virus.
I've already told Jack
everything I know.
Well, I want you to tell me.
First Jack, now you.
Hmm... what does that
remind me of?
You told Jack that Amador might
try to contact a Marcus Alvers.
So, where do we look for Alvers?
That's a nice ring.
Who's the lucky girl?
Hope you did a background
check, though, 'cause
you don't want to make
the same mistake twice.
You're going back to prison.
There's a good chance
you'll be executed as a traitor.
Now you know if you cooperate,
you may be able to save your own life,
but you're stalling.
Which means you know something
and you still think there's
a play you can make,
only now's not the right time.
Very incisive.
I hope your wife appreciates
that about you.
Why don't you tell me
about Alvers?
All I know is that he works
only with Amador.
I don't know him personally.
All we've been able to dig up on him
are a few random medical records
under one of his known aliases.
He had an MRI on
one of his knees,
there's a prescription for antibiotics,
treated for HIV...
Her pulse is spiking.
Someone hasn't been using
protection with Marcus Alvers.
She's probably had sex with him.
See, Nina,
my colleagues in the next room
tell me that something in those
medical records concerns you.
I'm guessing
it's not the knee.
I'm here to see Alvers.
Marcus.
Michael.
How was your trip?
Interesting.
I still don't understand why you
risked so much down in Mexico,
why you didn't
come here directly.
240 million dollars
made it worth the risk.
What about Nina?
If she wasn't killed by the bomb,
I'm sure our buyers took care of her once
they found out she didn't deliver the virus.
Either way,
she's out of the picture.
I hope so.
She can point to both of us.
We'll be long gone
before anyone starts looking.
Kim.
Look, I know we haven't talked
since I got back.
No, we haven't.
I know what you must be thinking,
but you need to give me
a chance to explain.
I don't know what to think.
Look, I'm happy that you're okay,
but this thing...
you have a baby, Chase.
We've been together for
more than three months,
and you kept this secret from me.
Who's the mother?
Where does she fit into this?
That's what I want
to talk to you about.
I didn't know I had a daughter
until a month ago.
How could you not know?
Angela's mother and I
went out last year.
Okay, it's over.
And when it ended,
she never told me
she was pregnant.
Now she calls a month ago
and tells me she has a baby,
and that I'm the father.
And she's in trouble,
and she can't handle it.
I was afraid to let
people find out.
I was afraid it was
gonna mess us up.
But you told Chloe.
Chloe and my sister have been
helping me take care of the baby.
She's a good friend.
Excuse me. Chase?
You wanted me to let you know
when Angela woke up.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Kim, I'm just as confused as you are.
But all I know is
that I love you.
And I'm falling in love
with Angela, too.
And I need to make this work.
Go on.
What's happening with
Nina in interrogation?
They're getting something.
What?
The connection between Alvers
and Nina might be deeper than we thought.
You'd better hope she's not
just spinning your wheels,
because she knows how to manipulate
our interrogation protocol.
Tony knows what he's doing.
Okay, fine. Look, I need to
get together with Chloe.
I need everything that she's got
on the Amador investigation.
Not yet.
Ryan, look,
you're wasting my time.
Now, I humored you
with the physical.
And we both know that my blood
work's gonna come back
with trace amounts of opiates,
but enough is enough.
Rae Plachecki from the inspector
general's office is here.
She wants to talk to you.
- Well, this is not the time.
- Actually, it is.
You'll talk to her,
then we'll evaluate whether you
can go back to work or not.
Come on.
Rae Plachecki,
this is Jack Bauer.
You know the drill, Jack.
I'm gonna ask you some questions,
but I want you to know,
I'm on your side.
We just want to establish that this heroin
addiction was a necessary part of your cover.
It was necessary
to maintain my cover.
Are we done now?
Sit down, Jack.
This is Rae Plachecki.
The time is 2:31 A.M.
This is the interrogation of Jack Bauer,
director of field ops, CTU.
Ryan Chappelle is present.
Jack,
tell us how you established
your cover with Ramon Salazar.
I first came in contact
with the Salazars
approximately two years ago.
They were an up-and-coming
narcotic cartel, coming out of Mexico.
So, when did you meet Amador?
Did you know him when
you were working at CTU?
Tell me something, Nina,
what kind of a deal
you think you're gonna cut?
You've betrayed
everybody you know,
including me.
You murdered Jack's wife.
You helped terrorists smuggle
a nuclear bomb into this country.
You're helping to unleash a deadly
virus into the general population.
Help me understand this.
What do you want?
What is it you get out of
being a mass murderer?
Your neck is bleeding.
Dalton, what do you got?
So far, the only reactions we're
getting from her are subliminal.
If she's not gonna say anything,
we need to be more plugged in to her vitals.
We can take her down to seven,
give her a passive response test.
Seven's not secure enough.
She stays here.
Where's Richards?
He's waiting.
All right, let's bring him in.
Send Darren in.
Nina, I don't think you've
met Darren Richards.
He joined us after you left.
Hello, Darren.
Don't take it personally.
He doesn't talk much.
Uh, something's not
connecting up for me, Jack.
You say that you weren't in with
the Salazars until early February,
but the first time you started
using was late December.
That's six weeks of shooting up
for the benefit of no one.
Am I missing something?
I was trying to pass
myself off as a junkie.
I wanted to be prepared.
What do you mean, "prepared"?
The Salazars lived their
entire lives in the drug world.
If I couldn't handle the narcotics
that went with that territory,
they'd have known I was a cop,
and they'd have killed me.
I needed to be able to handle it.
Yeah, that makes sense,
but in January,
when you were
putting needles in your arm,
you didn't have a meeting
on the books with these guys--
it could have been a year,
for all you knew.
What are you saying?
I am trying to establish incontrovertible
evidence that you did drugs
as part of your cover--
if I submit what you just told me,
it's not gonna hold up, Jack.
What do you want me to say?!
I did drugs to get in
with these people,
and I got in with them!
And no matter how difficult
it's been, I don't use anymore.
Look,
I'll write it up that way,
and maybe it'll fly,
but I just think you're
gonna have a problem
because you never told anyone,
not even your partner.
That's suspicious.
Rae, you know my history.
I've had a very difficult time
since my wife passed away.
If I'd told anyone that I was
using drugs to develop a case,
they would have misinterpreted,
and I couldn't afford that risk.
Yeah, well, that's what
they're gonna do now.
Rae,
let's put down that Jack started
using heroin in late January,
after the first meeting
with Salazar was established.
I appreciate what you're
trying to do, Ryan,
but that's not what happened.
Just trying to save us all
some paperwork.
I'm okay with that.
I'm not.
I started using in December.
I've got nothing to hide.
This office demands results,
and that's what I provide:
Results.
Fine.
Can I get back to work?
Not quite yet, Jack.
No, it's secure and we have it.
It will be as arranged.
He'll be here in an hour.
Just as long as we have enough time to leave
the country before they let this virus out.
Please be seated.
Five hours ago,
I went public with a statement that
there was a domestic terror threat,
but it had passed.
And now it appears that
that was premature.
Ladies and gentlemen,
do we or do we not have a threat
of this virus being released?
Sir,
I'm afraid we can't answer that
question with any kind of certainty.
What can you tell me,
Mr. Hammond?
What few leads we have
indicate that Michael Amador has
the virus and is in Los Angeles.
For what purpose,
we can't say.
Then we have to prepare
for defensive action here in Los Angeles.
And for that matter,
in all of our major cities.
Mr. President,
you know our position
here at homeland security.
We think being forthright
with the public and
making such preparations in
the open is the correct course.
Again, we have to assess
the downside of that course.
I have no problem
with that, Mr. President,
as long as we realize
we are working against a clock.
I want all departments present
to work up an open versus covert
containment strategy
and report back to me in 30 minutes.
In the meantime, I want
Health Services to issue guidelines,
but only to be
distributed internally.
That is all.
I'll be in my office.
David.
Give us a second, please, Aaron.
Of course, sir.
Secret Service just
received a phone call
from the west Los Angeles
police department.
Alan Milliken is dead.
What?
He was found 15 minutes ago
in his home.
All signs point
to a heart attack.
It isn't possible.
Well, apparently, it is.
You told me Sherry was on her way
over there about an hour ago.
She changed her mind.
Made some phone calls
from her car.
Came straight back here.
David, is that what she told you?
Yeah.
And where is she now?
Resting.
Aaron, take me to Sherry.
Yes, sir.
She's right this way.
Hasn't your shift ended?
I stayed on.
I sense it's a difficult day, and
I wanted to be here for you.
- I appreciate that.
- Right in there, sir.
Sherry.
David.
What's wrong?
Alan Milliken is dead.
What? How?
Why don't you tell me?
What do you mean?
I told you,
I didn't go there.
I know what you told me.
You sat in your car,
you made some phone calls,
and you came straight here.
Yes, and that's the truth.
Then you won't mind the police
checking your cell phone
and the car you used tonight.
You know...
you asked me
to take care of a problem, and I did.
If you want the police
to check phone logs, then
have them check yours first.
Because remember?
You called me tonight.
I am here because
of you, David.
What happened, Sherry?
I went over to the house
just to speak to Julia.
Alan interrupted us.
There was an argument and...
he had a heart attack.
There's going to be an investigation.
You're going to have to
tell the truth about this.
The truth isn't going to
save either one of us.
All they're going to hear
is that I was there on your behalf
to prevent Alan from meddling
with your presidency,
and that he died
from natural causes.
Now, how do you think
that's going to play out
in the New York Times
for the next six months?
What did you do to Alan?
Honestly, David,
nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Kim,
I transferred that feed
to your system.
Do you want me
to pull it up for you now?
Yeah
I don't think she's going to
give them anything.
We're going to have to find
Marcus Alvers by ourselves.
What can I do?
Um, I followed up on some
of those Asian connections,
but in the meantime, there's
something I want you to look at.
- It's a long shot.
- What is it?
A list of cities where Marcus Alvers
has been in the last three years.
Each time only
for a couple of days.
Maybe he was meeting somebody.
Cross it with the other suspects
in our database.
Let me know what
you come up with, okay?
Okay.
Look, I don't know why we
have to go through this again.
I already answered that.
What is it, Edmunds?
Just wanted to give you
an update on Nina.
Rae, could you pause that?
She give us anything
new on Alvers?
No,
other than the probability
she knew him personally.
She's not cooperating.
What are we doing?
Richards is working on her now.
I think that's a mistake.
Why? /I don't think anybody should be
in there that hasn't worked with her before,
doesn't know what she's capable of.
She'll manipulate him.
All Richards does is inflict pain.
There's no way for her
to manipulate him.
All right.
How much more of this
you want to endure, Nina?
I think this is about it.
- She hit an artery!
- Michelle, call medical!
No, she's bleeding too much.
We got to take her there now!
- Tell security!
- We need someone from medical.
- Interrogation room 819.
- Uncuff her.
Now!
So what did Sherry have to say?
That Alan had a heart attack.
And you believe her?
I'd be a fool to believe anything
Sherry says to save herself.
But murder?
I can't imagine she'd do that.
David, we can't allow ourselves
to be caught off guard this time.
Now we have to assume the worst.
Then we'd also have to assume
that Julia was somehow involved.
What?
Whoa, whoa, listen.
David, I'm sorry, but Julia's not
the same kind of person that Sherry is.
When we find out all the facts,
we'll proceed from there.
I have to go over
the morning brief with Jerry.
All right.
- Hello?
- Julia, it's me.
Wayne?
I just heard about Alan, and I...
are you alone?
The police are here.
I'm was just going to speak
with one of the officers.
All right, tell me
what happened.
Wayne, Sherry was here
when it happened,
but she told me
not to tell the police.
Julia, I need for you to tell me exactly
what happened over there, all right?
We were talking with Alan.
He got excited,
then he started to gasp for air.
He gets angina.
So you called 911, right?
No, no.
I-I tried to give him
his medication.
What do you mean you tried?
Sherry stopped me.
I went to help Alan,
but she grabbed my arm.
I just stood there.
I-I couldn't,
I couldn't move.
I... I...
- I killed him, Wayne.
- Shh, shh, shh.
All right, listen to me
carefully, all right?
I killed him.
Call Alan's lawyer, and
do not say anything,
anything to anyone
until he gets there.
You understand me?
Wayne, could you come
down here and help me?
No, and please don't call me.
I will help you, Julia, I will,
but for right now I have to keep
my distance, I'm sorry.
Excuse me, coming through.
- Let's move, right here.
- Okay, swing it.
Come on, come on, let's go!
One, two, three.
Carotid's been lacerated.
Start a twilight drip.
Yes, doctor.
Clamp.
Keep steady pressure.
3-0 silks.
3-0 standing by.
More gauze.
Gauze.
- Got it open.
- Okay, clamp it.
Here you go, doctor.
- Keep the pressure on.
- Yes, sir.
Let's get some more
gauze in here.
Okay, she's under.
I want you two
stationed right here.
Do not leave unless
you hear directly from me.
Okay, Jack, those are all
the questions I'm obliged to ask.
If you got anything else
you want to add, Jack,
now would be the time.
That's my statement, as it is.
My god, Tony.
Nina tried to commit suicide.
She jammed her neck
into Richards' needle,
ruptured an artery.
Where is she now?
She's in the clinic
being operated on.
Who's with her?
Don't worry, Jack, she's sedated.
I saw her go under.
Who's with her now?
Tony, who's with her?!
Damn it!
Which way did she go?
Lock down the building!
This is Ryan Chappelle.
Nina Myers is loose
in the building.
Lock it down, now!
Nina,
drop the gun
and put your hands
on your head,
now!
Kim.
What the hell are you doing?
You don't want to be
any part of this.
Shut up.
Just turn around
and walk away.
If you leave now,
you won't get hurt.
Kim.
Don't do it, Nina.
I swear to god, I'll shoot you.
You won't kill me.
Nina, damn it.
Kim, back up.
Back up.
Kim, I want you to go back into
CTU, tell them we got Nina.
- Dad, listen to me. We need...
- Kim, go now!
Please, baby, just go.
Go.
You don't have any more useful
information, do you, Nina?
I do.
No, you don't.
www.tvsubtitles.net