Hey, by the way, thanks
for keepin' me company.
And miss a chance to ride
out to the country? Sure.
Maybe you and jim will
move out here someday.
No. Jim is a city boy.
I think village square is about
as country as he's gonna get.
I never thought this
house would sell.
Yeah, you and me both.
It's changed hands
4 times in 10 years.
Well, you know what they say.
It is the most haunted house...
In driscoll county.
I think it's not selling
'cause it's a money pit,
Not because of the ghosts.
Wow. This from you?
Vacant houses usually
aren't haunted.
No?
They need the energy of
the living to feed off of.
There are more ghosts
in dentists' offices
Than there are in an
abandoned house like this.
Oh. Well, that must explain
my dentist's bad breath.
Eww.
Hey! My first guests. Come on in.
Hey. Steve, i
- I hope you don't mind i brought a friend.
This is melinda rdon. Hi.
I'm sorry. I just had
hand-To-Hand combat with a saw,
And the saw won.
Ouch. Yeah.
That word came in
handy a lot today,
Along with a few others, huh?
Well, i was just stopping by
to see how you were settling in,
If you needed anything.
Uh, yeah, a how-To
book on power tools.
This is my daughter.
Hi. Marlo, pioneer girl.
Do your horses need some feed?
Wagon wheels need a-Fixin'?
Marlo's just annoyed because the
closest mall is 10 miles away.
No, i'm annoyed because my
friends are a hundred miles away.
Anyway, i just have a couple papers
I need you to sign
from the title company.
Yeah, sure.
You know, i think i'm
gonna clean up my thumb.
I'd rather not sign in blood.
Well, you're gonna,
whether you want to or not.
Hey, you work at an antique
store, too, don't you?
Uh, yeah. That's my boss.
Oh. Hi.
Hi.
I found some really
cool old board games.
I was gonna keep some of them-
There's not a ton of entertainment
here at the homestead.
But i was wondering if you
could tell me what they're worth?
Sure. I could take a look at 'em.
Oh, perfect.
Have you ever heard
of a game called, uh...
Twister?
You wanna come and
check out the games?
No. I'm good. I'm
just gonna explore.
Ok.
Yep. This game. I'm not sure if
all the pieces are here, though.
This is a great game, yahtzee.
You've never played?
Never played it.
Is someone here?
Hello.
I can help you.
Who are you?
One of them will die.
Are you ok?
Wonder when this tipped.
Floor's rotted through underneath.
Made a little river
all through the ceiling.
What a mess.
I'm gonna see if marlo's
finished cleanin' herself up,
And i'll bring up some
paper towels and...
I'll bring her back up here.
You know, for a minute there...
You almost thought
there was a ghost?
No.
Have to remember my rule.
What rule?
Rational explanation
for almost everything.
Right.
Do you know why they moved?
You know, steve lost his
wife a few years back.
He said that marlo was having
A hard time in high school,
And i guess it was just too painful
To stay in the house.
Oh, that is so sad.
It's really hard on a kid
when they lose a parent.
Yeah.
It can be hard on
the other parent, too.
So do you know what happened?
Do you know why she died?
No. He didn't say.
I don't know if...
Wait. I know that
tone in your voice.
You are asking for a reason.
I saw something, someone.
Are you saying that you saw
a ghost in steve's house?
In the garage, actually.
What? It's just that-
I mean, there's always a damn ghost
Everywhere you go. What is that?
Ok, i wish they weren't
always there, too, believe me.
But it's not like i go
out looking for them.
Don't you?
What?
Look, i'm sorry.
It's just that marlo and steve
Have been through so much.
They just need a clean start.
They don't need to
hear about ghosts
And have their whole
lives turned around.
Yeah, but what if the
ghost is marlo's mother?
Melinda, they especially
don't need to hear that.
They need time to heal.
There's obviously a-
A rational explanation. Well,
it's not always that easy.
I am just asking you
to give them some peace.
It's up to the ghost, not me.
Fine.
You're gonna do
what you're gonna do.
I just sometimes
don't understand her.
I mean, what's it
gonna take, you know?
After all she's seen,
she can't just say,
"Ok, i get it. There's ghosts. "
Well, sometimes what
people don't believe
Is just as important to
them as what they do believe,
And some people feel better
Thinkin' that there's
nothin' after we die.
You didn't have a
hard time believing.
Well, it was because
i believed you.
Also, i don't know...
What?
Come on.
I always wanted to believe.
I mean, i always wanted to
believe that there was more.
I mean, after my father died,
I wanted to think that
everything we do here
Does not come to
nothing. And then...
There was melinda.
So what do you think?
Should i just stay out of it,
Let the family live in peace?
Hey, who says they're in peace?
I think you can cross this
ghost over quickly and quietly-
In, out, nobody gets hurt.
Ha. Famous last words.
Are you here?
You scared me.
What are you doing in my garage?
I'm sorry. Um, it's
just that the, uh-
The furniture, it's so interesting.
Um, we could sell some of
it for you if you wanted.
I had a little something for marlo.
That's ok. I'd like to give
it to her myself, if i could.
It's adorable. Thank you so much.
It suits her.
I have to keep her in here,
'Cause my dad's not
crazy about cats.
How's your dad doing? He seemed-
Moody?
Right.
He's been doin' pretty
well since my mom died.
What was her name?
Liz. Short for lisbeth.
She hated being called lisbeth.
Must be hard for you,
Moving and all, not knowing anyone.
She got me.
What?
My mom.
She-She got me.
She was the only one.
Well, i'm sure your father-
I know.
But not like her.
Now i don't think
anybody ever will.
Sometimes i think he
blames me for what happened.
What happened?
Where's dora?
I hope she didn't
go in my dad's room.
Hang on.
Liz?
What happened?
The cat, it died.
What did you do to her?
I didn't do anything to her.
I just found her like that.
Might have been some
rat poison or something.
I'm sorry, honey.
Steve, are you ok?
Yeah.
She sure did like that cat.
Yeah?
Hey. Steve. I'm so
sorry to bug you,
But i just thought i could walk
you through these county tax...
Rebate forms.
You know, it's a great program,
Especially if you plan on
putting any money into the place.
What's wrong with the place?
Well, you know. I
mean, whatever you do
For improvements, things like that.
I like the place
just the way it is.
Ok. Well, then, um, i could just-
Just forget it.
If it makes life easier,
he's not interested.
Yeah, well, you're the
expert on easy livin'.
Never do today what you can
put off till tomorrow, right?
What are you saying? I'm lazy?
You didn't think i was lazy
When certain things had to
be done to a certain person.
I should have stopped you.
That's easy to say now,
But you had too much
to gain, didn't you?
As long as i was doing it, you
weren't gonna stand in my way.
You know, it looks like
i came at a bad time,
So i'm just gonna
leave these over here.
Bad time for what?
Um, to sign the tax rebate form.
It's ok. I can just leave it.
If i sign it, will you
get the hell out of here?
Um, yeah.
It was like they were
2 different people.
It was so eerie.
Like they were in a trance?
Yeah, exactly. And
they kept talking about
Having done something to somebody,
And marlo said that her dad had
too much to gain to stop her. Weird.
Could they have been
talking about marlo's mother?
Well, why would you think steve would have
done something to the mother of his child?
Because of this.
"Liz sinclair, 36,
of oak hills died
"In a fatal fall
from a hiking trail
"In the northwest section
of ryden state park.
"Her hiking companions,
husband steven sinclair, 37,
"And daughter marlo,
15, were unharmed.
"Sinclair was questioned
late into the night
"By the county sheriff and
released the next morning.
Officials would make
no further comment. "
Yeah. Well, obviously
they let him go.
Yeah, which only means
they had no proof.
I mean, it could explain
why liz is haunting him.
Then again, marlo did
say that steve blames her.
Maybe she's haunting marlo.
Wait, wait, wait. Just hold on.
Did you say anything
The last time you were there
about ghosts or hauntings?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah, of course i'm sure. Why?
I don't know. Maybe it's like
Power of suggestion, you know?
They think they're haunted,
So then they just
start acting like it.
Ok, i love you
Like a sister, really, i do,
But you are the
most stubborn person
I have met in my entire life.
I mean, you will twist
yourself up into a pretzel
Trying to rationalize some-
I'm sorry, i'm just looking for
a logical reason for them to-
Oh, you mean the believable
reason, not the real reason,
But the easy reason.
Whatever makes you comfortable.
Let me get this straight.
Daddy and daughter move to the
country to get away from it all.
There's a ghost in the
garage that predicts
That one of them will be dead soon.
The cat turns up
somewhat less than alive,
And daddy buries it like it's
just another day of yardwork.
And this morning...
And this morning, delia
goes over to the house
And finds herself in the middle
of who's afraid of virginia woolf?
What are you doing?
Oh. I'm, uh-I'm trying
A radical new technique
to my class lectures.
What? Preparation.
Ok, so what am i looking
at with this ghost?
You're looking at, uh...
A little more jack nicholson,
little less linda blair.
Meaning?
Meaning it's not like there's a
demon taking over their bodies.
It sounds like there's a spirit
influencing them from the outside,
Controlling their
behavior from time to time.
It's called "oppression. "
You mean "possession. "
No. I say what i mean. I
mean what i say, damn it.
I said, "oppression. "
Ok, oppression. Sorry.
Never heard of it.
Basically it's when a
spirit controls a body
Without ever entering inside of it.
It's a bit like
hypnotic suggestion.
In essence, it directs how
it wants the body to behave,
And what's really
creepy is over time,
The person begins to act
more and more like that ghost.
It's possession lite, if you will.
It's all the bad manners
with half the head-Spinning.
Ok, so why not go
full-On possession?
Ah, possession, that's
a tool used by demons,
Spirits that never walked
the earth in human form,
Whereas oppression these are-These
are used by earthbound spirits,
Earthbound spirits
that are very stubborn
And will do whatever it
takes to get what they want.
Which is?
That's for the ghost to
know and for you to find out.
Ok, so how do i get the ghost
to stop, to leave them alone?
That's hard to say. I'm not
sure, but i do know this.
You have to be careful,
because an oppressive spirit
They will really take
advantage of any weakness,
Any vulnerability
that their host has-
A mental illness,
emotional turmoil.
Turmoil like, "i killed a loved
one"? That kind of turmoil?
Oh. Ok, i was thinking more
like white slacks in november,
But sure, that would work also.
Steve?
Hey. Uh, i-I'm sorry that
i didn't call first. I just-
You play from your
head, not your heart.
That's why you lose.
I don't always lose.
Sometimes just let you win.
Why?
Mess with your head a little bit,
False confidence
- Things like that.
Heh. You think i'm
falsely confident?
Why don't you make yourself
useful and go get me a drink?
Good idea.
Liz?
Stop it!
You're not liz
sinclair. Who are you?
You see me, don't you?
Leave them alone.
Matt, we have more company.
Whoa. It's scary when they
look right at you like that.
Marlo, look, i don't
know if you can hear me,
But you're being used.
I- I know that you can't see
them, but you- You can feel them.
Steve, please listen to me, ok?
You don't know what's happening.
Both of you get out of
this house right now!
Steve.
What did you do?
My daughter.
Where's my daughter?
She right here. She's fine.
She's goin' with you.
Hey, stay with these 2 guys.
They'll take care
of you, all right?
You're playing too rough.
You're gonna break them
like you broke the others.
You're just a sore loser.
No, i am not.
It's just that these two
are too perfect to lose.
I mean, all that guilt, i
can practically taste it.
What the hell are you two doing?
Sorry. It's a private game.
Oh, is that what this is? You just
play with them like they're toys?
None of your business. Buh-Bye.
Melinda.
Is he gonna be all right?
Zenorex prescribed
to steven sinclair.
Yeah, this is good news, actually.
It's an antidepressant.
He'd have to take a lot
of these to be fatal.
This guy just try to kill himself?
His daughter put it in his drink.
What? It wasn't really her, ok?
There's 2 ghosts in the house,
and they're trying to control them.
Wait. There are 2 ghosts
- What, they're possessed?
It's called oppression. They lived
here before. It's a long story.
Wait. You always say houses
aren't haunted, people-
Ok, just
- All right.
Well, do we call the cops?
Not yet. As long as they're
out of the house, they're safe,
And they don't even
remember what happened.
I just can't let this little
girl get taken away from her dad.
All right.
Ok, will you just keep
an eye on him for me?
I'll do what i can,
But i think they're only
gonna keep steven overnight.
I have to figure out who these
ghosts are and what they want.
Right.
Hey. Yeah?
You call me if anything changes?
You know it.
It was a man and a woman.
The woman is slightly
older than him.
It's not marlo's mother?
No. I don't think they're
connected to the family at all.
They might be
connected to the house.
But i thought you said places
aren't haunted, and people are.
All right, shush.
Hey, wait a minute.
You got steve and marlo
Out of the house.
That's a positive thing.
Except for the fact that marlo
practically killed her father.
Less positive, i admit.
Look, these oppressive ghosts, they're
stubborn. They're very powerful.
Powerful enough to survive
more than one owner,
Which is probably why the house
is haunted, and not the people.
Touché. All right.
So you said that these ghosts are treating
it all like it's some kind of a game?
Yeah. Like a contest.
What is it, the newlydead game?
That was good. I just made that up.
All right, what's the
point of their game,
Last ghost out of the house wins?
Last man standing. Steve and
marlo are the game pieces.
Why don't you just figure
out what their names are,
Figure out how to play, and
beat them at their own game
And get them to cross over?
Don't make it sound so easy.
Maybe i already have a name.
You said that steve
signed a tax form-Sorry.
He did? Oh, there you are.
When you went down
there. Can i see it?
Uh, why? Why-Why do you need to?
Please. I just need to see it.
Is it something
about his handwriting?
Okget ready to think
of a rational reason.
For what?
Why steve sinclair signed his
name as "matthew sembrook. "
You know, i don't get it.
Why would steve sign
somebody else's name?
Because that's who he thinks he is.
Here. Look.
"Matthew sembrook with father
erwin and mother vivian. "
Mother? She looks 10
years older than him.
Matt is erwin's son
from a previous marriage.
He was vivian's stepson.
It says here that matthew and
vivian died of natural gas poisoning.
What happened to erwin
sembrook? Where's he?
Dead, 6 months before.
Apparently, erwin died in an accident
shortly after marrying vivian,
So mother and son inherited
the house and the fortune.
So you're saying that these two,
Matthew and vivian, are
haunting the sinclairs?
Not only haunting them,
but controlling them,
Which i'm sure is what they did with
everyone else who lived in that house.
Well, their death, what happened?
Was it an accident, a suicide?
What does the article say?
Well, it says here that there
are unanswered questions.
Well, is there something
i can do to help?
Would you really want to?
Look. You're right.
I don't know why,
But there is just some default
switch that goes off inside my head,
And it always resets
to "that can't be. "
Well, maybe it can be.
Ok.
Maybe it can.
I just don't want to
feel like i'm hurting you
Every time that i question it.
It has nothing to
do with hurting me.
I just hate to see
you so closed off.
I mean, there are tons of things
in life that we take on faith,
That we can't see. Why can't
you do that with spirits?
I can.
I will.
I'm gonna try.
But if i can't-
I'm sorry.
Jim.
Mel, steve's being released
from the hospital tonight.
He's signing himself
out, goin' home.
I know who you are.
Matthew and vivian sembrook.
You like to play games?
So do i.
Let's see how you do with
someone you don't control.
Not so easy keeping up the energy
When the sinclairs are gone, is it?
Oh, you'll do.
You both need to cross over.
No, thanks. We're good here.
Ok. Then i'll play you for it.
For what?
A crossover.
20 questions.
If i can tell you what
happened when you lived here,
Then you have to cross over.
And if you don't guess?
I'll never bother you again.
Really? That is so stupid.
You don't bothers at all.
You mean nothing to us.
I like it.
Let's do it.
What were you doing when i
first saw you in the garage?
I never saw you in the garage.
Are you sure you want to
count that as a question?
Your late huand died in
this house, didn't he?
Yes.
And you were both here that night?
And you feel guilty
about what happened?
Just like you feel guilty
about a few things, don't you?
About someone in particular, maybe?
I'm asking the questions.
That's right, andrea, you are.
What?
I'm sorry. Did i call you
by someone else's name?
Did you kill your husband?
You want to know what
happened that night?
Come.
Vivian, mathew, are you up ther?
How can you do this?
He's my son!
He's not my son.
He does something you never do,
Pays attention to me.
Vivian, wait.
And you! What kind
of a man are you?
A man raised by you.
Don't you turn your back on me!
Look, it was an accident.
Ok, i just saw it.
He missed a step,
So you don't have
to blame yourself.
You guys can forgive each other.
And your dad, he's gonna
be in the light, ok?
He'll forgive you.
Wow. She did it.
She wins the game.
So now you can cross over
And you can leave
the sinclairs alone.
Wait. There was one more thing.
Why?
Stop it!
You killed him.
Yeah, sorry. It's just that...
Well, we're really
not very nice people.
Melinda, what-What are
you still doing here?
I'll explain later, ok, but
we have to get out ofere.
Now, you can just come a
- And stay with me,
But you have to get out
of this house right now.
Ok, let's go.
Ok.
Don't be a sore loser.
And leave us the hell alone.
Steve, please don't do this.
Who are you?
Are you liz sinclair?
Are matt and vivian stopping
you from going in the house?
I'm too weak.
They're too strong for me.
They're only strong
'cause they've spent years
Feeding off of other people's fear,
Playing their little games.
Did steve cause your death?
Yes.
But he had to.
Why?
The alternative would
have been even worse.
I think that steve's guilt
Is what's allowing matt and vivian
to have so much power over them.
It's not just steve's guilt.
What?
It's marlo, too.
He will always blame you.
Every time he looks at
you, he sees his dead wife.
Do you know what that does to him?
There's really only
one way to end this,
All this pain, all this anger.
You know what it is.
You know what you have to do
For your own protection.
To make sure you both get peace.
It's the best thing
for both of you.
It only hurts for a
second. You'll barely know,
And then you'll both
finally have some peace.
Don't listen to her.
Ok, this is not you.
This is a ghost that's
making you feel these things.
What?
This is what you do, isn't it?
You just play your story
over and over again,
Except it's a new person each te,
But your real story
Is that you were so guilty
about killing your husband
That you killed yourselves.
Looks and brains. I'm impressed.
The newspapers keep saying that
it's-It's poisoning from natural gas.
It's a little more complicated
than that, isn't it?
A bit.
And it wasn't about guilt either.
The thing is matt and i always
thought we were a perfect match,
Because neither one of us
had a shred of conscience.
Oh, it was just delicious.
The problem is that when you realize the
man you love is as dangerous as you are...
Let's just say it's
not a trust builder.
Attraction turns to suspicion.
There was a lot of money at stake.
Erwin had left us
both very well off.
So i started to wonder
Was matthew's devotion real,
Or did he really want
all that money to himself,
And what would he be willing to do?
He already knew what
i was willing to do,
And i'm sure he was having
the same thoughts about me.
Which is why i decided
That the best thing
for our relationship
Was for matt to have a
tragic, careless accident.
Control freak that i am, i wanted
to make sure that he fell asleep,
As it were, before
i left the house.
He was always so restless.
Imagine my surprise when i
fell asleep before he did.
Very sneaky stuff, natural gas.
Turns out i was much more
sensitive to it than he was.
Of course, matt
followed soon after.
Then we woke up, and we were dead,
And we've been here
having a blast ever since.
What? What is going on?
I'm gonna get you out
of this house right now.
We'll get your father.
I vote for my guy. He's
gonna go all the way.
You should have behaved.
What are you going to do?
Don't count my girl out.
Both of you just stop it.
This is family business.
You should have left us alone.
Too late now.
Steve, please stop, ok?
I've seen your wife.
I've seen her spirit.
My wife is dead.
You should know.
You killed her. Me?
If it wasn't for you,
she'd still be alive.
You let go!
You didn't listen to me!
Now that's entertainment.
Come on. Come on.
What's happening?
Just trust me. I'm
taking you to your mother.
Wait, waitwait!
What are you-What are
you saying about my mom?
Tell her i'm sorry that
it's been so hard on them.
Your mom is here with us.
I can see her.
Tell her i miss our nightly ritual
Of brushing each other's hair,
Her beautiful hair that she
got from her grandmother.
She misses brushing
each other's hair.
Dad, uh, she says mom's here,
Her-Her spirit or-Or
ghost or something,
And she wants to help.
What-What are you talking about?
That shirt he's
wearing is my favorite,
Because he wore it
when marlo was born.
She remembers your shirt.
You were wearing it the
day that marlo was born.
She said that?
She's really here?
They have to stop
punishing themselves.
She wants you to stop
punishing each other.
I'm so sorry, mom.
Dad's right. If it wasn't for me, i
- No.
It's all my fault, and-
No. It was me.
It was me.
I made the decision. It was me.
What happened that day?
We were so tired.
We'd been on that trail all day.
Watch my moves.
Oh. Hey, look!
It happened so fast.
Aah! Liz!
No!
One second, she was next to me.
The next, she was
hanging off a cliff.
I was trying to pull her up,
but i couldn't get any traction.
Mom! No!
Dad! Stay there!
And that's when it all fell apart.
I knew i couldn't stop marlo.
How can you stop a child from
trying to save her mother?
Mom! Aah!
Marlo was falling.
She was gonna die.
I couldn't get liz
back on the ledge.
I thought there was
only one way to save her.
I let go of liz,
And i grabbed ahold of marlo.
Mom! Liz!
I'm so sorry.
I should have tried
to save you both.
No. No, he couldn't.
He did what i wanted him to do,
The only thing that he could do.
You did everything that
she wanted you to do.
You saved marlo.
And i know you were
trying to save me.
She risked her life for me.
She doesn't blame you.
She was really proud of you.
I'm so sorry, mom.
I don't know how to do
any of this without you.
You will always have me
with you in your heart,
But most importantly,
you have each other.
They've gotta stop
punishing themselves.
Please tell them that
we'll always be a family,
And they have to take
care of each other.
I will.
I have to go now.
She crossed over.
Is she gonna be ok?
She was smiling, at peace.
She's always gonna
be in your heart.
How come i don't feel anything
bad when i go inside now?
They can't feed off your
guilt anymore. They're weak.
How can i sell this house to
somebody knowing what i know?
I'll come back, cross them over.
Don't worry about it. You
two just get a fresh start.
I cannot thank you enough.
Me, too.
Things'll get better
now. You'll see.
Would you mind checking
marlo into the hotel?
I just need to grab
a few more things.
Sure. Come on.
Only one way to be sure
things'll get better.
Well played.
My dad!
Fresh start.
Hi, mel.
Jim, you'd better get the fire
department to the sinclair house.
Steve did the only thing
he thought he could do.
What will we do?
What if nobody else comes?
This is our home, the-The
place where we met.
We can't leave.
Don't worry. Somebody always comes.
They'll build.
They'll buy and sell.
All we have to do is wait.
What do we do in the meantime?
How 'bout a game?
20 questions?
You're on.
Ok. Oh, i got a good one.
www.tvsubtitles.net