Previously on 24.
What's wrong?
Keeler.
He's bringing your
ex-husband into this debate.
The SEC's investigation
into his company.
Then face Keeler's lie with the truth
and trust that the people
will be able to tell the difference.
Jack, what's going on?
Where's Tony?
He's been shot.
- How bad?
- He was hit in the neck.
He's still alive, they're getting
him to the hospital now.
With Tony down,
you're in command.
Deliver Ramon Salazar
to the Van Nuys dam.
Whoever sent this message is
controlling Kyle Singer's movements.
We have two hours to find him
before they release the virus.
What are you into Kyle?
These cops, they came
to my apartment today
and they were saying
something about... using me to,
to bring some weird
disease into the country.
A disease...?
Go! Run!
I didn't do anything, man!
No! Stop!
- You're going to see Salazar?
- Yeah.
My dad said questioning
him was a waste of time.
No. Sitting around here
is a waste of time.
Kim, I need you to generate a
prisoner transfer document.
What's this about?
I need to move Ramon Salazar.
This has top priority clearance.
No one at CTU is supposed to know.
Either I hand over Ramon Salazar
or his brother will release the virus.
I understand that this is
an impossible choice.
I have another option
for you to consider.
Ramon Salazar would be broken
out of prison and delivered to him.
Sounds like quite a plan, Jack,
but who'll break Salazar out?
I will, sir.
This would be my last assignment.
If you play this cool, Ramon,
you're walking out of here with me.
Open the cell blocks now.
Let's go. Move!
The following takes place
between 5:00 pm and 6:00 pm
Good evening to those
of you on the east coast
and good afternoon
to those of you in the west.
Welcome to first of three debates
between President Palmer
and Senator John Keeler.
We'll begin tonight
with a two minute opening statement
followed by the first question
which will go to
President David Palmer
as decided by a coin flip
backstage just moments ago.
How're you feeling?
Is that a medical question
or a personal one?
Both.
I'm fine.
That will be conducted within formats of rules
agreed to by each member of the debate
and by the two campaigns.
Now we will bring to
the stage the candidates.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Senator John Keeler.
David, I'm sorry you have to deal
with my ex-husband's lies.
It's alright.
We have the truth on our side.
Ladies and gentlemen,
President David Palmer.
Thank you, John.
Good luck tonight.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Senator Keeler.
Good evening.
I'm looking forward to
discussing some
of the critical issues...
When I tell you to,
you start fighting with
me over the gun.
I gotta try and pull two guards
off the main corridor.
Okay. They're coming.
Help! Help! Help!
That's enough!
Put on his uniform and helmet now!
Split up your men.
I want a team at every security.
No, Jack and Salazar are
somewhere on east block.
You need to put
your men over there.
I got to control this prison,
your partner is not my only problem.
Warden, today he is.
He and Salazar need to be contained
and they need to be kept alive.
You want me to redeploy my men?
Then I need to know how
real this terrorist threat is.
Come here.
Ramon Salazar's brother will spread
a deadly virus into the population
unless we release him unharmed.
If we don't the death toll will be
in the hundreds of thousands.
This is Warden Mitchell.
Tactical unit five, report to control center.
You're now under the command
of agent Edmunds.
Thank you.
- Yeah?
- Chase, it's Michelle.
What the hell is going on over there?
Jack tried to bring
Salazar out of prison.
- He started a riot.
- What?
I think in his own twisted way
he thinks he's gonna deliver him to Hector
and stop the virus from being released.
Well he's gonna get himself killed
not to mention Salazar.
I know.
I know, I'm trying to protect him.
What about Kyle Singer?
We're getting close to locating him.
Michelle as soon as you do, call me.
If Jack knows we got the carrier
of the virus he'll give Salazar back.
We got everyone working on it Chase.
- We'll find him.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, Linda.
Linda.
Am I gonna die?
It depends...
if they find us in time.
What do you mean?
The guy from the government...
He told my dad that I had
a couple of more hours before I...
Before I become contagious.
Maybe they'll find us by then.
You'll be okay.
Yeah...
maybe.
What are you doing?
There must be some wires in here.
What do you need wire for?
To get you out of this.
Adam. Look at this.
Got it from a Caltrans server.
Traffic camera, right near the mall.
Look at that.
It's a blue shirt. Isn't that
what Kyle Singer was wearing?
Yeah.
I think there's enough to enhance.
Release it to my screen.
Got it.
- Kim.
- Yes.
I need you a second.
You got this?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
Is something wrong?
You haven't been following what's
going on at the prison, have you?
No, Adam and I have been
working on finding Singer.
Why, what is it?
Your dad's trying to break out Salazar.
What?
Yeah, he's not out yet but
he's acting on his own authority.
He's trying to remove Salazar by force.
I don't understand
what you mean "by force".
Looks like he started a prison riot
to cover the escape.
Why is he doing this?
That's what we're trying to figure out.
When's the last time
you heard from him?
About a half hour ago.
He asked me to issue a transfer order
for Ramon Salazar and
he gave me a password.
And you did it?
Yeah, he said that
Salazar needed to be moved.
But now you're telling
me this isn't true?
No, Kim. I'm sorry.
Your dad lied to you.
Why would he do that?
Because he knew
if he asked anybody else
they would know
he was violating protocol.
What's gonna happen to him?
We're gonna try to find him.
The best way out of this whole situation
is to find Kyle Singer.
Then your dad will give up Salazar.
So go back to work, help Adam.
Yeah, sure.
We're clear.
We gotta find all their forces through one
entrance to keep the personnel count.
There must be another way, Jack.
There is, but the prisoners
have taken control.
We're gonna have to fight
our way through them.
Get ready.
Hit them up.
Come on.
Come on. Get them on their feet.
Come on, let's go, let's go!
Move, move it!
Let's go!
Hold your fire!
We have hostages so back off!
Come on man!
We can make it through.
We've got to move.
Let's go!
Move! Let's go!
Go!
Move it! Move it!
And in order to do this,
our fossil fuels most be conserved.
Kim, did you send me that Kalman filter?
What?
The Kalman filter,
I needed to clean up that image.
Oh, shoot! I forgot about it.
It's in my help box.
How can you forget about it?
It's the only thing you're working on.
I'm sorry, look...
I'm sending it to you, right now.
Done.
Kim, I don't know where your head is at,
but we need to find Kyle Singer
before he's contagious.
Relax! I'm doing the best I can.
The best I can isn't what
we do around here, Kim.
- It's either done or it's not.
- So why are you lecturing me,
it's in your system.
Kaufman.
Is there a problem?
I just need to make sure things are
running smoothly around here...
Look, Adam.
I haven't had the chance to brief you but...
Jack created a situation over at the prison.
What kind of situation?
He started a riot to free Salazar.
Now they're caught up in the middle of it.
Wow.
He even used Kim to create a transfer
order that started the whole thing.
So cut her a little slack.
Umm...
Yeah, okay, I understand.
We're all under a lot of pressure here.
So let's just find Kyle Singer
before it's too late.
Yeah, okay. Thanks, Michelle.
Kyle, what are you doing?
There's no way out of here.
You don't deserve what happened.
I do.
If I die¡¦
the virus is dying with me!
Kyle!
Put your feet up here!
Kyle, hold on.
Oh, Kyle.
A "Welcome Home" party?
You shouldn't be doing this.
What are you talking about?
You've been running things.
Show Ramon you're
gonna be his partner.
Not his caterer.
Why do you care?
You don't want to be involved
in my business.
No, puppy, I care about you.
And I want you to get
what you've earned.
- Yes?
- It's me.
Riot's still going on.
But we know Ramon's alive.
Yeah.
But Bauer's got to get him out soon.
CTU is getting close
to finding Kyle Singer.
And if they do, they'll
never let Ramon go.
Then make sure
they don't find Singer.
- I'm working on it.
- Get it done.
That's him, that's Singer.
Was that a gun?
Yeah.
Someone's got him.
We're not gonna be able to get the
truck's license plate from this shot.
I'll get access to the traffic cameras
in the direction they're heading.
See if we can find them again.
- Dessler.
- Michelle.
We found Kyle Singer being driven
away from the mall, 47 minutes ago.
Are you working up a vehicle ID?
We will, as soon as
we're able to get any visual.
This camera's damaged. It's malfunctional.
Must have the hostages on the right.
Try and pan the camera over.
They may see the camera move.
We don't have a choice. Do it.
There they are.
We got to get in there before
they start killing everyone.
Come on! Come on!
Faster! Faster!
Let's start wasting the guards
unless they let us walk
First step outside, bang!
Headshot from a sniper.
You don't know that.
I know, cause that's
what went down in Chino
They'll let the guard get wasted cause
all they care about is keeping us in.
What the hell are we doing here then?
Give me your gun.
Bring them over here.
We're gonna have
a little fun with them.
Put them on their knees.
Who wants to live?
Okay.
Let's try it again.
- Who wants to live?
- Me.
I do.
Him. Over here.
Come on.
Who else?
I've never seen you before.
I'm new here.
Him. Over here.
One in six chance.
You first.
Please.
Don't make me do this man.
There's nothing to it, you little bitch.
- Just put the gun to your head.
- I can't!
I can't...
You're gonna do it.
You hear me?
- You're gonna do it.
- Please, please.
It's easy, see?
All you gotta do is smile...
and pull the trigger.
Now it's one in five.
Let's go!
No!
No, I can't...
I can't...
- This is a waste of my time. Shoot him.
- No, wait!
- Shoot him!
- Wait!
Come on, man.
Just do it.
This way at least you've
got a chance, okay?
Do it.
Come on!
If you're not gonna do it,
we will.
We have a winner.
Let's hear it for the new guy.
We're now seeing concrete results.
This is a road we will continue to travel.
I got a shot coming in from a camera at the
next intersection definitely the same truck.
Can you read the license plate?
We won't be able to read anything
until it finishes downloading.
I just saw the IAD inquiry
coming over the system
about what you're father's
doing at the prison.
They're questioning the transfer
you generated for him.
I heard.
If you want me to say that you didn't know
he was gonna use it to break out Salazar¡¦
I will.
Thanks. I'll be okay.
Hold on. It stopped downloading,
I'm getting an error message.
Error 402 that...
means trouble with the internal router.
Gael.
What are you doing?
There's a problem with
one of the routers.
I'm trying to fix it.
Why don't you call Tech.
No, it's okay.
I think I found the problem.
Checks on circuit kicked in.
Must have been one of the line surge.
Should be up and running now.
Let me know if you have
any more problems.
I will.
Hey, it's back up. What was it?
I'm not sure.
Is it possible a line surge
could have knocked out a router?
Well not from my side,
you can ask Chloe?
Got it.
Hold on.
Dessler.
Michelle, I've got a plate on the pick up.
Good, where do you last have it?
The shots on the north part of
Santa Fe Springs, it was driving west.
Okay, I want you to put this
out to mobile units LAPD.
I want everyone looking for this vehicle.
Okay, right.
Alright, Ryan, I'm back.
So do you have any idea if Bauer
is trying to break out Salazar on his own
or if he is working with someone?
I'm trying to figure that out now.
- I'll get back to you when I found out.
- You do that.
Chloe?
Yeah, Michelle?
Are you following
what's going on at the prison?
I just saw the update come over.
What the hell's happening?
We don't have all the details
yet but Jack's behind it.
I need you to check
his phone logs, e-mail¡¦
See what case files he's
accessed recently.
What am I looking for?
Anything that'll help us
figure out why he's doing this.
Are you sure? You really want
me snooping in his office?
Yes.
You got it.
Surgery?
Yeah, this is Tony
Almedia's wife Michelle.
- How's he doing?
- Ah... I'll check. One moment please.
- Mrs. Almeida?
- Yeah?
He's still in surgery.
You'll be contacted as soon
as he's rolled into recovery.
What room is he in?
Umm... Operating room 4.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Network ops, Evan.
- Yeah, Evan, it's Michelle.
Do you know if we get all
our feeds from Good Samaritan?
Let me check.
Yeah, they do.
What do you need?
See if they're video docu-ing OR4.
Yeah, they are.
Where do you want it?
- Send it to my desk top.
- Alright. It'll take a second.
Right, there you go.
Anything else?
- No. Thank you.
- Sure.
- Four by four.
- More pressure.
- Hold that down.
- I've got it. /- There you go.
Do you have another clamp?
Clamp.
The laundry room's
a hundred yards in.
I'll ID the exact locations for
the explosives once we get there.
Yes, sir.
Sir, we're ready for you.
Monitor's up.
You should be seeing it on your IPC.
- It's working.
- Okay.
Alright, let's go.
Radio silence while we're in there.
If they hear us, they might kill everyone.
- Copy that.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Alright!
Round two!
Then you.
I'm a prisoner, not a guard.
I'm Ramon Salazar.
- I'm sure you've heard of me.
- You should pick someone else,
he's telling you the truth.
He's just transferred to cell block
less than a week ago.
I'm a federal agent, I was
escorting him out of the prison.
That's why you've never
seen us here before.
Good.
Federal agent.
What's your name?
Jack Bauer.
Alright.
It's gonna be agent Jack
against Ramon Salazar.
A battle to the finish!
Come on, Jack.
Show this foreigner how it's done.
If I die,
- my brother will find you.
- Shut up!
Do it!
Alright.
You're up.
Looks like your mother's a title, Jack.
Ramon, stay down!
Come on!
All clear!
Hold your fire!
Jack!
I have no triumphs.
Only defeats.
God!
- Lab.
- This is Chloe O'Brian.
I'm in Jack's office.
Could you send someone
up the drug kit, please?
It's on its way.
The differences on the issues are clear.
But I believe you don't elect a platform.
You elect a man.
And I am frankly troubled
by some of the personal choices
that this president has made
and continues to make.
We're all aware of the allegations
and indictments surrounding
the President's former wife.
Most of us have operated
under the assumption
that the President will
not repeat his history
of associating with the persons
of questionable moral character.
However,
my office has just learned
that the woman with whom the
President is currently involved,
Doctor Anne Packard
is being accused of helping to fabricate
the results of a clinical drug trial.
A drug which later led to the deaths
of three innocent people.
This is outrageous.
This debate is not a court of law
nor is it a tabloid paper.
This is neither the time nor the place
to launch a personal
attack on a private citizen.
Mr. President
the Senator still has 30 more seconds.
Sir, please.
This is exactly the right time.
Because I believe the choices your
leaders make in their own lives
reflect the choices that they
will make on your behalf.
And so the question remains.
Did the President know of these
accusations and choose to ignore them?
Or is he repeating past
mistakes once again?
Mr. President your rebuttal.
I can tell you with complete confidence
that the Senator's accusation is false.
And that I believe it is the Senator's
way of aborting the issues at hand.
Now I came here tonight to discuss
the real issues pressing our country.
Oh, god.
- I assume that the Senator was...
- Now do you get it?
I do not believe this is something
to be swept under the rug and forgotten.
It's positive.
I'll go tell Michelle.
Chloe, what are you doing
in my dad's office?
Michelle wanted me to go
through your dad's stuff.
Why?
To find anything that can help us
understand what he's doing.
What's up?
I wanted to know if a line surge could shut
down a router on your side of the ITS room.
No, my circuit protectors are upstairs.
Not in my ITS.
Why?
Ah, it's probably nothing.
Did you find anything?
I can't talk about this.
Why not, maybe I can help.
You can't help so just go, okay?
What's in the box?
Just stuff I'm taking to Michelle.
This is really an
inappropriate behavior, Kim.
Why are you doing this, Chloe?
I mean...
I'm just trying to help you.
You can't help.
And I don't have to have this conversation.
Under field op mandate,
there's a regulation.
I believe it's 40 or 41 that says
that I have jurisdictional prerogative.
So could you just leave?
Not until you tell me what's in the box.
I think your dad's been using drugs.
- What?
- That's right.
Rubber tourniquet,
syringe.
We just had the vials tested of opiates,
It was positive.
He's been acting really weird. Okay?
It's really not fair you made me do this.
It's very uncomfortable.
Michelle?
I didn't find anything in Jack's records
but there is something you need to see.
You found this in his office?
I wanted to make sure
what it was before I showed you.
The liquid in these vials
tested positive for opiates.
Probably heroine.
I think Jack's a user.
I got it.
A patrol car just found the
truck Kyle Singer was in
parked in a industrial complex
in Fuller and fourth 2000 block.
Pipe these into the teams on standby.
Assume everyone on the site is contagious
and use level 1 CDC protocol.
Let's get him!
Damn!
Is there any other way out?
No, we're pinned in.
We must have known this could happen.
What's the plan, Jack?
Give me the shotgun.
Take off your uniform.
I have worked the past year with my
administration on my overall academic plan.
The projection could not look better.
- Dessler.
- This is Cowgil.
Approaching the industrial complex on Fuller.
There are three warehouses on the property.
I'll see if we can narrow it down with infrared.
Roger.
Kaufman.
Adam, see if you can pull up an infrared
satellite on the industrial complex.
On it.
Kim, log into the NHA server.
We need to see if they have
any satellites in position.
Kim!
Okay.
What's the matter?
Nothing, I'm fine.
We just swept these blocks.
There's no sign of Jack or Salazar.
Look I got a team in the assault block.
They can't do a proper
search until we lock it down.
That can take up to a half hour.
If you want to get out of this thing,
you gonna have to trust me.
And do everything that I tell you.
You understand?
Alright.
- Come on, let's go.
- Okay, here's what I want you to do.
I want you to take that chopper
and I want you sweep the perimeter.
Chase!
- What are you doing, Jack?
- You get these people to move back.
Or you're gonna have to take me out.
We need that chopper.
Don't do this.
I just spoke with Michelle,
we're close to getting Kyle Singer.
Close ain't gonna cut it this time.
I gotta deliver Salazar now!
I'm not letting you go, Jack!
How long is it gonna
take to find Kyle Singer?
A half an hour? An hour?
I gotta get Salazar in the air,
in that chopper in the next 60 seconds.
Or hundred thousand people will die.
- Let him go.
- Let him go?
Let him go.
We'll track the chopper. I need you to
keep your people under control, Warden.
Please.
I can't have anything happen to Salazar.
Alright.
This is Warden Mitchell,
I want all teams to stand down.
I repeat, stand down!
Agent Bauer will take Salazar
to the SWAT chopper.
I want a conformation from
all teams on the stand down order.
Let him take the chopper.
Stand down.
Alright? Back off.
Alright, Jack.
No one's gonna try and stop you.
Get these men to back off
and holster their weapons.
Back off! Stand down!
Let them through!
Let's go.
- Get them to holster their weapons.
- Holdster your weapons!
- Lower your weapon!
- Stand down!
Get the snipers down,
off the roof, now!
- Now!
- Off the roof! Get off the roof!
Back off!
Do what he says!
We have Singer plus one.
Center, Singer plus one.
What's he doing?
Disabling or calming the locator.
Yes?
Chase, it's Michelle.
We have Kyle Singer.
I can't hear you.
We found Kyle Singer.
- We've got Kyle?!
- Yes!
Jack!
Jack, we found Kyle Singer!
Jack! Jack!
Jack!!
You can talk about facts or figures
all night, Mr. President.
Once again
I see this as a question
of judgment and integrity.
Ignore this issue, an issue of rectitude
and foresightedness...
Congratulations.
Now you are an even bigger enemy
to your country than me.
www.tvsubtitles.net