Whoo!
Okay, guys, i just want to say
congratulations On our 50th show!
That's 50 hours of comedy,
over 300 sketches,
One unsolved crew death, and
an emmy magazine cover story.
Ansomeone
got us booze gifts.
- Oh, sweet.
- They're all empty. What the hell?
Congratulations on 50 shows, everyone.
Enjoy your decorative
air holders.
You deserve them.
Lemon, a word.
It's a pretty lame present, jack.
Cutbacks.
Our parent company sheinhardt wigs is announcing
losses this quarter For the first time since the civil war.
And even i am not immune.
I had to let jonathan go today.
Oh, my god.
How did he take it?
better than i expected.
Can't leave if living is without you
- okay, last verse, jonathan.
- i can't live!
I'm warning you now that the entertainment division
Is gonna come under some very close scrutiny.
The days of your wild
coke parties are over.
Well, if by "coke,"
you mean "sodas"...
I do. It's really bad.
It's so bad. It's stsare hiring
An outside consulting firm.
What does that mean?
It means they're bringing in
hatchet men to trim the fat.
And on monday, you will have
to present and justify Your budget to them.
- Can you handle that?
- Handle a presentation?
Jack, i put on a live show
every week Unless there's wrestling.
- I'm on it.
- Good.
I've got some more
downsizing to do upstairs
So i've got no time
for hand-Holding.
- let's get this right.
- i've got so tcks up my sleeve.
- That's my girl.
- No, trix, the cereal.
Some fell in my sleeve.
It's sticking to the fibers.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@ÏÄ·ç
Sync:FRS@¹ÅµÂÄÎÌØzZZ
30 Rock S03 E17
you wanted to see me, sir.
Kenneth, as you may have heared
Jonathan no longer works here.
Yeah. The assistants talked about last night
At finnegan's, the bar we all go to after work...
in my dreams.
Yes, uh, well, obviously,
i'to need an assistant.
And i'm going to have
to ask you to fill in.
Ut what about my page duties?
Oh, don't worry.i've taken care
of that. you'll do both jobs.
This is a very difficult.kenneth.
I'm gonna be counting on you.
You'll do fine so long
as you follow my three ds:
Discretion, docility,
and don't use my bathroom.
Mr. Donaghy's office.This is
kenneth. How may i help you?
it's greg windham from aviation.
I'm not here.
But you are here.
I can see you.
I don't want to talk to him.
Oh, corporate intrigue.
He's not in right now.
I'll tell him you called.
I feel like i'm
the pelican brief!
Do i already know too much?
Liz.
brad halster.the himler group.A division of advantrix
theconsulting.
liz lemon. this is
my associate, peter hornberger.
Liz, is there a conference room where
we can sit down And get started?
Actually, i thought
we'd do this outside the box.
I'd like to tell you
about three television programs.
A comedy show,
a musical variety show,
And a live television event.
Comedy, music show,
live show.
Comedy, music, live.
Are you getting it? Yeah.
They're all the same show.
They're all tgs.
Now i could stand here, brad,
And i could bore you with numbers.
I could tell you that we are the number
one late night show among men 9-13
and the morbidly obese.
I could tell you that we'ree.In final negotiations
To create exclusive content for america's jails
But i'm not the one
being judged here.
So i thought i'd let
the show speak for herself.
dessert!
Someone put too many farts
in this engine!
It's about to explode!
I'm flavor obama
and i'd like to introduce The under
secretary of housing and crystal meth, boy!
It's the bear and robot talk show!
My name is suri cruise.
Put your hands in the air.
I came out of the womb
with a full head of hair.
It's farting!
That's our show for tonight.
See you next week!
Good night!
This is tgs!
So where's that conference room?
- Oh. Golly.
- Whoa, k.
I am sorry, mr. Jordan.
I'm just overworked.
With my page duties and being
mr. Donaghy's assistant,
There's not enough hours
in the day.
I'm sorry about that.
But just let me know
if there's any way i can help.
- Actually, there is one thing.
- No. I was just saying that.
Why can't you read
human facial queues?
All right, what is it?
Well, with both these jobs, I don't know
when i'm gonna be able to get home.
I'm worried about my bird,
sonny crockett.
Would you mind going
to my apent and feeding him?
Yeah, okay. Birds are
like little dinosaurs.
So what i'll be doing is
actually pretty cool and brave.
Thank you, sir.
Here are my keys.
Oh, and one thing,
don't go into my bedroom.
- What?
- Do not go into my bedroom.
25%? How am i supposed
to cut a quarter of our budget?
Well, there is some fat.
What about sid?
Sid? I can't fire our announcer.
He'll lose his insurance.
You know, he has a lot
of health problems.
Yeah, because he was hit by lightning
And can't really talk anymore.
It's tergis with tracky
ng-Jong And jimmy moop!
No. Sid is off the table.
I'm not firing any of my people.
I'm not doing that to their families.
Or in sid's case, their much younger wife
With whom they have an open relationship.
All right, we'll find
the money somewhere else.
- The food budget--
- No!
All right, what about straws?
We spend $1,200 a year on straws.
Okay, fine. No mstraws.
Everyone drinks
from the can from now on.
- Oh, no, we need straws.
- Oh, god! That's its bathroom!
Listen, liz, i'm gonna need your
revised budget By the end of today.
I don't know, brad.
Tgs is a complicated machine.
- Every part's important.
- Get it.
You don't want to be
the bad guy.
But if you don't make
the cuts, i will.
And i don't give a crap
about anyone here.
Matthew, i know this isn't ea
But the company's facing cutbacks.
And you have to admit your boom box
division Is a little bit behind the times.
We're not behind the times,
we're groovy!
I can offer you
two weeks severance.
Mr. Donaghy, i know you said only
interrupt you If it was very important,
But tashonda from time
warner cable Is on the phone
And she's offering three
free months of showtime.
But we have to act now.
Kenneth, this does not qualify
As something important.
I do not want showtime.
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't want you to miss out
On this exciting opportunity--
Thank you, kenneth.
Take your time.
Hey, little guy.
don't go in the bedroom.
- Don't go in the bedroom.
- I wasn't going to!
I wa't going to! Bye!
Hello, miss lemon.
Are you here to see kenneth the page
Or kenneth the mr. Donaghy's assistant?
Well, i need to see jack.
Hello, miss lemon.
Mr. Donaghy is in an important meeting.
And i've been told not to interrupt him.
What is this pertaining to?
The tgs budget.
Oh, my. That sounds very important.
- Mr. Donaghy.
- Kenneth!
i've worked here 20 years.
I was wrong.
That was not important enough.
It's me, kenneth the page,
this job is hard.
Please have a seat.
Mr. Donaghy will be right with you.
Do you know what these
meetings are about?
I hear people are getting fired.
Yeah. I don't know.
- Do you know jack donaghy well?
- Pretty well.
Do you happen to know
If he's a boob man or a butt man?
- What? Why wouou ask that?
- Because i don't want to get fired.
So i'm gonna have to go in there
And boink my way out of this
I'm cheryl, by the way.
You're gonna try to have sex with jack?
I have to.
I have 15 employees.
I'm responsible for them.
Do you have any idea
what that's like?
Well, yeah, i have
200 people under me, but--
Wow. Maybe we could team up,
go in there together,
- lez out, give him a show.
- No. Cheryl, get a grip.
Oh, boy.
Miss lemon, mr. Donaghy
will see you now.
Make it quick, lemon.
I'm in the middle
of a very unpleasant day.
Okay, well, so am i.
I know this cutback stuff
is difficult.
I don't want to fire anyone.
And i don't want to take
anything away from my crew.
And i want to keep making free,
long-Distance prank calls
To people like seattle's
richard sacmuncher.
And i think
that's reasonable.
So what do i do
to get out of this?
The only thing to do is make your cuts
And live to fight another day.
What? That's it?
I thought you'd tell me
to cook the numbers
Or shred something or do
some pelican brief stuff.
Why is everyone talking
about that movie?
It's playing
on showtime.
Kenneth, get me showtime.
What? Why now?
I'm sorry.
I know this is hard,
but there's no way out of it.
Well, little heads up,
Your next meeting might disagree.
She's planning to change
your mind By hitting...
- ...that.
- Oh, no, not again.
This last guy tried
to take my belt off.
But the sad thing is,
it sometimes works.
Sexual bartering pays off.
Salome. Mata hari.
Deborah norville.
Well, good luck downstairs.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Oh, and one more thing,
uh, don't cut the straw budget
'Cause i've already cut the exterminators.
Jenna, something weird
is going on.
You mean this budget stuff?
Don't worry about it, tracy.
It's just gonna affect
the non-Specials.
No, it's not that.
Jenna, you're the smartest
person i know.
You think kenneth
could be a murderer?
What? Why would you
think that?
Well, i might be crazy,
But neither he nor his bird
would let me into his bedroom.
And why wouldn't you want
to let tracy jordan Into your bedroom
unless you got a bunch
Of dead nurses in there?
Well, i had to study serial killers To prepare
for my role as criminal profiler Jill st. Ferrari
in the lifetime original
miniseries Hushed rapings.
And all masked murderers
share three characteristics:
Cruelty to animals...
- He grew up killing pigs!
- Bedwetting.
No wonder he's fascinated
when i do that!
And an inability to read
human facial queues!
I admonished him
for that earlier!
Three for three.
He's a monster!
Okay, we've gotta go
tell jack.
You know, if kenneth is actually
a killer, We're gonna be heroes.
Liz, our food is gone.
They took it.
It happened this morning.
Do you have a cookie?
Mommy's baby needs his yum-Yums.
Oh, my god.
Sid, did you get fired?
Good-Bye, lerz.
- Liz, it's a massacre!
- What is going on?
Brad came in this morning
and started making cuts.
I can't go back to
teaching high school math.
Those girls pretend
they're not women yet, But they are.
- Do something, liz.
- You're our only hope.
Halster, you look hot in those trousers.
how about we grab drinks tonight?
Marissa, update my sched.
Good morning, sir.
Kenneth, i know there's a ere,
But i need you to focus.
No mistakes now.
Think before you speak.
Understand?
Yes.
- oh.
- Hey, k.
- Where's jonathan?
- Jonathan's not here anymore.
- How may i help you?
- Um, we need to see jack.
I don't know if i can allow that.
I've made some mistakes lately.
- Terrible mistakes.
- Uh-Huh.
So i need to know
what this is about.
I can't have you getting me
into trouble.
It's not about you.
Yeah,t'out someone else.
I'm afraid this guy know in ca
Might be a serial killer.
- And what his name?
- Kenneth.
I mean--I'll tell you his name.
It's kenneth.
Excellent.
I will be sure to let him know As soon as
he's done firing steven lee from microwaves.
What?
Oh, mr. Lee, i forgot.
He's ready for you now.
I've got chills.
He's evil.
If i had any doubts out this before,
and i don't think i did,
they're gone now.
We gotta go to his apartment
and save who we can.
We're defitely gonna be heroes.
yeah, like julia and denzel
in the pelican brief!
Lee, i need that dress jenna
wore for the hooker sketch,
The heels tracy wears
when he plays michelle obama,
And double--Wait--
Triple spanx.
I need a makeup artist!
No,the sluttier one.
Thanks, liz.
You're our hero.
They may take my dignity,
But they will never take our straws!
Yeah!
Oh, my god.
Why does he have a rolled up towel
Against the bottom of the door?
It's so creepy!
Jenna, i just want you to know that
if we find Any human remains in there,
I'm gonna throw up
all over your face.
Oh, no!
Kenneth's a murderer
and the riddler's coming!
no. it's a bug bomb.
get out. get out.
- It's poisonous. Ah!
- Ah!
So thanks for dinner.
- You sure know a lot about sushi.
- Well, you gotta be careful.
They try to up-Sell you
the real crab.
- So...
- so...
list, i gotta get going.
i got a lotta work tomorrow.
all right, listen,
we're both adults here.
We know the deal.
Let's cut to the chase.
That's certainly direct.
We go upstairs.20 minutes.
Open mouth.I will work your ears.
I don't know, liz. What you're
asking me to do is a big deal.
If i go through with this,
i need to know it's worth it.
Fine. 30 minutes.
I'll make some sounds.
And you can say
one weird thing to me.
All right, hardball.
30 minutes. sounds.
Top front of my body is now
in play. Deal?
Deal.
Lemon, i heard a rumor that you went out
With one of the consultants last night.
Well, i had no choice.
I had to give him
a little taste of the lemon.
And it was not sour,
my friend. Not sour.
It's interesting
you put it that way
Because your writers' room is now the headquarters
For telemundo's coverage of
world cup soccer qualifying.
Equador tiene que ganar
o atar contra peru
Para avanzar en los finales.
- What the what?!
- Ssh.
Brad and i had a deal.
I gave him top front.
Top front? Good lord, lemon,
that's your worst quadrant.
Kenneth, you know how you told
tracy Not to into your bedroom?
Well, naturally, we assumed
you were a serial killer.
and as you can imagine,
your bird is dead.
yeah, but on the bright side,
You've been downgraded From
"suspect" to "person of interest."
Some day, we're gonna
look back on this and laugh.
time does heal all wounds!
now you wait just one minute.
I am sorry to be using my barn voice
In front of a lady, but i am riled up.
it is not enough that you killed
the bird I've had for almost 60 years.
But the fact that you didn't
trust me is unforgivable.
But whd i expect?
Look at you two walking around
without a care in the world
As budgets are slashed
And people keep getting called
into mr. Donaghy's office To be fired.
I may just be a non-Special,
But what you two did
is inexcusable.
Good day.
I'm out of letters.I have to
return my kids' braces.
What did you do?
We trusted you!
You ruined it
with your talking, didn't you?
Hey!
Why are you
still messing with my show?
What about last night?
Liz, last night was what it was,
But business is business.
Right. And last night,
i gave you the business.
We had an agreement.
Top front and some light ear work!
You got your quid, halst
where's my quo?
Oh, my god.
Last night was about the show?
Oh, please,
you know it was.
You were all, oh,
it's gotta be worth it
And what you're asking me to do
is such a big deal.
It was a big deal.
Being with a woman for the
first time since my wife died.
- Ah, snap.
- It was just a transaction?
What kind of person are you?!
Does it help if i tell you I thought
we were doing sexual espionage?
Oh, god.
Sharon! Angel!
i swore to you the next
one would be worthy, But she's not!
she's a monster!
Marissa, add dr. Walters
to my sched.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Okay
so mr. Halster has filed a complaint
against you With human resources.
Specifically, his claim suggests that you tried to barter
sex In exchange for professional consideration.
In the human resource world, We refer to
that as "being a filthy prostitute."
Now, since this is your first incident
And, uh, mr. Donaghy has explained
The mitigating circumstances...
I'm convinced that this sexual outburst
Was brought on by menopause.
We are recommending only
a two-Week suspension Without pay.
Okay. That's fair.
and obviously mr. halster cannot
function In this hostile work environment.
His company has reassigned him.
And your budget review process
will start over again Under my supervision.
- Really.
- Yes, really.
I hope you've learned
your lesson, miss lemon.
When you harass sexually
in the workplace,
Things do not somehow
just work out in the end.
Mr. Donaghy, i thought you'd like to know
That there's a spider on the printer.
Oh, no.
Am i interrupting?
Is this another firing meeting?
It is now.
Kenneth, have a seat.
Ken, we feel bad that we--
But mostly jenna--Gassed your bird.
I agree.
Not to name names, but it's so sad That
a certain black individual Found it necessary
to trick someone so pretty
Into believing you were a murderer.
I'm sorry, is there
a point to all this?
I've had a bad couple of days.
Well, we feel terrible
about what happened,
So we did a little something
to make it up to you.
looks like i've got
some naming to do.
Pat. Balthazar. Donna.
lorne. michael.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net