Okay.
Now,you're all here because you've been
suspended om work for sexual harassment.
But through this seminar,
You will learn the skills to keep you from making
the same kinds of mistakes that got you here.
Excuse me,mr.
Winerslav--
It's pronounced "weener-slave."
okay,jeffrey.
Is there anything I can do to
speed this process up so I can just
I'm afraid not.
But someone who's in a
rush to get back to work?
That's somethin' you
don't see every day.
Now,that is an example of a very
appropriate and very,very funny joke.
Jenna, I need to speak with you.
Jack,i did not hit that asian page.
I was just swinging my arm
and she walked into me. Twice.
Jenna,it's not about that.
It's about your sheinhardt-universal
janis joplin biopic.
Wait. We can call her janis joplin?
We got the life rights? It's
not janie jimplin anymore?
Apparently, neither name cleared.
It looks like your character's
going to be called jackie jormp-jomp.
- Oh,okay. So what's the good news?
- I didn't say there was any.
Sheinhardt-universal did
some focus testing this week.
- We got 100?
- You're holding that upsiddown.
- Oh,no.
- Yes. I was afraid of this.
It turns out not having the life rights or any
janis joplin songs was a negative for audiences.
But what about my duet with
jimi hendrickson at woodstocks?
We're all here at woodstocks
someday there will be a black president
uh,jenna, Sheinhdtniversal does
not wanna release the picture.
And how will that
affect my oscar chances?
Adversely. Unless we get
independent distribution.
To do that, "sing dem blues,white girl: "the
jackie jormp-jomp story" has gotta get some buzz.
I'm gonna need your help for that.
Do you need a sex tape
released? 'Cause I got a wrdne.
It's night vision and you can
see that his buddy is robbing me.
No,jenna,i want you on the pr warpath.
If there's a red carpet,i want you on
it talking up the movie starting monday.
The kids' choice awards? Fine.
I'll set aside my feud with
raven simone for one day.
But she knows what she did.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
30 Rock
Season03 Episode18
Miss lemon,you aren't
supposed to be here.
You're on
s-e-x probation.
Yeah,i know,i just wanted
to stop by and check in.
Kenneth,stop. I just want
a script or a rundown,okay?
Put that down. You
give that to me,kenneth.
Did you hear what I said?
Mr. Donaghy,help! Rule breaking!
This is sad.
Lemon,come with me.
Lemon,you know you're supposed to
go home after your pervert seminars.
I'm going. I just hate not being here.
- You have to rehearse!
- No! Passive resistance!
I learned that from dr. King! I'm brave!
- You sure you miss this?
- Yes.
As crazy and stressful as this
place is, not being here is worse.
I feel for you.
Remember that time I came back from
the world economic forum with mono
And missed a week of work and I wanted to pull
my hair out but I couldn't because it's too thick?
People like us, we need the stress.
We're only happy when
we're overcoming obstacles.
You take that away, we start bouncing off the
walls, spend our days jabbering at doormen.
Hey,i brighten their day.
Before I go,can I at least
find out what frank's hat says?
- "constant cving."
- He could do better.
Has anyone looked at this sexual
harassment stuff they gave us?
I don't need to read it.
The whole thing is loosely based on
a evening I spent with isiah thomas.
No wonder liz got busted.
According to this, you can't do anything
without it being considered harassment.
Did you know you have to
report in-office relationships?
- Is that true?
- It's the first thing listed.
Have you read this?
Well,i wanted to, because
it's full of rules,
but ms.Vieira made me throw it away.
And said pretty boys like me shouldn't
be filling their heads with ideas.
- Hi,frank.
- Hello.
Coworker.
Ms.vieira...
Of course my job is annoying, but
that doesn't mean I don't love it.
I'm sure your job can be annoying.
Not all the tenants are as fun as me.
I get it.
Hey,would you mind if
brought a chair down here?
Yes,my job is stressful. Very stressful.
But in the end,i get
paid to make people laugh.
We have a saying that laughter is the best
medicine, so I'm kind of like a doctor here.
Like you were,in poland.
We have a show tonight.
I've never missed a show.
Not even the time I had that virus
they kept saying only raccoons get.
I can't believe I'm not there.
Hey,I've-- uh,I've picked
up some polish from you guys.
******
It's kinda cold out for a jog.
- Oh,I'm just going downstairs to the fitness center.
- What? This building has a gym?
Yeah,it'the door right next
to the vending machines.
Vending machines? What kind?
I don't know,sorry. I'm emily.
Are you new to the building?
No,I'm liz. I've lived
here for four years.
I usually work crazy,long hours, but I'm
on leave right now for normal reasons.
- And you're feeling a little lost.
- I am.
Right now,i should be standing in a toilet
stall so nobody bothers me while I eat lunch.
God,i miss it.
I was an investment banker for 15 years.
80-hour workweeks, corner
office, secret candy drawer...
A a decoy candy drawer to
throw others off the trail?
Smart.
The point is you get
addicted to the stress.
Think it gives your life purpose.
- And then when you stop--
- for normal reasons...
You see how stupid you were.
It just takes time to realize there
are much better ways to be happy.
Wait for me... Lady.
Kenneth, what can I do for ya?
Well,sir, I recently learned
that company policy requires
That employees disclose their relationships
with their cowkers to their immediate supervisor.
I am not kyo there are
perhaps 40 people between us.
Pete,for instance.
Oh,i just don't trust
mr. Hornberger,sir.
He has a ridge on the section of the
skull associated with deviousness.
Okay. So there's a girl.
Yes,sir. Her name is daphne.
She's one of thetgsdancers.
And when I watch her dance,
my heart skips a beat.
And not because of my acute ventralitis.
Wait. You're dating one of the dancers?
Oh,no,sir.
I actually haven't spoken to her yet,
but I have a long-term plan to marry her,
And I wanted the company to
be aware of my intentions.
I see. I'll be sure to mention
that at the next board meeting.
Thank you,sir.
Oh,also, I don't know
if this is harassment,
But someone atthe today show made me
eat an unripe bana in front of her.
Hey,ken. Do you know who
our immediate supervisor is?
I will not be able to
attend your wedding.
Because of a prior conflict.
Oh,what's the special occasion?
Weekday.
w,so this is normal?
This is,like,your version
of sweatpants and pop-tarts?
Not too shabs.
Short for shabby. Hilarious.
This could be your life too,liz.
Just short the housing market.
Or write a cookbook specifically
for mixed-race children.
Or marry a rich, old dude who dies.
Clive,i wanna say?
Or have mild lupus and great insurance.
So,here is the plan for today.
- Start with facials and massages...
- Yes,please.
Then private shopping at bergdorf,
- swing by the dermatologist
for a tune-up. - Fabulous.
Dinner at jewel bako,
then a nightcap back here.
Wow,that is a plan.
But,uh,i don't think I should go.
Oh,liz is still stressed
about her old job.
It's just-- it's friday,and at
my job that is our biggest day.
I don't think i'd be good company.
But thank you for inviting
me. I'll have one drink here.
Have two.
But then I really should
go home, 'cause i,you know--
I'm still in work mode, I'm
not really in spa/shopping mode.
I wouldn't be able to enjoy myself.
And I don't wanna crash your
day together and ruin it.
- We're always together.
- Thank you.
Cocktails.
It's just so stressful thinking aut my
employees trying to do everything without me.
- Those look great on you.
- Then I'm buying them.
I guess I'm just one of
those people that needs work.
You know,i
thrive there.I--
- and it's gone just like that?
- Just like that.
- Thank you,dr. Binderman.
- ***
My point is,you are
so sweet to include me.
Believe me,I'm jealous, but
today's just not the day.
So,you know,i'll hang out
with you guys for a little bit,
and i'll have my one drink,and...
- What time is it?
- Almost midnight.
If we're gonna get up in time for our
mani/pedis, we really should turn in.
Bye.
I forgot to watch my show.
I'm prepared to do a
nipple slip if you need it.
Just talk about the movie.
Hi,I'm ethan fromnick magazine.
- Whose mom are you?
- Thank you. Well,tonight's about fun.
I'm wearing taylor dayne for
express, and my peace sign,of course,
- Is a nod to janis joplin, who,I'm
so-- - dora the explorer's backpack!
Backpack, is map in you tonight?
here are your lunches, gentlemen.
Dotcom,i forgot to
get you extra mustard.
All right,enough!
This fighting stops now!
I asorry. Mr. Slattery hurt
me, and now I'm hurting him.
He'll never get mustard.
Except for the mustard that
comes with the sandwich.
I said I was sorry,ken.
I didn't even mean to hurt you.
Oh,really? I love you too,dotcom.
- I didn't say-- - I knew
this would happen someday.
A woman would come between us.
Well,I'm not standing
by. I'm taking action.
Oh,sir,before miss lemon left,i promised
her I wouldn't let you start any adventures.
Yeah,well, liz lemon's in jail now.
And somebody has to step up
and take charge around here.
Let the problem solving begin.
Are you daphne? Yeah,you're fired.
First a backpack upstages me, then the
paparazzi kept calling me dina lohan,
And now the cyrus family has
decided to rock a bunch ofunky hats.
You can't give up now.
Did jackie jormp-jomp give up when
those vampires attacked woodstocks?
Nobody even knows I'm here.
From dreamworks's upcoming feature
film on top of spaghetti, helen mirren.
Good evening.
And now we
take a moment--
oh,that's horrible.
You got me.
And now we take a moment to remember those we
lost this year in the kid entertainment industry.
******
R******
E******
J******
Was that me?
Did they just say I'm dead?
I thought you spoke to the producers.
Look,connor,if we don't get some
traction, jenna maroney's picture's dead.
- We need your help.
- Maroney. Picture. Dead. Got it.
This is a disaster.
No,no. We hit the jackpot.
You being dead is the best thing
that ever happened to this movie.
- Jenna. I wanna tupac you.
- Fine. But I have to pee first.
No. No,no,no, tupac shakur,the rapper.
He sold ten times more albums when
he was dead than when he was alive.
That's what we're going
to do with this movie.
Die young,become a
legend. Just like janis.
Or rusty,the bear fromthe magicals.
Yes. Now... You just need to
stay dead while I sell the movie.
Oh,i can play dead.
I watched my whole church
group get eaten by a bear.
Congratulations,miss lemon.
You've completed your
sensitivity traing.
Your suspension is up, and
here is your certificate.
Wow,so I can go back to work tomorrow?
That's soon.
Well,i know how eager
you are to return to work.
I guess so.
But coming back to
work isn't always easy.
Work means stress.
And stress can make you
fall back on old behavior.
So tonight, I want you to
really think about th d back.
Visualize everything that's facing you.
Think about walking through that door and immediately
dealing with 100 different problems and responsibilities.
Your coworkers' demands
on you, the long hours,
the pointless meetings
and endless phone calls.
Think of the frustration, the futility,
and the time That you will never get back
as you creep closer and closer to the grave.
Okay. Any questions for me?
Just one.
Why don't you drop those dockers
and gimme a piece of that sweet ass?
- What're we doing today,ladies?
- More of the same.
- Chell-o? - Lemon,what the hell
happened at your reinstatement hearing?
Jeffrey weener-slave said you
put your fingers in his mouth.
Did i? Or did he put
his mouth on my fingers?
It's gonna take at least six weeks
paid leave to g to the bottom of this.
I'm very busy right now faking
jenna's death to sell her movie.
I'm not going to engage on that. Mantra.
But I am calling h.r.and getting
you back for the next show.
No,i just-- I need a little more
time off. I'm on humanity leave.
Good god,what indigo
girls song is that from?
Syllabus of usoff
vagabonds,martyrs,and quilts.
The point is I have met the
most amazing group of women,jack.
They just live.
And they spin every morning,
and they go to museums.
- Lemon,you are not a rich divorcee.
- I know.
But I have some money
saved-- enough for two years.
Maybe four if I give up cable.
So I will me back to
the show in four years.
You're fooling yourself. You
know you can't live like that.
Yes,i can. Emily and
her friends are happy.
Believe me,there is no
solace in their luxury.
Only deep despair.
How do you know all
these indigo girls songs?
Listen,you are wrong about emily.
Oh,god,there's a spider
nest in my yo mat!
Mr. Jordan. Mr. Jordan,what did you do?
You fired daphne?
I had to.
Friendship and trust in the
entourage is the most important thing.
Like that hbo show. John adams.
- Well,me and dotcom are back to
being best friends. - We were never--
but the other dancers are refusing to
come to work out of solidarity with daphne.
Usually,this is the point in my process when
liz lemon steps in and takes care of everything.
Heavy is the head that eats the crayons.
I'm gonna take a nap.
See you in ten hours.
Kenneth. Have any of the
dancers come in yet today?
Pete. A word.
- Jenna's dead.
- I don't feel anything.
- What's wrong with me?
- No,no, it's a marketing ploy. For her new movie.
But it mns you won't have
her for the show on friday.
And you need to put together
some sort of on-air tribute.
We actually already have
an obituary reel for jenna.
We put it together after
she cheated on that mobster.
That's good.
Oh,eating right, working out,sleeping...
Bm-ing like a rock star?
All right,all right. What's
the hump day schedule look like?
Oh,it's esy, liz,it's thursday.
I read somewhere it's tuesday.
Mr. Jordan,it's friday. We really need to
tell mr. Hornberger that the dancers quit.
No we don't. He's not even
gonna notice they're gone.
- Oh,my.
- These are the new dancers,kid.
- Say hi to velvet.
- Hello,miss velvet.
Just think,an hour ago they
were brawling in a parking lot,
But tonight, they're gonna be stars.
Show ken here what we worked on.
Oh,boy.
Oh,boy, I am really starting to feel the
benefits of massages and yoga five days a week.
Check this out.
Look at you.
Last week you were flipping
out about missing work.
Oh,no,that's old liz.
My boss kept trying to tell me that I would go
crazy living a life of leisure,That it's unhe
well,he's actually right.
No,no,he's not,emily.
No,i used to be a neurosurgeon before
jasmine guy and I wrote our cookbook,
And the human brain needs
stimulation or it atrophies.
And your pleasure
center literally shrinks.
That's why we do our special activity.
To combat that.
What,like,sudoku?
uh,we did a games night for a
couple of weeks. Didn't last.
So charity work?
No,charity work sucks.
- Should we tell her?
- Erin,it's too soon.
- Punch me in the face,liz.
- I'm sorry,what?
You heard me.Punch
me as hard as you can,
and then I am coming
at you like an animal.
Oh,god, is this a fight club?
The pain provese're alive.
Oh,this is very dispointing!
Come on,hit me. Get a taste.
I brought a roll of
quarters to hold in my fist.
Oh,god. Jack was right.
Oh,i have to get back to my show.
- I need the show.
- You want out,liz?
You're gonna have to fight your way out.
As we celebrate the
life of jenna maroney...
The coast guard won't officially declare her
dead yet, but what the pirates did to that boat!
Well,it's a very generous
offer. We'll be in touch.
Jenna,what the hell are you doing here?
They're talking about me.
I'm really better today.
So's the laundry, *******
that was some of jenna
maroney's earlier work.
It's hard to believe that both
of those women outlived her.
Especially the woman on the right.
We'll be right back.
A coupla gay guys were crying.
Oh,jack,thiss just the
greatest night of my--
What the hell is that?
Well,it's you. What's the problem?
It has the year I was born on it.
Therealyear, not the actress year.
Now almost a million people
are gonna know that I'm f-- f--
- It's too late to change it,jack.
- Jenna,calm down.
I'm selling the movie in the
next 12 hours. Your movie.
Think about what matters here.
In five,four,three...
And finally tonight, what more fitting
way to say good-bye to our friend
than with the gifts
she gave all of us...
Her music.
Ladies and gentlemen, itzhak
bemelmans and the tracy jordan dancers.
Gimme me a microphone.
* Whole grain,low fat I
know you want a piece of that
* but I just wanna dance
still alive.Not yet 32.
Sorry,jack. Worth it.
- I'm back.
- What did it turn out to be? Lesbians?
No. Fight club.
this this is a disaster.
* But I'm just here to dance
what is wrong with you two?
You guys mess up everything you touch,
and then I have to come in here and fix it.
- I am so mad.
- Why are you smiling?
You're freaking me out.
Oh,you two troublemakers. Come here!
- She's gonna do something to us.
- You're crazy!
I'm back,nerds.
www.tvsubtitles.net