- Hello?
- Lemon. Good morning.
What... what is that sound?
Are you frying bacon?
No,it's my new running shoes.
Come on. Lemon,I'm going over the guest
list for my fiftieth birthday party.
and you haven't gotten RSVPed.
Oh,right. Sorry. My
mail's been piling up.
And I keep forgetting
to buy toilet paper. So.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing,i'm coming.
Good. And don't wear
that thing with a belt.
What thing with a belt? Don't hang
up. I have a lot of belts that...
Ugh,what is this idiot doing?
I will be brief. I have decided to
fulfill my dream of going into space.
If you have a spaceship and are
looking for a hillarious astronaut
with an irregular heartbeat
and thirty million dollars.
I'm prepared to leave
as soon as tomorrow.
I wrote that yesterday. I
will not be taking questions.
- Hello,dummy.
- No!
Nope,not interested. Have a good life.
It's important. It's about my mom.
That was a lie.
But listen,Elizabeth. I recently
discovered that I'm a sex addict.
- No,you're not.
- Yeah,yeah.
I'd be an even worse sex addict if I wasn't
so consumed by my latest business adventure.
I don't wanna hear
about your job,Dennis.
One word. Coffee. One
problem. What do you get it?
Anywhere,you get it anywhere.
Wrong. You get it at my
coffee vending machine.
38 and 6th in the basement at K-mart.
You just go downstairs.
You get the key from David.
- And boom,you plug into a machine.
- You're done.
But the point is I'm
Dennis. And I'm a sex addict.
And one of my steps towards
recovery is atonement.
Please,stop talking.
Or my sex partner.
I'm sorry that my disease has made
you my victim of my sexual chrisma.
I'm sorry that I've
ruined you for other men.
Apology accepted. Now
get out of my apartment.
You know,my sponsor said you were gonna try
to pick a fight to lure me in and hit sex.
It's not gonna work,Elizabeth. My
support group is lousy with infos.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
∑≠“Î£∫
30 Rock
Season03 Episode16
Have you seen this tracy thing?
I am aware of it.
I have a google news
alert for the phrase
"tracy jordan ridiculous disaster."
Have you spoken to him?
We're on the phone with his assistant
Setting up a time for us to talk.
Well,when do you expect him?
I think he has stuff all morning.
You think or you know?
Hang on. I'm going into a tunnel.
What is this?
My mother sent me a box
of old donaghy home movies.
For your birthday? That's sweet.
No,not really.
This is the card that came with it.
"jackie,here is some of your junk.
"it was taking up the space
"my new boyfriend
needed for his golf bags.
His name is paul and he
doesn't want to meet you."
- mm.
- at any rate,
I had jonathan convert
the movies to dvd,
Preserve these memories forever.
Oh,my god.is that you?
I like your little sweater vest.
Oh! Hi-yo!
- you threw up?
- what?
As a kid you never got
so excited you vomited?
No. No one does that.
I mean,i've peed a little.
Help me!
His tie caught in the shredder!
I'm lizzing! I'm lizzing!
"lizzing" is a combination
of laughing and whizzing.
Uh,well if you want
a good lizz,read this.
- What is it?
- A list i made in the fifth grade...
Of the things i wanted to have done
By the time i turned 50.
Oh,my god. This is adorable.
"go to disneyland. Ride in an airplane.
Kiss peggy fleming."
Done,done,and oh,boy. Done.
"live in a house with stairs.
"beat up a russian.
Hit mom with a car."
I wonder what that ten
year old would think
If he could see himself now.
"fly on a plane." i've
flown on air force one.
"go to disneyland."
Lemon,i've held walt disney's
frozen head in my hands.
That's awesome.
I've danced with queen noor.
I've hunted the world's
most dangerous game.
Man.
Excuse me. Manatee.
I once shot a manatee.
Well,if that kid could
see himself today,
He would throw up.
Thank you,lemon.
There's only one left.
"be friends with batman."
There's still a couple of hours.
Jonathan.
Could you get adam west's
agent on the phone please.
Griswald talent management.
Representing excellence.
It's funny.
I actually played peter pan on broadway.
Did you know there's a
broadway street in tampa?
Now this is important.
This needs to be threaded all the way up
In order to lock.
Otherwise you could fall.
- in bed.
- pay attention.
Also,you can't have
anything in your pockets.
Oh,my phone.
Will you hold that? Thanks.
Ready.
I'm flying!
Oh,my god.why are there
so many dead doves up here?
Jenna's phone.
Hey,jenna. This is dennis duffy.
Yes,hello,this is jenna.
I bet you never thought
You'd be hearing from me again now,huh?
Yes,really.why so ever
would you be phoning me?
With the help of webmd
I was recently self-diagnosed
as a sex addict.
So former sex partner,i'm
sorry that my disease
Made you a victim of my sexual charisma.
I'm sorry that i ruined
you for other men.
Look,i would've come down
there and done this in person
But it's complicated because
of the whole liz thing you know.
Naturally.liz. Always.
If she found out about
this she couldn't handle it.
And it would ruin your friendship.
You know,i was the love of liz's life.
I'm not sure you were
but apology accepted.
Oh,no. i totally was.
Peace.
Forget it,tracy.
Tracy,listen. You cannot go into space.
Your contract expressly
prohibits dangerous activities
Like extreme sports or riding
the subway on st. Patrick's day.
What is this? Horseville?
'Cause i am surrounded by naysayers!
- wordplay.
- that is solid.
Look,when i was a kid
growing up in the projects,
I would look up at the stars
And dream of going into
space. Of escaping the slums.
Of killing an ewok!
Now the man that that kid has become
Can make those dreams come true.
Do you know what that's like?
I do,tracy.
Then you know why i have to do this.
As robert browning once wrote,
"oh,but a man's reach
should exceed his grasp.
Or what is a heaven for?"
I was prepared for the
possibility of this meeting.
Tracy,i'll call up my friends at nasa
And i'll set up a flight for you.
Thank you,jackie d.
Jack,what the hell?
I'm not taking his childhood
dream away from him.
Not on my birthday.
So you're just gonna let him do this?
Of course not.
I don't have friends at nasa.
Bunch of nerds.
You're gonna have to use your tv magic
And fake a space launch for tracy.
Aw,i was gonna go for a run today!
Oh.ha ha.
You missed a call.
Was it my doctor/trainer?
No,it was dennis. Dennis duffy.
Calling me? Why?
Well jenna,dennis has been going around
Calling all the women
he's ever had sex with.
- did you speak to him?
- yes.
- did you pretend to be me?
- i did.
Did you do an impression of me?
- of course.
- was it british?
- it was.
- oh,my god,liz.
First of all,the reason i
have some english inflection
In my speech is because
i lost my virginity
- to the my fair lady
soundtrack. - jenna--
Second,you guys had broken up
And dennis and i were
in a very emotional place
- because of hurricane katrina.
- jenna,stop.
Yes,what you did was disgusting.
But how long have we known each other?
15 years.
We met at that car dealership
audition in chicago.
You were trying to be an actress then,
- despite your neck
- right. Yes.
Well we have both seen
this happen too many times.
A strong female friendship
torn apart by some guy.
But that's not what's
gonna happen this time.
Dennis duffy said he didn't want this
To hurt our friendship.
As if someone like him ever could.
Oh,thank you,liz.
I mean,the idea that
that guy is walking around
Thinking he means anything
to me--to either of us--
It's ridiculous.
It's unacceptable.
We shouldn't let him get away with it.
Are you thinking what i'm thinking?
- yeah,let's stab him.
- let's give him a piece of our mind.
Yeah,your thing.
More gifts,mr. Donaghy.
Oh,you got a new tuxedo for your party.
You know i wore nothing
but hand-me-downs
Until i was 12 years old.
But i thought you were the oldest,sir.
Oldest boy.
- now look at me.
- i already did.
Wow. That's a lot of loot.
My last birthday,i cleaned up.
Look at this keychain i got.
Every time you move
his head,his head moves!
Look!
Kenneth,i wonder what it's like
Seeing the world through your eyes.
I don't know,mr. Donaghy.
I think i see the world
pretty much the same
As everyone else.
Really?
* 'cause i think you're
very special,kenneth *
Pardon me.
* to be able to get so much joy *
- * from simple things *
- * simple things *
* simple * things.
But most of us grow up
And lose our sense of wonder.
- oh,that's sad.
- not really. No.
I've surpassed my wildest dreams.
I'm--i'm happier
than i've ever been.
Of course you are.
You've got all these fancy presents
From business associates
And this big empty
house to store them in.
Happy birthday,mr. Donaghy.
Hello,dummy.
Hey.
What's up?
I know about you and jenna,dennis.
Oh.
I--i get why
you're here.
You want me to rank you.
- apples and oranges,ladies.
- no. Stop. Shut up.
I'm here because i want you to know
That i am not mad at jenna about this.
Well,you can't be mad at me either,liz.
I mean,i went to your apartment
that night looking for you.
To be with you.
Wait a minute,hang on. My apartment?
Okay,i can explain that.
You had gone on that over 30
outward bound trip to arizona.
And you had asked me to housesit.
Well,dennis came over.
And as i mentioned,
We were both pretty torn
up about hurricane katrina.
What those people were
doing to the superdome.
Fine. All right.
You know what,it happened.
What do you want from me?
This is what i want from you.
I want you to understand
exactly how unimportant you are.
You are not the love of my life.
You are not capable of hurting me.
And you could never do anything
to damage this friendship.
It was in your bed.
Aw,guys,come on! i eat in there.
No,i'm gonna take the high road.
So good luck with your fake addiction
And your inconveniently-located
vending machine.
No,not okay,liz.
Not okay.
All right,fine. You know what?
I'm ranking you now.
Hey,blondie. You're number one.
- thank you,dennis.
- i don't care.
You got it.
Ladies and gentlemen,i can't stay long.
I'm on a case.
The penguin's in town.
But i would like to
introduce my good friend.
The man of the hour.
Jake delahey!
Jake.
This is wrong.
It's all wrong.
Everyone go home now.
The party's over.
I was told i'd get a meal.
Fine. Why don't you just,uh...
Jack,am i the first one here?
Ugh! i waited. This always happens.
Lemon,what's inside that box?
I don't know. A toy?
Tonight was supposed to be special.
And all i could think
about was that kid.
So happy,he threw up.
The closest i came to vomiting tonight
Was when i saw ann
coulter's shoulder blades.
What happens to us?
We grow up.
I have a good life,
But i'll never be that happy again.
I want that back.
Well,there's nothing
you can do about that.
I disagree.
I'm going to find out
what was inside that box.
I'm going to buy it with money.
And it's going to make me happy.
If that doesn't work,
I'm going to benjamin button myself.
We're not meeting in the middle.
Oh,hey.
I just wanted to get you to approve
The other astronauts we hired.
Looks good. Where's tracy?
In cape canaveral.
By which i mean through that door.
We told him he had to be
blindfolded before launch
- to prevent space madness.
- sure.
And then we put him on the channel four
Traffic copter for a couple hours.
And now he's landed
here in sunny florida.
- well done,hornberger.
- yeah.
As a child,i dreamed
of being a congressman
Like my father.
Now i do this.
One dui in high school.
At least it's dry heat here in florida.
Good work astronaut jordan.
Now do 20 space sit-ups.
Computer,when do i get some tang?
Also,i'm thirsty.
Wordplay.
Morning,jenna.
Hey,you.
God,telling dennis off
together was so empowering.
I felt so jacked up on the way home
That i threw a brick through the window
Of a banana republic.
Yeah,it was something.
I can't believe dennis
tried to do that to us.
But he got his,right? Sisterhood.
Sure. Sisterhood!
- oh.
- what?
Nothing.
Ah! Ah!
Be careful,'cause that thing is open.
I'll go get the
emergency floor marshall.
Floor marshall!
Hey,you called tech support?
I need to see what's inside that box.
If i learned anything from watching 24,
You're gonna want to
zoom in and enhance.
Why don't you ask jimmy what's in there?
It says "from jimmy" on it.
Jimmy flaherty.
Jimmy,what did you get
me for my tenth birthday?
Uh,i thought this was a job interview.
I flew down from boston.
I have to know,jimmy.
I need to know what you
got me that made that happy.
I don't remember,jack.
Doesn't this thing have any sound on it?
You're clearly saying something.
Jonathan,get me a deaf person.
I was told this was a job interview.
Tell me,wendy. What am i saying?
You're saying,
"apollo,apollo,apollo--"
Oh,my god! You puked!
Why wouldn't you warn me?
I'm staring at your mouth!
Apollo.
I know what it is!
Liz lemon.
Hey,sista! How's the leg?
You are a piece of work.
These crutches are real,everyone.
- liz tried to kill me.
- what are you talking about?
Oh,please,you saw the harness
and you didn't do anything.
T-minus ten minutes.
- be quiet. Tracy's coming.
- all systems are go for launch.
Star wars.
All that stuff about
our friendship was a lie.
You would've let me die,liz!
- over dennis duffy.
- so okay,i did a bad thing.
But you slept with dennis.
And now we're...even?
Even? i can't even look at you.
You know what?
You're no long my plus one
to the canadian grammys.
Two,one,zero.
- lift off,we have a lift off.
- i'm scared
But i'm also excited!
Whoo!I'm lizzing!
Ah ha ha ha! Lizzing!
I'm lizzing!
Yeah! Ha ha!
Oh,what is that,sir?
This is an apollo
command and lunar module
That i just paid $7,000
for at a vintage toy store
Where a morbidly obese
gentleman called me "pal."
Whoa.
Tracy to earth. Come in,earth!
Mr. Jordan.
How is space?
Great wink,kenneth.
Space is very cold but very beautiful.
And sometimes it sounds like
jenna yelling in the distance.
I think i--
oh,my god.
Where did you get that rocket?
Mr. Donaghy's letting me hold it.
It's awesome.
You know,i actually envy you two.
Sometimes i wish i could see the world
Through your eyes instead of mine.
Hey,jackie d.
If everyone could see the
world the way i see it,
It would be a better place to live.
I bet that's true,tracy.
But that part of me is gone forever.
I guess i just see the
world the way i see it.
Is he letting me keep this?
I think so.
I wish i was there so
i could play with it.
Hi,miss lemon.
What do you want?
I want to make it up to you,jenna.
What can i do?
How about on the next
show you could do that song
That they wouldn't let you
sing at the inauguration?
No.
Chocolate rainbow is too good for tgs.
You can tell them.
You can tell the writers.
Tell them what?
About my commercial.
The one i was in back in chicago. Ugh
Everyone,listen to me.
No,it's a real thing this time.
When we were both living back in chicago
And liz was still
trying to be an actress,
The only job she ever booke
- was for a local phone sex line.
- what?
It was a chat line for urban singles.
And they only hired her
Because their first choice was deported.
Okay,we're even.
So you will
not find it--
I found it. It's on youtube.
What?
No--
I have a cable to hook
the computer up to the tv.
Then shut your wet
mouth and get that cable.
- get it!
- come on,guys.
Let's all be cool.
That's not gonna--
Don't wait.
How did you do that so fast?
Hi,i'm bijou.
- bijou!
- call me.
Oh,my god!
I have since had invisalign.
That is not attractive.
Call us. In english,german,or polish.
That's not even enough numbers.
21 hours a day.
What is this?
It's a commercial that
liz did back in chicago.
That's liz.
No.
Call us. We love to party.
I remember that girl.
She cried all day.
No,this is not happening!
What's so funny?
Oh,is that billie jean king?
Oh,my god!
I haven't laughed this much since...
Since...
Everybody back up.
Get out of the way! He's gonna jack!
Goodness gracious!
- god,he's mortal!
- what just happened?
Oh,lord! Oh,lord! Ah!
Hey,are you feeling okay?
I feel great. i feel like a kid.
Lemon,i honestly don't know
what i would do without you.
I'll see you tomorrow,jack.
See you tomorrow... Bijou.
www.tvsubtitles.net