Subtitle by: Kisauseven
- How late is Tracy now?
- 2 1/2 hours.
[buzzes]
This is outrageous.
Especially after I was told
I can't leave during the day
For my ridiculous anger
management stupid piece of crap!
How did this happen?
I had Grizz call him
at 8:00 this morning
and pretend it was 11:00.
I printed up that fake
rehearsal schedule for him,
Saying we were starting
at 9:00 instead of noon.
Oh, and I set all his
watches and clocks
- to say P.M. when it's really A.M.
- Oh, boy. We may have overdone it.
What the hell time
is it?
Hey, you're here!
Let's rehearse!
No! I took my son to his
cello recital this morning
at what turned out to be
midnight yesterday!
White oppressors,
answer my question.
What time is it, really?
- 2:45 P.M.
- You're a bunch of racists.
What? How did we jump
to that already?
You treat me like a child!
No--worse than that!
You treat me like one of those
little pageant girls
with the clip-on teeth.
No, no, Oprah says that you
teach people how to treat you,
and this is what you've taught us,
because you're always late
And you take no responsibility
for your actions.
Irregardless!
You know what?
Race card.
No, don't accept it!
Hey, Jack,
just a heads-up.
Tracy knows what time it is.
- Damn it.
- Sir.
Your mother would like to have
breakfast with you
At the hotel tomorrow,
And she had me make dinner
reservations for tonight.
And by night,
I mean 4:30 this afternoon.
Colleen's in town?
If you need a break,
I'd be happy to take her out.
There's a restaurant hostess
in midtown I'd like to see cry.
Thank you, but I need to be
the attentive son this visit.
This Thursday marks
an anniversary for my mother,
An unpleasant one.
35 years ago, my father,
Jimmy Donaghy,
Went out for a pack
of cigarettes,
Came back, smoked one,
Told my mother
he was leaving forever,
And walked out the door.
Oh, boy, that must be hard...
For both of you.
He treated her like dirt
all those years,
Coming and going,
taking up with other women,
Including more than one
Unitarian!
Every time he came back,
I promised myself
I would tell him off.
I had my speech all planned.
But I always chickened out.
It's the biggest regret
of my life, Lemon...
And I once made love
to Kathy Hilton.
Do you...Want a hug?
What is this,
the Italian parliament?
No, thank you, Lemon.
Well, you're a good son.
I know she's not easy.
Sir, your mother had me
move her from the plaza
To the Carlyle.
Evidently, the concierge
at the plaza
"has a beard," and she'd
rather not get raped.
Please,
tell me we've started.
Yes, actually, we're on
our second run-through.
What is this?
[buzz]
Tracy hasn't come back yet,
But he did sent a gibbon
to rehearse in his place.
[laughs]
he's pretty good.
Hey.
Did you guys know about this?
Tracy has asked us
to read this prepared statement.
- "Dear racist Liz Lemon..."
- oh!
"this is how you treat me,
"like a white-whiskered gibbon
"put on this earth
to do nothing
"but dance around
for your amusement
And reduce the insect
population of Malaysia."
Okay, I don't know
Which of these five
cell numbers he answers,
But you get
Tracy down here right now.
Why? The gibbon is on time,
he knows his blocking,
And he doesn't try
to bite the dancers!
I think
I've proven my point.
Oh, my god!
Like we really
have time for you
To walk down the stairs
that slowly!
Time jump!
Tracy, it costs the show
a lot of money
When you pull
these shenanigans.
Don't patronize me with your
Celtic slang, Liz Lemon.
We have
a black president now.
What do you care?
You voted for Nader!
This is post-racial America,
And I demand to be treated
like everyone else.
You wanna be treated
like everybody else?
Fantastic.
Then tomorrow, I'm sending
a regular town car for you
Instead of one of those
duck tour boats.
Fine.
And you're no longer allowed
to point at women
In the cafeteria and yell,
"I wanna get that pregnant!"
Fine, I'll bring
my lunch from home.
And be here tomorrow at
10:00 A.M. And know your lines.
[commotion, murmuring]
You don't think
I could do that?
We'll find out tomorrow
at 10:00 A.M.
Fine, but I'll have
the last laugh.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[overlapping laughter]
Hoo hah hah hah hah!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
[exciting jazz music]
Beth, that was
a big mistake you made.
Grizz, it was a year ago.
You're engaged now.
Just drop it, okay...
Oh, hey, Dotcom.
Yelling at Tracy
in front of everybody
Was a bad move, Liz.
Yeah, well, it's not my job
to protect his feelings.
I told you
she would turn cold.
She's an ice queen.
- Grizz.
- I'm just sayin'.
You humiliate Tracy
in front of everybody like that,
You give him two choices...
one, he won't show up tomorrow,
And you'll look like a fool
in front of your crew.
Or two, he will show up...
and he'll find an even
worse way to act out.
Exactly.
Jack!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pick you up
for dinner.
No dinner.
We're having breakfast
in the morning.
I told your girl.
- My assistant is named Jonathan.
- Yes, I know. I met him.
And he also said we had a
reservation for dinner tonight.
Well, Jack, there's been
a misunderstanding.
I have a previous engagement
with a friend.
Hey Colleen, can I borrow
one of your ties?
Oh, brother.
Paul, this is Jack, my son.
Jack, this is Paul Brett.
Mother, I didn't realize
you were bringing
a companion along.
Companion? Ha!
How fancy.
Paul lives in Florida.
He paints landscapes
and he makes his own soda.
Jack, why don't you
join us for dinner?
Great!
I'll call the restaurant.
See if they can seat
a third wheel.
Ah. Another day done.
Now let's get outta here
Before we realize
we've forgotten about something.
I feel like
we're half-assing this.
Oh, I didn't know
anyone was here.
That wasn't me
screaming in the bathroom.
What are you doing with him?
Oh, Mr. Jordan says
he doesn't need it anymore.
So you're just
letting him go?
Well, don't worry.
Once it tries to mate
with a child,
I'm sure animal control
will just shoot it.
No! He's not an animal.
Look at him!
He's a little person!
[giggling]
Oh, he loves me!
Somebody loves me.
I'm gonna name him
little Jenna
And let him live
in my dressing room.
Lemon, Colleen brought
her boyfriend.
His name is Paul.
- What? Really?
- I don't like this guy.
I don't trust him.
I mean, he's four years
younger than my mother.
He wears a pinkie ring.
When the waiter brought over
the food, he said, "abbondanza."
Okay, Jack, I know
this is a stressful time
For you and your mother...
You're right--I don't like
the timing of this at all.
Colleen is very
vulnerable right now,
And scam artists
can smell that sort of thing.
Have you ever
been to Florida?
It's basically
a criminal population.
It's America's Australia.
Come on,
maybe he just likes her.
You know, some men
like older women.
Let's...Not make this
about you, okay?
I've gotta call
my private investigator.
Liz, they want you
onstage for rehearsal.
- Tracy's here already?
- I guess so.
You know, this food area
Is always the first place
I go to look for you...
Thank you, Cerie.
Tracy, you're here already.
Professional
is my middle name.
No need.
I've got it memorized.
I'm going to do
a Valentino cross,
Camera right,
then dump the laugh.
So stay on your fours,
guys!
One, two, three,
jump and pose!
3:15.
Time for union break.
[applause]
Thank you, Tracy!
That is so great for morale.
Listen, about yesterday...
No. Do not apologize.
In fact...
Everyone gather around.
Actor announcement.
I want to publicly thank you,
Liz Lemon,
For you have shown me
that in today's world
Everyone should be treated
exactly the same.
No one should get
preferential treatment.
I agree.
Exactly.
Not black comedy superstars.
Not Hispanics.
Not Indians.
Not whatever this guy is.
And not women, Liz Lemon.
I'm right there
with you, Tracy.
Good. I feel parched
from being so professional.
Could I trouble you
for some water?
Yeah, of course.
Brian, would you
help me out with this?
No! No!
- Equality.
- What?
Everyone should be treated
the same, right, Liz Lemon?
You should change it.
Yeah, okay.
I know how to do this.
No one help her!
I got it.
That's good.
Just gotta get my hammies
in the handles so I...
Hold on.
Oof!
[panting]
All right!
Let's...Take it
from the top.
[clicking]
Hello, Len.
Oh. Thanks for meeting me
here, Mr. Donaghy.
You, uh...Staking out
a cheating husband?
No. I'm taking
a photography class.
Look at the way the sunlight
hits that cobweb.
[clicking]
So, uh, what have you
got for me?
Well, I looked into
this Paul Brett guy,
And I gotta tell you,
This is the weirdest case
I've ever worked.
I knew it.
What is he, a check forger?
Real estate swindler?
Bird owner?
- No, he's clean.
- What?
I've never seen
anything like it.
Everyone's
got something to hide.
For instance, I'm wearing
a child's Halloween costume
Under this.
But this guy...
no priors, no debts.
He's been married to his wife
Louise for 35 years.
- He's married?
- Yeah.
I wish I had more
to give you.
But this Paul Brett guy,
he's, uh...
He's like a boy scout.
I'm sorry, Mr. Donaghy.
Miss Maroney, I have
the ukulele you asked for.
Oh, it's not for me.
Someone's in a little
mariachi band today.
Ma'am, this is a wild animal.
You can't treat it
like a person.
No, he's happy.
His costume
is hiding his erection.
Well, as a child,
I had a prize pig
That I thought
was my best friend.
But then one day,
I picked up one of her piglets.
She went crazy!
She bit off my nut sack
That I kept tied around
my belt to feed squirrels.
Please be careful,
Miss Maroney.
Tracy did that thing
with the water on purpose.
Grizz and Dotcom warned me
he would act out.
Look, if Tracy's revenge plan
Involves him
being good at his job,
You might have
to just take it.
Hello, Liz Lemon.
I was just
telling these fellas
About how you don't wanna be
treated any differently
Because you're a woman.
Well, thank you.
Of course I don't.
Really. You don't want us
to hold back anymore.
I'm sorry--were you guys
holding back something?
Our farts,
to start with.
Also, we didn't invite you
to Lutz's fake bachelor party.
Lutz's what?
I realize I'm never
getting married
Because of my gland thing...
But I wanna have
a bachelor party.
Well, you should have
invited me.
It's not fair...
That you didn't.
We're goin'
to a strip club.
I'm glad that we're having
this conversation,
Because we live in a world
Where a lot of
the old divisions
Are starting to disappear.
And I hope to have
a daughter someday,
And I want her to...
Aghh. Oh, god,
what is that smell?
Oh, dear lord, frank!
It's like orange-flavored egg!
It's in my mouth!
Good. We're learning.
This next one's me.
Ohh!
Hey, Jack,
do you treat me any differently
Because I'm a woman?
Well, I pay you
a little less, yes.
No, I mean day-to-day.
- Do you coddle me?
- In some ways.
With a man,
I can be more direct,
But with you, uh,
I have to have a conversation,
Talk things through more.
Gimme an example.
Well, uh...
Right now comes to mind.
Are we through listening
and sharing,
Because I have something
I want you to look at.
It's a marriage certificate.
It's Paul's
marriage certificate.
My mother's boyfriend.
- He's married.
- What?
I knew I was right.
That guy is shady!
Oh, my god.
Have you told Colleen?
No Colleen.
I have an opportunity here,
Lemon,
A chance to go back
to the past to put things right
That once went wrong.
That's the quantum leap
intro.
Be that as it may,
I'm finally going
to stand up for Colleen.
The small part of her
that is still human deserves it.
I'll see Paul,
And I'll give him the speech
I wrote for Jimmy Donaghy.
- Paul's not your dad, Jack.
- But Paul's here.
And he's taking advantage
of my mother.
Now, what I originally
wrote for my father
May be dated.
Who would be our current
Nikita Khrushchev?
Mm...Simon Cowell?
[gasps]
Now you're standing
on the very spot
Where Gracie Allen
took Jack Paar's virginity.
I thought I heard a tour.
Boy, people
are not gonna believe
That you saw this.
- So take a lot of pictures.
- Miss Maroney.
No good will come of this.
This is unnatural.
It is unnatural...For
a grandmother to look this good!
Little Jenna
had a baby last night.
Crowd: Ooh!
Thank you.
Good job
with the water, Liz.
Ow, frank!
What the hell?
What? I'm trying
to treat you like one of us.
Hello, Elizabeth.
Tracy, shouldn't you be
working down on stage?
I'm done with my work.
I was very professional.
Hmm. That must have been
hard for you.
It was.
All right, Tracy's here.
Let's do this bachelor party.
- Yeah!
- You coming, Liz Lemon?
Because a dude boss
would be a jerk
If he didn't come
to Lutz's bachelor party.
Also a dude boss
would pay for it.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Of course I'm coming.
- But you're not.
- Twist!
You have to stay here.
I haven't gotten your notes
on the rewrite,
And your input
is invaluable to the process...
Since we're all equal now.
Let's go see some naked
daughters and moms!
- All right!
- Whoo hoo!
[indistinct cheering]
Oh. Hello, Jack.
I'm sorry.
Your mom's out shopping.
I know.
My credit card company
called to confirm
My purchase of a book entitled
intercourse after hip surgery.
Well...Why don't you
come on in?
I'm just watching
the hotel channel.
You can check out
on the TV.
I bet you can,
you son of a bitch.
I beg your pardon?
I am tired of watching you
treat my mother like this.
I am not afraid of you.
You're just a big bully.
Like Simon Cowell.
That's right.
I just called you
a communist.
I want you out
of our lives forever,
[door opens]
and I want you to know
That I am never
going to be
Anything like you
when I grow up.
What in god's name
is going on here?
Paul is leaving, mother.
And I think you should know why.
He's married.
Oh, my...
I know that!
[sighs] Paul...
Find something to do
in the bathroom.
I have to talk to my son.
Okay.
Shoot.
You knew?
It's Florida, Jack!
It's like it never stopped
being the '70s down there.
And a guy like Paul,
who can drive at night,
You just don't say no
to that!
Well, I apologize then.
I thought we were going
to get through this together.
I guess your coping mechanism
Is to bring a married man
back to your hotel room!
Coping?
What am I supposed
to be coping with?
It's the 35th anniversary
of dad leaving!
Which time, Jack?
That man left and came back
so many times
That I totally lost count!
One night,
he went out to move the car,
And he was gone...
From the spring of '57
until...
One night he just
showed up out of the blue!
"put your shoes on, Collie.
We're goin' to see
some like it hot."
You honestly don't remember
when he left for good,
Because I sure as hell do.
Oh, my god.
Is that what this is all about?
Is that what you've been
holding onto all these years?
Jack, stop wasting your time
thinking about that man!
You're nothing like him,
you know.
No way you ever could be.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I'm old, Jack, you know?
And I don't know what I'm
thinking about half the time.
I do know this:
You're my good boy.
[voice breaking]
I just love ya to death.
Thank you, mother.
And I love you too.
Paul!
You're on your own tonight.
I have a date with my son.
He's taking me out
to a late dinner.
It's, uh, 6:00.
Whoops!
Say you like my body.
[crying]
I don't wanna be here!
I don't like it here!
Who's this guy?
[sobbing]
Okay, which one of us
is gonna give up first?
The black one.
I can't take it anymore!
I hate it!
One of those strippers
took of Lutz's shirt.
That gland thing
is no joke!
Everything is upside down!
We need to go back
to the way things were
With both of us getting
preferential treatment.
Yes. We upset
the natural order.
You're going to strip clubs.
I'm up writing all night.
Look who's a sailor!
We're dressing monkeys up
as people,
And monkeys are playing
with people as toys!
It's not a toy, Tracy.
Little Jenna thinks
that this is her baby.
[screeching]
- Oh, no!
- You said you loved me!
Your foot fingers
are so strong!
We don't wanna end up
like those two.
You're so right.
[Jenna laughing]
We're okay!
He's just expressing himself!
[monkey chittering]
Hey, before you hear crazy
rumors and start believing them,
The gibbon did not
attack Jenna.
He was trying to mate
with her face.
- What?
- Nothing. Everyone's fine.
Hey! Some like it hot.
I love this movie.
My mother told me
she and my dad
Went to see it together,
And if that's the stuff
she remembers,
Maybe that's how
I should remember him too...
On a date with my mom
instead of walking out the door.
1959. Boy, it would have
been fun to write back then.
You could get away
with crazy plot twists
Because audiences were
so much less sophisticated.
Wait a minute.
This movie
came out in 1959?
How could my father
have been gone
From the spring of '57
until 1959
If I was conceived in '58...
Jimmy Donaghy's not my father.
[gasps]
Twist!
www.tvsubtitles.net