Oh,good morning, dr. Baird.
Good morning, regular person lemon.
Oh,hey,are you around this weekend?
- Uh,maybe we could have
that date talked-- - Yes.
Okay. Uh,how 'bout... Friday?
Oh,no,friday I have a stupid...
Show. How 'bout saturday?
Saturday,uh... Okay. I guess
that doesn't have to be weird.
- Okay then.
- Okay.
Valentine's day it is.
Saturday is valentine's day?
Norts!
You sound so sexy when you say that.
Say it again.
Your mother's gone back to florrrida.
These mcflurries are amazing.
I know.
The soft swirl of vanilla, And the
hard crunch of candy and cookies.
You'd think they fight each other,
But no,together they are perfecto.
Some would say that describes us.
Who would say such a crazy thing?
We are us.
Let a mcflurry be what it is--
The world's greatest dessert.
Actually,the world's greatest
dessert Is served in a restaurant
right here in new york Called plunder.
It costs $1,000.
Lucky for you,your boyfriend got
reservations For valentine's day.
But I have to go to church.
On valentine's day? Is that a thing?
It is the feast of the
martyrdom oft. Valentine.
Please,jack,don't tell me you're
one of those Convenient catholics
That only goes to church every sunday.
No.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
30 Rock
Season03 Episode11
Oh,kennet h ey,you know how the company
makes an effort To hire the disabled?
Do i!
I wouldn't have this job If it
weren't for the mouth on my back.
Yeah,i'm supposed to supervise some
blind chick They hired to edit the reruns.
But three of the dancers just found
out They're all dating the same guy,
So i'm gonna go watch that.
So if you see a blind
chick, I don't know.
Um,give her one of yr ring tours.
Yes,sir. Yes,sir.
I was just funnin'. It's all sewed up.
I'll help you,miss.
Oh,thank you so much.
All my friends warned me about the big
city, But look,right away I meet a gentleman.
Is everything okay? Because
now I smell burnt plastic.
Hello? E you there?
Hello?
I can't make this guy go on
a first date On valentine's.
Why are you so nervous about this?
Because it's a delicate situation,jack.
There is handsomeness involved.
How much?
Oh,come on,lemon.
- What is this,a green card thing?
- No.
- Closet case?
- I don't think so.
- Slump buster?
- No,not a ballplayer.
Bundy-esque serial killer?
That wasmyfirst thought, but no.
This is actually happening,
and i'm blowing it.
Who pushes for a first
date on valentine's day?
Lemon,here's how you
correc this misstep.
Instead of going to a restaurant,
Where it'll be nothing but people in
love And rings hidden in pastries...
Cook him a nice meal at home.
Nice... You mean, like,stew?
I certainly do not mean stew.
I mean,try to forget
it's valentine's day.
I'm into. I'll be in church.
What? Why?
Elisa is deeply religious.
If I had those knockers,
i'd be thanking god too.
All I want for valentine's day is to go
to plunder And eat the lovers' delight.
That sounds filthy,jack.
It is.
Imagine a
dessert for two--
Tahitian vanilla bean
ice cream in a pool ofogc,
Drizzled in the world's
most expensive chocolate,
Amadei porcelana, Covered with shaved
white, black,and clear truffles,
And topped with edible
25-karat gold leaf.
Can you imagine anything better?
I don't know,you ever put
a doughnut in the microwave?
Come on,church won't be so
bad. Aren't you catholic?
I was catholic.
But I haven't set foot inside a
church Since I was 13 years old.
So listen,so you go sit through a night
of church, And then you go to plunder.
Elisa's worth it.
You're right. Elisa is worth it.
And I can fake
enthusiasm when I need to.
Hey,that scarf is fun!
Thanks. I found it at
dunkin-- Wait a minute.
Nbc. Blah blah blah. Thank you.
Ken,you need to snap out of it
And ask out that sexy miss magoo.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I know love at first
sight when I see it.
I saw it when I met angie, I saw it the first
time dotcom laid eyes On grizz's fiancee.
Okay,there is something about jennifer
That just makes me all car sick inside.
Now is the time for gallantry.
It's you again. I can tell.
Well,cotton and fiddles!
I enjoy your smile.
Oh,my.
I'm jennifer rogers.
You may ll me kenneth the page.
Because that is who I am.
Would you like to go out with me
tomorrow night, Yes-indeedy corncobs?
Well,i'm gonna say yes.
Because this just feels right, And
my instincts have never let me down.
Except for looking at that eclipse.
It's a valentine's datelie-doo!
That was really good stew.
Thank you. It's my own recipe, Where
I use cheddar cheese instead of water.
You know,i'm glad we stayed in tonight.
It's good to take things slow.
Well,please know that when invited you over,
I didn't realize it was valentine's day.
Yeah,you still have that rotting
jack-o'- lantern In the hallway,
So I feel like you don't have a
great sense Of what month it is.
Well,it's just gotten so small That
I kinda want to see if it disappears.
So,uh,first date stuff.
Where are you from?
Well,um,there's a really interesting
answer To that question,actually.
I was born on the border of
maryland and pennsylvania.
Okay,i feel like I should do the
right thing here And tell you that
Your breast is falling out of your
blouse, And I can see all of it.
Okay,well,i guess we just
jumped ahead to date four.
It's not the good one,either.
- Jack donaghy's office.
- Jonathan!
Our jonathan, who art in the
office, Hallowed be my reservation.
If you are able, hold my table,
At plunder, As we will
not be there by 7:00.
Have them delay our heavenly
dessert, And forgive us our lateness,
As we forgive those who
cause lateness against us...
Well,thank you for explaining that.
I always wanted to know how
a universal remote works.
Well,that's how idoes.
Would you excuse me just one second?
I'll be right back.
Oh,cheese stew! What was I thinking?
I think your brownies are burning.
You want me to take 'em out?
Yes,please.
But whatever you do, Don't
open that kitchen window...
- No!
- Oh,too soon!
The draft made the door fly open!
I know. It's not a big deal.
So we skipped from date four to date...
No,date never. I would
never let that happen.
Liz,it's okay,i'm a doctor.
- I've seen much worse.
- Really?
I'm just kidding. That was pretty bad.
Hold on. Sorry. I have to get this.
Hello,mandy.
Yeah,no,i'm downstairs in 3-b. Why?
No,mandy,you can't just
drop her off without calling.
Mandy? Is that like a guy
friend? Like mandy patinkin?
No,i can't.
Because I am on a date right now.
No,mandy, do u
Sorry. That was my ex-wife. My
daughter bethany is on her way up.
You have a daughter?
You will see her. You
will say she's cute.
But let me just say that
she is... Complicated.
My mother usually watches her when I can't,
But my mother has been in the hospital recently,
And she's not doing very
well. And that has been...
Hard f me to handle.
I'm sorry that all this
keeps falling apart.
I was really looking forward to tonight.
Well,we can try again some other time.
- Or...
- I'm listening.
Maybe tonight is a gift.
Maybe we embrace the toilet thing, And the
bra incident, and my ex-wife, And my daughter,
And we just get it all out in one night.
And if by the end of it we still like
each other, Then maybe it's the real thing.
That would be bethany.
Well,this is it. The express
train is leaving the station.
- I'm on the train.
- Okay.
Mom's keying your car.
Bethany,this is liz.
- Hi,it's so nice to mee--
- Why does it smell in here?
- Cheese stew.
- I got sick.
Okay,be nice.
I will be right back After
I go talk to your mother.
And... Give me your purse.
Why don't you ever trust me?
Because,honey,you keep
setting fire to things.
And now a prayer For the pregnant
members of our congregation.
Anita alvarez...
Anna alvarez...
Anabel alvarez...
Honey,this is a catholic church.
We'll be here until morning.
All right, you've been good.
Let's go.
We just have to go to
confession before we leave.
Benita alveroz.
Okay,here's how this is gonna go.
We're gonna sit here in
silence For about three minutes,
Then i'm going to take
my girlfriend to plunder,
Where the pope himself
could not get a table.
- You sound troubled,my son.
- Can it,ther.
That was a nice try,though.
That limo ride was weird.
It felt like we just
circled the block 50 times.
That's how you get to
manhattan's fanciest restaurant.
Ah,monsieur parcell.
Votre table est pret.
I didn't know itas french restaurant.
Yes,i found it on my
favorite web site--
Stopshowingoff.com.
It's busy tonight.
It's the best darn-tootenest
restaurant In all of new york.
This is thbe thank you,kenneth.
You're one in a million.
Man,can you believe we're
working on valentine's night?
My fiancee's gonna be upset.
Not to worry. I sent her
flowers and a beautiful card.
You're the best.
Don't you have faith?
I have faith in things I can
see, And buy,anderegulate.
Capitalism is my religion. Now,you want
to have an intellectual argument? Fine.
But I should warn you,
I went to princeton.
I went to harvard divinity school.
You crimson guys never
miss a chance,do you?
You want a confession?
Let's get this done so I can go eat.
I am divorced.
I take the lord's name in vain
often and with great relish.
I hit my mother with a
car, possibly by accident.
I almost let him choke to death
Right there on the football field.
I looked the other way when my wig-based parent
company Turned a bunch of children orange.
I once claimed, "i am
god" during a position.
And I may have sodomized
our former vice president
While under the influence of
some weapons-grade narcotics.
It feels good to say
that out loud,actually.
That one was weiinon me.
Wow,i,uh...
I don't know what to say.
I don't want you to say anything.
I already made that clear.
Then what... Brought you here tonight?
What brought me here?
What brings anyone anywhere?
Why do men build bridges?
Why are there jets?
I was hoping to have sex tonight.
Have you ever made
love to a woman,father?
Come on,man.
Imagine cradling your face into
the curve Of a velvety-soft neck.
Your hands cupping the warm
heft Of the greatest pair of...
I need backup! Harvard
did not preparme for this.
Father?
I like your bracelets.
Girls at my school get them For
doing different things on the bus.
Blue is for showing your boobs.
Purple's for doing
stuff over your clothes.
- Black is for doing
stuff-- - okay,uh...
Your mom left. How are
you two getting along?
She had some more stew
while you were outside.
- Wow,liz, did u kill the whole bottle?
- What?
Sorry... Hello.
Yes,gloria. Why are you crying?
Gloria? How many ex-wives does he have?
That's my aunt. She'snotgonna like you.
No,of course. I'll be
there as soon as I can.
Yeah. Good-bye.
Mom has taken a turn.
Oh,i'm so sorry.
Look,i know we said that we would take
this In fast motion tonight, but...
No,no,i know.
I really am glad we did, Because I don't
think I could handle this by myself.
Okay.
What? Liz knew.
Entertainment?
Not just any entertainment.
The best singer in the
world-- Michael mcdonald.
Wow,he does not sound good live.
**********
*****
********
***********
*****
*********
******
**********
Okay,in english. In english.
You tortured that poor priest.
Let me ask you somhing.
Do you even believe in the
teachings Of the catholic church?
No.
But I saw your photo with the pope.
That's just good business. I
have photos with a lot of people.
The dalai lama,rabbi yosef, Toby keith.
I see.
You have no faith, only business.
You kn wt your problem is,jack?
You intellectualize
everything with your big head.
Well,you have big boobs!
Which you'll never touch again!
This conversation has
taken an unfortunate turn.
Maybe this is god trying to tell
me That we do not belong together.
Maybe this is a sign.
Look,my driver just
pulled up. That's a sign.
God wants us to leave here, get a good
meal, And go to town on each other.
How dare you say something like that
So close to the statue of santa lucia,
The patron saint of judgmental statues?
Go to your stupid restaurant.
Eat your gold ice cream.
Please come with me.
No. You blew it,jack.
And now you will never see
the crazy underwears I have on!
Elisa!
What kind of god would let that happen?
Oh,drew,finally.
- Who's this?
- This is liz. This is our first date.
On valentine's day?
Funny story.He saw
me on the toilet--
liz?
Dr. Baird,your mother's asked
to speak to you... Privately.
I'm sorry.
Is this,like, asixth sensething?
Should I bring a place
setting for your friend?
- Mom...
- Who is that?
That's my friend liz.
Hi,mrs. Baird.
It's too soon,andrew.
I know. We tried to take it slow...
Life!
I have more I want to do.
Oh,right,you. Of course.
I'm gonna grab her
chart. I'll be right back.
Mandy,you look terrible.
Oh,,i'm not mandy. I'm liz.
Mandy,you have to tell
drew something for me.
The woman he thinks is his
sister Is really his mother.
What?
I'm his grandmother.
You have to tell him, or
I won't get into heaven.
Thank you for a truly
unbelievable evening.
It doesn't have to end here,y'allsies.
Wait. This isn't right.
Kenneth,why do you suddenly sound white?
I lied to you,jennifer.
I was too scared to talk to you,
So my sophisticated friend tracy
Said the things that I couldn't.
I'm very,very sorry.
Well,if you could've talked
to me, Whatould you have said?
That you're the sweetest, prettiest,
Blindest girl i've ever met.
And when i'm with you, my heart jumps Like
a frog on july asphalt, right before it dies.
You're so beautiful on
the inside,kenneth parcell.
Can I feel your face?
Yeah.
Oh,look at the time. I
forgot,i have a-- a thing.
That is cold, blind lady!
Oh,and by the way, You're
not so attractive yourself!
No,i'm-- i'm
pretty sure i'm hot.
Yes,you are. I tried.
******
I'm so sorry.
Listen, thank you so much For
being so great during all this.
Let's do this again sometime.
Except have it not be
anything like this at all.
Yeah.
- Good night.
Uh,liz,you my mom did just die.
Funny story... Hear me out.
I'll have a,uh...
- A mcflurry,please.
And I have a coupon. You
know where I found it?
In the collection plate.
It was a sign.
I followed it,and it
brought us back together.
Now do you believe?
I believe.
I believe that we were reunited By the
most successful capitalist enterprise
Of the last hundred years,
Despite the mclean deluxe, or the mcemu.
Whatever.
Someone's trying to tell
us that we belong together.
- Maybe it's god.
- Maybe it's ray kroc.
Maybe it's the hamburglar.
Happy valentine's day, querida.
Happysaintvalentine's day, mi amor.
Boy,he that guy's not planning
To kill her and eat her.
Jack,you're such a romantic.
www.tvsubtitles.net