Thanks for coming out.
Thanks for watching.
Love,peace, and hair grease.
Hey,liz me,lutz,toofer,and josh are gonna go to
that bar where the waiters are dressed like ninjas.
You in?
No,I'm just gonna go to the
24-hour donut place and go home.
All right.
Donuts and then bed.
What are you depressed
about or celebrating?
It's this endless adoption
process.It took me three months--
liz. I am totally humiliated.
How could you cut diaper chicken?
Wait,i know. Because tracy's the star.
Oh,brother, she's feeling neglected.
How's she gonna act out th te?
My ankle!
Oh,imaginary injury.
I would have said
death of a voice coach.
Her birthday's on tuesday.
Maybe all that attention will
make her ankle feel better.
Hey,jack! What are you still doing here?
It's friday night. I
need something to do.
Don't you have some gallery opening or a
fundraiser to give bowties to inner city youths?
Of course. But I'm committed to elisa.
While she's away I'm
trying to avoid temptation.
I just need somewhere I can
socialize where women aren't an issue.
Finally!
Hey,now.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
30 Rock
Season03 Episode13
Excuse me?
Can we get a little
service over here-- okay.
Dude,i know you're getting these messages
because I know how to check your voicemail.
You are officially a d-bag,tim.
I hope you lose your indoo
sorry,what n I get you?
A dozen assorted for me
to take home to my family.
And the lady will have...
A dozen assorted.
Adoption brochure.
Should you be working the
night shift alone like this?
It's fine. They gave me a gun.
That's $6.80
I will have mine to stay, please.
You want a dozen donuts to stay?
And a skim milk.
- What are you doing,liz?
- Making a new friend.
I don't like this. You have crazy eyes.
You have shut-up mouth.
- I don't want any part of this.
- Enet out of here.
Boy,that creative thing you guys do, writing
jokes for a living, making the world laugh.
What do your dads tell
their friends you do?
Surgeon.
Optometrist.
Died.
I never really knew my dad. So I
just lie to myself. Space assassin.
I grew up without a father too,frank.
Good ol' billy donaghy
left when I was two.
He'd show up every now and then to impregnate
my mom, punch out umpires in my little league.
Last time I saw my dad, he went out to get
the candles for my fourth-birthday lasagna
and never came back.
My whole life I said I
was gonna be something.
Restore the glory of the rossitano name.
In sicilian dialect, it
means "well poisoner."
In gaelic,donaghy means "dung basket."
So I worked my ass off at
s.u.n.y. Got into fordham law.
No. You went to law school?
Yeah. But I had to drop out after
a semester 'cause my mom got sick.
Mothers.
So what are we doing next,fellas? Don't
tell me we're calling it a night already.
How lame do you think
the night is young.
We're going to lutz's to watch movies.
Tonight,a classic.
Harry and the hendersons. You in,jack?
Uh,yes,but I don't wanna
go to lutz's apartment.
His contract is up and I
don't wanna feel sorry for him.
What do you say we go to my place?
- I cado it.
- Sounds good.
And when I told tim I was pregnant, he just
freaked out and didn't call me for a week.
Then he texted me and he
was like, "oh,i love you.
No,I'm mad at you. You did
this on purpose." As if.
Meanwhile,his myface page horny."
And I'm,like, if you ce out me at all, at
least have the decency to skype me face to face.
Man,there are just so many different
devices for guys to not call you on now.
When I was your age,
you could just be like,
"oh,he probably tried to
call me but my line was busy."
And then just watchfalcon
crest and cry yourself to slee
thanks for listening to me blab.
So what's your plan when the baby comes?
I don't know.
I've been talking to an adoption lady, but I just
don't feel comfortable with any of the people.
They all just seem really old and wei.
Not one of them even knew who neo is.
* I need you *
finally,thank you.
Somebody cool for once.
Geouof here!
Can't you see we don't want you anymore?
Why can't you go back
where you came from?
And leave us alone!
Go.
Go!
Good-bye,my friend.
He had to be mean to save him.
Hay belonged in the woods.
It gets me every time.
This reminds me of my favorite movie.
Shane.
Aww,when joey wants to go with
shane and shane makes him stay?
Maybe it's because we
didn't have fathers.
Maybe at why we're drawn to
movies where the father-figure
pushes away the child/legendary
north-american forest ape.
Yeah,but in the movies,
it's a good thing.
Harry went back to the woods.
It works out in real life too.
We're both doing all right.
Yeah.
Excuse me,Mr. Jordan.
I was just updating my staff birthday
list and I discovered I don't have yours.
That's because I don't
have a birthday,ken.
What?
I don't have a birth certificate 'cause
I was born inside of yankee stadium.
I bound around foster families so much,
no one ever bothered to throw me a party.
Oh,but even prisoners
have birthday parties.
I saw one onoz.
It was... Interesting.
I don't need a birthday.
'Cause I buy myself
all the presents I need.
And because of my drinking,
they're often a surprise.
Oh,but birthdays aren't about presents.
They're about being surrounded
by people who love you
And eating a cake with your
name on it and making a wish.
I'm sad you never had that.
My birthday's september
21st, not that anyone asked.
Hi,frank.
Oh,hey,jack.
This morning it hit me in the shower why
the hendersons named their guest harry.
Yeah.
That film has layers.
I was also thinking about what you told
me about your family and law school.
Yeah,sorry. I was drunk. I
shouldn't have told you that stuff.
No,no,no. I'm glad you did.
We have a lot in common.
We both have recurring dreams about
being overpowered by a female bodybuilder.
Okay,we were both drunk.
But I wanna help you.
So I made some phone calls and if you want,
you can resume your law studies at columbia,
This semester,full schorsp,
no strings attached.
Are you serious?
Make your mother proud, frank.
Make your father hate any
new children he might have.
But... I've got a whole other life now.
I guess.
But we both know you shouldn't
be wki at a desk with...
Fake vomit on it.
Right. Fake.
Excuse me.
Oh,god,please don't be a
daughter I didn't know about.
Becca!
Congratulations.
What is she doing here?
She is the show's new youth consultant.
It's a thing. The cw has them.
Oh,my god.
I can't believe you're
in charge of all of this.
It is challenging and satisfying
but it can't fulfill all of me.
I've got so much more to give.
Welcome.
Um,so do you want me to
start youth consulting now?
Because kids would not be into that.
Oh,lutz? Yeah,that guy's the worst.
Kenneth,this is the dress i'll
be wearing to my birthday party.
Please maksure no one else
plans to wear the same thing.
Yes,ma'am.
Did you know Mr. Jordan has
never had a birthday party?
He was too poor growing up.
Oh,that's horrible.
My heart goes out to
all the inner city kids.
Especially those too fat
to dance their way out.
I'm glad you feel that way, 'cause
we have ts g party planned for you.
I know.
Oc and we thought you could
share it with Mr. Jordan.
The party, the attention,everything.
Isn't that a great idea?
That's so great.
I can't believe tim hasn't called.
I guess I don't even
care about us anymore.
But this is his baby.
I mean,him not even being there
for the kid is totally washed.
Typical tim.
Anyway. I guess I have two choices.
Go back home, try to get back
with tim and keep the baby,
Or give up the baby
and focus on my music.
So,tim,keep baby.
Music,give up baby.
Can I play you one of my songs?
* Now we are joined in
a cobweb of rainbows *
stop.Stop right there. Tears.
The world needs to hear your music.
You have crossed a line, liz lemon.
Becca's never gonna
make it with those songs.
Says who? Being terrible has never
prevented success in the music business.
Look at biz markie or the doors.
Look,before we were happily married with
five kids, paula and I were tim and becca.
30an she is confused
and he is terrified.
- He ran away,pete.
- So did i.
Five times. But I came back.
And when my caveman brain saw those babies
with their little hornberger foreheads,
it clicked.
You gotta give tim and
becca the same chance.
Hey,what are you doing?
My pregnant teen message board says the
baby gets all its food from the mother,
So you have to give it stuff it likes.
No,the baby can't taste anythi
it just gets nutrients from you.
I'm gonna post a reply to juno32
and tell her she's a giant asswipe.
I can't believe you don't have kids.
What's that?
Well,you'd make such a great mom.
You're smart,succesul, grounded.
Aw,go on.
- You already dress like a mom.
- And stop.
It's not the right time
for me to have a family.
But is that something you'd want?
Yeah,becca. It is.
- Will you sing with
me,liz? - Oh,i'd ra--
* mothers and fathers hm
and jugglers and judges *
* now we are joined in
a cobweb of rainbows *
he's coming! The plan is
working! I bit my tongue!
Surprise
Oh,what a schmo, entering first.
Now I'm the headliner and
he's just the warm-up act.
I'm Mr. Don rickles and he's just me.
But I don't have a birthday!
You do now 'cause we all love
you and wanted you to feel isoy.
I do feel it.
You're all so amazing.
And to think I was just calling
y'all a bunch of racists.
Stop. Jenna time.
- Friends.
- Frank?
I am leaving tgs for columbia
law school to pursue my dream
of becoming a lawyer.
Did you know that if you sing happy
birthday on a tv show you have to pay for it?
I did not know that.
my dad got us all seats for opening
day at the new yankee stadium!
Cerie,cerie,cerie, cerie,cerie!
No one ask me about my back brace.
Make a wish,Mr. Jordan.
Blow out the candles.
Cerie,frank,and tracy!
No one ask me about my back brace!
- Hey,jack.
- Frank.
Is that you?
I decided to take you up on your offer.
Good man,and you went to my tailor.
That's the same cut reagan
wore the day he got shot.
My mom is going nuts.
She's insisting you come over
and let her cook you dinner.
Home cooked italian? I'm there.
Now let me hear you say the seven most
important words in the american judicial system.
My client has no memory of that.
I also would have accepted, "you can't
prove that's the governor's semen."
- Okay.
- Yes!
What's the matter, Mr. Jordan?
I know you only make cheese friends
when something's bothering you.
You were right,ken.
Birthdays are special.
And now mine's over. And who knows
when february 24th will come again?
Now that warm, happy feeling is
gone, there's no cake in my mouth,
and that birthday wish is malarkey.
Malarkey!
Come on,daniel.
I am so proud of you. A lawyer.
Someday you'll have and on the
subway in english and spanish.
Yeah.
And this man.
What you have done for my boy.
Frankie,go open up some more wine.
You got it,mom.
What do you think
you're doing to my boy?
I'm trying to help him.
I see myself in frank.
I mean,we both have
fathers that abandoned us.
What do you know about his father?
You want frank to be a lawyer
so he won't be like his father?
His father was a lawyer!
And his father's father.
All the rossitano men are lawyers.
It's in their blood to be lawyers!
- Then what's
the-- - for the mob!
What?
Frankie's father didn't abandon him.
He's in hiding in phoenix.
Every rossitano man is either
in hiding or six feet under.
You want me to paint you a picture?
'Cause I did!
It's part of a
therapy-through-painting thing.
I had no idea.
Well,you shoulda guessed.
I don't think I should have.
Whatever.
I am not gonna take my
kid's dream away from him.
You made this mess, you
clean it up. I don't care how.
But francis rossitano
cannot become a lawyer.
Yeah,hold on a second.
Liz. Do you know a tim?
What? Why?
Security says that there's
a tim baker downstairs.
Here? Heame here? That's
becca's ex-boyfriend.
Tell them to send him to 15.
He's coming to steal my baby.
- Don't even ask about the wheelchair.
- Okay.
Also, my old vocal coach died!
Come on,come on, come on,come on.
Lemon,are you okay?
That pregnant girl, she was
going to give me her baby.
But now that dad is here, he's g
what are you about to do?
I'm the one who's been there
for becca for almost two days.
This tim guy is totally washed!
Lemon,there was once a great
american named george henderson.
He met a woodland ape, or sasquatch, and despite its
dangerous message of environmentalism, became his friend.
When the time came to do the hard thing and
send it back into the forest Where it belonged
and birds could perch on its
shoulder because it was gentle,
George henderson summoned the
strength and by god,he did it.
Did it hurt? You bet
it hurt. Like a bastard.
But he did it because it
was the right thing to do...
For the woodland ape.
You think about that.
What?
Is that harry and the hendersons?
You've seen it?
This is my life,jack.
Oh,my! Miss maroney, are you okay?
Well,i think i'll be okay
in time for tomorrow's show.
But then I have to go in forore tests.
I'm so brave.
Oh,i wish you felt better so
you could help us figure out
what Mr. Jordan's
birthday wish coulda been.
What? Why?
So we can make it come true and
his birthday can go on and on.
We've narrowed it down to wn a robocop,
"hunt that elephant that
paints, or breakfast in bed."
But it wasn't his birthday.
It was my birthday.
Oh,forget it.
I'm tired of making you
people try to care for me.
You don't care for me,
clearly. Nobody does.
- My birthday wish came true!
- What?
I wished for you to get better.
I was gonna wish for breakfast in bed
with robocop while a elephant paints us.
We were close.
But then I saw you with that back brace
on right before I blew out my candles.
It's a birthday miracle!
Tracy, that's the kindest
thing anyone's ever done for me.
Now let's make miss maroney's
birthday wish come true.
Oh,that's so sweet.
But who would I celebrate with
if y'all were in a car accident?
Are you tim? Becca's tim?
I'm her friend,jenna. And
she does not wanna see you.
She's very mad and
she wants you to leave.
Okay. That's,uh...
That's for the best. Yeah.
Excuse me. What floor
is the sci-fi channel on?
Fine,lithgow. I'll do
the right thing. God!
I guess someone's been watching
the world according to garp.
Damn it,tim,wait. Becca
does wanna see you.
She wants more than anything,okay?
No,when you said she didn't wanna
see me, it was such a relief.
This baby thing is freaking me out.
You know how many people want
what just got dropped in your lap?
"oh,now's not a good time.
I wanna go to burning man."
Shut up,tim! Do you love becca?
She's,like,my soul mate.
- I mean,in another life--
- you're not listening,dummy!
Nut up right now, get a
job, and help raise that kid.
Love it because it has your
goony face and get married
And have disposable cameras at the wedding
because it's fun and people like it.
Where are we going? I
already cleaned out my office.
You've gotta go back where you belong.
You've gotta go.
No,I'm gonna be a lawyer.
I'm going to be like you.
Get outta here! Go to the writer's
room! There is no scholarship!
Can't you see we don't want you anymore?
Think about it,tim.
Do you really want your kid
to grow up without a father?
Jack,i don't understand.
Why don't you go back
where you came from?
Leave me alone!
Good-bye,my friend.
Those two,they both
grew up without fathers.
Hey,baby.
My god. Look at your boobs.
Kiss or something. Go on.
* Rainbows and the cobwebs and
the cobwebs of the rainbows *
and stop.
I guess,in a way, we
both lost children today.
Yeah,but mine was real,
jack. Yours was frank.
Don't worry,lemon.
I'm confident that someday
you'll have everything you want.
Can someone please tell me
how to g out of this building?
It-- it's
like a maze!
I keep walking past
the same... Sbarro's!
Yeah.
I'm a celebrity! Please!
Sad.
www.tvsubtitles.net