Liz, did you hear?
Yeah, is your brother
Gonna be okay?
Oh, no, not that.
A new movie about janis joplin
Is going into production.
And sheinhdt-universal
Is making it.
I know jack can get me
An audition.
So i'm gonna storm
Into his office in character.
Yay!
Oh, liz, i knew
You'd be happy for me.
- somebody's sleepy.
- i am sleepy.
But i'm also so excited.
Hey, max, is this
Your baby sister?
Oh, what a cute little girl.
Or boy if you grow up and feel
That's what's inside you.
Omg, liz.
Look at you and me
And our biological clocks.
You're going baby crazy
And i keep getting turned
On by car accidents.
I'm not baby crazy, jenna.
This whole adoption thing
Is just taking a lot longer
Than i thought.
Where did you get
That little shoe?
It isn't stealing
If it fell on the ground.
So, uh, that's the tour,
Elisa.
I think you'll find being
My mother's nurse a mixed bag.
When she's in a foul mood,
It can be horribly unpleasant.
But at other times,
She is...asleep.
I understand.
Elder care can be stressful.
Uh, especially when
The object of that care
Wanders around at night
In depression-era petty pants.
You should've seen my
Grandmother in her later years.
Do you know
What kind of clothes
Old puerto rican ladies
Wear around the house?
No.
Me neither 'cause
She never wore any.
But family is family.
And you're a good son.
Well, i do what i can
For my mother.
Jack, somebody's gotta
Dry me off.
He just left, mrs. Donaghy.
I'm coming to help you.
www.1000fr.com presents
sync:frs@luscinia
30rock s03e07
Tracy, your friends and i
Are concerned about you.
We think your spending
Has gotten out of control.
Give me an example.
Well, you bought three hours
Of network primetime
For your salute to benny hill.
Jack, you don't get it.
I don't want to spend
So much.
I have to.
I'm afraid angie
Will divorce me
If i ever have enough money
For her to live off of half.
So before she can get,
I have to spend it all
On useless things
Like gold shoes
And grizz and dotcom.
Well, she's not gonna get
Half your money, tracy.
What does your pre-nup say?
I don't got a pre-nup!
When angie and i
Got married,
My only assets were
A toaster oven and two tickets
To a young mc concert.
You need to be protected.
Let's bring angie in here.
We'll think of something.
A post-nup, if you will.
Something that will bring you
Peace of mind.
Okay.
I'll bring angie in.
But i'm gonna tell her this
Is all your idea.
Don't help me.
I'm too proud.
Hi!
Hiya, bunny!
Uh, excuse me.
Hello, there.
Did you just touch my head?
Well...
I had to do something
To get your attention.
Okay, you've got it.
Yeah, i do.
I like your tie.
And i li aggressive women
With a nerdy vibe.
How about we grab
Some coffee and explore this?
Yeah.
What?
Howdy, jack!
It's me, janis joplin!
And i want to audition for
My sheinhardt-universal biopic so bad
That i came here
Dressed as me.
Actually, i am me
So, well, i dressed normal.
But my friend, jenna
She should be my understudy.
I mean, she should audition
For me.
But i'm me now actually.
I'm going train wreck aside,
I love this idea.
- it's great synergy.
- yeah.
By putting a tv actress
Into the movie world
We can promote both.
It's like we're including
A heroes dvd
With missile guidance system
We sell.
- i'll call the studio.
- yes!
I'm so glad that
I time-traveled here from 1969.
Whoa, what is that iron bird?
They had airplanes
In the '60s, jenna.
Oh, right.
Boy, i feel like
I've just been talking nonstop.
No, you also ate quite a bit.
It's my fault for wanting
To hear all about your job.
It's just so much more
Interesting than the u.n.
Oh, come on, really?
You got all the different
Languages and the costumes.
And that big meeting room.
It must be like working in
The galactic senate in star wars.
They are similar.
We are also very concerned about
The growing influence
Of the sith lords.
Wow.
Are you free for dinner
Some night this week?
Yeah, sure, i'd love it.
Sounds great.
Who was that?
A guy that i met.
Is this part
Of your mommy thing?
Only in so far as we met
Because i touched his head
Thinking he was a child.
Oh, liz.
I like him.
He's smart.
He's funny.
He's got a job.
- yay!
- but you know what?
I'm gonna screw this up.
I always find a way
To screw good things up,
And this one
Is a mine field.
Did i mention that we met
Because i thought he was a baby?
He doesn't have to know that.
He can't know that.
But what if i say
Something stupid
Like order a tall coffee
Or talk about my nintendo wii?
Liz, you like this guy.
You're a grown woman.
Take a lesson from janis
And show some self-control.
How far into that biography
Are you?
Not very.
Why?
What happens?
So let me get this straight.
If i sign this
And then tracy decides to run away
With that chunky chick from hairspray--
Or any female
Of equivalent thickness.
Then i get $8,500?
That's correct.
Ugh.
What do i care?
I'll sign your stupid contract.
Never gonna leave this man
Anyway.
You're not?
Baby.
I'm gonna be with you
To the very end.
I'm gonna watch you die,
Tracy jordan.
She's done it before, jack.
Forget it!
I know you're not
Gonna leave me.
I got somebody
Who's gonna watch me die!
Tracy, let's not get
Emotional.
This is happening, jack.
You could stay
Or you could leave,
But it's gonna take a while.
Oh, yeah!
Uh, liz, jenna got the lead
In the janis joplin biopic
That i'm co-producing.
And i want her to open
The next show
With a song from the movie.
Aw, come on, jack.
You can't fight synergy, lemon.
It's bigger than all of us.
Nice dress.
Are you going to dinner?
Don't forget your book.
I'll have you know that
I'm having dinner with a man.
So stuart, what is it like
Living under a bridge?
Kenneth!
Hey, liz.
I was just telling him about
My new apartment
In williamsburg...
Under the bridge.
The u.n.?
They still have that?
I could've sworn
They turned that building
Into a barnes and noble.
Like you guys in corporate america
Are doing any better?
Have you learned how to say
"do you want fries
With that" in chinese?
Ha!
Jack donaghy,
Ser vp for television
And microwave oven programming.
Stuart lagrange,
U.n. High commission
On water temperature and food taint.
And how did you and lemon meet?
Uh, liz here just saw me on the street
And went for it.
Lemon did that?
Yeah. You know me.
Spend my lunch hour
Walkinup and down 6th aven
Looking for a hot meal.
Okay.
Classic lemon man-eater.
Cat sound.
Well, nice to meet you, jack.
Yeah.
There he is!
I owe you, jackie d.
When i'm on my death bed,
Frenching my wife,
I will think of you.
Please don't.
No, no.
Not again.
This is real, people!
This is not a drill!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Tracy, my back!
Ooh, baby,
Hurt my back.
- yeah!
- oh!
I just want you all to know
As i prepare to venture
Into moviedom,
That an actor is only
As good as the words--
Oh, my thing is on.
Everyone shut up.
Shut your mouths.
Breaking news now
About a new janis joplin biopic.
Julia roberts has agreed
To play the tragic singer...
What?
In a film directed
By martin scorse
And written by the best
Screenwriter in the world,
Whoever that is.
The announcement is a huge blow
To a competing project
From jenna moroney
And steven spielberger.
That's right.
Spielberger.
Here's moroney on a windy day.
Don't turn it off,
Ms. Moroney.
They haven't shown that good news
You were telling us about.
'Cause that all seemed
Like really bad news.
It's 7:00.
Why don't i hear my mother
Yelling "go home"
To the asian contestant
On jeopardy?
'Cause she's asleep.
Really?
How did you do that?
She fought me at first,
But i find that authoritative
Rapid spanish subdues white people.
Well, i'm heading out
For the evening.
Oh, i forgot.
Somebody dropped that off
For you earlier.
Oh, good god.
Oh, gold shoes.
My nephew just joined
The marines
To try to pay for college,
But that's fun.
No, no,
They're from tracy jordan.
I tried to get him
And his wife to sign a pre-nup,
But all that led to were pledges
Of everlasting love and devotion.
Was ridiculous.
What's ridiculous about love?
Well, the idea of depending
On one person
For the rest of your live
Is irrational.
You come in alone,
You go out alone.
That's the saddest thing
I ever heard.
There's nothing sad about it
At all, actually.
I have a great life.
Tonight i'm going out
With a fox news correspondent.
We'll have some dinner,
Some laughs, some sex.
Not necessarily
In that order.
But i'm not counting on spending
The rest of my life with her.
So what's your plan?
Get old, die alone
In an empty room
With your gold shoes?
That's what happens
To most of us.
At least i'm prepared.
Without getting
Into specifics,
My exit involves
A mcflurry machine
And a video tape of
Risque commercials from overseas.
Well, i don't even know
What to say to that.
Except that in puerto rico,
A mcflurry, it's called
Asenor flurry.
This guy makes badhushas.
They're like an indian donut.
They're amazing.
Careful, buddy, it's hot!
Are you trying to pick me up
To keep me from touching fire?
Kiss me.
Wait a minute.
When you first met me,
Did you think i was a child?
Yes, i did, sir.
Unbelievable.
I knew i should've listened
To my friends.
Kofi said you were
Too good to be true.
Na ah
Told me to wait three days
Before i called you.
And yet here we are.
Was anything even going
To happen between us tonight?
No.
But not because of your size.
It's because i have a thing
About intimacy.
I'm the weird one.
I'm weirder than you.
- ??
- you're not.
That came out wrong.
You came out wrong.
Oh, and i lied
About your show.
I have seen it.
Be careful crossing the--
The lady will be having
The tasting menu
But with some substitutions.
Instead of any of it,
She'll have a cup of hot water
With a chicken bone in it
And a bowl of salted ice cubes.
A towel, sir?
I have something on my ball.
Mint?
Good morning.
Morning, everyone.
Are you all right?
You look very pale.
I'm fine.
I had a good hour
Of sleep last night,
Took a few showers.
There anything you want
To talk about?
I am a nurse.
It's nothing.
It's embarrassing.
More embarrassing
Than your cd collection?
I didn't know michael buble
Had so many albums.
If you must know,
I found a lump.
On your testicle?
Let me see it.
No, thank you.
I think i have it
Under control.
What?
You're talking so fast.
Is that the subjunctive?
How did you do
I told you i was
A professional.
And you forgot
To put on your underpants.
So, uh, any big plans
For your day off?
I'm going to prospect park.
It's my goddaughter's
Quincenera.
Oh, it'sind of like
A debutante...ball.
You did that on purpose.
I did.
Well, there is something there.
Could be a number
Of things.
You should get it
Checked out by a doctor.
Thank you for telling me
What i already know.
You should work
Forthe huffington post.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you have friends
Or family you can call.
I'm fine.
Oh, please.
Don't try
To besenor macho solo.
Which is actually
What we call a mcrib sandwich.
I'm fine.
I'm handling this...
All alone.
Jack, what are we doing
About this julia roberts movie?
Aren't people over her?
I mean, come on!
Jenna, you're single like me.
Do you think we need
Some mythical soul mate
To hold our hand through life?
Why, do you want
To get married?
I'll do it?
- what?
Uh, no.
Uh, never mind.
The movie's gonna
Work out fine.
We're very close to securing
Janis joplin's life rights.
Close?
I'm supposed to sing
One of her songs friday night.
Do we at least have
The music rights?
Uh, yes and no, jenna.
Yes, i'm talking.
No, we do not have the music.
But i'm on it.
It's all gonna be fine.
Hello.
Stuart, it's me.
Look, liz,
I'm really busy right now.
I just wanted to apologize
For the other night.
But i didn't get a chance
To explain myself.
I'm...kind of baby crazy
Of late.
Socially inept and baby crazy.
I feel like i'm
In a beer commercial.
Yeah, i get it.
I'm a piece of work.
But i really like you.
And if you gave me
Another chance,
Maybe this could be something.
Liz, at this point
In my life,
Maybe just isn't good enough.
Okay, here's a thought.
Did you see
Thesex in the citymovie?
Once again, liz,
I am an adult man.
Okay, well miranda and steve
Were having issues
Because steve cheated--
Oh, so bored.
The point is they decided
To take a break
And then meet up
At the brooklyn bridge
At such and such a time
If they wanted to stay together.
Maybe we could do
The same thing.
Brooklyn bridge,
This saturday, 2:00 p.m.
Okay.
But for whatever reason,
If i don't see you there,
Take care, liz lemon.
You too.
Oh, and can you transfer me
To the italian ambassador's office?
Because i lika to maka
Prank phone call.
Please hold.
Jack.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to come by
And thank you for all your help.
I wasn't sure what
You were serving,
So i brought a '65 moet
And some pizza-blasted pringles.
That was very thoughtful.
I'm sorry if i was rude
The other day.
Oh, you were not being rude.
You were just being stupid.
Did you go to the doctor?
I had a biopsy,
And i'm waiting
For the results.
So i'm handling it.
Good.
I'm glad.
Excellent.
So, uh, here you go.
Thank you.
Jack, would you like
To stay?
Oh, i don't want
To impose.
Oh, come on.
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
Oh, thank you so much.
All of these people
Are your family?
Why are they smiling so much?
Who's being ostracized?
Everybody, this is
My friend jack.
???
??
????
I need to ask your advice
About stuart.
We decided to do this whole
Meet me at the brooklyn bridge
If we still want
To be together thing
From thesex in the city
Movie.
They do that a lot in movies.
An affair to rember,
Sleepless in seattle,
And that remake of
An affair to rember that i was in,
A blaffair to rememblack.
I just don't know
What to do.
Here's what you don't do.
Be alone.
We were never meant
To be alone, lemon.
Surround yourself
With people and love
And babies
With pierced ears.
What is wrong with you?
I've had a crazy 48 hours.
It all started when
I realized i'm probably dying.
You see, i have this thing
On my testicle.
- ew, my god.
- no, no, it's okay.
Whatever happens,
It's okay.
I don't want to die alone
And now i don't have to
Because...
I'm in love
With my mother's nurse.
Now you have what
Me and angie have,
Minus the hypertension.
Jack, slow down.
Have you been to a doctor?
I'm waiting for
The results of a biopsy.
We went to this picnic.
Lemon, have you ever had
Apiragua?
It's exactly like a snow cone
Except they call it apiragua.
It's my doctor's office.
- you take it.
- no, jack.
I'll do it
Hello?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
The test was positive.
No, no, no, no--
I mean positive
Like it's good.
The test results
Were negative.
Oh, i see your confusion.
That is funny!
- okay.
- funny!
Jack thought the test results
Was positive!
Supersonic idiotic
Disconnected not respected
Who would ever really want
To go and top that
Top that
Thank you.
That was the rap song"top that"
From the movieteen witch.
Once again, i apologize
That our regular warm-up comic
O.d.ed at a gay man's
Apartment this morning.
30 seconds.
I've decid to go
To the bridge tomorrow.
You've inspired me.
What if this experience
Hasn't changed me?
Maybe everything
I was feeling for elisa
Was just neediness
And fear.
I mean, can two people fall in love
Over a benign gonad cyst?
Why not?
It's not about
Where things start.
It's about where it goes.
Tracy told me that.
He's kind of on a roll.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss janet jopler!
Who?
Until we get the life rights,
We have to
Protect ourselves.
I'd like you to come on
Come on
Come on and take it
Take another little chunk
Of my lung now, mister
Also, we didn't get the songs.
I wrote this myself
Five minutes ago.
You know you bought it
If life makes you
Sweet food
Now this i like.
Waiting for someone?
What?
What do you think
You're doing?
Oh, i'm so sorry!
I thought he was someone else.
Liz.
Wh--
Shut it down!
Chunk of my lung
And take it
Take a big ol' chunk
Of my lung now baby
Take it
Take a big old chunk
Of my lung
Chunk of my lung
You know you bought it
If you buy it with things
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net