Ms.Lemon, here's the research you
wanted for that white house skit.
Oh,okay,thanks.
You know it, lady broseph!
- What!
- Those are your new interns.
Aren't they a little
old, and over-dressed?
They're all former investment bankers who
were laid off after that economic crash
that nancy pelosi caused.
They've had zero real-world
skills, but god, they work hard.
Gentlemen, I need you to run
out and pick up some flowers,
A collection of bath soaps, and some
spanish-language gossip magazines.
Soap and spanish magazines?
What,are you expecting a
visit from the,uh-- um--
- Oh,lemon,don't start unless you've got something.
- Okay.
Elisa's grandmother's coming to visit.
I don't think she likes me.
*******
*********
I don't understand it.
Well,as long as elisa likes you,
that's all that matters,right?
Oh,no. I need concepcion on board.
She's the matriarch of this family.
And in puerto rico, elderly women
are held in very high esteem.
You should go there,lemon.
They'd love you.
None of this is mine.
I live in 3-b, this is 13-b.
You know what, i'm gonnsay it.
Women should not deliver the mail.
Dr. Andrew baird? Do you know this guy?
I don't think so.
Well,he's a pediatrician,
so you know he likes kids.
Or feet. No,no,kids.
He has a bill from a divorce
lawyer, so you know he's single.
And he has a golf magazine,so
you know he's not gay or poor.
Jenna,come on.
Now let's see what
kind of movies he likes.
What are you doing?
That's a federal offense.
And you already have two strikes.
I do not support this!
Muppets take manhattan.
Caddyshack.
And a documentary
about how pies are made.
Hello,dr. Baird.
Wasn't that a treat?
Only the special tours get
to see conan without his wig.
Mi programa esta empezando ahora.
Oh,i'm sorr but her show's on now.
Do you think
we could--
uh,yes,yes.Jonathan,would you
come and help mrs. Padriera?
I think your grandmother hates me.
I don't understand.
She's usually a very loving person.
- Is it because i'm white?
- No.
I've had white
boyfriends. Black,cuban...
- Brazilian guys with
german heritage-- - I get it.
You've been with other
men. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- What is she watching?
Los amantes clandestinos.
It's a mexicantelenovela.
But who is that?
That isel generalissimo. He's
the villain of los amantes.
Pa!
The name of the actor is hector moreda.
Dime donde estan los diamantes.
Nunca!
Dime.
He looks exactly like me.
He does look like you.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
30 Rock
Season03 Episode10
Dude,i have to meet you. I'm brian.
What's up,brian?
We love you."this honky
grandma be trippin'"
hey,when I quote lines from your
movie, that's not racist,right?
Of course not. I transcend race.
Hey,look,we're all going out after
work, and I know you like to party.
We'd be hore rdoc k if you come with.
You shouldn't end a sentence
with a preposition at.
But yeah,i'm in.
We'll start off at
mcmanus-mcminnigan's.
Have you ever drunk a yard of beer?
A yard,like a lawn? Yes,i have.
Tracy jordan!
He has an ice cream maker? Come on!
Don't be weird-looking,
don't be weird-looking.
Ah,girl!
Oh,god!
Dr. Baird,tre's someone at your door.
Oh,thanks,oswald.
Oswald was just helping
me hang some pictures.
I live in the basement,
so I have all the nails.
I'm drew. Sorry I smell like
frosting. I just love to bake.
I want to go to there.
So will I see you before saturday?
Jack,about this weekend...
I don't think you should come to my
cousin's police academy graduation,
or my other cousin's parole party.
Boy,i hope those two n' rtoc k eventually have
a showdown that pits family against justice.
Hang on,you mean you
don't want me to come?
It's not me.
Abuelathought it should just be family.
Is this about the generalissimo?
Jack.
As a child,my grandmother worked in a
silver mine without proper ventilation.
Now her mi is squishy like a hacky sack.
But no matter what,
she's still myabuelita.
Even though sometimes she comes at me
with a knife because of a silver frenzy.
I'll call you tomorrow,okay?
Okay,good night, querida.
Generalissimo.
Look at dr. Baird. How did
you get a picture of him?
I told him his haircut was exactly what
i've been trying to describe to my barber.
Yeah,smooth,i know. I'm
way out of my league here.
Okay,don't get intimidad.
You know he can't be perfect.
No,he might be.
I got some more of his mail.
And I opened it.
Uh-huh,yeah, i'm the worst.
It just proves that I
don't deserve this guy.
He went to medical school at
columbia, all kinds of charity baloney.
He gets l of the movie
channels, including starz.
And he trains seeing eye dogs at home.
Oh,well, that's no good for
you. You're allergic to dogs.
- I guess i'll have to step in then.
- Shut up. Just let me think!
Please keep your voices down.
Mr. Jordan is a little hung over.
He pulled an uncle
harland parcell last night.
Minus the wistful jug blowing.
I went out with the interns.
Those white boys are not kidding around.
Have you ever tasted scotch?
It's terrible!
And this thing they call "box seats
at the rangers game," it's so cold!
And what is rohypnol?
Tracy,those are roofies!
So I shouldn't have taken
two of them for my headache?
There he is!
Tonight,shooters at blockheads, lay a base, at
meet up with my bro-hams at the cornell club?
Hey,you know it,bri-man! A'ight!
I have no idea what
either one of us just said.
He thinks you're going out again.
You gotta tell him you can't.
I have a rep to maintain.
If I can't keep up with a
bunch of wall street frat boys--
Uh-oh, here come the roofies.
You can do whatever you want to me.
Uno,dos
- you wanted to see me?
- Lemon,this is elisa.
What? Come on,you're a nurse?
Yeah,some of us are hot.
Lemon,we have a problem... With him.
Boy,that guys looks a lot like you.
Precisely.
Two hours a day, five
days a week, hector moreda
And the generalissimo are poisoning
elisa's grandmother against me.
Oh,he just blew up that kid!
Elisa and I have enough obstacles.
Our work schedules, our cultures,
her adorably broken english.
Metrocards are a real thing,jack.
You use them on the subway.
Anyway,this morning, telemundo, which
is owned by sheinhardt-universal,
- purchasedlos
amantes,uh-- - Clandestinos.
And now,i own it.
Isn't that romantic?
Now,all I have to do is kill off the
generalissimo, and clear a path to elisa'sabuela.
Lemon,the director needs a script by this afternoon,
and elisa here will help you with the spanish.
No,no,no, don't drag me into
this. I have my own problems.
And i've never even watched that show.
All you need to know is thatel
geralissimo is pure evil, look at him.
He stole that girl's love
letters and opened them.
Opened her mail? That is
just shocking. He's a monster.
Or he has a really good reason to do it.
Oh,no, his only reason was to trick
her into giving up her honor to him.
Uh-huh,and how did he use
her mail to do that,exactly?
He read her most intimate secrets, and
turned himself into that which she desired.
What she loved, he pretended to
love too, until it was too late.
My dog ran away!
Oh,my god. Let me get my coat.
- Buster.
- Buster!
- Come here,boy!Buster!
- If see the dog,give us a shout.Thank you.
The funny thing is this
is what I love about him.
Don'worry,liz. We're gonna find him.
If we don't, I don't think I
could ever be around dogs again.
You know, i'm actually on the board of the
pediatric restless leg syndrome association.
Oh,i forgot I even had this on.
I have so many charity t-shirts.
We have so much in common.
Well,buster's probably dead.
Do you want to go to the wine bar around the
corner, deal with these emotions, get some dinner?
Uh,i would love to, liz,i really would.
But,i just got divorced
not that long ago.
I'm really not ready for
this kind of thingust yet.
Plus,i have not given up
on that dog. He's a fighter.
Buster!
Yeah,buster!
Shoot it,dog!
I'm going to! I'm tracy jordan.
Why would I be afraid
of fire next to my mouth?
Drink,drink,drink!
- Is she watching?
- Yes.
I told her it was a
very special episode.
Good-bye,general.
Esto es por mi padre!
Fallaste!
Wait,wait,wait. What did he just
say? That wasn't in the script.
He said "you missed."
Fallaste otra vez!
He said "you missed again."
Y ahora,esta pocion me
dejara vir por siempre!
"and now,this potion's
gonna make me live forever."
What's happening,jack?
El generalissimo was supposed to die!
Morena has gone broken arrow. Jonathan!
We really should have had somebody
on the set who speaks spanish.
I'll call you back.
Moreda.
Moreda!
Welcome,jack.
Cigar,brandy?
What happened,hector?
- The general was supposed to die.
- Ay.
Do n t ry to
out-generalissimo me,my friend.
This role has made me
rich, famous and respected.
I get to cut the line at
disneyland, if I come mid-week.
I have a lucrative endorsement
deal with sabor de soledad!
Ahora con mas semen del toro.
I am not going to let you
ke all that away from me.
I know where you came from,hector.
Play ball,or you'll be back doing r-rated
hypnotism at the bull fights so fast,
you won't know what hit you.
You come over here and
say that to my face.
- No,you come over here.
- Nunca!
If you refuse to be reasonable, I
must call the presidente of telemundo.
La oficina de jack donaghy.
Hola?
Well-played,jack.
I see that we are not
so different,you and i.
- We laugh alike.
- We think ali.
At times,we even drink alike.
You can lose your mind.
Look,you should know, i'm
doing this for a woman.
This woman.
Wow,i am super gay, and I
would totally switch for her.
She's amazing.
But her grandmother hates me, because she
hates the generalissimo, so he's gotta go.
El generalissimo does not have to
die to clear the way to theabuela.
Not if theabuela comes to love him.
But that's impossible.
Seduction ner impossible
forel generalissimo.
I will become everything that
old hispanic women desire.
I will make her love me.
You really think you can pull that off?
It will be the
performance of a lifetime.
Like julie harris
inthe belle of amherst.
Wow,you are surprisingly gay.
Okay,so?
So did you ever find buster?
What did youerstan that
picture is from a dog food ad.
Hi,lemon. Here's today's script.
I translated it,and took
out thestar warsreferences.
Are you an actress?
No,i'm a nurse.
Oh,good.
Don't listen to anyone who says
you should become an actress.
Okay.
Uh,i also cut the scene between
the general and tia maria.
They cannot be together.
Not after what he did
to maria's daughter.
Why? What did he do?
Oh,it was despicable.
Even worse than his misuse of the mails.
The generalissimo tricked her to the
villa by inviting her to a fancy party.
But when she got there, it
was just the two of them.
He drugged her champagne
and had his way with her.
Later,she gave birth to the
devil. You know,sweeps week.
That's what I could do to drew.
Drug him? Liz,no.
Having been on both sides of that, I
could tell you it's not a good idea.
No,i'm going to tell drew
that i'm having a little
"wcome to the building" party
for him, but there is no party.
And then,when he shows up, i'll laugh
and say "oh,it's the wrong night."
And then he'll laugh, and say
"oh,well, one glass couldn't hurt."
And then I will put
my mouth on his mouth.
No,lemon, do not do this.
The trickery, the deceit
is a slippery slope.
Yeah,but you haven't seen dr.
Baird. He lks like a cartoon pilot.
Be very careful.
El generalissimo was once a good man.
But the years of
loneliness drove him insane.
I am not the generalissimo, elisa.
Mr. Jordan, I called my clharland,
and I got his hangover cure.
"mix two cups boiled possum meat with
one messload ragweed, stir in alcohol-- "
Ken. These interns are wearing me out.
It's like I said in my not-hit comedy cruise
boat, "i'm gettin' too old for this ship."
Well,you are getting older,sir.
There's no reason you have
to keep acting like you're 20.
Yes,there is.
Do you know what happens to a comedian
when he gets old and loses his audience?
He starts to get offered serious roles.
And do you really want to
see me play arthur ashe?
,that would be terrible.
You leave him alone!
Exactly.
So if i'm gonna keep my hilarious
reputation, these interns gotta go!
But where?They don't
know how to do anything,
and there are no jobs
left on wall street.
Then i'll find something for them to do.
Drew.
Oh,uh, am I the first one here?
What?
No,the party's tomorrow night.
Tonight, i'm just hanging out,
eating fondue by candlelight.
Bucome in, I was just opening
a bottle of wine to drink alone.
Okay,i guess one glass couldn't hurt.
- I found your dog!
- What?
He lost his collar, but I
recognize him from the poster.
That's not possible.
Of course it's possible.
How could he not want to come
back to this beautiful lady?
My dog is back!
I'll open the wine.
Just put him down.
*********
*******
**********
**************
Oh,muy dulce.
Si,si,si.
*************
Oh,you need more.
Buster,you wang!
Let's get you back in your
special kitchen cabinet.
Man,that dog is giving me a headache.
I have some aspirin in my
white bag there if you need any.
Everything okay in there?
Yeah,it's okay, he's just playing along.
Or he bites me.
Alone at last.
Are you okay?
Yeah,i'm,uh--
you've been roofied!
You did what?
No,no,not me. The pills!
Is this my mail?
Okay,no, you're not thinking clearly.
Why is it all open?
That's not your dog.
I can explain. Just relax.
Help!
I am the generalissimo!
I don't know what that means.
Abuelamade you breaded calf's brains.
Muchas gracias.
She really liked the chgeyou
made inlos amantes clandestinos.
She's very proud that I am dating
such an important television man.
Oh,well--
What are you going to
do about the nbc news?
It's too sad.
I'll look into it, uh,abuela.
Hi,liz.
Again,i am so sorry
about everhing--
I actually got some of your mail.
Oh,okay. Hope you didn't open it.
I did. Live at the
hollywood bowl. Classic.
Membership in the
cheese of the month club,
And the steak of the month club,
and a copy ofvegetarian times.
I'm a ip-flopper.
Also a response to your complaint
about bad grammar in subway ads.
The word "whom" deserves a defender.
I'm just saying that based on your mail,
I actually would have wanted to
meet this elizabeth lemon in 3-b.
Really?
Do you want to try this again?
I know that I lied to you,
and I accidentally roofied you,
But weirder things have happened,right?
Isn't that tracy jordan?
The lehman brothers investment bank will reopen
under the direction of comedian tracy jordan.
I'm doing this so no one
will know i'm getting old.
But you just told us you're old.
This interview is over.
Yeah,i guess weirder
things have happened.
And now to lighten things up, some
pictures of beautiful latin babies,
and the music of tito puente.
Jackthis is ridiculous.
Okay,it's a date.
Okay.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
www.tvsubtitles.net