Miss Lemon! Let me help you out.
Thanks, Kenneth.
What are all these little
plastic containers for?
Are you pickling squirrel meat?
Cause I can lend you my skull presser
No, I went to the new
flagship compartment store on 5th Avenue
and got everything I need
to get my life in order.
A stacker thing to separate junk mail
from your humidifier catalogs.
A thing you stick on your laptop
that holds your keys.
A round plastic deal
that holds your shoes
with a pocket for a photograph
of what shoes are in there.
I'm going to become wonderful.
It's a new beginning.
- Like a phoenix rise...
- Look out!
Or...
maybe this is gonna be
the worst day ever.
Subtitles: - Feygnasse Team -
Synch: Collioure
Episode 314:
"The Funcooker"
Morning meeting.
Everybody shut up.
Shut up, Lutz.
Already today,
I have lost faith in decor-ganizing,
chipped a tooth...
And lost a shoving match
to what I thought
was a female bike messenger.
So I am asking all of you
for the next 12 to 14 hours
to just be cool.
Let's have a normal day.
- Guys, seriously, be cool.
- Why are you not wearing pants?
They still have the heat set for winter,
and my office is boiling.
Put on your pants!
Please make me
a dentist appointment today.
You can't go today.
You have jury duty.
What? No!
I'm registered in Illinois.
How did New York find me?
I changed
your voter registration for you.
What's wrong?
You told me to be more proactive.
I told you to buy more Proactiv!
Mr. Donaghy wants to see you now
about what Jenna and Tracy did
during St. Patrick's day parade.
Was it something good?
Have a seat. It was very simple.
I asked you two to host NBC's
coverage of St. Patrick's day parade.
Read the cue cards. Promote the show.
So would you explain to Mr. O'Cannon
why it went so very wrong?
Sir, as I'm sure you know
from reading my blog,
I'm currently shooting
a feature film inspired by,
but, for legal reasons,
not based on Janis Joplin.
Synonym's just another word
for the word you wanna use
we can't sing the original songs,
but it's gonna be phenomenal.
But, between the movie at night
and working here during the day,
I am so exhausted.
So when I got to the parade...
That's no excuse, ye banshee.
You and this gravy face
have slarneyed up
a real donnybrook.
Here comes the County Cork steppers.
Their traditional dance
celebrates the spirit
and the ingenuity
of the Irish people.
Wake up, mother...
You're a disgrace.
Passing out and cursing
on St. Patrick's day?
Is nothing sacred?
I should be rewarded
for going this long
without swearing on live TV.
The FCC disagrees. They've decided
to make an example of you
- and fine you personally $50,000.
- 50 grand?
Can anyone cut this in half?
Look at you! I told you.
You're spreading yourself too thin.
- I only heard the thin part.
- Lemon is right.
Obviously, you can't do
both TGS and Janie Jimplin.
I choose the movie.
My face is bigger on it.
I don't mean quit,
Liz will find a way to make both work.
Am I right?
I'll have to use you less
in the show.
And I'll scale back the movie.
We could cut the lesbian scene.
But the Oscars love
that kind of thing.
There's 2 guys in my gym
named Oscar.
You have got to start
taking care of yourself.
You're a wreck.
I am fine.
Jenna, that's a glue stick.
You're going to the doctor.
OK, great meeting.
Let's try to have a calm week
downstairs, shall we?
Yes, I'm trying.
I don't need any distractions.
On Friday,
Microwaves is announcing
a very big project
or, should I say, very little?
The pocket microwave?
You can buy it on Friday
along with everyone else.
It has a ham button.
You used my idea!
I understand what it's like
having too much on your plate.
Between medical practice and this job,
I'm pulled in every direction.
What can I do, doctor?
Haven't been this tired
since I was forced to do
that dance marathon in Dubai.
I can give you
these pamphlets on stress
and diet and doing a movie
and a TV show at same time.
But they're all gonna tell you
that you need to give something up.
And they're wrong.
You can burn the candle
at both ends.
Go on.
My lab works is in the field
of sleep research.
Mostly because I checked
the wrong box on a form once.
We are current working on a pill
that keeps people awake
under any circumstances.
It's being funded
by the U.S. Military and the WNBA.
- Does it work?
- It's kept my lab rats awake for days.
- But we're looking for human subjects.
- Where do I sign up?
Please, we don't want a paper trail.
Take 25 of these a day
for the rest of your life.
I am going to jury duty,
but I will be right back.
I got my princess Leia outfit,
some Playgirl magazines
from the early 1980s.
They will dismiss me
immediately as a weirdo.
- Who's in charge while you're gone?
- Let's see.
Pete is spending spring break
with his kids,
so no one.
No one here is in charge in any way.
If no one's in charge,
who will yell at me
for goofing up the lunch order?
We all will, Kenneth.
We all will.
You guys are my best friends.
There you are!
You wanna buy half a watch?
I have to pay my fine in cash.
I guess FCC stands
for Federal Bunch of Sticklers.
I hope you've learned
a lesson from this.
I sure have.
I learned that if you pay
some money afterwards,
you can say whatever you want on TV.
I can even say what Ernest Borgnine
whispered to me at...
Stop. That's not the lesson.
That's always the lesson.
If you have money,
you can do whatever you want.
Now I'm off to appear
on Martha Stewart live.
It's gonna be raunchy.
Great news.
I'm in the clinical trial
for a military-grade anti-sleeping pill.
Of course you are.
Now I can still be on the show
as much as you want and do the movie.
Look how much energy I have.
Come on, guys. I just have to go
and get out of jury duty,
and we can talk
about all of this when I get back.
I thought you left.
Listen to me.
I am not asking you this as the boss
you love to undermine,
but as the friend whose birthday
you love to forget.
Just be normal sauce
for like two hours.
Please.
I will be right back.
And I don't really think
it's fair for me
to be in a jury
because I'm a hologram.
You seem fine to me.
Report to jury room B.
Charles what now?
The subject's unusually thirsty.
Everyone shut up.
Shut up, Lutz.
- Where's Lemon?
- She went to get out of jury duty.
Can we get lunch from McDonald's?
I need your creative input.
I've spent the better part
of last 3 years developing
a portable,
miniature microwave oven.
Most of that time has been spent
focused on coming up
with a hip name for the product,
that will appeal
to the marketing holy trinity:
college students, morbidly obese,
and homosexuals.
Unfortunately,
legal just informed me
that the name we settled on
for our bite-size microwave,
the bitenuker,
is highly offensive to those
who speak French or Dutch.
A Franco-Dutchman
would pronounce it "bet nyuker."
Zat's awful.
I'm sorry,
miss Laroche-Van Der Hoot.
This product rolls out in 2 days.
We're in danger of losing
the European market.
Everyone here needs
to brainstorm new names.
Starting today, you are all members
of the microwave division.
- We should make t-shirts!
- Yes. And you're in charge of that.
Remember, this isn't TGS, guys.
Let's not shoot
for the middle this time.
Absolutely not.
Excuse me, imperial guard,
how long do these arson trials
typically last?
Couple of weeks, probably.
You can drop the voice.
This used to get me out of jury duty
in Chicago all the time.
This ain't Chicago, honey.
Look at these people.
Studio 6H.
- It's Liz.
- Where are you?
The pig spoor has hit
the wind spinner.
Mr. Jordan cussed at Martha Stewart,
Miss Maroney drank all
the water out of the toilets.
And I keep starting to sneeze,
but nothing comes out.
What?
Does anyone there listen to me?
It's not my fault.
You didn't put anyone in charge.
I've been put on a jury.
I'll head up there as soon
as we are dismissed for the day.
Try not to let anything else
bad happen.
I'm in charge.
Attention, everyone.
All menstruating women go home
immediately.
He's been doing that
for almost eight hours,
Dr. Vicky.
You know what I like to do
for 8 hours?
The TV guide crossword puzzle.
Give me your hand.
Now look into my eyes.
Now let's try one
where you're not...
- clawing at the window.
- I don't think so.
This feels more natural.
- You're saying, "give me your hand."
- This is what my character would do.
You're back.
Guess I'm not in charge anymore.
Guys?
I've got a couple hours.
- Where is everybody?
- They're all dead.
They're all dead unless they come up
with a name for my pocket microwave.
They're up in my office,
where there are fewer...
foosballs.
So who's writing the show?
Now that you're back,
I thought you could do it yourself.
How hard can it be?
"Hey, I'm rapping Obama".
"Welcome to another episode
of robot/bear talk show".
I'm Josh doing an impression
of De Niro as an auctioneer.
"Do I hear $1,000?
Do I hear $1,000?"
Really good!
Jenna fills in time with a song.
"Good night, good night". Mild applause.
You'll be done in an hour.
In the meantime,
any ideas for microwave names?
The small wonder.
The micromate. The porta-hotty.
If you're not going to take this
seriously, then do your job.
Write the show, and more important,
deal with Tracy.
How? That guy's got enough money
to pay FCC fines for the next 200 years.
Forget the fines.
I've dealt with the FCC.
And NBC is issuing an apology
on Tracy's behalf.
Your problem is
your advertisers are pulling out.
- My god. With no ads...
- No ads, no TGS.
No TGS...
I see you self-publishing your novel
and moving back in
with your parents.
I'll go talk to Tracy.
Just catching up on some work.
Really?
What sounds more shocking?
Or...
Here you go. Everything's OK.
No, just because you have money
doesn't mean you can say
whatever *** thing that you want.
This has gotten bigger
than you just paying fines.
Our sponsors are pulling out
because of you.
And if we don't have advertisers,
they're gonna pull the plug on TGS.
Think about how
you're hurting the crew.
I don't want to hurt the crew.
I love the crew.
All we do is joke around together
about our stupid boss, Liz Lem...
Anyway, unless you know
an advertiser that really wants
to be associated with this,
you need to stop.
Great idea.
Which part are you talking about?
The first 2/3.
I don't need to stop being myself
if I am the advertiser.
I have the money.
I'll just buy up all the ads
and let that hilarious
Tracy Jordan character
- do whatever he wants.
- Put the phone down. You can't do that.
- Jack won't let you.
- We'll see about that.
I need you to set up a meeting with you
and the folks from ad sales.
What do you mean
you're not in charge anymore?
Tracy Jordan from Tracyco
called to invite you to a luncheon
- celebrating their new ad campaign.
- What... seriously, not now.
All right, everyone,
back to the drawing board.
Legal rejected all of our ideas.
Every names we came up with
was offensive in some language.
Including English.
They knew what a Hot Richard was?
So we're going to think
outside the box a little bit here.
I'm going to pick some random letters
from this bag of Scrabble tiles.
Let fate choose a name for us.
Why don't we start over?
I have an idea. Why don't I just
pull them all at once?
Why don't we take a break?
Could you get Lemon
on the phone for me, please?
Ms. Gaulke,
how long have you been an employee
of Mailboxes Plus?
I've been an assistant manager there
for over seven years.
And how would you describe the events
that took place there on December 17th?
The night of the fire.
Christmas was always
a very busy time at the store.
Throw in a late Hanukkah and the fact
that I work in a "Kwanzaa neighborhood",
and it all made
for a very stressful day.
I sent Malik uptown
for more 18-inch boxes,
but he returned unrepentant
with 12-inch ones.
Christine was late,
as well as Harry S.
They said it was a problem
with the subways,
I suspect they were doing
sex with each other.
How many employees
do you have, Ms. Gaulke?
I supervise 12 employees,
most of whom would be
unemployable in any other field.
They are selfish,
irresponsible people
who I know talk about me
behind my back.
They seem to think that their job
is wasting my time and energy
by making their every
minuscule problem
my personal responsibility.
They don't care.
And don't even get me started
on Tracy and Jenna.
And when the last one of them
trundled off that night,
I smelled the air,
and I could feel that it was time.
Time for a new beginning.
And I knew that this was possible
only through a cleansing fire.
It would all have to burn.
The packing peanuts,
the delivery slips...
All of it would dance
in the warm mouth of my fire.
And a new, better, wonderful me
would rise from the ashes
like a phoenix.
Behold...
the splendor of my beginning!
I rest my case, your honor.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
Underlings, I wanna hear your ideas.
I knew this day would come.
I have so much inside of me.
My first idea is a movie
that combines action and romance.
Kenneth, you go.
A name...
for a pocket microwave oven.
That's neat.
A little microwave oven.
So it's kinda like a funcooker.
The Funcooker!
It's snappy, fresh,
and incapable of offending.
Get legal on the phone.
- I owe you one.
- One hug, you mean?
They're reading Mr. Jordan's apology
if you want to watch it.
"I regret any pain my words and actions
may have caused.
"I apologize to my family my fans,
"and the American public.
"Peace and love, Tracy Jordan."
A heartfelt apology from a comedy icon.
And we'll be right back.
I do not apologize, America.
I didn't even write that apology.
I am advertiser Tracy Jordan,
and I approve this message.
I am an advertiser.
Is that 30 seconds yet?
Doesn't matter.
We have The Funcooker.
Hi, it's Liz.
I should be able
to get up there in an hour.
Where are you rushing off to?
Work?
Not me.
I'm gonna have a sandwich
in my cell and take a nap.
This man opens doors for me.
I'm free.
I'm freer than you.
Freer than you.
Professor Bananas is dead.
Look, I know we're fighting,
but I need to borrow your car.
30 seconds.
- How are you feeling, Miss?
- Great. Alert.
Is your vision steadily
narrowing down to a pinpoint
- as if darkness is closing in on you?
- No, ma'am.
Cast is set
for robot/bear talk show.
I'm back.
What's going on? What have they done?
Do we need to shut this down?
Calm down. Everything's going
to work out just fine.
The show's about to begin,
your sketch is adequate,
and I've got The Funcooker.
- What about the...
- It's the bear and robot talk show.
Jenna needs to sleep,
or she's going to die!
Which one of you is Jenna?
Go to sleep!
Sleep, Jenna!
Sleep! It's for your own good.
Don't fight me.
- Sleep or die!
- Hey, America.
- Come on Tracy. Please cover for them.
- Check out my funcooker.
Did he just say funcooker?
That's where I've heard that.
Go to commercial!
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan.
My wife's throwing away
some of our old towels.
Do you want them?
Cause they're out by the trashcans.
Now that's got to be 30 seconds.
Nine?
Here comes the funcooker.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Could we get some diet slice
and pita chips up in here?
Bitenuker!
9:00 A.M. Monday.
Right? I'll be there with pants on.
You're the best.
Hi, girlfriend.
Let's go out this weekend
and talk about you.
All I did was ask for a diet slice
and some pita chips.
Nice try.
Now it's my turn.
They're all terrified of you.
That'll get you a week of good behavior.
My containers.
My new beginning.
We've both had a rough week.
You went firebug, and I'm sitting
on four million...
mini-microwaves that legal
won't let out of the warehouse.
I suggest we both go to our
respective homes, open a bottle of wine,
and heat up some ham in the shower.
It works in the shower?
You know what?
This really is the best day ever.
Here comes the funcooker!
www.tvsubtitles.net