Are you sure you don't wanna go
to a real restaurant?
No, this food car is great!
Look at this guy, used to be a man once.
What is that supposed to mean?
Don't you want what he has some day?
Family, wife, children.
Lemon, you're a woman.
Of course I am!
That doctor was a quack,
I don't even know why
my parents listened to him.
I need advice. Elisa is coming by
this afternoon to, uh,
- talk about us.
- Ach, ladies are such a bummer.
Where is this going,
how serious are we,
why don't you listen
to my story about my friend?
Well, where is it going? Ladies like
to know what that next step is, they--
we can't help ourselves.
Oh, believe me Lemon, I want
to take that next step.
- You mean, like, marriage?
- No, the one before that.
- Moving in together?
That's huge! - No,
the thing you do before that.
- think "you in the mid-nineties."
- You haven't had sex?
Elisa had a very strict,
very religious upbringing.
She does not take that step lightly.
We have, of course,
- pleasured one another--
- No, stop, I believe.
But she wants me to make some
kind of commitment before we go forward.
Obviously I care about her a lot,
but she keeps confusing me
with this ridiculous notion that "sex"
and "love" are somehow connected.
OK, two things: one, be honest,
if this is a big deal to her
do not take that next step
unless you are sure,
and second, and more importantly,
in 2009 I have done it
two more times than you.
Give it up what, what.
Whoo, do not leave a brother hanging.
You're ready for Larry King Live tonight?
You know it occurs for two hours straight
just to get it out of my system you dumb bitch.
- Oh, no. - Listen, we have a request,
can you, please, try to remember
to talk about TGS tonight?
You only have to plug it once:
"TGS, Fridays at 10:30 on NBC."
You got it! "NGS Fridays
at c-thirty on TB-10."
Thank you.
What's that, you're calling me,
how's that possible? Hello!
This phone was left in my cab
by a woman wearing
- the shirt of a man.
- Ah, you left your phone in his car.
- Hi, I'm Liz, you have my phone?
- Yes. This is Asseef,
I'm in Green's Taxi dispatch
in Long Island City, you come?
Yes, I will, thank you.
Hey, why do you have Tracy Jordan's
phone number in your address book?
I work with him, if you want
I could bring a signed photo.
You bring 800 dollars, rich lady,
or I throw the phone away.
What? Oh, yeah, I'll definitely
do that, on Opposite Day.
I'm new to this country,
is that a real thing?
Hi baby, I got you something to
remember me while I'm in Puerto Rico.
It's a caricature
of me on a skateboard.
So I guess you're still
planning on taking your trip?
Well, I've been going home
every winter for the last 15 years.
I guess I could consider staying,
if I knew where this was going.
And the woman talk begins.
Well played. Look, you know
I'm serious about us,
we're great together.
We're Jack and Elisa -- Jalisa.
That's really lame, Jack.
Yeah that was just a joke.
I don't wanna go all "Marc Anthony" on you,
but I need to know how you feel.
I love you.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, Jack Donaghy.
Then you'll stay?
OK, I'll stay.
But if I have to give up my trip,
then I want us to spend that time together.
Just us, "Jalisa."
Jonathan, clear my schedule
for next week, starting with tonight.
You won't be coming in at all?
But what about "Jackonathon?"
I think tonight is going to be
a very special night.
- If you know what I mean...
- I think I do.
Don't forget your skateboard.
But then he scores a basket,
even though he's not a wolf anymore.
We're here with Tracy Jordan,
who just recounted, by the way,
the entire plot of
the movie Teen Wolf.
What? Oh, hold on, Tracy.
My producers are telling me
there is breaking news.
The Asian financial markets
have just opened to a huge sell-off,
- and we're gonna switch to that story right now.
- Good. I'm glad I'm here.
Your thoughts, Tracy Jordan,
on how this is gonna impact Wall Street.
Larry, I'm not an expert,
but I do have a strong opinion.
New York as we know it
will no longer exist tomorrow.
- Expand on that!
- Look, I grew up here, Larry,
in the days before Starbuck.
and if Wall Street crashes,
it will be the 1970s all over again.
People will get mean, the streets won't be safe,
it will be graffiti everywhere,
and the movies are only cost three dollars.
Tracy Jordan, saying three serious things,
and then a joke.
Oh, Jack, have you taken a gander
at the Asian markets?
The ??? index is off the charts!
Well, good luck with that, Jorgensen
but I'm on vacation now.
But, I have these papers.
- Hey, Jack, how are you doing?
- Like a lion, ready to take its mate.
How are you calling me?
Ach, I lost my phone
and this jagweed cabby has it.
Hey, stop harassing my friends, Asseef.
Hey, Liz, I just wanted to let you know
that I found that special picture
- that you took with your phone.
- What picture? Oh my god!
- Yes.  That one.
- There's a picture on my phone.
- An adult picture, of me.
- What?
Drew took it as a joke, I'm making a face like--
Why am I telling you this?
Top-end bottom, may I speak with Asseef?
- OK, what do you want?
- 2,000 cash or I email the picture
to everyone in your address book.
Have you been to Asia, Tracy?
Oh, my work has taken me there,
I was supposed to be in that movie Rush Hour
but two weeks into shooting
I was replaced by Jackie Chan.
- OK, I'm going to get my phone.
- You're gonna pay that guy?
Well, it's, you know I need
my address book and stuff.
But I'm not going alone
to meet some creep at a taxi garage.
Will one of your guys go with me?
- No ma'am.
- Good luck.
- I would, but I don't want to.
- I will escort you, Miss Lemon.
We pages are accustomed to danger.
Thank you Kenneth, can you
leave now, this place is in Queens.
Oh, Miss Lemon, I can't
leave Manhattan on page business.
NBC's interns doesn't cover it.
I'll have to do this as a friend.
OK, fine.
Say it. Say I'm your friend.
Fine. You're my friend,
Kenneth. Let's go.
The Mumbay stock exchange
is now down in early trading.
Is this panic becoming global?
Tracy Jordan, talk us through this.
Larry, what everyone needs to do,
is to take a deep breath,
calm down, and start preparing their bodies
for the Thunderdome.
That is the new law.
That's my TV!
This is as far as we can get by subway.
We need to find a cab.
Hold, Miss Lemon, this is
a pretty bad neighborhood.
Aww, I just got tagged.
Mr. Jordan and Mr. Larry King are right,
New York is not safe anymore.
And I'm not risking your life
for a cell phone.
It's not just a phone, Kenneth,
it's what's on it.
I don't understand, what
could be so important?
It wasn't something of
sentimental value, was it?
Yes, very sentimental.
It's a song, a lullaby that my nana Lemon
used to sing to me every night
Oh, was it "The Day is Done My Sweet,
For the Lambs Have Been Decapitated?"
No, it was... a German song,
she was German.
And my nana got very sick recently,
and I went to visit her
and I had her singing it for me
one final time
and I recorded that on my phone
and I'm glad that I did because
she died a few hours later.
It was my birthday.
Miss Lemon, I am so sorry,
would you sing it for me?
* Hast du etwas Zeit für mich *
* dann singe ich ein Lied für dich *
Stop. Now that I know,
the reason we are doing this
is not only moral, but beautiful
then I will not rest
until I get my friend her phone.
OK, come on.
- That was amazing.
- Thank you.
I watched an American Masters
last night about Baryshnikov.
I picked up a couple of ideas.
Our sushi. No, no, no, no, no,
I'll get it. You'll need your rest,
we're going again in 15.
- Jack, you've got company.
- Jack, why aren't you answering your phone?
What are you doing here?
People are freaking out about
this Asia thing, and we can't find Geiss.
He's AWOL, now everyone's looking to you, Jack.
I don't care what's going on out there.
I'm staying here.
There are some things more important than
a stock quote crawling across a screen.
I'm in love with this magnificent woman,
and there is no amount of money this company
could lose that would cause me to--
yes, that's the amount,
I'll get dressed right now.
Bill Hewitt, Undersecretary of the Treasury,
what advice can you give our viewers
in these uncertain times?
The worst thing you could do
in a time like this is to pull out
your investments, don't panic,
because I think that--
Devil's avocado here, Larry, I think
people should freak the geek out.
- Withdraw all your money and hide it!
- Interesting strategy.
It's what I've always done.
I hide cash everywhere.
At home, at church, even at work.
In fact, I've hidden so much money
that if some of it was gone
I'd probably wouldn't even notice.
- Now why would you say that?
- I don't know.
Don't worry Miss Lemon, I'll protect you.
Ah, it's just kids.
What is going on with people?
They took my wallet.
- Was this your nana Lemon?
- Yeah, she's the one we're doing this for.
- She's dead, come on.
- Wait, why is she wearing these glasses?
This is from New Year's, but you said
she died on your birthday,
and that's in November.
No, that's not a New Year's thing,
that's the year she wanted to live to,
- and she didn't make it.
- Sing that lullaby again!
* Hast du etwas Zeit für mich *
* dann singe ich ein Lied für dich *
Keep going.
* von 99 Luftballons *
I knew it! That's "99 Red Balloons,"
Nena's famous anti-balloon protest song.
- You lied to me.
- Yeah, alright, I lied, so what?
You want the truth Kenneth, you want the truth?
I can't handle the truth!
There's an adult picture of me
on that phone!
Adult? You mean like you're
driving a car or wearing a suit?
It's a boobies picture, Kenneth,
and I only kept it because for once
they were both pointing in the same direction.
I knew you wouldn't help me
if I told you the truth.
So you lied to me?
That's not something that friends
do to each other.
Then maybe we're not friends.
- But we are! You said so before we left.
- You made me say that!
Well I guess then I'm here as a page
in violation of NBC's interns policy.
I should probably head back to Manhattan.
Good.
I don't need you!
Co-worker!
- Did you get hold of Geiss?
- No.
- Did you try his mistress?
- Not there.
- How about his manstress?
- Nothing. I think we should listen
- to Tracy Jordan and panic, sir.
- What?
I'm saying the disneyfication of New York
is over, everyone.
At the stroke of midnight,
your Lexus is gonna turn back
into a high-powered rats,
fighting over a human finger.
Joining us on the phone is
GE Vice President Jack Donaghy,
Jack, what's your outlook on all of this?
I just wanna preach caution, Larry
if there was anything to worry about
I would be at my office.
Instead of at home, right now,
with my beautiful girlfriend.
- She's Latin.
- Expand on that.
Look, my point is that some of the things
that Tracy is saying are just fanning the flames.
Hang on. I know Jack Donaghy,
and that is an impostor.
- Hang up! Hang up on him Larry!
- I'm going to, but not because you told me.
Lincoln, Nebraska, you are on the air.
So is this what you'd rather be doing
than spending time with me?
- It smells like dude in here.
- I tried to call you why didn't you pick up?
Because I'm sick of listening to you.
"Oh, I love you, Elisa."
This was all just another Jack Donaghy lie.
Like when you said
you could dunk a basketball?
I can, on a regulation hoop.
Look, this is an emergency,
if I'm not here, tonight--
What? What's gonna happen?
People are gonna die?
No. You'll all just get poor like the rest of us.
You'll eat cereal that comes in a bag,
and you'll keep the free hand wipes
from the casino.
You might even have to spend some
time with your children.
Who is this woman,
why isn't someone shutting her up?
Now why don't you just go
back to my apartment
and I will meet you there, eventually.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to Puerto Rico!
Elisa, don't do that, you don't understand.
What's happening here is
a once in a lifetime thing.
So am I.
Well, that was kind of neato, she just,
whoop, flipped your words around on you.
Sorry.
- Forget it, we're never gonna find Tracy's money.
- There's something under here!
- It's nothing but a bunch of tarantula food.
- What? I didn't even know Tracy had a tarantula.
You know what? There's
an easier way to do this.
Our next caller is Pete from Manhattan,
- Pete, was is your question?
- Hey Larry, first time caller, I adore the show--
Hey, I'd recognize that voice anywhere Larry,
that's my friend Peter Frampton on the phone.
Ah, sure.
Uh, sure, listen, Tracy I love
the idea of hiding cash at work,
could you be more specific about
where you hid your money?
Of course Pete, I hid my money
in the safest place at 30 Rock.
Without giving it away: the place I picked
is very dry and warm.
Its top is hard, but its bottom is soft.
And although the location changes all the time,
the money stays in the same place.
If you're just joining us, we're with Tracy Jordan
who is giving guitar icon
Peter Frampton enigmatic clues
about a secret treasure. Stay with us.
Mr. Donaghy, this just arrived.
It's from Mr. Geiss.
Everything is gonna be alright. Geiss is back.
- Jonathan, can we even play this thing?
- Oh yes, I keep a VCR so
I can watch your old football tapes.
- Jonathan, what is that camcorder for?
- Nothing. I don't know.
Hello. If you're watching this, you're an executive
of the General Electric Corporation
and the unthinkable is happening.
Capitalism is ending, either because
of the Soviets or of something ridiculous,
- like a woman president.
- God, he looks so young.
I'm speaking to you in the year 1987,
but my message is timeless.
Avoid...
the night.
We've all worked hard, but now it's over.
There's only one thing for you to do.
Go to your loved ones.
Hold them close.
Because in the end and if you're watching this
it is the end,
love is all that matters.
How the hell am I gonna turn this damn thing off?
What's that gizmo?
Elisa?
I was about to do the whole run-to-the-airport
thing like Ross did on Friends
and Liz Lemon did in real life.
What are you doing here?
The taxis want 500 bucks to go to J.F.K.
and the buses are worse.
Everything's gone cocoa for cuckoo poops!
- Is that right?
- Elisa, listen to me.
I meant everything I said but I know that
that's just words, you want commitment.
Here it is:
Let's get married.
- Jack!
- I love you, Elisa
and I don't wanna be with anyone else.
Okay.
But I want a ring so big,
that it gives me back problems.
- That's my phone, I'm Liz Lemon.
- Where is the 2,000 dollars?
I don't have it, I lost all my money
and my bank card's in my retainer. Geez.
Please, Asseef, give me my phone.
Maybe you could call a friend
to get the money or, wait!
Every number in this address book
is a work number.
Work number, work number, work number.
You have no friends.
Yes. I. Am.
OK, you have 2,000 dollars?
No.
I'm gonna watch TV until
you come up with my money.
Maybe you get it through sex trade.
You're a pretty young thing.
- You're disgusting.
- I'm not talking to you.
- Frank, calm down.
- It's not in here.
This isn't about the money,
this is about my own issues
- with Liz.
- Stop it!
We have Peter Frampton on the phone again.
Come on, Tracy, just tell us where the money is,
where's the safest place in 30 Rock?
- Is that Pete?
- I already told you, it's dry and warm,
its top is hard but its bottom is soft,
and although the location changes,
it's always in the same place.
There's nothing like that in 30 Rock, nothing.
I never said it was a "thing."
It's me.
I am the safest place in 30 Rock.
I would thank you to give the lady
its cell phone back.
Thank you for coming back, Kenneth,
you're a good friend.
- You mean it?
- Yes!
Because I'm having an asbestos removal party
in my apartment on Sunday,
Yeah, I'm in.
Now that the US markets have opened
unaffected by the Asian melt-down,
many people are blaming the panic
in New York last night on one man,
Tracy Jordan.
He is here with me now. Tracy, a lot of of people
are calling you a "fear monger,"
and, I'm quoting here, "an idiot."
What do you have to say for yourself?
Watch TGS Fridays at 10:30 on NBC!
Word.
- Morning Jonathan.
- Good morning sir, crazy night last night.
Lots of emotions, people getting carried away.
Yes, it was a crazy night. Is Elisa here?
We're having a couples spa day.
She came by earlier,
she asked me to give you this,
she said to just press "play."
Hi Jack, I'm on my way to Puerto Rico.
I'm sorry.
Yesterday was crazy, lots of emotion.
I think maybe you asked me
what you asked me out of panic.
So, I'm gonna go see my family and
give us both a chance to think about everything.
OK, I'll call you.
Adiós mi amor.
Aww, how do you turn this damn thing off?
No!
That's personal.
** Subtitles by Siggboy **
www.tvsubtitles.net