Hi.
I'm looking for an engagement ring.
Are you sure?
Maybe you should have had a ring
The first time you proposed
- then Elisa wouldn't have said no.
- She didn't say no.
- She said we should think about it.
- Yeah, that does not mean yes.
In my experience,
"let's think about it"
usually ends up with
me watching solid gold
in my basement on prom night.
The point is I have thought about it,
and I haven't changed my mind.
In fact, I've coined a new term
to describe what Elisa is to me:
- The one.
- The one?
As in the only one for me.
The one I'm meant to be with.
Get it? The one.
Yeah, you should be a writer.
Whoa, check out the bling!
Or whatever it's called now.
- Aah!
- Huh!
- Good god.
- I got it!
Oh, god, there's a vent!
She's very... Spirited.
Like a show horse.
- You're a lucky man.
- Oh, no, no. She's not the bride.
- This is the one I am marrying.
- Oh, my apologies, sir.
Please follow me to the real showroom.
- Yes.
- My finger is caught in the vent.
Hey, where are my snow balls?
I was gonna go to the gym later,
so I deserve a treat.
Oh, Miss Lemon,
we can't have coconut products out
anymore because of staff allergies.
What? No, allergies are psychosomatic.
The only reason I'm allergic to dogs
is because one bit me
- the first time I got my period.
- No, allergies are real.
If I have a strawberry,
my throat shuts up
- Faster than a girl in math class.
- I didn't know you had allergies.
You know if my cousin
Stephanie eats a walnut,
Her throat shuts up faster
than a Filipino at a...
Guys! Come on. Not okay.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Rossitano,
no unauthorized food.
Don't worry, no food in here, Kenneth.
Just a doughnut box with a mouse in it.
Oh, are the pranks-men
going after Lutz again?
Someone say my name?
- Hey, look.
- Awesome! Doughnuts!
Aah! Aah!
Oh!
Hey, we've narrowed
it down, Liz Lemon.
Oh, great.
What are we talking about?
Tracy has to get a
present for his wife.
This Saturday is the 20th anniversary
of the night that me and Angie met.
She was working at the
Dyker Heights Arthur Treacher's,
and I was residing there.
She slipped me a free shrimp combo,
and we've been together ever since.
So this present has to be special.
It's either gonna be a denim jacket
that says "hot bitch" in diamonds...
- Uh-huh.
- Or a slanket.
Yeah, Angie doesn't want that.
Why don't you just ask
Angie what she wants
instead of spending
all this money on junk?
You are wise, Liz Lemon.
Like a genetically manipulated shark.
So as a token of my gratitude,
I got something specially for you.
Wow.
I'll take that slanket too
if you're not gonna use it.
- Puerto Rican!
- That's interesting.
I mean Puerto Rico,
where you're supposed to be.
- When did you get back?
- Actually, Lemon, three weeks ago.
- What? Why doesn't Jack know that?
- Because I don't know what to do.
I'm afraid he's gonna want to go through
with his proposings of marriage.
Sorry, I haven't spoken
English in two menses.
Are you saying that you
don't want to go through
with his proposings of marriage?
I don't understand, Elisa.
You love him.
- I do. That's why I call him "El Uno. "
- Yeah.
But I cannot marry him
because of a terrible secret.
- Please don't ask me what it is.
- I won't. I don't want to know.
- Are you a man?
- Really?
That's your guess, a man?
- You want to see me naked?
- Sort of.
I love Jack so much.
I don't think I have the strength
to tell it to his head.
- That's why I was hoping that you...
- Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, thank you for
doing what I cannot.
Good-bye forever,
Liz Lemon.
Well, I see why he likes it.
I hope you guys
have learned a lesson.
Because of what you did,
we almost lost a monitor.
I'm sorry.
You're a big fan of mine,
and you're not gay?
- Not even bi-curious?
- I don't know what to tell you.
I love your show.
I read your blog.
I've got all your albums.
Even the one you did with Phil Spector.
I still think that would have sold much
better If he had shot me in the face.
Well, I'm glad you
didn't get shot in the face.
- Thank you.
- But if you had...
I would have liked to
have gotten that call.
That would have been nice.
Jenna, Us Weekly is calling to confirm
a story that your animal rescue shelter
is supplying quesadilla meat
to amusement parks.
What?!
I need to call my lawyer.
I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere.
Dude, we have got to go man.
I stole some pens.
Mr. Lutz, this is my telephone number.
Please give it to Jenna Maroney.
You okay?
Good!
Hey Jack, do you have a sec?
It's over Lemon.
It's over before it started.
- Drink with me.
- I'm Sorry,
but I'm glad it didn't
have to come from me.
- What are you talking about?
Wigo.com, Sheinhart's Wigs
user generated video content site.
All anybody posted on it were penises.
- What did you want to talk to me about?
- Hey, Jack... Right... Okay...
I've been trying to
figure out how to
- not tell you this...
- Oh mi amor.
- Querida!
- I'm Back. Let's Get married.
I'll call Pablo to have them hold the table.
So we can celebrate in style.
And carbo-load for the reunion sex.
Lemon, isn't it wonderful?
Don't dare say anything about
what I told you about my secret.
I'm not going to,
because you have to.
♪ baby cried the day
the circus came to town. ♪
- Uh... You okay?
- Oh, I didn't see you there.
I'm fine.
♪ Don't cry out loud! ♪
You sure you don't want to
talk about something?
Well, it's kinda none of your business.
But all right.
I met this cute paramedic yesterday.
He thinks I'm incredible,
we're perfect for each other.
But he left before
I could get his name.
Well, I'm sure there's a way to find out.
I called 911, they wouldn't even
connect me to their celebrity service.
I don't know what to do!
You know, your dilemma reminds me
of a book I read once.
- See ya later Pete.
- No, no, listen, listen.
There's this question psychiatrists
use to identify sociopaths.
A woman goes to her mother's funeral,
where she meets the perfect man,
it's love at first sight.
But he leaves before she
finds out who he is. So...
What does she do to see him again?
She kills her father hoping that
the guy will come to that funeral too.
That's correct!
Oh boy...
- Thanks for the advice.
- No, no, no. That wasn't advice.
But of course she'd also have to
kill her father's doorman,
and anyone else who might have seen her
and you for giving her
the idea in the first place.
- Liz Lemon, you dummy!
- I'm Wearing it as a joke.
I asked Angie what she
wanted for our anniversary
and she wants me to get
a tattoo of her name
Oh, okay, you like tattoos.
And above it she wants
this picture of her face.
I can't have this on my chest
scaring off beautiful women in the clubs.
- Tracy...
- You know I like to socialize Liz Lemon.
and you know my signature
move with the ladies.
- is taking off my shirt!
- Is taking off your shirt!
Now it's a Sophie's choice.
I can't get this tattoo,
and I can't tell Angie no.
What do you want me to say Tracy?
I'm sorry I made it harder
for you to cheat on your wife?
That's a start Liz Lemon.
That's a start!
Strawberries!
My real name is Diplin!
Oh, somebody call
the cute guy at 911!
Lemon I need to ask you
something about Elisa.
Did she say anything to you,
anything at all, about a secret...
- Desire to keep her maiden name?
- Oh, no, sorry.
Because I'd like her to be Elisa Donaghy,
but if she wants to be Elisa Padriera Donaghy...
Elisa Padriera?
Ah!
- Viuva negra!
- What?
- What does that mean?
- The black widow!
Elisa has a terrible secret,
my current theory is
she's the mother of those
Michael Jackson's kids.
Okay, I searched Elisa Padriera
and the black widow,
But all the web sites are in Spanish.
- Blue writing on green. Why?!
- Call that cleaning lady back.
- We need somebody who speaks Spanish.
- I speak Spanish.
- Puerto Rican!
- La viuva negra!
Really, Lemon?
- Jack, let me explain.
- Elisa, there is nothing you can say
That will change the way I feel.
I'm so sorry to tell
you such a dark tale
while wearing such a silly T-shirt.
I was married once,
and I killed my husband.
It was a crime of passion.
He cheated on me.
And in a rage I took my revenge.
You know me, Jack.
I'm a Catholic.
I take the bonds of
marriage very seriously.
- Why aren't you in jail?
- They threw my case out.
I couldn't get an impartial jury
after that song about me came out.
♪ Elisa, Elisa ♪
♪ La viuda negra ♪
♪ Elisa ♪
I guess I'm glad you know.
I understand if this changes everything.
It's up to you.
My god,
I already put my wedding announcement
in cigar aficionado.
How about this?
You get the tattoo,
but when you hit the clubs,
you draw a mane around
the face with a marker,
and make it look like a
lion named "Tangiers".
Dotcom, that is a great idea!
If you want everyone to
think I own a gay lion!
- Tangiers?!
- No judgment in brainstorming.
Look, this is my reputation
we're talking about here!
Use your heads!
The Moroccan national
soccer team is the lions.
Tangiers is in Morocco.
So, yeah, I guess I'm an idiot.
Have you ever met anyone
that's killed somebody?
I think my grandpa may have.
But he never really liked to talk about
what happened at Kent State.
I still want to marry Elisa.
- Wow, you do? Really?
- So she had one bad day.
Being in a relationship means
overlooking certain flaws.
I mean,
somewhere right now,
a guy is on a j-date
with Monica Lewinsky.
Nobody's perfect.
- Jack!
- I'm 50.
To put it in perspective,
that's like 32 for ladies.
How many more Elisas
am I going to meet?
Okay, well,
God bless.
I guess I just really
don't understand men.
Nobody ever said you did,
Lemon.
Nyah...
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, what are
you two doing here?
Where's the hot guy?
Ma'am, are you taking any medication?
Yes. Where's the cute paramedic
who was here last night?
He was wearing a uniform.
He was totally into me.
If he was here at night,
he must work the evening shift.
So there are different shifts?
Like on a Sheik's pleasure yacht.
Thank you.
Lemon.
It's not product placement.
I just like it.
- What?
What if I marry Elisa
and I accidentally cheat?
She could snap again.
She's very passionate, and she doesn't
react well to betrayal.
Why won't you open?!
Yes. What a quandary.
Oh, wait, I have a suggestion...
- Don't cheat.
- But you never know, Lemon.
What if I find myself
stranded in a snow cave
with a stern but comely lady geologist,
both of us knowing that
our only chance for survival
is the heat from our naked bodies?
- Sorry, I just do not get you guys.
- Again, that is not being disputed.
But my options for male
advice around here are limited.
So I think the pranks-men
should all wear fedoras.
- Could the hats have feathers?
- Yes! Yes!
Face it, you are the closest thing to
a man working here right now.
Well, dude,
I guess you gotta find a comely geologist
and a snow cave and see what happens.
Tracy, I need your help.
My fiancee murdered her ex-husband
when he cheated on her.
- Continue.
- I love her.
But the only way I can make
sure that I won't stray...
is for me to arrange a
test of erotic temptation.
- Yes.
- Exactly.
We're going out tonight, Jackie D,
and you're gonna be tempted
like Jesus in the wilderness.
Jesus is my stereo guy, and the
Wilderness is a club I took him to once.
Jenna, come quick.
Kenneth's passed out again.
Oh, no, I can't believe this
is happening during night shift!
Oh, for god sakes!
What is this, third watch?
Somehow Kenneth ate strawberries again,
and now he's gone into
acute strawberry shock.
- Is that a thing?
- Just ask this real EMT.
We're gonna have to cut off his hands
to get the sickness out.
He's gonna have to learn
how to urinate with his feet.
- How could this have happened again?!
- It's my fault. I did it.
I just wanted that hot EMT to come back.
I didn't mean for it to go this far.
Oh Kenneth, I'm so sorry.
But I am not a monster.
I'm just a girl standing in
front of a boy she poisoned
So this other boy
would go to town on her.
- I think she's had enough, sirs.
- Aw, Kenneth!
What's happening?
Is this a trick? I knew it!
I was just playing along.
No, seriously, what's happening?
Jenna, do you feel genuine remorse?
Thank god.
Sociopath downgraded
to extreme narcissist.
Now quit it with the strawberry stuff.
Or you might once again
feel the righteous lash
of the pranks-men.
Is that a thing?
Hey, Tray.
- You and your friend wanna party later?
- Sure thing, baby.
Give the kid a call.
- Holla.
- This is decadent?
And I once went to Miami
with Darryl Strawberry.
Tip of the iceberg, Jackie D.
You can have all of
this whenever you want.
Or you can marry that nice
lady that you're in love with.
- It's up to you.
- Look, I love Elisa.
- But you love Angie, right?
- Of course I do. Angie's the one.
The one?
Where did you hear that?
It's a thing I made up
after seeing the Matrix.
Well, Elisa is my one.
But Tracy,
sometimes I think men like us
aren't built for marriage.
Okay, this is something
I've never told anyone.
This is my terrible secret.
In the 20 years that I've known her...
I've never cheated on my wife.
There.
I said it.
Don't look at me.
Wait a minute.
That can't be the truth.
The partying is just for show.
And because I'm a
high-functioning alcoholic.
All the phone numbers
you see me hand out,
They're not even mine.
Hello?
No, this isn't Tracy Jordan.
Really?
I've not heard of that term before.
Do you know how to get to Connecticut?
Oh, my god.
That's an inspiration.
- I mean, if you can do it...
- So can you.
Because I'm a ridiculous,
unstable human being.
What is wrong with me?
I mean, if Elisa's only flaw is
that she demands I be faithful,
Then I will be faithful!
And if Angie wants me to get
a tattoo of her to prove my love,
then I'm getting that tattoo!
Grizz, get the car.
Dotcom, get the coats.
And which one of you ladies
wants to pick up the tab?
Oh, me! Me!
I put strawberry juice
in your chickpeas.
And in your water.
- And on your harmonica.
- My what?
Oh, you mean my mouth radio?
I am so sorry, Kenneth.
I just want you to know that I would not
do this to you for just any guy.
He was special.
I really thought that he was...
- The one.
- Oh, Miss Maroney,
it's horrible to think you might
have found your true love,
- but only to lose him.
- It hurts more than my foot botox
to know that he's out there,
and I have no way to find him.
When you call 911,
tell them they have to send everyone.
- Earn... This!
- Oh...
You remarkable son of a bitch!
We have an emergency!
♪ workin' on my night cheese ♪
Oh!
Jack?
Do you know what time it is?
I was sound asleep.
I heard you singing "night cheese".
Lemon, I've had a crazy night.
We all can learn a lot
from Tracy Jordan.
We went out clubbing.
His life is like Enron, 1999.
- It's wild.
- I'm sure it was.
How are you so quiet when
your parades are so loud?
You were supposed
to be thinking about us.
And you spent the whole night
partying with that black guy!
- Did she not come here with you?
- Have you been following me?
And then you come here
at 4:00 in the morning?!
I knew your relationship was too weird
not to be sexual!
Okay, everybody be cool.
Wait a minute, you're jealous of Lemon?
That's insane.
Yeah,come on,
look at me.
- Ooh.
- Elisa, I proved to myself tonight
that I would never cheat on you.
That's why I went out with Tracy.
And I came to Liz's because...
- Because she's your bro.
- Exactly.
- Oh...
- Elisa, this is troubling.
And how do you think I feel?
I get a ring on my finger for one day
and I start acting like Glenn Close
- in "Atraccion Fatal".
- Oh, that has a whole different title here.
Lemon, isn't there a slanket somewhere
you should be filling with your farts?
Shoo.
Baby, this is my curse.
I love too deeply.
And eventually it makes
me loco for choco-puffs.
Querida, if you ever find yourself
less in love with me,
I hope you'll give me a call.
But if tonight is what
it's going to be like,
obviously, engagement-wise,
we are not going to forge ahead.
Is it my English? Or was that
not a great breaking-up speech?
It was your English.
That was quite moving.
Boy, you look happy. What, did you settle
that lawsuit over your exercise tape?
Even better.
I had an amazing date last night.
- And it's all thanks to Kenneth.
- Oh, it was nothing.
Sure, I was legally
dead for five minutes,
- But I did it for true love.
- Well actually,
it turns out Roger has sole custody
Of his five-year-old son,
So pffft!
- Wait a minute, you were dead?
- Oh, I'm fine.
But I think I brought
something back with me.
Tracy, did you even go home last night?
And where is your shirt?
No,
and at large.
I might've went out and had a little
too much to drink last night,
but you'll be proud of me,
Liz Lemon "Cool J".
'cause I went out and got that tattoo
Angie wanted me to get.
Pow!
How you like me now?
Wow, that is one gay lion.
Subtitle by: kiasuseven
www.tvsubtitles.net